<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Witch Trials of J.K. Rowling on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-witch-trials-of-j.k.-rowling/</link><description>Recent content in The Witch Trials of J.K. Rowling on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 06:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-witch-trials-of-j.k.-rowling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Chapter 7: What If You're Wrong? | The Witch Trials of J.K. Rowling</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1558640001/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1558640001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Host Megan Phelps-Roper asks J.K. Rowling to respond to pushback from some of her critics. The two also discuss the difficulty of discernment—why it can be so hard to know what’s right. Produced by Andy Mills, Matthew Boll, Megan Phelps-Roper, with special thanks to Candace Mittel Kahn and Emily Yoffe. This show is proudly sponsored by the Foundation for Individual Rights and Expression. FIRE believes free speech makes free people.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 6: Natalie and Noah | The Witch Trials of J.K. Rowling</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1558640002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1558640002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Transgender fans of Harry Potter share their criticism of J.K. Rowling—and the experiences that inform their views. Produced by Andy Mills, Matthew Boll, Megan Phelps-Roper, and Candace Mittel Kahn, with special thanks to Emily Yoffe. This show is proudly sponsored by the Foundation for Individual Rights and Expression. FIRE believes free speech makes free people. Learn more at thefire.org.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chapter 5: The Tweets | The Witch Trials of J.K. Rowling</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1558640003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1558640003/</guid><description>Podcast Description After years of observing the conflict between advocates for trans rights and women’s rights, J.K. Rowling weighs in. Produced by Andy Mills, Matthew Boll, and Megan Phelps-Roper, with special thanks to Candace Mittel Kahn and Emily Yoffe. This show is proudly sponsored by the Foundation for Individual Rights and Expression. FIRE believes free speech makes free people. Learn more at thefire.org.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chapter 4: TERF Wars | The Witch Trials of J.K. Rowling</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1558640004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1558640004/</guid><description>Podcast Description The movement for trans rights hits its stride in the early 2010s, but encounters fierce resistance from an unexpected source. J.K. Rowling watches the battle unfold with mounting unease. Produced by Andy Mills, Matthew Boll, and Megan Phelps-Roper, with special thanks to Candace Mittel Kahn and Emily Yoffe. This show is proudly sponsored by the Foundation for Individual Rights and Expression. FIRE believes free speech makes free people. Learn more at thefire.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 3: A New Pyre | The Witch Trials of J.K. Rowling</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1558640005/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1558640005/</guid><description>Podcast Description The early days of the internet collide with the feverish fandom of “Harry Potter,” and a sprawling, global community emerges. But the hopefulness of this new technology brings with it the darker impulses of human nature. Produced by Andy Mills, Matthew Boll, and Megan Phelps-Roper, with special thanks to Candace Mittel Kahn and Emily Yoffe. This show is proudly sponsored by the Foundation for Individual Rights and Expression. FIRE believes free speech makes free people.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 2: Burn The Witch | The Witch Trials of J.K. Rowling</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1558640006/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1558640006/</guid><description>Podcast Description As &amp;ldquo;Harry Potter&amp;rdquo; becomes an international phenomenon, it coincides with the culture wars of the 1990s. In the backlash from Christians across America, author J.K. Rowling is accused of mainstreaming witchcraft and poisoning children’s minds. Produced by Andy Mills, Matthew Boll, and Megan Phelps-Roper, with special thanks to Candace Mittel Kahn and Emily Yoffe. This show is proudly sponsored by the Foundation for Individual Rights and Expression. FIRE believes free speech makes free people.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 1: Plotted In Darkness | The Witch Trials of J.K. Rowling</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1558640007/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1558640007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Host Megan Phelps-Roper writes a letter to J.K. Rowling—and receives a surprising invitation in reply: the opportunity for an intimate conversation in Rowling’s Scottish home. Produced by Andy Mills, Matthew Boll, and Megan Phelps-Roper, with special thanks to Candace Mittel Kahn and Emily Yoffe. This show is proudly sponsored by the Foundation for Individual Rights and Expression. FIRE believes free speech makes free people. Learn more at thefire.org.</description></item><item><title>Trailer | The Witch Trials of J.K. Rowling</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1558640008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1558640008/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Witch Trials of J.K. Rowling premieres Tuesday, February 21, 2023. Learn more Read an essay by host Megan Phelps-Roper
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>