<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Imperfects on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-imperfects/</link><description>Recent content in The Imperfects on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-imperfects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mrs Claus - Santa’s Better Half | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170141/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Heads up: Mrs Claus is VERY close friends with comedian, Urzila Carlson. As such, this Special Christmas Episode is definitely not appropriate for kids.
Last year, we were honoured to sit down with the one and only Santa Claus as he joined us in The Vulnerabilitea House. A big thank you to Glenn Robbins for organising that interview for us! Link below if you missed it.
This year, Hugh, Josh and Ryan meet the woman who claims to be the brains behind the operation, Mrs Claus (or is it Ms Claus?</description></item><item><title>Dr Emily - Merry Not-Enoughmas | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170001/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170001/</guid><description>Podcast Description For some people, Christmas Day is the most wonderful time of the year. But for others, catching up with friends and family at this time of the year can lead to pain and sadness and as Dr Emily describes it, an overwhelming feeling of “not-enoughness”. In this special bonus episode, Dr Emily explains where this feeling comes from and why it pops up year after year. But as always she gives us some helpful advice on what we can do to address it and feel a little less alone this Christmas.</description></item><item><title>Chanel Contos - Consensual Healing | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170002/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dear Men,
Please listen to this episode about consent and rape culture. Hugh, Ryan &amp;amp; Josh x
On the face of it, this Academy of Imperfection with Chanel Contos may seem like a heavy episode. An episode about consent, rape culture and sexual violence might not seem like an episode that concerns you. That may be true, but if the #MeToo movement taught us anything, it’s that you probably know someone who’s either been raped or sexually assaulted in some way.</description></item><item><title>Gina Chick - Don't Fight Life | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170003/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gina Chick grew up… different. She wasn’t like the other kids, and they let her know about it. But as an adult she learned to see her “different” as a strength, which led to her most well-known achievement, outlasting everyone else for 67 days in the Tasmanian wilderness to win ALONE Australia. But as you’ll hear, that’s only a part of her story - as is the fact that she’s very close friends with Hugh Jackman.</description></item><item><title>Hamish Macdonald - How To Be You | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170004/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170004/</guid><description>Podcast Description As co-host of The Project, Hamish Macdonald has seen and done more than most journalists could ever dream to achieve in their entire career.
Before The Project and a stint hosting ABC’s Q+A program, Hamish worked and reported around the world from war zones to natural disasters, winning a bunch of prestigious awards including a coveted Walkley Award in the process.
But as he discusses with Hugh, Ryan and Josh, he’s also faced bullying throughout his life, whether that be from students during his high school days, or from online trolls during his Q+A days - a challenging experience that drove him to leave social media forever.</description></item><item><title>Dr Louise Newson - Maybe it’s Menopause | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170005/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Menopause, or THE Menopause according to our guest lecturer Dr Louise Newson, affects every woman at some point in her life. That’s 51% of the entire world! And even if you’re not a woman, chances are you know a few of them. Either way, the menopause IS coming. And you better be ready.
Dr Louise Newson is a GP and Menopause specialist who is campaigning for better menopause care for all women.</description></item><item><title>Dr Emily - Who Do You Desire? | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170006/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170006/</guid><description>Podcast Description We know, we know, we know. ‘Who Do You Desire? is a very click-baity title. But we’re pretty confident that if you DO take the bait (come onnnn), you’ll be nicely rewarded. In this episode, our resident psychologist Dr Emily talks with Hugh, Ryan and Josh about the concept of Mimetic Desire - the idea that whether we like it or not, pure originality is impossible. All of us are being influenced by someone.</description></item><item><title>Steve Hooker - The Ups &amp; Downs &amp; Ups | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170007/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Not many of us have won Olympic Gold. And even fewer of us have jumped over a 6m high bar. But Australian pole vaulting champion Steve Hooker has done both. And boy oh boy does he have a story to tell!? That was rhetorical btw, he definitely does have a story to tell.
What would you do if you were the best in the world at something one day, and then the next day you suddenly couldn’t do that thing anymore?</description></item><item><title>Lewis Hobba - Success Is Never Enough | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170008/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lewis Hobba grew up idolising Triple J. But despite being chosen as Triple J’s drive-time co-host by the age of 30, and being selected by Andrew Denton as one of Australia’s most creative and talented young performers for the show Hungry Beast, Lewis never felt like he succeeded in anything. In this Vulnerabilitea House, Lewis tells Hugh, Ryan and Josh what it was like behind the scenes for him during this time and how he dealt with crippling anxiety on a daily basis until eventually seeking help.</description></item><item><title>Taryn Brumfitt - Every Body Is Perfect | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170009/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170009/</guid><description>Podcast Description As Australian of the Year, Taryn Brumfitt is making a massive impact on an issue that effects people everywhere… BODY IMAGE.
Not only is Taryn a body image campaigner, she’s also a documentarian, having made two docos encouraging us to EMBRACE our bodies, not matter what they look like. We highly recommend you watch them - links below.
In this Academy of Imperfection, Taryn talks with Hugh, Ryan and Josh about her own body image journey, including a vulnerable Before &amp;amp; After image of herself that broke the internet and changed her life.</description></item><item><title>Tim Minchin - Lucky To Be Here | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170010/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tim Minchin is an Australian comedian, actor, writer, musician, poet, composer, and songwriter. He’s probably best known for his music, his comedy, and well… his ‘Matilda: The Musical’… but has it really all been “luck”?
Tim talks with Hugh, Ryan and Josh about so many different things in this fascinating chat about art and creativity, family, free-will, success, failure and the importance of taking life one level at a time.</description></item><item><title>Vulnerability Update: Josh Wrote a Song! | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170011/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you know, you know. And if you do know, you’re just as bonkers excited as we are.
Buuut if you don’t know, that’s totally fine too.
Those that were able to make it along to our Live On Stage show this year were treated to the debut performance of a song, written and performed by our very own Josh van Cuylenburg. But this song was not without context.</description></item><item><title>Dan Sultan - Stopping The Bullshit | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170012/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eastern Arrernte and Gurindji singer/songwriter Dan Sultan is a 5-time ARIA Award winner and respected stalwart of the Australian music industry. But alongside his creative achievements, is Dan’s struggle with addiction. Dan talks with Hugh, Ryan and Josh about everything from the adversity he’s faced on and off the stage, to the joy he now gets from his young family, and his ongoing love of creativity.
To purchase or listen to Dan's new album, Dan Sultan, follow this link: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>Jack's Gambling Addiction Story | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170013/</guid><description>Podcast Description For Jack, it’s progress, not perfection when it comes to his battle with gambling addiction.
This one is a slightly different episode for The Imperfects. Jack isn’t a celebrity, or an expert. But he is a person with imperfections, just like everyone else. And Jack has been kind enough to share his all-too-familiar story with Hugh, Ryan and Josh.
Jack discusses his crippling battle with sports gambling, his experience at rehab, and how he was finally able to escape his life of keeping secrets.</description></item><item><title>Dr Emily - Other People Matter | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170014/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr Emily is back - and once again proving why she is increasingly becoming the most popular person on The Imperfects.
This Emisode is all about a fundamental part of Positive Psychology… the beautiful idea that OTHER PEOPLE MATTER.
Now, you’re probably thinking… of course other people matter, right? Seems pretty obvious. But here, Dr Emily explains what it is about ‘other people’, that matters so much, and how much it relates to our never-ending search for that elusive thing we call “happiness”.</description></item><item><title>Brooke Blurton - The Path Of Most Resilience | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170015/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170015/</guid><description>Podcast Description To only say that Brooke Blurton was on The Bachelor and The Bachelorette, would not only be a crime to Show Notes, but a huge disservice to you. As Hugh, Ryan and Josh quickly discover, that doesn’t even scratch the surface of what makes Brooke the inspiring, resilient, game-changing, youth-working, breath of fresh air that she is.
While Brooke does touch on her Bachelor and Bachelorette experiences (and why she decided to do it), what makes this Vulnerabilitea House truly special is the story that she vulnerably tells about her upbringing in WA.</description></item><item><title>Penny Moodie's New Book - OCD &amp; Finding Joy Again | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Penny Moodie first shared her OCD story on The Imperfects in 2020. Since then, we and she have been flooded with incredible feedback from OCD sufferers who finally felt seen. Now Penny is back because she’s written an incredible book about OCD called The Joy Thief and it’s out now (link below).
In this beautifully moving episode, Penny talks openly with Hugh, Ryan and Josh about some of the confronting moments from her book.</description></item><item><title>Professor Tim Spector - Food Fight | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170017/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Food is such a mystery. Well, I mean, it’s the stuff we eat when we’re hungry, we know that much. But there are so many mysterious things ABOUT food. Like… What actually are healthy foods? What are good fats? Is meat good for you? Is orange juice really that bad? And can food truly be as effective as medicine? Professor Tim Spector has done all the research, written books (link below) and is one of the world’s top 100 most cited scientists.</description></item><item><title>Grant Denyer - Self-Worth Was Worth Fighting For | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170018/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Whether it was Family Feud or whether it was the weather, Grant Denyer has been a larger than life fixture on Australian TV for 25 years. But it hasn’t all been big smiles and Gold Logies. In this raw and vulnerable chat with the most joyous man on the telly, Grant opens up about his past dependence on the pain medication (OxyContin) that he needed after suffering a serious injury that broke his back.</description></item><item><title>Dr Emily - Friendship 4 Eva | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170019/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Monica. Chandler. Rachel. Ross. Phoebe. Joey. We all love Friends. But what about friendSHIPS? Why are our friendships so important to us? In this episode, Dr Emily explains everything - our different types of friends, why they matter SO much, and what it is about someone that makes us like them? (Spoiler alert: it’s got nothing to do with how impressive they are)
To listen to Will McMahon's Imperfects episode, follow this link: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>Myf Warhurst - The Anxiety of Uncertainty | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170020/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf Warhurst is an icon. An Australian icon. Everyone, we have an icon on our podcast.
From Spicks &amp;amp; Specks to Triple J, and Eurovision to Bluey… oh and doing a whole show about menopause… HER menopause… Australia has LOVED Myf Warhurst for a long, long time. You might even think it’s impossible to love her more, well just wait until you hear her honesty and vulnerability in this Vulnerabilitea House.</description></item><item><title>Osher Günsberg- In &amp; Out Of Control | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170021/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170021/</guid><description>Podcast Description For 20 years, Osher Günsberg has been one of Australia’s most famous and successful TV/radio/podcast personalities. Since hosting the wildly popular Australian Idol, to handing out roses on The Bachelor (and SO MUCH in between), there aren’t many showbiz stories that rival Osher’s sustained success. But if we’ve learned anything on this podcast, behind every perfect story is an imperfect reality. And as you’ll hear in this honest chat with Hugh, Ryan and Josh, Osher’s journey has been exactly that.</description></item><item><title>Dr Richard Harris - “That Thing In Thailand” | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170022/</guid><description>Podcast Description While our guest might humbly refer to his heroics as “that thing in Thailand”, it was in fact far more significant…
In 2018, the world was gripped by the terrifying story of thirteen boys who were miraculously saved from inside a Thai cave. Maybe you’ve seen one of the billion docos made about it, or the Hollywood film directed by Ron Howard. As you probably already know, the most miraculous part was HOW these boys were saved, thanks in large part to today’s guest, Australian deep-diving anaesthetist, Dr Richard “Harry” Harris.</description></item><item><title>Dr Emily - When Are You Triggered? | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170023/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170023/</guid><description>Podcast Description The phrase, “That’s triggering” or “I’m triggered”, has become more and more common. And while people are triggered by an event, or a topic, or even a scene in a TV show, what does it truly mean to be ‘triggered’? And should we really be avoiding triggering topics, or should we be exposing ourselves to them?
In this extremely helpful episode, Dr Emily goes deep on triggers. She explains to Hugh, Ryan and Josh what it means to actually be ‘triggered’, and how we often use the term incorrectly.</description></item><item><title>Christie Whelan Browne - Unbreakable | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170024/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Christie Whelan Browne is one of the funniest (and most talented) people in Australia. If you know, you know. She’s won multiple awards and done everything from stage and musical theatre, to TV drama and comedy… and most recently Dancing with the Stars.
But it’s her journey, before the #MeToo movement (and continues today) that’s making the biggest impact. Christie has rarely spoken so openly about her very public and tumultuous experience through the courts, in the media and even within her own family, as she became the face of a high-profile criminal trial and subsequent defamation trial that turned her life upside down.</description></item><item><title>Laura Henshaw - What Do They Think Of Me? | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170025/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Laura Henshaw has achieved a lot. Not only is she an author, law graduate and podcaster, but she is the CEO and co-founder of the wildly popular and successful health &amp;amp; fitness app, KIC - which she started and still runs with friend, and former Imperfects guest, Steph Claire-Smith. But behind her success, Laura still worries what people think of her. And in this Vulnerabilitea House, she vulnerably tells Hugh, Ryan and Josh where this comes from and how this anxiety continues to crop up for her in everyday life.</description></item><item><title>James van Cuylenburg - Love Your Wonky Bricks | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170026/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Other than being a Clinical Psychologist (with a child specialisation), Dr James van Cuylenburg is not only Hugh and Josh’s cousin, but in Hugh’s opinion, he’s the greatest piano player in the world - which provides zero context for this incredible episode.
James covers so much in this 90 minutes that it’s almost impossible to sum up here. Everything from the development of our kids today, screentime issues, the cost of ambition, the importance of self-compassion and James’s own experiences with bullying and how it motivated him to study psychology.</description></item><item><title>Dr Emily - How to Stress Less | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170027/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170027/</guid><description>Podcast Description What do you do when you’re stressed? Watch the telly? Scroll the innuhnet? Fix yourself a stiff VB on the rocks? We all feel stressed and burned out from time to time. It’s unfortunately a reality of life. But double-unfortunately, most of us don’t know how to correctly deal with it. And that’s why Dr Emily is here to help!
In this extremely practical episode, Dr Emily explains the science behind WHY we get stressed.</description></item><item><title>Hugh &amp; Penny - The Elephant in the Relationship | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170028/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170028/</guid><description>Podcast Description You might remember Penny Moodie from her first appearance on The Imperfects when she talked about her own experience with OCD. Link below if you don’t! Well, Penny is back to talk about something else; her marriage with Hugh. Or, more specifically, and far less click-baity, the mental load in her marriage with Hugh. “The mental load” is the cognitive effort that’s required to juggle the often invisible labour of running a household.</description></item><item><title>Michael (Wippa) Wipfli - Light at the End of the Tunnel | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170029/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170029/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you live in Sydney, you probably know Wippa. He’s on NOVA every morning with Fitzy and Kate Ritchie (or 6-7pm in the rest of the country), but he's also a veteran of Australian radio, having been on air for 20 years, making his start in Port Augusta before moving to Perth, then Melbourne and now Sydney.
Wippa and Ryan have been great friends for a long time. They even co-hosted the NOVA drive show for two years with Monty Dimond in 2009 and 2010.</description></item><item><title>Kemi Nekvapil - The Secret of Your Success | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170030/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 20:41:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170030/</guid><description>Podcast Description We all want to be successful. But what is ‘success’? And what if we’ve been thinking about it in the wrong way? Enter Kemi Nekvapil… back for the second time on The Imperfects!
Kemi has worked in the wellness industry for 25 years and holistic leadership for 10 years. She is a mother, a wife, an endurance athlete, a gardener, an author with three books, and a certified Dare To Lead facilitator having trained personally with the one and only Brené Brown!</description></item><item><title>Ben Shewry (Pt 2) - How The Chef Was Made | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170031/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170031/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is Pt2 of our chat with award-winning chef and owner of Melbourne restaurant, Attica. Go back and listen to Pt 1 if you haven’t yet. It’s a doozy. As the second part, this is a double-doozy… or a... twoozy… I guess.
In this episode, Ben explains how he managed to build empathy amongst the staff at Attica through something he created called Staff Speeches. He also shares a harrowing bullying story from his childhood when his mother saved him from certain catastrophe, and finally Ben opens up for the first time publicly about his challenging journey with body image.</description></item><item><title>Ben Shewry (Pt 1) - The Other Side of Excellence | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170032/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Originally from New Zealand, Ben Shewry is the head chef and owner of Melbourne-based restaurant Attica - the highly respected restaurant that has been included in the World’s 50 Best Restaurants numerous times.
Ben’s chat with Hugh, Ryan and Josh was so big and so special, it needed to be split across 2 big and special episodes.
In this first big and special part, they talk about what makes Attica such a unique place, how he approaches his work, and how he deals with the anxiety that arose from his divorce.</description></item><item><title>Dr Emily - Curb Your Perfectionism | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170033/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170033/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’ve spent about four and a half years on this podcast telling you why we’re all imperfect. But on this episode, Dr Emily actually explains why trying to be PERFECT is… well… really bad. And not only why it’s really bad, but why perfectionism’s mere existence is stealing all the good from our lives. Take it away Dr Emily……… PSYCHOLOGIST!
To learn more about Lynn Lyon's work around anxiety and perfectionism, follow this link: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Broden Kelly - When Anger &amp; Creativity Collide | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170034/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170034/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you don’t know comedy sketch group Aunty Donna, then take a moment, open your local internet browser and watch their incredible stuff for a bit (some of it is linked below). Then come back and listen to this episode with Aunty Donna's, Broden Kelly.
In this Vulnerabilitea House, Broden talks about his own and Aunty Donna’s creative process, and how it’s evolved over the years while working together on stage and on the telly.</description></item><item><title>Emma Murray - How Mindfulness Actually Works | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170035/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emma Murray is the high-performance mindset coach for the Richmond Football Club and Mum to four children.
As the founder of High-Performance Mindfulness - a company that uses mindfulness, psychology and meditation to help people perform at their best - Emma works with elite athletes, corporate executives, students and actors.
In this very practical and vulnerable episode, Emma explains how high-performance mindfulness has not only helped her clients, but also helped her when in 2016, her son Will (13 at the time) sustained a spinal cord injury that left him in a wheelchair for life.</description></item><item><title>360 (Matt Colwell) - From Addiction to Authenticity | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170036/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170036/</guid><description>Podcast Description This extremely raw and revealing episode with Australian rapper 360 is all about authenticity. 10 years ago, 360 (Matt Colwell) was one of the most successful and respected artists in Australia. His songs and albums went multi-platinum, he was winning prestigious ARIA and APRA awards and his enormous tours sold out nationally. But what no one knew at the time, is he was simultaneously battling an addiction that nearly took his life.</description></item><item><title>Dr Emily - How Anger Affects Us All | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170037/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170037/</guid><description>Podcast Description We all get angry. Some of us show our anger and some of us suppress it, but at the end of the day, we’re all susceptible to being angry.
In this episode, Dr Emily goes into the many aspects of anger - how it can show up in our lives, how it affects us and the people around us, and of course, what we can do about it.</description></item><item><title>Bronte Campbell - Comparison, The Thief of Joy | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170038/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170038/</guid><description>Podcast Description What if you were one of the best swimmers in the world, but you still couldn’t beat your older sister? That’s what Olympic swimmer Bronte Campbell has been facing for most of her career with her sister, Cate Campbell.
In this Vulnerabilitea House, Bronte opens up about being at the top of the professional swimming world, but still living in someone’s shadow. And how comparison stole much of the joy she might have otherwise felt.</description></item><item><title>Some Things We Wish We Knew Earlier | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170039/</guid><description>Podcast Description This B-B-B-BONUS episode arrives thanks to Hugh - a man who claims to hate lists. At least he did until he saw a list called “40 Things I Wish I’d Known at 40” (link below).
The list of things resonated with Hugh so much, that he sent it to Ryan and Josh and they decided to do an episode about it. This is that episode. It’d be weird if it wasn’t though wouldn’t it?</description></item><item><title>Ann Davidman - Should You Have Children? | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170040/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170040/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Ryan spoke about his ongoing indecision surrounding whether or not he should have children (Episode: To Breed or Not To Breed - link below), it definitely struck a chord with a lot of people who could relate. One of those people was “Parenthood Clarity Mentor” Ann Davidman, who helps people all over the world to answer the question, ‘Should I have children?’
So, as a sort-of-follow-up episode, Ann joins Hugh, Ryan and Josh in the Academy of Imperfection to provide some much-needed guidance to anyone who is also stuck in the ‘not-knowing’!</description></item><item><title>Dilruk Jayasinha - When Drinking Stopped Being Funny | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170041/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dil’s rise from accountant, to one of Australia’s most successful stand-up comedians is incredible. But what might be even incredible…er is how he was able to finally get sober after years of relying on alcohol.
In this vulnerable episode, Dil reveals to Hugh, Ryan and Josh what his life was like when his drinking was out of control, and how when he stopped, it forced him to change the way approached his work and his life.</description></item><item><title>Dr Emily - A Guide To Getting Therapy | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170042/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr Emily is back in the studio with Hugh, Ryan and Josh to deliver a slightly different, but extremely practical episode.
You may not be ready to see a therapist, but even the thought of it can be really overwhelming. Where do you start? Who’s the right therapist for you? What even happens once you’re in a therapy session? And which movies or TV shows get it right? Dr Em guides us through all of that, which will hopefully help you in your journey to find the right therapy for you.</description></item><item><title>Ben Crowe (Pt 2) - Now BE Your Inner Fan | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170043/</guid><description>Podcast Description This Academy of Imperfection is a Part 2, or… addendum episode… with the phenom that is Ben Crowe! So, if you haven’t heard Part 1, please listen to that one first by following the link below. In this episode, Ben expands on what he said in Part 1 about listening to your inner fan rather than your inner critic. He guides Hugh, Ryan and Josh through some simple exercises where they access positive memories from their past, so they can reframe their belief system, that they’re worthy of love and connection and belonging, and also worthy of having the courage to chase their dreams and goals.</description></item><item><title>Ben Crowe (Pt 1) - Meet Your Inner Fan | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170044/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ben Crowe is a huge part of our humble Imperfects history. Ben’s first episode with us in 2021 continues to be one of our most listened to episodes, helping many of you, your friends and your family members.
Ben is back in the Academy of Imperfection (split over two episodes) to spread even more wisdom that he's accrued from decades of working with elite athletes at Nike and now at MojoCrowe.</description></item><item><title>Samuel Johnson - A Life of Vulnerability | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170045/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Most of us first met actor and writer Samuel Johnson - and his silky voice - when he burst onto our screens over 20 years ago in the iconic show, The Secret Life of Us. Since then Sam’s experienced a lot of good times, but also some of the most challenging times any of us could imagine. In this Vulnerabilitea House, Sam chooses to answer the card, ‘What childhood challenges best prepared you for adulthood?</description></item><item><title>Hugh's Special... Verrry Special | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170046/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170046/</guid><description>Podcast Description A lil b-b-b-bonus ep to announce some exciting news...
Our very own Hugh van Cuylenburg has filmed and released his Resilience Project talk as a Special on Amazon Prime Video! It's called 'Hugh van Cuylenburg: G.E.M' and it's out now.
Hugh has been talking to people about Gratitude, Empathy and Mindfulness for a loooooong time, but now it's finally been filmed so everyone can watch it whenever they want.</description></item><item><title>Chrissie Swan - Honesty | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170047/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170047/</guid><description>Podcast Description A few years ago, Australian TV and radio legend Chrissie Swan decided to finally be honest with herself. She stopped doing the things she didn’t want to do anymore, and started doing the things that made HER happy. In this inspiring episode, Chrissie tells Hugh, Ryan and Josh how she was able to turn her life around and live as her true self. No more role-playing, just 100% Pure Swan.</description></item><item><title>Season 5 Trailer | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170048/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170048/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s Season 5 and oooooooooooh baby, are we excited!!! Yes we are. Why? Because everything’s new BUT everything’s also the same! Y’know? Like when your fish and chip shop does a big renovation and you’re really excited because the shop’s all spiffy and new, but you’re also really excited and relieved that they still have potato cakes and dim sims and prawn toast and all the stuff you liked last year.</description></item><item><title>Lael Stone - Take Care of Yourself | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170049/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Okay so quick brag… last year’s episode with parenting expert Lael Stone was 2022’s #1 Most Shared Episode on Apple Podcasts, which you can listen to at the link below. 💁‍♀️
But now, Lael is back for a brand new b-b-b-bonus ep with Hugh, Ryan and Josh to talk all about YOU! Well… you and your kids and your loved ones and some other very shareable things that you might be verrrrrry interested in.</description></item><item><title>How (and Why) Ryan Dumped His iPhone | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170050/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ryan loves his smart phone. Or at least, he used to.
Recently, he became fed up with it ruling his life. Endless scrolling, lost time, and just general bleh. So, three months ago he traded in his beloved iPhone for a not-so-smart flip phone - which he affectionately refers to as his ‘SmugPhone’.
In this b-b-b-bonus episode, Ryan talks Hugh and Josh through every aspect of his smug journey so far:</description></item><item><title>Santa Claus - A Special Vulnerabilitea House | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170051/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Well… it doesn’t get more exclusive than this!
During the busiest time of his year, Santa Claus has been kind enough to join Hugh, Ryan and Josh in the Imperfects studio, so he can enter The Vulnerabilitea House.
Despite some issues with parking his sleigh and some disruptive reindeers during the recording of this episode, Santa still manages to answer all three of the cards he pulls from the Vulnerabilitea House deck.</description></item><item><title>Hugh van Cuylenburg - Ageing, and Other Reflections | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170052/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170052/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this third of three b-b-b-bonus episodes, Hugh enters the Vulnerabilitea House and answers the question, ‘What do you see when you look in the mirror?’
For the first time in Hugh’s life, he doesn't see a young man reflected back at him, and he generously tells Ryan and Josh how this is effecting him.
How do we feel when we realise we’re not “young” anymore? It really is the age-old question isn’t it?</description></item><item><title>Josh van Cuylenburg - How to Defeat Envy | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170053/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170053/</guid><description>Podcast Description In yet another b-b-b-bonus episode, it’s Josh’s turn to draw from the deck Vulnerabilitea House cards.
And in doing so he shares his struggle with envy and jealousy amongst his successful friends, but also how it’s changed for him in recent years. And why.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Esther Perel - Let's Be Better Lovers | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170054/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170054/</guid><description>Podcast Description If there’s such thing as a b-b-b-bonus B-B-B-BONUS ep, this is it.
Psychotherapist Esther Perel is THE woman to turn to for relationship advice - IYKYK! Her two TED talks have been viewed over sixty million times, she’s written two books that have both been featured on the New York Times Bestseller list, and her intimate podcasts with real people in real counselling sessions have positively changed the relationships of millions of couples - including ours.</description></item><item><title>Ryan Shelton - To breed, or not to breed | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170055/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teeeeechnically the season is over… but who cares about rules when you’ve got three hosts who eat rules for breakfast!
Hugh, Ryan and Josh have decided to add three B-B-B-BONUS Vulnerabilitea House episodes to the end of the season!
To kick things off, Ryan answers the question: What parts of ageing scare you most?
Ryan goes on to share something big that’s been on his mind recently - whether or not he should have children - and his fear around making a decision that he may regret later in life.</description></item><item><title>Nedd Brockmann - The Man, The Myth, The Neddgend | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170056/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170056/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you look up ‘Nedd Brockmann’ in the dictionary you won’t find anything because it’s a proper noun. But if you google ‘Nedd Brockmann’, you’ll see the true meaning of ‘legendary’.
For 46 days in 2022, Nedd ran 100km a day from Cottesloe Beach to Bondi Beach, literally RUNNING ACROSS THE ENTIRE COUNTRY.
Why? That’s the best part. Nedd (23!) not only wanted to raise $1m for homelessness (it’s currently at $2.</description></item><item><title>Dr Emily - Lonely? You're Not Alone | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170057/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr Emily is back with Hugh, Ryan and Josh for the final Emisode of the year, and she’s chosen to talk about something we can all relate to in one way or another… loneliness.
In reflecting on last year’s raw episode with Christian O’Connell (link below), Dr Emily deep-dives into the many facets of loneliness.
- Why do we feel lonely?
- How do we handle our own loneliness?</description></item><item><title>A DARN GOSH BIG ANNOUNCEMENT | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170058/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170058/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re doing it. Well… there’s no turning back now.
Hugh, Ryan and Josh are going live on tour around the country with a stage show that they promise will be some of the most imperfect shows they’ve ever done. Live. Uncut. 100% guaranteed imperfection!
The Imperfects… LIVE ON STAGE in 2023
Special pre-sale tickets available from November 11-14 2022
Tickets available from livenation.com.au
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Kate Reid (Pt 2) - The Life-Saving Croissant | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170059/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170059/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you haven't heard Part 1 of our chat with Lune founder and master-baker, Kate Reid, we recommend you do that first. Because this episode, the sequel in our Croissantology, continues Kate's miraculous story as she attempts to overcome an eating disorder that forced her to leave her dream career in Formula 1.
Here, Kate explains how she did that by going all in on creating the "perfect" croissant.</description></item><item><title>Kate Reid (Pt 1) - The Impossibility of Perfection | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170060/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lune is highly regarded as the most respected patisserie in Australia. The New York Times even called the Lune croissant the best in the world. And the woman behind it all is Kate Reid, a former Aerospace Engineer at the Williams F1 Team in the UK.
Kate’s story has to be heard to be believed. It’s so epic, we had to break it into 2 parts.
In Part 1, Kate talks about her time at Williams, and generously shares her struggles with anorexia, which eventually forced her to end her F1 dream and return home to Australia for her recovery.</description></item><item><title>Oliver Burkeman - The JOY of Missing Out | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170061/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170061/</guid><description>Podcast Description 4000 weeks. Like it or not, that’s (approximately) the average length of a human life. And while we intend to use that time wisely, and do all the things we care about, we often find ourselves doing the opposite.
In this episode, UK author Oliver Burkeman tells us how to focus on the things that REALLY matter, rather than filling our time with the not-so-important things. Pulling from his best-selling (and incredible) book, Four Thousand Weeks: Time Management For Mortals, Oliver is this week’s lecturer in The Academy of Imperfection.</description></item><item><title>Linda Marigliano - Strict Parents &amp; Being a ‘Good Girl’ | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170062/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170062/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a DJ, TV presenter, award-winning podcaster and Triple J royalty, Linda Marigliano has had a big career and spoken to some of the biggest artists of all time. And now she joins Hugh, Ryan and Josh in The Vulnerabilitea House.
Linda talks about her life growing up as the child of an Italian father and Chinese mother, and explains about how the criticism she received from her mother made her feel about herself - both then and now.</description></item><item><title>Dr Kiran Martin - Truth, Leadership &amp; Gratitude | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170063/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170063/</guid><description>Podcast Description After listening to this Academy of Imperfection, you’ll no doubt be heartily agreeing with Hugh, who introduces Dr Kiran Martin as the most impressive person he’s ever met.
Over 30 years after jumping the fence to get inside a slum in Delhi so she could help treat the people in need, Dr Kiran now runs ASHA, an organisation she created that has helped over 900,000 people in over 100 slums across India.</description></item><item><title>Dr Emily - Rejection Sensitivity | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170064/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170064/</guid><description>Podcast Description None of us like to feel rejected. Whether it be at work, with friends, or on a date.
In this Dr Emisode, Dr Emily - our very own psychologist - tells Hugh, Ryan and Josh why some of us have a sensitivity to rejection. She explains what we can do about it, and how we can act compassionately towards others, and avoid making them feel unnecessarily rejected as well.</description></item><item><title>Hamish McLachlan - A World Turned Upside Down | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170065/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170065/</guid><description>Podcast Description While many of us may think of Channel 7’s Hamish McLachlan as the voice of sport in Australia, Hamish is very quick to point to Bruce McAvaney instead. As it turns out, we all love Bruce McAvaney A LOT and apologetically talk about him for quite a while - including a few wonderful Bruce stories from Hamish.
When we finally get to the Vulnerabilitea House card selection, Hamish answers the question, ‘When did your life get turned upside down and how did things change?</description></item><item><title>Nazeem Hussain - Losing a Parent | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170066/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stand-up comedian Nazeem Hussain lost his father to COVID-19 in 2021. In this episode, Nazeem shares the difficulties surrounding his family’s loss, and how his Dad’s life and sudden death has impacted his own life. But Nazeem also tells some wildly funny stories - in particular one about a "comedy concert" he did in Sri Lanka in front of The Prime Minister, which turned out to be organised by none other than his Dad.</description></item><item><title>Johann Hari (Pt 2) - Why Do We Do What We Do? | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170067/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170067/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Part 2 of this Academy of Imperfection, author and profanity purveyor, Johann Hari answers more of your brilliant questions.
As a result, Johann talks with Hugh, Ryan and Josh about intrinsic and extrinsic values, and how they affect the things we do and social media’s role in why we do them.
Also (speaking of click-bait), in an Imperfects exclusive, Johann reveals his go-to KFC order.
And double-also, we recorded this episode before the passing of Queen Elizabeth II, which will make more sense when you listen.</description></item><item><title>Johann Hari (Pt 1) - How Can We Change? | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170068/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Imperfects regular, Johann Hari joins us IN STUDIO for the first time to answer your questions!
In this very special edition of The Academy of Imperfection (which we’ve split into 2 MASSIVE EPISODES OVER 2 MASSIVE... um... EPISODES!), Johann Hari talks with Hugh, Ryan and Josh about our ability to change our habits in the face of addiction. And why we can learn from the approach of Overeater’s Anonymous to help our addiction to our phones and the internet.</description></item><item><title>Mark Wilson from JET - Dealing with Loss | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170069/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170069/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2003, JET’s Are You Gonna Be My Girl was one of the biggest songs on the planet. It was so big, Apple even used it for their first iPod ad. Remember? The one with the dancing silhouettes on the colourful backgrounds? Yeah, that was JET.
As the bass player for JET, Mark Wilson has lived the dream of any musician. He’s toured the world and played to packed stadiums, and even stood with Beyonce and Jay Z at the MTV Video Music Awards before playing on stage in front of them.</description></item><item><title>How to Write a Gratitude Letter | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170070/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170070/</guid><description>Podcast Description To celebrate Father's Day, Hugh plays some intimate audio of him reading a chapter of his book, 'Let Go', to his Dad (and Josh's Dad incidentally). But not just any old chapter, the final chapter ABOUT his Dad.
Afterwards, Hugh explains to Ryan and Josh, how writing a gratitude letter to your Dad (even if he isn't around anymore) can have a hugely positive impact.
But of course, Gratitude Letters aren't just for Dads, they're for your Mum or any carer in your life as well.</description></item><item><title>Dr Emily - Who Is Your Inner Critic &amp; Why Is It There? | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170071/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170071/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Emisode, Dr Emily explains some reasons why the inner critic is there in the first place, and where it’s coming from.
To watch Shirzad Chamine's Ted Talk, 'Know Your Inner Saboteurs', follow this link: https://bit.ly/2Ybu5Aa
To learn more about Daniel Siegel research and to purchase Mindsight, follow this link: https://bit.ly/3TnNVV5
To read the research article 'Positive Self-Statements, Power For Some, Peril For Others', follow this link, https://bit.</description></item><item><title>Darcy Vescio - They/Them Matters &amp; Here’s Why | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170072/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Carlton footballer Darcy Vescio is one of the biggest names in the AFLW, having won multiple awards including the Carlton Best &amp;amp; Fairest, 2-time All Australian selection and the Mark of the Year. As a marquee player, Darcy is at the top of their game.
But that’s just part of Darcy’s story. Less than a year ago, Darcy publicly came out as non-binary, announcing to the football community that they would now go by the they/them gender pronouns.</description></item><item><title>Dr Paul Callaghan - How To Follow The Dreaming Path | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170073/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170073/</guid><description>Podcast Description This Academy of Imperfection is a little different. As Hugh explains in the opener, this episode actually IS more like a lecture. But trust us, that’s a good thing.
Dr Paul Callaghan has a lot of wisdom to share that he's accrued over a lifetime of wins, losses and even a near death experience that changed his life forever. As an Aboriginal man, much of Paul's wisdom has come from his experience on The Dreaming Path, which also happens to be the title of the book he’s co-written with his friend and Aboriginal elder, Uncle Paul Gordon.</description></item><item><title>We Need to Talk... Again - Hugh, Ryan &amp; Josh have a chat | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170074/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170074/</guid><description>Podcast Description B-B-B-BONUS EP!!! A-A-A-AGAIN!!!
Every now and then, Hugh, Ryan and Josh like to get together and chat about their own imperfections that they’ve been dealing with recently. This is one of those episodes.
Hugh talks about “life seasons”, Ryan explains why European holidays aren’t always as perfect as they appear, and Josh talks about watching Morning Wars with Jennifer Anniston. To read Hugh’s recommendation of Kimberly Gillan’s article in the Age, ‘Are You In Tune With Your Life Season’, follow this link: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>Dr Emily - You Are Not Your Emotions | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170075/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170075/</guid><description>Podcast Description She’s back again! Our very own psychologist, Dr Emily!
In this emisode, Dr Emily reflects on a very moving chat we had with comedian Steen Raskopoulos. She talks with Hugh, Ryan and Josh about the concept of Emotional Awareness, and explains why it’s not only important to identify your unpleasant emotions, but why it's even more important to express them when they arise.
Oh, Hugh and tells us about going to Bondi.</description></item><item><title>Steen Raskopoulos (REPEAT - but with new intro!) | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170076/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Okay, so we're dabbling with repeat episodes because we've taken a week off. But we have recorded a new intro bit so there ya go, at least there's SOME new stuff!
This episode with comedian Steen Raskopoulos is not only one of our favourite episodes, but it's also the subject of next week's emisode with Dr Emily - which we can't wait for!
So yeah, back to regular, imperfect programming next week!</description></item><item><title>Michelle Brasier - The Case For Optimism | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170077/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Maybe you know Michelle Brasier from Aunty Donna. Or maybe from Shaun Micallef’s Mad as Hell. Or maybe she’s made you laugh (or cry) in any number of things she’s done on the stage and screen over the years. Or maybe you don’t her……… YET!
Michelle Brasier is a singer, actor, writer and comedian who - as you’ll hear in this Vulnerabilitea House - has overcome multiple adversities since a young age.</description></item><item><title>Martin "Rac" Heppell - The other F word... FAILURE | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170078/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170078/</guid><description>Podcast Description We all fail. All of us. Why? Because we’re all imperfect. And no one talks about failure more passionately than The Resilience Project’s own Martin “Rac” Heppell. And he’s today’s guest lecturer in The Academy of Imperfection.
Some of you may remember Rac’s first memorable appearance in The Vulnerabilitea House last season. If you haven’t heard it, we know you’ll want to listen (or re-listen) after this one - link below.</description></item><item><title>Libby Trickett - When is Enough, Enough? | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170079/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Australia has had a LOT of success in the Olympic Swimming Pool. That’s an understatement. But one of our most successful and loved Olympians of recent times is golden girl, Libby Trickett. During her successful swimming career Libby was all smiles after winning gold medal after gold medal at three consecutive Olympic Games, but as she shares in this episode, on the inside she was struggling with a powerful feeling that she wasn’t enough.</description></item><item><title>Dr Emily - The (pesky) Hedonistic Treadmill | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170080/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr Emily is back to help us all!
Reflecting on our episode with Olympic BMX rider, Sam Willoughby from Season 2, Dr Emily talks us through the dangers of the Hedonistic Treadmill, and its slightly lesser known cousin, Hedonistic Adaptation.
There’s a lot covered in this episode, including ‘Growth Mindset’, being mindful of what we want and why, and how quickly we actually adapt to finally getting those things we want.</description></item><item><title>Glenn Robbins - Listening to the Voice in Your Head | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170081/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170081/</guid><description>Podcast Description For over 30 years, Glenn Robbins has been one of the funniest and most loved performers in Australia. From The Comedy Company and Kath &amp;amp; Kim, to The Panel and of course Russell Coight, Glenn has guaranteed his spot in the comedy history books.
But Glenn hasn’t always seen it that way. From a young age he was told he was "average", and despite his many successes, has dealt with a lifetime of performance anxiety.</description></item><item><title>Lael Stone - Creating Emotionally Intelligent Humans | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170082/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170082/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the words of her own child, Lael Stone “works for the kids”.
But while Lael is technically a therapist who supports parents in understanding their children, everything Lael talks about in this edition of The Academy of Imperfection could easily be applied to all of us in understanding the people in our lives - no matter what age. Whether that be our friends, parents, colleagues or even ourselves.</description></item><item><title>Harry Garside - A Boxer Who Dares To Be Different | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170083/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Harry Garside is an Australian boxer who won bronze at the Tokyo Olympics - the first Olympic medal in boxing for Australia in 33 years. But to simply describe Harry Garside as a champion boxer, would be to sell him waaaaaaay short.
Because Harry is also a ballet dancer, a plumber and the guy who asked to wear a dress at the Olympic Opening Ceremony with the desire of defying gender stereotypes (request denied).</description></item><item><title>Dr Emily - Truth vs Harmony | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170084/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170084/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Emisode, Dr Emily returns to talk about a topic that is VERRRRRY close to the bones of Ryan, Hugh and Josh. The ongoing battle of Truth vs Harmony.
Does that ring any bells for you? Do you choose to live truthfully? Or harmoniously? And what does that even mean? What’s the difference? And how do living ‘truthfully’ or ‘harmoniously’ affect us and the people around us?</description></item><item><title>Max Gawn - The Comment That Changed Everything | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170085/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Big episode. HUGE episode in fact. Especially for Ryan.
Ryan has been a long-suffering/recent-celebrating supporter of the Melbourne Demons his entire life. And today, Premiership captain of the Dees, Max Gawn is in The Vulnerabilitea House.
Ryan. Breathe.
Max tells Hugh, Ryan and Josh about a courageous comment made by one of the players in a team meeting that addressed the negative way players were speaking to each other.</description></item><item><title>Tarang Chawla - Men Talking About Men’s Violence | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170086/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170086/</guid><description>Podcast Description We seriously hope you listen to this one. I mean, obviously we hope you listen to all our episodes but THIS ONE... well, we reckon this one’s important.
Tarang Chawla’s younger sister Niki was the kindest person he knew. But in 2015, Niki was murdered by her partner who she was trying to break up with, as a result of domestic violence. Since then, Tarang has become an activist against men’s violence, educating all Australians on the many forms of abuse and its role in the mental health crisis.</description></item><item><title>Narelda Jacobs - Being True To You | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170087/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170087/</guid><description>Podcast Description You might think that TV journalist and proud indigenous woman Narelda Jacobs has a perfect life. She’s the co-host of Studio 10, makes regular appearances on The Project, she’s a three-time host of the Sydney Gay &amp;amp; Lesbian Mardi Gras, and she’s... done lots of other things that are also on her Wikipedia page.
But like all of us, Narelda’s life has been far from perfect. I mean come on guys, we’re all imperfect, surely you’ve learnt that by now!</description></item><item><title>Dr Emily - Managing a Panic Attack | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170088/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome back to Dr Emily, our very own... PSYCHOLOGIST!
Reflecting on the recent episode with Luke McGregor, in this episode Dr Emily talks about panic attacks. What are they? Why do we get them? And what do we do when they show up and scare the hell out of us?
Thanks Dr Em
To find out more about by Russ Harris, The Happiness Trap and his work as an Acceptance and Commitment Therapy Trainer visit; https://www.</description></item><item><title>Oliver Twist - Where is Home? | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170089/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Originally from Rwanda, stand-up comedian Oliver Twist spent 14 years in a Malawi refugee camp before finally arriving in Ipswich, Queensland with his family.
In this Vulnerabilitea House, Oliver answers the question, “Where is home for you?” - a simple question for some, but a complicated one for Oliver.
Oliver shares stories from his extraordinarily imperfect life in great detail. Everything from being displaced by the Rwandan Genocide, to living in the refugee camp, and eventually seeing Trevor Noah perform stand-up comedy on the internet.</description></item><item><title>Kemi Nekvapil - How to Live a Life Without Apology | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170090/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Okay, so get this...not only is Kemi Nekvapil an author, speaker and coach, but she was trained by Brené Brown. Yuh. THE Brené Brown.
As an author, Kemi has written a new book that you must read. It’s called ‘POWER: A woman’s guide to living and leading without apology’. And in our imperfect opinion, as 3 NON-women, it’s exactly what we all need right now.
In this edition of The Academy of Imperfection, Kemi shares her childhood experience living in foster care - being moved between 5 different families across England - and how it’s shaped her as the powerful woman she is today.</description></item><item><title>Luke McGregor - Being Funny And Having Panic Attacks | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170091/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Like all of us, Luke McGregor is imperfect. From his challenging childhood at home and school, to his crippling panic attacks on stage as a stand-up comedian, Luke generously shares some of the many stories from his imperfect life with us and of course with you.
A lot gets covered here, including Luke’s ongoing battles with OCD and why he eventually turned to professional comedy after trying a handful of other careers first.</description></item><item><title>We Need to Talk - Hugh checks in with Ryan &amp; Josh after a big month | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170092/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170092/</guid><description>Podcast Description B-B-B-BONUS EP!!!
After what has been a very vulnerable month for The Imperfects, Hugh wanted to check in with Ryan and Josh to see how they’re feeling after some “big shares” in the first 4 episodes of the season.
Firstly, Ryan reflects on how he’s feeling after revealing his worries around the supposed “love triangle” with Hugh and Hamish during Hamish’s Vulnerabilitea House episode. Then Josh talks about his self-doubt surrounding his role on the podcast, and of course where he’s at with his internet use since bravely sharing addiction with the group during the Johann Hari episode.</description></item><item><title>Introducing Dr Emily… PSYCHOLOGIST!!! | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170093/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Please welcome the newest member of The Imperfects family... our resident psychologist, Dr Emily!
Dr Emily recently joined The Imperfects behind the scenes, ensuring our episodes are released with care, compassion and professionalism.
This season however, Hugh, Ryan and Josh begged Dr Emily to bring her knowledge directly to you with her very own regular episodes! Each month she will join Hugh, Ryan and Josh and bring in something from The Imperfects archives, to then give general advice and information based on the stories and themes from the episode.</description></item><item><title>Hamish Blake - Let's Talk About Self-Doubt | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170094/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish Blake is a very funny man. No surprises there. But as it turns out, Hamish Blake is also a man who experiences self-doubt. Hmm, SOME surprises there!
And as the latest guest in The Vulnerabilitea House, Hamish tells Hugh, Ryan and Josh about the self-doubt he’s experienced while performing on TV, even after doing it for almost 20 years. Whether it be during one of his many appearances on panel shows, or even while standing in front of the contestants on his first day as host of Lego Masters.</description></item><item><title>Johann Hari - Why You Can't Pay Attention | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170095/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170095/</guid><description>Podcast Description We can all feel it. And unfortunately, it’s getting worse. Paying attention and properly focussing these days is getting harder and harder. And in the first Academy of Imperfection for 2022, Johann Hari is here to explain to Hugh, Ryan and Josh exactly why that is. The good news is... it’s not our fault. But luckily there are things we can do about it. If you want to delve deeper into the topics and themes from this episode, please read (or listen to - like Hugh and Ryan did) Johann’s incredible new book, Stolen Focus: Why You Can’t Pay Attention.</description></item><item><title>Kate Langbroek - Love Story | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170096/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kate Langbroek, in our humble opinion, is a very special person and we absolutely love her.
Kate has experienced decades of success on Australian TV and radio - whether it was every Wednesday night on The Panel, or with her mate Hughesy on the radio. Now she’s written her first book, “Ciao, Bella” - filled with stories from her amazing and colourful life. But even with all her success, like all of us, Kate’s life hasn’t been perfect.</description></item><item><title>Season 4 Trailer | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170097/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170097/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re back... for a warm up ep... and as you’ll soon hear... we’re properly professional now!
Not because of the three of us, because of the new members of our Imperfects team... Bridget Northeast, BOTH British Andys (Hall and Poole), George Martin, Jamieson Moore and Dr Emily!
This really is our highest level of excitement EVER.
So, so, so good to see you,
Hugh, Ryan &amp;amp; Josh
See omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>Georgia &amp; Hugh | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170098/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this extremely special episode, Hugh reads the opening chapter from his second book, ‘Let Go’ to his younger sister (and Josh’s older sister) Georgia van Cuylenburg - a heartfelt letter from him to her.
What follows is an incredibly powerful conversation between the two of them that, for the first time, addresses unspoken feelings and issues that have existed for years.
We’ve been fortunate to have witnessed many beautiful examples of vulnerability on this podcast over the years… but guys… seriously… this is next level.</description></item><item><title>Almost end of year wrap - (Part 2) | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170099/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 07:32:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170099/</guid><description>Podcast Description A Part 1 wouldn't be complete without a Part 2. So here it is... wrapping up the wrap up!
After Hugh kicked things off with a beautiful bang in Part 1, Part 2 sees Josh and Ryan follow suit and reflect on 2 moments from the podcast that meant a lot to them in 2021 - powerful moments from Martin Heppell and Ben Crowe.
Once again, thank you for your ears.</description></item><item><title>Almost end of year wrap - (Part 1) | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170100/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170100/</guid><description>Podcast Description We had to split our "End of Year Wrap" into 2 parts because of what came up in this ep.
Without wanting to spoil it, it's yet another example of what can happen when we start the conversation and show a lil vulnerability to the ones we love.
There will obviously be a Part 2, and then a few more very VERY special episodes to round out the year.</description></item><item><title>The Vulnerabilitea House - Peter Helliar | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170101/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 01:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Whether it’s TV, film, stand-up comedy, radio, books, podcasts... or... Straughanie, Peter “Pete” Helliar has been making us laugh for over 20 years and has found a lot of success doing it. But like anyone, Pete’s life has at times been imperfect.
In this episode of The Vulnerabilitea House, Pete speaks with Hugh, Ryan and Josh about one of the most difficult times in his life when one of his close friends and colleagues, Richard Marsland, took his own life.</description></item><item><title>Your Non-Free Gift! (Unannounced Surprise Podcast Episode) | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170102/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 23:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Surprise! We have something special for you. Okay fine... it MAY be merchandise. Fine, you twisted our arm... it IS merchandise. But GOOD merchandise! PUN merchandise!!!
Have a listen and go to thevulnerabiliteabag.com. BUT BE QUICK!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Academy of Imperfection - Jeff Warren | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170103/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 09:03:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170103/</guid><description>Podcast Description You may have an image of what a “meditation teacher” sounds like. Whatever you’re thinking of, we’re pretty sure you’re not thinking of Jeff Warren. Jeff Warren is not your traditional meditation “guru”. He’s just... well, a guy. A Canadian guy! And alongside his own challenges with ADD and Bipolar diagnoses (among other things), he’s found a life and successful career in mindfulness and meditation. And if you’re like us, you’ll want to be his best friend.</description></item><item><title>The Dyl &amp; Friends crossover episode | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170104/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 00:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170104/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’ve been big fans of the Dyl &amp;amp; Friends podcast for a long time now. We love everything about the former AFL footballer and host of the Dyl &amp;amp; Friends podcast, Dylan Buckley. To that end, we are very excited to release this episode of our podcast as a Dyl &amp;amp; Friends and The Imperfects collaboration. As you will hear, Dylan is authentic and open. He embraces his imperfections and as such this chat is a true mix of both shows.</description></item><item><title>The Vulnerabilitea House - Dr Yves Rees | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170105/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 06:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we welcome Dr Yves Rees into The Vulnerabilitea House. One morning, in a hotel room in Canada, aged 30, Yves had a life changing epiphany. With this came a range of emotions - happiness, confusion, pain, joy...and almost everything in between.
As well as being a renowned history professor at La Trobe University, Yves is transgender.
In today’s episode of The Imperfects, Ryan, Josh and Hugh are educated and enlightened by the insightful and vulnerable Dr Yves Rees.</description></item><item><title>Becky Lucas - The power of laughter | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170106/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 03:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170106/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week's episode of the podcast we talk to Australian comedian Becky Lucas. Becky has written a book -Acknowledgements, and as you will hear Hugh is BIT of a fan.
We cover a-lot in this ep, from bitchy English exchange students, Becky’s parents' divorce, 'dick-lit’, the stresses of lock down; and somehow we manage to squeeze in a discussion of 90s NBL basketball under the ‘auspice’ of a special birthday surprise.</description></item><item><title>The Vulnerabilitea House - Martin Heppell | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170107/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 04:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170107/</guid><description>Podcast Description There is no one else in the world quite like our guest this week. For years people kept telling Hugh he needed to bring on a new presenter to meet the demand from schools and workplaces around the country. He said he would only ever do it if he found someone extraordinary. In 2015, Hugh found that extraordinary person - Martin Heppell. In today’s episode, Ryan, Hugh and Josh are both moved and inspired as Martin steps into the Vulnerabilitea and shares a heart breaking story from his childhood.</description></item><item><title>The Academy Of Imperfection - Daniel Ellenberg | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170108/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 23:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ready to learn? Us too.
In The Academy of Imperfection this week, imperfect students Hugh, Ryan and Josh speak with American psychologist, leadership coach and specialist in the area of male relationships, Daniel Ellenberg. Daniel shares some very insightful stuff on how men relate to other men - why they do what they do, and why they DON’T do what they don’t do! But by the end of the episode, what was supposed to be a casual “lecture” turns into a men’s workshop of sorts, as Hugh, Ryan and Josh show a lot more vulnerability towards each other than they were expecting.</description></item><item><title>The Vulnerabilitea House - Josh Van Cuylenburg | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170109/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two episodes in a week, what is going on? Well, it's another Vulnerabilitea House that's what. This week it's Josh's turn.
Lockdown rules meant this teahouse was spread across three tea houses but it doesn't detract from the quality of the tea, and the vulnerableness. Josh discusses an issue he's had for a long, long time and Hugh takes some time to delve a little deeper into the concept of vulnerability.</description></item><item><title>Just The Three Of Us (a bonus snap podcast because we needed a chat) | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170110/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 04:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170110/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the beginning, it was novel. A change of pace. A good excuse to bake our own bread and believe that “we’ll always bake our own bread from now on because it’s so nice to wake up to the smell of fresh bread in the morning!”
But come on... seriously... we’re not baking bread anymore are we? This whole COVID thing has become a proper bummer. Like, next-level maximum bummer.</description></item><item><title>Travis Boak - Dealing with trauma | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170111/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 03:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Travis Boak is one of the best footballers in the country. At age 33, he is showing no signs of slowing down, in fact many believe he is just getting better. His brilliance on the ground is a direct result of the hard work he puts into his game. What many don’t know however, is that he works just as hard on his mental and emotional health. Due to the tragic passing of his father, Travis has, for way too long, carried the baggage and trauma of this tragedy.</description></item><item><title>The Vulnerabilitea House - Ryan Shelton | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170112/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Thirsty? How about a nice cup of Vulnerabilitea from The Vulnerabilitea House? Join Hugh and Josh as they listen to co-host Ryan Shelton pick a card at random and get vulnerable.
Ryan shares some recent discoveries he’s had with his psychologist in regards to how certain aspects of his childhood prepared him... or DIDN’T prepare him for adulthood.
N.B. There’s also a quick digression into the nostalgic world of 90s NBL Basketball.</description></item><item><title>The Academy of Imperfection - Dr Billy Garvey, Paediatrician | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170113/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 04:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Go get your pens and notebooks everyone!
In this edition of The Academy of Imperfection, students Hugh, Ryan, Josh sit down with famed paediatrician, Dr Billy Garvey of The Royal Children’s Hospital.
Currently, Billy regretfully has a two and a half year waiting list to see him in person, but is keen to reach as many of you as possible NOW. And with all the talk on our podcast about parenting recently, we felt this was a very necessary episode.</description></item><item><title>The Vulnerabilitea House - Hugh van Cuylenburg... Round 2 | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170114/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 23:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our very own Hugh van Cuylenburg is back in the hotseat for a second round in the Vulnerabilitea House! And guys... wowee. Potentially inspired by the most recent Vulnerabilitea House episode with Missy Higgins, Hugh opens up about how much he is actually struggling right now. In fact, he’s probably as raw and honest and vulnerable as he’s ever been on The Imperfects. The Vulnerabilitea House (and the whole podcast tbh) is all about encouraging vulnerability by sharing our own struggles and imperfections.</description></item><item><title>Christian O'Connell - Breakfast Radio, panic attacks &amp; starting afresh | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170115/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 23:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170115/</guid><description>Podcast Description At the beginning of 2018, Christian O'Connell was the host of the number one breakfast radio show in England, he averaged over 2 million listeners a day, he'd won basically every award possible in the radio industry, he was seemingly on top of his world.
Unbeknownst to almost everyone in his life though, he could barely make it on the air. At the age of 45, Christian had started suffering debilitating panic attacks.</description></item><item><title>The Vulnerabilitea House - Missy Higgins | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170116/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 09:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Prepare yourself for a very different episode of The Vulnerabilitea House (for a few reasons):
We welcome our first guest... MISSY HIGGINS IS BACK ON THE POD!
We all live in Melbourne and it was COVID lockdown at the time of recording so we were on Zoom.
The whole thing almost didn’t happen at all... and you’ll hear why.
For those new to The Vulnerabilitea House, here’s how it works.</description></item><item><title>The Academy of Imperfection - James Victore | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170117/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 21:35:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome back to The Academy of Imperfection - a conversational lecture series that features guest lecturers talking with students Hugh, Ryan, Josh and you about different areas of imperfection. Today, designer, author and teacher, James Victore talks about CREATIVITY.
Before writing his brilliant 2019 book ‘Feck Perfuction: Dangerous Ideas on the Business of Creativity’, James created commerical work for Moet &amp;amp; Chandon, Time magazine and Yohji Yamamoto and has had his work exhibited in Nwe York’s MoMA and The Louvre in Paris.</description></item><item><title>The Vulnerabilitea House - Josh van Cuylenburg | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170118/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170118/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re back in The Vulnerabilitea House! This time it’s Josh van Cuylenburg. The proven question-ASKER, becomes a first-time question-ANSWERER as he sips some Vunerabilitea and shares an honest and raw story from his past that not even his brother Hugh knew about - all in the name of vulnerability and connection. Pour yourself a cup of tea everyone... it’s great to see you again.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Jamila Rizvi - Living with the effects of a brain tumor | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170119/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jamila Rizvi is a writer/author, journalist, commentator, change advocate, feminist and all round wonderful human being.
In 2018 Jamila was met with horrible news. She was diagnosed with a rare brain tumour. In the podcast, Jamila tells us of these challenging recent years...the multiple surgeries, the radiotherapy treatment the continuing recovery and the effects all of this has had on her life, her family and her mental health.</description></item><item><title>The Vulnerabilitea House - Ryan Shelton | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170120/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170120/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast we return to The Vulnerabilitea House, and this time its Ryan Shelton's turn.
The Vulnerabilitea House, is a new style of episode from The Imperfects, where we share something honest and a little bit vulnerable, all over a nice cup of tea.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Academy of Imperfection - Ben Crowe | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170121/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to the very first episode of The Academy of Imperfection!
Presented by The Imperfects, this new series of conversational lectures will feature experts talking about different areas of imperfection with students Hugh, Ryan, Josh and you.
The inaugural guest lecturer is someone we are extremely excited about. Ben Crowe. Along with Brene Brown, Ben has easily been the most mentioned person on The Imperfects over the last few years.</description></item><item><title>The Vulnerabilitea House - Hugh van Cuylenburg | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170122/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170122/</guid><description>Podcast Description The most hyped pun in podcasting, well, sort of...
This is a new style of episode from The Imperfects, something a bit shorter than normal, which we’ll scatter between the longer eps. As you’ll see from the title of these episodes (pun revealed in the ep!), they’re designed to encourage vulnerability. First up. it's Hugh's turn to be vulnerable, if all goes well, we'll try and get some more imperfect people sharing something honest and a little bit vulnerable, all shared over a nice cup of tea.</description></item><item><title>Rick Davies - Living with OCD | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170123/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 10:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Best known for his role as ‘Jimmy’ on TV show, Offspring, actor Rick Davies doesn’t remember a time in his life without Obsessive Compulsive Disorder (OCD). Despite that, this is the first time Rick is speaking publicy about it. Rick selflessly shares a number of uncomfortable (and slightly embarrassing) stories from his life with OCD, and afterwards Hugh chats with Ryan and Josh about some resources for anyone who has OCD or knows someone who does.</description></item><item><title>Trailer - Season 3 | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170124/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170124/</guid><description>Podcast Description In preparation for what they “promise” will be the biggest year yet for The Imperfects, Hugh, Ryan and Josh catch up for a short warm-up episode. Yes, there’ll of course NEW episodes in Season 3, but also there’ll be new TYPES of episodes, including one that involves an extremely overhyped pun.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Steph Claire Smith - Body Image, Modelling &amp; Instagram | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170125/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 00:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Steph Claire Smith
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Will McMahon - Depression &amp; High School Expectations | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170126/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 23:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170126/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2019 Will McMahon and Woody Whitelaw (of Will &amp;amp; Woody fame) released the video, "Best Mates Sit Down For A Heart To Heart About Depression". If you haven't seen it, you really must. It's a fantastic example of the power of vulnerability.
Will McMahon has enjoyed a phenomenal career in radio, currently co-hosting the drive slot on the KISS network. He's at the top of his game, yet Will has achieved all this whilst enduring the undulations of living with a mental illness.</description></item><item><title>Sam Willoughby - The Tragic Injury That Changed His Life | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170127/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 01:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170127/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week’s episode, Hugh chats with Australian BMX racer, world champion, multi-Olympian, Sam Willoughby. In 2016, Sam experienced a life-changing neck injury which left him with tetraplegia. At 29 Sam has lived a remarkable life and is an incredible person who tells his life story with candour and honesty.
Following the chat, Ryan and Hugh discuss Sam's journey whilst exploring some of the life lessons we can learn from this incredible person.</description></item><item><title>Steen Raskopoulos - Comedy &amp; Depression | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170128/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 23:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170128/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we talk to the wonderful Australian comedian, actor and improviser Steen Raskopoulos. Over the past 8 years Steen Raskopoulos has enjoyed a remarkable career with acclaimed stand up shows, starring roles on tv shows, working with his comedic idols, copious awards...the works. In this episode Steen talks candidly of the mental health struggles going on behind the scenes during this meteoric rise.
Following this, Ryan and Hugh discuss some of the valuable lessons we can learn from Steen's story.</description></item><item><title>Catriona Bisset - Exercise, Anxiety &amp; Female Empowerment | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170129/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 01:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170129/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we talk to Australian athlete, the incredible Catriona Bisset. Catriona talks candidly of her unconventional...almost unintentional journey of becoming the fastest woman in Australian history over 800m.
Following this, Ryan and Hugh discuss some of the valuable lessons we can learn from Catriona's fascinating journey.
If this episode has triggered anything for you around mental health, we strongly recommend lifeline on 13 11 14.
The Imperfects is brought to you by The Resilience Project.</description></item><item><title>Johann Hari - The Importance of Connection | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170130/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 04:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hugh sits down with author/journalist Johann Hari for an illuminating chat
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trailer - Season 2 | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170131/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 03:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170131/</guid><description>Podcast Description All new guests and a little bit more&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Penny Moodie - Obsessive compulsive disorder (OCD) | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170132/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 03:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Obsessive compulsive disorder (OCD) - An often quoted, yet misunderstood mental health condition. In this very special bonus episode Hugh talks to Penny Moodie about what living with OCD Anxiety is really like. Penny, amongst other things, is also&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus &amp; our mental health | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170133/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 11:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170133/</guid><description>Podcast Description A different episode for very different times. In this special one off episode, Ryan &amp;amp; Hugh take a break from our standard format to discuss some tools and strategies we can implement to increase our resilience and improve our mental health during&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ryan Shelton - Shame, Jealousy &amp; Purpose | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170134/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 00:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170134/</guid><description>Podcast Description This very special, end-of-season episode sees co-host Ryan Shelton step into the interviewee&amp;rsquo;s chair. Ryan talks about his bold career ambitions, the complex feelings of jealousy and shame when he didn&amp;rsquo;t feel like he was successful enough and how&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Clare Bowditch - Music, Panic Attacks &amp; Body Image | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170135/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 23:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170135/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The Imperfects, Hugh sits down for a moving chat with musician, songwriter, radio host and all-round legend, Clare Bowditch. Following the interview, Ryan quizzes Hugh on what we can learn from Clare&amp;rsquo;s story, and how these lessons&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Georgie Gardner - Parenting &amp; Living in the Spotlight | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170136/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 03:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170136/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The Imperfects, Hugh sits down for a fascinating chat with Georgie Gardner, host of The Today Show. Following the interview, Ryan quizzes Hugh on what we can learn from Georgie&amp;rsquo;s story, and how these lessons can be applied to our&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Erin Deering - How Money Doesn't Always Make You Happy | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170137/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2019 05:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Triangle Co-Founder
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jack Watts - Anxiety, Pressure in Football and Mistakes | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170138/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 07:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170138/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The Imperfects, Hugh sits down with Australian rules Footballer Jack Watts, who talks openly of his mistakes and the pressures of professional sport. &amp;ldquo;No one&amp;rsquo;s perfect and that&amp;rsquo;s a realisation I had to come to..I felt like I&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Missy Higgins - Quitting Music, Depression &amp; Connection | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170139/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 09:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170139/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this first episode of The Imperfects, Hugh chats with Australian singer-songwriter Missy Higgins, who makes herself vulnerable in a way she never has before publicly. In sharing her battles with her own mental ill-health and how it drove her to temporarily quit music, Missy explains why ‘connection’ was ultimately her saviour. Following the interview, Ryan quizzes Hugh on what we can learn from Missy’s story, and how these lessons can be applied to our own imperfect lives.</description></item><item><title>An introduction | The Imperfects</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3615170140/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 05:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3615170140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Interesting people, allowing themselves to be vulnerable and sharing with us, their imperfect lives.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>