<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Call Me Back - with Dan Senor on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/call-me-back-with-dan-senor/</link><description>Recent content in Call Me Back - with Dan Senor on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 06:03:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/call-me-back-with-dan-senor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Two-State Solution - with Haviv Rettig Gur | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900176/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 06:03:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900176/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are increasingly hearing from policymakers in the U.S. and around the world about re-starting the path to a two-state solution after the war. That is our focus today in our weekly check-in with Haviv Rettig Gur. Is there a path to a two-state solution in the near or medium term? If so, what has changed where the two-state solution has failed in the past. We also discuss a more optimistic take on the differences between the Israeli Government and the Biden administration.</description></item><item><title>What starts with the Jews, rarely ends with just the Jews - with Yuval Levin | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900001/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 00:31:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900001/</guid><description>Podcast Description On previous episodes of this podcast we’ve discussed the origins and history of antisemitism. But what does this antisemitic moment tell us about society more generally? If you look back throughout history, the persecution of Jews has often coincided with an even bigger crack-up in society.
Is this antisemitic moment the first sign of something bigger going on – is it a vessel for broader and deepers trends? This is what we will discuss with Yuvan Levin.</description></item><item><title>The 'Day After' in Gaza - with Haviv Rettig Gur | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 05:04:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900002/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s weekly check-in with Haviv Rettig Gur of The Times of Israel, we discuss Israel&amp;rsquo;s current thinking about what a post-Hamas Gaza might look like - from a governance perspective and a security perspective. It&amp;rsquo;s a topic we&amp;rsquo;ll return to from time to time as the planning is fluid, but we are beginning to learn about early thinking from Israeli officials.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Would Gazans rise up against Hamas? - with Amos Harel | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 19:01:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we get an update on the IDF operation in South Gaza, what Israel is learning about the Gaza tunnel system, what Israelis are learning through further de-briefing of the returned Israeli hostages, and what to make of reports of Palestinian civilians&amp;rsquo; growing frustrations with Hamas. We also wanted to discuss the tragic loss of Gal Eisenkodt and what it says about Israeli society.
Amos Harel has been the military correspondent and defense analyst for Israel&amp;rsquo;s Haaretz newspaper for 25 years.</description></item><item><title>Hamas’s psychological warfare — with Haviv Rettig Gur | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 06:44:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900004/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s weekly check-in with Haviv Rettig Gur of The Times of Israel, we discuss the volatility in Israel, as Israelis pivoted from fighting the war to collectively embracing returning hostages during the pause in fighting. And, now, the IDF and Israeli society at large have pivoted back to fighting the war.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Haley's path &amp; Biden's only move - with Mike Murphy | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900005/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 05:11:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900005/</guid><description>Podcast Description There are two storylines we have been following closely that are not necessarily shaped by the minute-to-minute developments in Israel, but their outcomes could have an outsized impact on U.S. policy on Israel, Gaza, and the broader Middle East. The first is the Republican contest for president. The next debate is this coming week – December 6. In the last GOP presidential debate, the issue that attracted the most airtime was the October 7 war and America’s response.</description></item><item><title>Douglas Murray debunks 5 lies about Israel | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 12:36:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Douglas Murray, a British writer and commentator, has been on the ground in Israel for about a month, covering the war as a reporter and analyst. He writes for the New York Post, the Sun, and Spectator. He is an international bestselling author of numerous books, including &amp;ldquo;The War on the West&amp;rdquo;, which can be found here: https://www.barnesandnoble.com/w/the-war-on-the-west-douglas-murray/1140022863
He is the host of the Uncancelled History podcast &amp;ndash; https://podcasts.</description></item><item><title>Lessons learned from the hostage deal - with Haviv Rettig Gur | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today is our weekly check-in with Haviv Rettig Gur of The Times of Israel. We discuss early lessons that Haviv is identifying for Israeli leaders and security officials – and for Israeli society – based on: the implementation of the agreement by Hamas to release hostages, the overall negotiations, the release of Palestinian prisoners from Israeli prisons, and the pause in fighting. What are the implications for this next phase of the war?</description></item><item><title>The hostage deal: a new phase in the war - with Amos Harel | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 16:53:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amos Harel has been the military correspondent and defense analyst for Israel&amp;rsquo;s Haaretz newspaper for 25 years. He is among the most well-sourced and thoughtful journalists and analysts covering Israeli security affairs inside Israel. Prior to his current position, Amos spent four years as night editor for the Haaretz Hebrew print edition, and from 1999-2005 he was the anchor on a weekly Army Radio program about defense issues.</description></item><item><title>The Price of Israeli Hostages - with Haviv Rettig Gur | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900009/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Haviv Rettig Gur returns for our weekly conversation from Jerusalem to provide real-time reporting and analysis on the war, and invaluable historical context.
More than 240 people, including a number of U.S. citizens, were taken hostage during the Oct. 7 massacre. More than half of the hostages have foreign nationalities (either as dual citizens or solely as foreign nationals). Four hostages, including two U.S. citizens, have since been released, one has been rescued and two others were found dead.</description></item><item><title>A conversation with Yonit Levi &amp; Jonathan Freedland | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900010/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900010/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode &amp;ndash; which we recorded just after the historic rally in Washington, DC and as we approached the sixth Shabbat since October 7th &amp;ndash; I have a wide-ranging conversation with Yoni Levi in Tel Aviv and Jonathan Freedland in London. Yonit and Jonathan are co-hosts of the popular podcast, UnHoly, which you can find here: https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/unholy-two-jews-on-the-news/id1548441108
This episode is a sharecast, in which we are dropping the conversation in each of our respective podcast feeds (&amp;ldquo;Call Me Back&amp;rdquo; &amp;amp; &amp;ldquo;UnHoly&amp;rdquo;).</description></item><item><title>Anshel Pfeffer - Embedded in Gaza | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 13:12:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900011/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s 5:45 am on Thursday, November 16 in New York City. It’s 12:45 pm in Israel.
Early this morning, I spoke with Anshel Pfeffer, who is just back from his second trip into Gaza embedded with the IDF. Anshel has covered Israeli politics, Israel National &amp;amp; national security, and global affairs for over two decades. He is a senior correspondent and columnist for Haaretz and Israel correspondent for The Economist.</description></item><item><title>Flipping the Script -- with Haviv Rettig Gur | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Haviv Rettig Gur returns for our weekly conversation from Jerusalem to provide real-time reporting and analysis on the war, and invaluable historical context. Today, we talk to Haviv about the hostage crisis in the context of Israel&amp;rsquo;s war fighting. And we also discuss Haviv&amp;rsquo;s contrarian view of how Israel is reacting to the growing international pressure it is encountering – what it means for Israel and what it means for Jews around the world.</description></item><item><title>Israeli Resilience, Pre- &amp; Post-10/07 - with Liel Leibovitz | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900013/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a crossover episode with Liel Leibovitz in which we jointly release a conversation on the Call Me Back podcast feed and the Tablet Magazine&amp;rsquo;s Unorthodox podcast feed.
Liel Leibovitz, who was born and raised in Israel, is editor-at-large for Tablet Magazine and a host of its weekly culture podcast Unorthodox. He also hosts the daily Talmud podcast Take One. He is the editor of &amp;ldquo;Zionism: The Tablet Guide&amp;rdquo; and he&amp;rsquo;s uthor of the new book, &amp;ldquo;How the Talmud Can Change Your Life: Surprisingly Modern Advice from a Very Old Book.</description></item><item><title>American Jews on the Left, post-October 7th | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we release the new book by Saul Singer and me: &amp;ldquo;The Genius of Israel: The Surprising Resilience of a Divided Nation in a Turbulent World&amp;rdquo;, which you can order now at: www.amazon.com/Genius-Israel-Small-Nation-Teach/dp/1982115769/ref=sr_1_1?crid=3LKV3ZLWLBOL1&amp;amp;keywords=dan+senor&amp;amp;qid=1694402205&amp;amp;sprefix=dan+senor%2Caps%2C87&amp;amp;sr=8-1 OR www.barnesandnoble.com/w/the-genius-of-israel-dan-senor/1143499668
Today&amp;rsquo;s guest is Ruby Namdar, who was born and raised in Jerusalem to a family of Iranian-Jewish heritage. His first book, &amp;ldquo;Haviv&amp;rdquo; (2000), won the Israeli Ministry of Culture&amp;rsquo;s Award for Best First Publication.</description></item><item><title>30 days, 3 pressure points - with Haviv Rettig Gur | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900015/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we release the new book by Saul Singer and me: &amp;ldquo;The Genius of Israel: The Surprising Resilience of a Divided Nation in a Turbulent World&amp;rdquo;, which you can order now at:
www.amazon.com/Genius-Israel-Small-Nation-Teach/dp/1982115769/ref=sr_1_1?crid=3LKV3ZLWLBOL1&amp;amp;keywords=dan+senor&amp;amp;qid=1694402205&amp;amp;sprefix=dan+senor%2Caps%2C87&amp;amp;sr=8-1
OR
www.barnesandnoble.com/w/the-genius-of-israel-dan-senor/1143499668
Haviv Rettig Gur returns for our weekly conversation from Israel to provide real-time reporting and analysis on the war, and invaluable historical context. We focus on three pressure points facing Israel, and we also touch on some good news about Jewish-Arab relations inside Israel.</description></item><item><title>BIDEN: "Don't!" / NASRALLAH: "I hear you." - emergency episode with Dr. Matthew Levitt | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 16:58:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900016/</guid><description>Podcast Description We just had a conversation with Dr. Matthew Levitt, an expert on Hassan Nasrallah and Hezbollah, getting his immediate reaction and analysis on Nasrallah’s first public address since the October 7 War.
Matt is the director of the Program on Counterterrorism and Intelligence at the Washington Institute for Near East Policy. He served as deputy assistant secretary for intelligence and analysis at the U.S. Department of the Treasury. During his tenure at Treasury, he played a central role in efforts to protect the U.</description></item><item><title>Understanding Israel's battlefields (&amp; U.S. involvement) - with Dr. Fred Kagan | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900017/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 12:20:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Next week we will release the new book by Saul Singer and me: &amp;ldquo;The Genius of Israel: The Surprising Resilience of a Divided Nation in a Turbulent World&amp;rdquo;, which you can order now at:
www.amazon.com/Genius-Israel-Small-Nation-Teach/dp/1982115769/ref=sr_1_1?crid=3LKV3ZLWLBOL1&amp;amp;keywords=dan+senor&amp;amp;qid=1694402205&amp;amp;sprefix=dan+senor%2Caps%2C87&amp;amp;sr=8-1
OR
www.barnesandnoble.com/w/the-genius-of-israel-dan-senor/1143499668
The speech that I reference in today&amp;rsquo;s episode &amp;ndash; in which I discuss the resilience of Israelis in this moment &amp;ndash; can be found here: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WygtNbwf-tk
By the time you listen to this episode, we may be witnessing escalation on Israel’s Northern border.</description></item><item><title>Antisemitism. Everywhere. | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Next week we will release the new book by Saul Singer and me: &amp;ldquo;The Genius of Israel: The Surprising Resilience of a Divided Nation in a Turbulent World&amp;rdquo;, which you can order now at:
www.amazon.com/Genius-Israel-Small-Nation-Teach/dp/1982115769/ref=sr_1_1?crid=3LKV3ZLWLBOL1&amp;amp;keywords=dan+senor&amp;amp;qid=1694402205&amp;amp;sprefix=dan+senor%2Caps%2C87&amp;amp;sr=8-1 OR www.barnesandnoble.com/w/the-genius-of-israel-dan-senor/1143499668
The speech that I reference in today&amp;rsquo;s episode &amp;ndash; in which I discuss the resilience of Israelis in this moment &amp;ndash; can be found here: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WygtNbwf-tk
As for today&amp;rsquo;s episode, according to the ADL, from Oct 7-23, anti-semetic incidents in the U.</description></item><item><title>A post-October 7th security doctrine for Israel - with Haviv Rettig Gur | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Haviv Rettig Gur returns for our weekly conversation from Israel to provide real-time reporting and analysis on the war, and invaluable historical context. We wanted to check in with Haviv, who is the political analyst at The Times of Israel, where was also a long time reporter. He’s also working on a book. Haviv was also a combat medic in the IDF where he served in the reserves. Listen on Apple Podcasts: https://podcasts.</description></item><item><title>The Ground Operation Begins/End of hostage negotiations? — with Avi Issacharoff | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900020/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 14:30:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Avi Issacharoff returns for an urgent update on overnight developments and their implications. Avi has been an analyst and journalist for The Times of Israel, Walla, and Haaretz. In these roles, he reported extensively on the inner workings and leaders of Hamas and other Palestinian factions in Gaza and the West Bank — Avi has extensive networks in the Israeli security services and the Palestinian Territories. He is also the co-creator and writer of the Netflix original series “Fauda”, and other television series for Netflix and Showtime.</description></item><item><title>A brief history of Hezbollah - with Dr. Matthew Levitt | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900021/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Much like our earlier episode on the history of Hamas, today we look at the history of Hezbollah, an even greater threat to Israel than Hamas. Our guest is Dr. Matthew Levitt.
Matt is the director of the Program on Counterterrorism and Intelligence at the Washington Institute for Near East Policy. He served as deputy assistant secretary for intelligence and analysis at the U.S. Department of the Treasury. During his tenure at Treasury, he played a central role in efforts to protect the U.</description></item><item><title>The Oldest Hatred... Post-October 7 - with Ritchie Torres, Michal Cotler Wunsh &amp; Ethan Missner | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Among the questions we&amp;rsquo;ve been getting since October 7 are those about antisemitism. Does this time feel different? Why? Or, another question, when is it appropriate to be critical of Israeli Government policy, and when does it cross the line into antisemitism? What is the difference between antisemisitm and anti-zionism? Or is there a distinction at all? Is the latter simply a modern-day version of the former?
These are some of the issues we discuss in this episode with our guests: Congressman Ritchie Torres (D-NY) and Michal Cotler Wunsh, who is the Israeli Government’s Special Envoy for Combating Global Antisemitism (she is also a former Member of Israel&amp;rsquo;s Knesset).</description></item><item><title>The Fog of Waiting - with Haviv Rettig Gur | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Haviv Rettig Gur returns for our weekly conversation from Israel to provide real-time reporting and analysis on the war, and invaluable historical context.
We wanted to check in with Haviv on increasing questions we are hearing from within Israel and the U.S. about &amp;ndash; as it relates to the call-up of reserves and the deployment along Israel&amp;rsquo;s southern border - why &amp;lsquo;hurry up and wait&amp;rsquo;?
In this conversation we explore the &amp;lsquo;known knowns&amp;rsquo; of equities that Israeli decision-makers must be balancing.</description></item><item><title>Forecasting the war’s path ahead - with Michael Oren | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900024/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 15:26:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900024/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode will be the first of a few conversations in which we touch on the range of directions this October 7th war could go (especially when considering comparisons to Israel&amp;rsquo;s previous wars, including those with Hamas and also the 1973 Yom Kippur War). Michael Oren is the author of numerous books, including: “Six Days of War: June 1967 and the Making of the Modern Middle East” and “Power, Faith, and Fantasy: America in the Middle East: 1776 to the Present”.</description></item><item><title>The Laws of War — with Matt Waxman | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900025/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900025/</guid><description>Podcast Description In President Biden’s address from the Oval Office, we continue to hear calls for Israel to respect the laws of war. In recent days, we have also heard others call for “proportionality” in Israel’s response. What does that actually mean? According to what definition of proportionality? And according to whose rules? Is Israel subjected to different rules of war than other countries? Is Hamas a different kind of enemy?</description></item><item><title>Public sentiment on the eve of invasion - with Haviv Rettig Gur | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900026/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Haviv Rettig Gur returns to our podcast to provide real-time reporting and analysis on the war, and invaluable historical context. He will be a weekly guest on our podcast through the duration of the war. Today he is focused on Israeli public sentiment as the country mobilizes, and also looks at how the October 7 is perhaps changing perceptions in and of the Israeli Arab community.
Haviv is the political analyst at The Times of Israel.</description></item><item><title>The Gazan Battlefield — with Avi Issacharoff | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900027/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we consider to what to expect when the IDF enters Gaza. Avi Issacharoff has been an analyst and journalist for The Times of Israel, Walla, and Haaretz. In these roles, he reported extensively on the inner workings and leaders of Hamas and other Palestinian factions in Gaza and the West Bank — Avi has extensive networks in the Israeli security services and the Palestinian Territories.
He is also the co-creator and writer of the Netflix original series “Fauda”, and other television series for Netflix and Showtime.</description></item><item><title>The October Massacre changes... Everything - with Elliott Abrams | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900028/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900028/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode with Elliott Abrams, we provide additional detail on the history of Israel-Gaza/Hamas — this time from a White House insider on U.S.-Middle East policy during a critical period in Hamas’s takeover of Gaza — what were leaders in Washington and Jerusalem thinking at the time?
Elliott takes us into the Situation Room: What did they get right and what did they get wrong? This part of the discussion is a good complement to our conversation last week with Jonathan Schanzer on this history of Hamas.</description></item><item><title>The world unites against Hamas... for now - with Yaakov Katz | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900029/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900029/</guid><description>Podcast Description For analysis of the Israeli Government&amp;rsquo;s formation of a (Netanyahu/Gantz) unity government and war cabinet, preparations for the invasion of Gaza, and anticipating the Hezbollah threat from the northern border, we are joined by Yaakov Katz. Yaakov is a columnist for the Jerusalem Post and senior fellow at the Jewish People Policy Institute.
Previously, Yaakov served as editor-in-chief at the Jerusalem Post, before which he was the paper&amp;rsquo;s military reporter and defense analyst.</description></item><item><title>The history of Hamas, and its likely grim future - with Jonathan Schanzer | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900030/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900030/</guid><description>Podcast Description We have been getting a lot of questions about the history of Hamas, its ideological roots and objectives, its allies and rivalries, how it wound up in charge of Gaza, the origins of this war, and whether there could actually be a post-Hamas Gaza. For this tutorial, our guest is Dr. Jonathan Schanzer, who is senior vice president for research at Foundation for Defense of Democracies.
Jon previously worked as a terrorism finance analyst at the U.</description></item><item><title>ISRAEL AT WAR: The multi-front probability - with Bret Stephens | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900031/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 19:06:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bret Stephens, Pulitzer Prize winning columnist for The New York Times, returns for a conversation immediately on Day III of this war.
Bret came to The New York Times after a long career with The Wall Street Journal, where he was most recently deputy editorial page editor and, for 11 years, a foreign affairs columnist. Before that, he was editor-in-chief of The Jerusalem Post. And prior to working in Israel, he was based in Brussels for The Wall Street Journal.</description></item><item><title>ISRAEL AT WAR: The Hostage Dilemma - with Haviv Rettig Gur | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900032/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 16:20:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Haviv Rettig Gur returns to our podcast to provide real-time reporting and analysis on the war, and invaluable historical context. His insights on how Israel might prosecute this war &amp;ndash; and the possible end of Israel&amp;rsquo;s security paradigm with Gaza and its approach to Israeli hostages &amp;ndash; are especially important. Haviv is the political analyst at The Times of Israel. He was a long time reporter for the Times of Israel.</description></item><item><title>Karl Rove on our new (or not so new) political dysfunction | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900033/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 10:59:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900033/</guid><description>Podcast Description One day we’re talking about the 2024 presidential election being a re-match of the 2020 election. The next day we’re watching the Speaker of the U.S. House of Representatives being defenestrated through a historic vote OUT of the Speakership.
What is going on here? Is it a new level of crazy, or not that new at all? Karl Rove puts this period of political dysfunction in historical context.</description></item><item><title>Who will tell Biden? The dread of 2024 - with A.B. Stoddard | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900034/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 13:41:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Many Democratic activists, strategists, donors, officeholders, and party leaders are privately discussing the weaknesses of President Biden&amp;rsquo;s candidacy, heading into what now appears to be a very competitive 2024 election. But is anyone telling President Biden? Is anyone credible and viable willing to challenge President Biden for the Democratic nomination? We are constantly told that American democracy hangs in the balance. Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t this be the time? These are some of the topics we discuss with A.</description></item><item><title>What's with the GOP &amp; these debates? - with Eliana Johnson | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900035/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 21:11:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900035/</guid><description>Podcast Description What to make of the most recent presidential debates? What to make of what we&amp;rsquo;re learning from these debates? What to make of the media&amp;rsquo;s coverage of and role in these debates? And where do things go from here? Eliana Johnson is the editor-in-chief of the Washington Free Beacon. She is a former White House correspondent at POLITICO. She previously served as Washington editor of National Review, where she led the organization’s election coverage of the 2016 presidential election.</description></item><item><title>What's with Republicans &amp; Ukraine? - with Aaron MacLean | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900036/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why is U.S. assistance for Ukraine being held up in Congress? What is at stake for the U.S.?
Aaron MacLean is a senior fellow at the Foundation for Defense of Democracies. Previously, he was Senior Foreign Policy Advisor and Legislative Director to U.S. Senator Tom Cotton. Aaron served on active duty as a U.S. Marine for seven years, deploying to Afghanistan as an infantry officer. Following his time in the operating forces, he was assigned to the faculty of the U.</description></item><item><title>Will Saudi Arabia's MBS save Israel from its political crack-up? With Micah Goodman | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900037/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you pessimistic about Israel’s future? My new book – which I wrote with my &amp;ldquo;Start-Up Nation&amp;rdquo; co-author Saul Singer – should give you reason for optimism. I care deeply about Israel. I’m endlessly fascinated by Israel. I travel to Israel regularly. Some may say this is a fraught period for anyone who cares about Israel. But in our new book, &amp;ldquo;The Genius of Israel: The Surprising Resilience of a Divided Nation in a Turbulent World,” we write about the health and resilience of Israeli society, a topic that could not be more relevant to this period.</description></item><item><title>Unprecedented polarization, or has Israel been here before? With Meir Soloveichik | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900038/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 16:17:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you pessimistic about Israel’s future? Optimistic? Or somewhere in between? My new book – which I co-authored with Saul Singer – will you give you reasons for optimism. And there is a special pre-order campaign for my loyal podcast listeners. If you order the book between now and this Friday, simply email confirmation of your purchase to book@dansenor.com and we’ll email you right back a special chapter sampler (in the form of a PDF document) that deals with some of the issues being debated in Israel – and about Israel – now.</description></item><item><title>Can we be optimistic about Israel? With Yossi Klein Halevi | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900039/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan Senor&amp;rsquo;s weekly podcast about the economy, politics and foreign policy.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mohamed El-Erian on B-R-I-C-S (&amp; J-E-T-S) | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900040/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 13:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Mohamed El-Erian returns to the podcast to discuss the implications of the recent announcement of the expansion of BRICS, China&amp;rsquo;s economy and possible spillover effects in the West, past forecasting of recession/stagflation, and the Fed&amp;rsquo;s inflation target. We also discuss Mohamed&amp;rsquo;s new book: &amp;ldquo;Permacrisis: A Plan to Fix a Fractured World&amp;rdquo;
We begin the podcast with a conversation about the upcoming NFL season. To go straight to the discussion about the BRICS, the macro economy and global markets, begin listening at 17:00.</description></item><item><title>The inner workings of an untold (Iran) deal - with Rich Goldberg | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900041/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 13:30:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Back in July, we dedicated an episode to the question of whether the U.S. was on the cusp of reaching a new deal with Iran. Or was an unofficial deal already hatched that nobody was talking about?
According to Rich Goldberg, the answers to these questions are now becoming more clear.
Rich has also been focused on another development that didn’t get sufficient press attention this summer: the release of US hostages by Iran.</description></item><item><title>A peek into a Trumpless election, or just a mirage? With Kristen Soltis Anderson | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900042/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 11:01:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kristen Soltis Anderson is a GOP pollster, messaging strategist, and Founding Partner of Echelon Insights, an opinion research and analytics firm that serves brands, trade associations, nonprofits, and political clients. Through her work at Echelon, she regularly advises corporate and government leaders. Kristen also leads focus groups for The New York Times’ opinion section “America in Focus” series.
Items discussed in this episode:
“Republican Voters Aren’t Looking to Be Rescued From Trump” https://www.</description></item><item><title>Yevgeny Prigozhin falls from the sky | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900043/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 10:50:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Special episode with Dr. Fred Kagan on the Russia-Ukraine war (and Putin&amp;rsquo;s hold on power).
Fred is the Director of the Critical Threats Project at the American Enterprise Institute. He is also working closely with the Russia team at the Institute for the Study of War. Fred is a former professor of military history at the US Military Academy at West Point. He completed his PhD in Soviet and Russian military history at Yale University.</description></item><item><title>Why China is studying America’s Forgotten War - with Rep. Mike Gallagher | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900044/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 10:32:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900044/</guid><description>Podcast Description There is a lot these days to discuss with a US official who is an expert on China and has major influence over US-China policy. But today we take a longer view of the Cold War (II) we are in with China by looking at a historical comparison in Cold War I. Congressman Gallagher just wrapped up teaching a history class on one such historical comp – the Korean War.</description></item><item><title>The Summer of Geopolitical Heat - with Walter Russell Mead | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900045/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Throughout modern history, there were major wars that were triggered by fits of inattention or inadvertence. In retrospect, these moments can seem obvious – sometimes even linear. Walter Russuell Mead is observing some of these fits of inattention right now. Walter believes there is some kind of collective denial about these trends. He calls it “geopolitical climate denialism.” That’s what we discuss with him in this episode.
He’s also just back from another trip to India, where he’s been spending a lot of time.</description></item><item><title>Mike Murphy on Plan B for 2024 | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each national political party should be thinking about their Plan B for the 2024 presidential election. Mike Murphy returns to the podcast to discuss each party&amp;rsquo;s predicament and where they can go from here. Murphy has worked on a number of presidential campaigns and run 26 gubernatorial and US Senate races across the country. He was a top strategist for John McCain, Mitt Romney, Jeb Bush, and Arnold Schwarzenegger.</description></item><item><title>Is Israeli society collapsing, or just growing up? | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900047/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900047/</guid><description>Podcast Description One week ago, Israel’s parliament passed the first pillar of its judicial reform package. This, despite 30 weeks of massive protests against the reforms. Calling these mass protests understates it. Hundreds of thousands of people turning out each week, culminating last week in a historic protest march from Tel Aviv to Jerusalem.
We have received a lot of questions and comments from listeners to this podcast about the current situation in Israel.</description></item><item><title>A techno-skeptic on the A.I. revolution - with Christine Rosen | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900048/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Christine Rosen is skeptical of all the techno-optimism around the coming era of artificial intelligence. In this episode, she responds to our recent guest, Tyler Cowen (episode # 120).
Christine Rosen is a senior fellow at the American Enterprise Institute, where she focuses on American history, culture, technology and feminism. Concurrently she is a columnist for Commentary magazine and one of the cohosts of The Commentary Magazine Podcast.</description></item><item><title>The (Iran) deal that shall not be named - with Rich Goldberg | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900049/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is the US on the cusp of reaching a new deal with Iran? Or has a deal already been hatched that nobody is talking about? To help us understand what is going on, Rich Goldberg returns to the podcast.
Rich is a senior advisor at the Foundation for Defense of Democracies. From 2019-2020, he served as a Director for Countering Iranian Weapons of Mass Destruction for the White House National Security Council.</description></item><item><title>Cracks in the Kremlin? With Fred Kagan | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900050/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 12:30:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Does Putin’s hold on power now look stronger or weaker? What can we learn about where the Russia-Ukraine war is heading? And what is actually happening with the Ukraine counter-offensive?
Fred Kagan is the Director of the Critical Threats Project at the American Enterprise Institute. He is also working closely with the Russia team at the Institute for the Study of War. Fred is a former professor of military history at the US Military Academy at West Point.</description></item><item><title>Contrarian take on the Wagner Putsch - with Richard Fontaine | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900051/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last weekend, Yevgeny Prigozhin, the leader of the Wagner mercenary group, launched a rebellion, coup or putsch against Moscow. It&amp;rsquo;s still hard to discern what it was. As of now, It seems Prigozhin has halted the Wagner operation. The situation is fluid, and we aren’t going to leap to conclusions on this podcast. But our guest today, Richard Fontaine, told me he is skeptical that these events so far reflect real cracks in President Putin’s rule.</description></item><item><title>SELECTS: The American College Crack-Up - with Niall Ferguson | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900052/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 12:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900052/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this special re-published episode, we revisit a captivating conversation that resonated deeply with our audience, offering new listeners an opportunity to delve into the insights shared by Niall Ferguson.
In this decade we may finally experience a true crack-up in higher education. There have been comparable periods on American college campuses in the past (in the 1960s and 1980s, for example).
But our guest today, historian Niall Ferguson, believes what’s happening now is on a whole other level.</description></item><item><title>"Losers Don't Come to Their College Reunions" -- with Bruce Feiler | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900053/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 12:16:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900053/</guid><description>Podcast Description These days there are lots of conversations about the re-shaping of the workforce as a result of the pandemic.
Bruce Feiler is just out with a new book – THE SEARCH: Finding Meaningful Work in a Post-Career World – based on years of research on this topic.
He is the author of seven New York Times bestsellers. His book WALKING THE BIBLE describes his 10,000-mile journey retracing the Five Books of Moses through the desert.</description></item><item><title>Bret Stephens teaches college grads to argue! | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900054/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 11:46:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bret Stephens, Pulitzer Prize winning columnist for The New York Times, returns for a conversation immediately following his address at the University of Chicago’s Class Day, where there was an organized — and ultimately unsuccessful — effort against his speech.
We discuss his address, the effort against him and lessons learned. Bret also recently returned from a mission to rescue 111 Ethiopian Jews, part of a multi-decade effort to bring thousands of Ethiopian Jews to Israel to become Israeli citizens, the history of which he unpacks at the end of our conversation.</description></item><item><title>Optimism, AI (and the end of homework!) - with Tyler Cowen | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900055/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 12:40:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s guest is surprisingly upbeat about the world. A big factor in his optimism is the revolution in artificial intelligence that we’re about to live through.
Tyler Cowen is an economics professor at George Mason University and he’s the faculty director of the Mercatus Center. He is the coauthor – with Alex Tabarock – of the economics blog Marginal Revolution (the #1 economics blog in the world) and the co-founder of Marginal Revolution University.</description></item><item><title>Highest Risk: 2025-2026 - with HR McMaster | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900056/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 11:42:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Upon graduation from the US Military Academy in 1984, HR McMaster served as a commissioned officer in the US Army for thirty-four years. He retired as a lieutenant general in June 2018.
From 2014 to 2017, General McMaster designed the future army as the director of the Army Capabilities Integration Center and the deputy commanding general, futures, of the US Army Training and Doctrine Command (TRADOC). As commanding general of the Maneuver Center of Excellence at Fort Benning, he oversaw all training and education for the army’s infantry, armor, and cavalry force.</description></item><item><title>The Invisible Primary - with Mike Murphy | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900057/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 12:20:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900057/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, we go deep on the current phase (the invisible primary) of the 2024 presidential primaries with Mike Murphy, who has worked on a number of presidential campaigns, as well as run 26 gubernatorial and US Senate races across the country. Murphy was a top strategist for John McCain, Mitt Romney, Jeb Bush, and Arnold Schwarzenegger. He’s a political analyst for NBC and MSNBC. He’s co-host of the critically acclaimed &amp;ldquo;Hacks on Tap&amp;rdquo; podcast.</description></item><item><title>How do we know if a country is a success? Israel at 75, with Daniel Gordis | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900058/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 12:11:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900058/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do we know if a country is a success? It’s a question that our guest on this episode, Dr. Daniel Gordis , tried to answer in a new book, timed for the 75th anniversary of Israel’s independence. His book is called “Impossible Takes Longer: 75 Years After Its Creation, Has Israel Fulfilled Its Founders’ Dreams?”
Gordis moved to Israel in 1998, where he raised three children. He is one of the most thoughtful observers of Israeli life and Israeli history.</description></item><item><title>The *real* tensions inside Israel — with Micah Goodman | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900059/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 11:40:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the past 16 weeks, Israel has experienced one of the biggest protest movements since its founding. On the surface, these protests were about proposed judicial reforms. But was something deeper going on &amp;ndash; for both sides of this debate? On a recent trip to Israel, Dan sat down with Dr. Micah Goodman to better understand the forces shaping this debate.
Micah, who has been on our podcast before, is on the speed-dial of a number of Israeli political leaders.</description></item><item><title>IRAN - pariah no more? with Mark Dubowitz | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900060/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 11:25:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we sit down in Israel with Mark Dubowitz, who is the CEO of the Foundation for the Defense of Democracies (FDD), at a time that Saudi Arabia is reopening its embassy in Tehran, and Iran&amp;rsquo;s relations appear to be flourishing with Beijing, Moscow and much of the Sunni Arab Middle East. Six months ago, Iran was under enormous pressure. What happened?
In his role as CEO of FDD, a nonpartisan think tank based in Washington, DC, Mark has advised the Bush, Obama, Trump and Biden administrations and lawmakers on both sides of the aisle, and he has testified more than twenty times before the U.</description></item><item><title>Broken schools, newsrooms, governments &amp; other institutions — Fixable or forever broken? with Alana Newhouse | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900061/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900061/</guid><description>Podcast Description “The real debate today isn’t between the left and right. It’s between those invested in our current institutions, and those who want to build anew.” This is according to Alana Newhouse in a provocative essay she penned for Tablet Magazine. Alana offers a a new frame through which to asses the dysfunction we see in institutions all around us, and what to do about them.
In the conversation, Alana also discusses another essay recently published by Tablet, called “The Vanishing”, by Jacob Savage.</description></item><item><title>"Silver Linings" in Israel's crisis? with Yaakov Katz | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900062/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yaakov Katz – Editor-in-Chief of The Jerusalem Post and a former advisor to Israeli Prime Minister Naftali Bennett – returns to our podcast.
Earlier, Yaakov Katz served as The Jerusalem Post’s military reporter and defense analyst. He is the author of &amp;ldquo;Shadow Strike: Inside Israel&amp;rsquo;s Secret Mission to Eliminate Syrian Nuclear Power&amp;rdquo; and co-author of two books: &amp;ldquo;Weapon Wizards - How Israel Became a High-Tech Military Superpower&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Israel vs.</description></item><item><title>Special Episode: Update on Israel's political crisis | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900063/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 15:02:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900063/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this special episode we play a conversation that Dan recently had on the Commentary Magazine podcast on the current crisis, how Israel got here and where it goes from here. Be sure to subscribe to Commentary Magazine and its podcast: https://www.commentary.org/
Transcript</description></item><item><title>US-China De-escalation? (&amp; the latest on covid's origin) -- with Josh Rogin | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900064/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is the US Government trying to re-engage and bring down the temperature with China? Why right now?
And what about the resurgent findings on the possible lab leaked accident (on the origin of the pandemic)? Where does this fit into the de-escalation dynamic?
Josh Rogin is a long-time foreign affairs journalist, currently a columnist for The Washington Post. He’s also a Political Analyst for CNN. He’s the author of the bestselling book: “Chaos Under Heaven: Trump, Xi, and the Battle for the Twenty-First Century”</description></item><item><title>"Did we break Iraq?" with Eli Lake | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900065/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Twenty years ago this past week, on March 19, 2003, the United States invaded Iraq, marking the second time the U.S. fought a war in Iraq in just over a decade. What is the legacy for U.S. foreign policy, for the Middle East, and for domestic public opinion on America&amp;rsquo;s role in the world?
Journalist Eli Lake traveled to Iraq six times since the invasion 20 years ago. He is contributing editor to Commentary Magazine and a columnist for The New York Sun.</description></item><item><title>China Surprise: Saudi-Iranian Detente | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900066/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900066/</guid><description>Podcast Description China just announced that it had brokered a deal between Saudi Arabia and Iran to restore diplomatic relations, for the first time since they were officially severed in 2016. But this news begs more questions than it answers. To help us understand what it means for Washington, Jerusalem, Beijing, Tehran, and Riyadh, Rich Goldberg joins the podcast.
Rich is a senior advisor at the Foundation for Defense of Democracies.</description></item><item><title>Western ideas at their best &amp; why they're under attack - with Eric Cohen | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900067/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eric Cohen is the CEO of Tikvah. He was the founder and remains editor-at-large of the New Atlantis, and he serves as the publisher of Mosaic. Eric has written for The Wall Street Journal, The Washington Post, and Commentary, He is the author of In the Shadow of Progress: Being Human in the Age of Technology. He previously worked for the U.S. President’s Council on Bioethics.
Eric&amp;rsquo;s work can be found at: TikvahFund.</description></item><item><title>What does Biden mean by “as long as it takes”? - with Richard Fontaine | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900068/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 13:12:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900068/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the topic of geopolitics, international flashpoints and the state of the war, a surprisingly optimistic Richard Fontaine returns to our podcast. Richard is the CEO of the Center for a New American Security (CNAS), a bi-partisan foriegn policy think tank in Washington, DC. Prior to CNAS, he was foreign policy advisor to Senator John McCain and worked at the State Department, the National Security Council, and on the staff of the Senate Foreign Relations Committee.</description></item><item><title>Niall Ferguson: How Cold War II Turns Hot | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900069/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 13:12:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Historian Niall Ferguson returns to the podcast to look at how the current Cold War could turn hot.
Niall has taught at Harvard, Cambridge, Oxford and New York University. He’s authored 17 books. He’s currently at the Hoover Institution at Stanford University where he is the MIllbank Family Senior Fellow, and Managing Director of Greenmantle, a macroeconomic and geopolitical advisory firm. Order Niall’s most recent book, “Doom: The Politics of Catastrophe” here: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode: Check-in on the Abraham Accords - with Aryeh Lightstone | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900070/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900070/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Abraham Accords were signed in September 2020. This agreement between Israel, the United Arab Emirates and Bahrain, marked the first full normalization agreement between Israel and an Arab country since the 1994 Jordan-Israel agreement. Soon after the September 2020 signing, Morocco and Sudan joined the Accords as well.
Since these historic breakthroughs, Israel has been through wild political swings, from a left-right coalition government that included Naftali Bennett from the Right, Yair Lapid from the center-Left, and Mansour Abbas from a Muslim-Arab party.</description></item><item><title>Mike Murphy on the 2024 presidential primaries | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900071/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900071/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, we go deep on 2024 presidential primaries with Mike Murphy, who has worked on 26 gubernatorial and US Senate races across the country.
Murphy was a top strategist for John McCain, Mitt Romney, Jeb Bush, and Arnold Schwarzenegger. He’s a political analyst for NBC and MSNBC. He’s co-host of the critically acclaimed &amp;ldquo;Hacks on Tap&amp;rdquo; podcast. Mike is also co-director of the University of Southern California’s Center for the Political Future.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode: Super Bowl &amp; Beyond - with Mike Tanenbaum | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900072/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 19:17:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mike Tannenbaum has more than 2 decades of experience in NFL team front offices. He was an executive vice president of football operations for the Miami Dolphins (2015-18), and executive vice president and general manager for the New York Jets (2006-12).
Under Mike’s leadership, the Jets advanced to the playoffs in three seasons, won four playoff games and made two AFC Championship game appearances. Mike’s tenure as general manager of the Jets marked the most successful seven-year period in franchise history.</description></item><item><title>Maggie Haberman on 2024 | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900073/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are we actually headed for a replay of Trump vs Biden in 2024? How strong is Trump heading into the GOP primaries? Is Biden certain to be the Democratic nominee? Do Biden and Trump need each other? And what role will Trump play in 2024 if he’s NOT the Republican nominee?
Maggie Haberman, senior political correspondent for The New York Times, returns to the podcast. For the entirety of the Trump administration, Maggie Haberman was a White House correspondent for The New York Times.</description></item><item><title>US Foreign Policy in 2023 - with Congressman Mike Gallagher | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900074/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Congressman Mike Gallagher returns to our podcast, this time to look ahead at American foreign policy in 2023. Congressman Gallagher &amp;ndash; of Wisconsin&amp;rsquo;s 8th CD &amp;ndash; has a unique perspective, since he’s just been tapped to lead the newly created House Select Committee on China.
Congressman Gallagher served for seven years on active duty in the Marine Corps, including two deployments to Iraq. He served as a top staffer on the Senate Foreign Relations Committee.</description></item><item><title>Our new media diets - with John Podhoretz | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900075/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 13:51:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900075/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, we break down changes in our media diets that have been changed as a result of the pandemic and the tech market boom, and what will revert back to VERY pre-pandemic habits. John Podhoretz returns to our conversation. He’s been a prolific TV and film critic for over four decades. John is editor in chief of Commentary Magazine and host of Commentary’s award-winning daily podcast, he’s a columnist for the New York Post, a book author, and was film critic for the Weekly Standard and television critic for the New York Post.</description></item><item><title>The Economy in 2023 -- with Mohamed El-Erian | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900076/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 13:45:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is there any precedent for combating inflation that doesn’t end in recession or depression? This is one of many questions we have for Dr. Mohamed El-Erian as we look ahead to 2023. What should we expect this year in the markets and the economy?
Mohamed El-Erian is President of Queens&amp;rsquo; College at Cambridge University. He serves as part-time Chief Economic Advisor at Allianz and Chair of Gramercy Fund Management.</description></item><item><title>Speaker McCarthy - with Matthew Continetti | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900077/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 12:39:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Transcript</description></item><item><title>Understanding Netanyahu’s new government - with Yaakov Katz | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900078/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 11:48:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900078/</guid><description>Podcast Description WIth Prime Minister Netanyahu&amp;rsquo;s new government now sworn in, and also developments for Israel at the UN, Yaakov Katz – Editor-in-Chief of The Jerusalem Post – returns to our podcast.
Earlier, Yaakov was an advisor to former Israeli Prime Minister Naftali Bennett. He served as The Jerusalem Post’s military reporter and defense analyst. He is the author of &amp;ldquo;Shadow Strike: Inside Israel&amp;rsquo;s Secret Mission to Eliminate Syrian Nuclear Power&amp;rdquo; and co-author of two books: &amp;ldquo;Weapon Wizards - How Israel Became a High-Tech Military Superpower&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Israel vs.</description></item><item><title>Special Episode: Bret Stephens on Cancel Culture | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900079/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 12:40:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900079/</guid><description>Podcast Description One of our regular guests – Bret Stephens, Pulitzer Prize winning columnist for The New York Times – returns for a conversation on cancel culture, anti-semitism and a new issue of a journal he edits, called Sapir.
Bret joined The New York Times after a long career with The Wall Street Journal, where he was most recently deputy editorial page editor and, for 11 years, a foreign affairs columnist.</description></item><item><title>Geopolitical threats as we enter ‘23 - with Senator Tom Cotton | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900080/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900080/</guid><description>Podcast Description U.S. Senator Tom Cotton recently announced that he would not run for president in 2024. And yet at the same time, he continues to be one of the most important voices in Washington on all matters involving American foreign policy and national security.
Senator Cotton also recently penned a new book, called Only The Strong. He returns to the podcast to discuss issues ranging from Iran and Russia/Ukraine to China and a proposed ban of TikTok.</description></item><item><title>2024: DeSantis vs Polis? -- with Yuval Levin | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900081/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yuval Levin returns to the podcast. He&amp;rsquo;s especially focused on whether we will have a replay of Trump vs Biden in 2024 or a new generation of leaders from both parties. Yuval discusses the promise of a number of these newer candidates and challenges they face.
Yuval is the Director of Social, Cultural, and Constitutional Studies at the American Enterprise Institute. He’s the editor-in-chief of National Affairs, a quarterly journal of essays about domestic policy, political economy, and political thought.</description></item><item><title>Sleepwalking Through a Decisive Decade - with Bret Stephens | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900082/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900082/</guid><description>Podcast Description President Biden recently warned that the U.S. faces a &amp;lsquo;decisive decade&amp;rsquo; in its rivalry with China. Are we sleepwalking through this decisive decade? That&amp;rsquo;s what Bret Stephens of The New York Times argues in the Times. (Not only with regard to China but also a range of geopolitical challenges across the globe.) In this conversation, Bret looks at China, Russia/Ukraine, and U.S. defense readiness. He also raises important questions about where the revolution in Iran is going.</description></item><item><title>Unrest in China — with Matt Pottinger | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900083/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900083/</guid><description>Podcast Description From civil disobedience we have not seen in China since Tiananmen Square, to loosening zero covid policy, and leadership tightening its political grip in unprecedented ways, this has been quite a few weeks in China. What is US policy on a range of issues – the protests, semiconductors, Taiwan and also TikTok?
Matt Pottinger returns to the podcast. Matt covered China and lived in China as a journalist for Reuters and then The Wall Street Journal.</description></item><item><title>Should the Democrats have won the House too? With Howard Wolfson | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900084/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 11:51:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Most of the post-midterm commentary has been focused on how the Democrats pulled off a surprise win in holding the majority in the U.S. Senate, and only lost the U.S. House of Representatives by a slim margin. But former Clinton and Schumer strategist &amp;ndash; and current Bloomberg senior advisor - Howard Wolfson is asking something entirely different: why DID the Democrats lose the House? Suggesting that they could have bucked history altogether and won the House too.</description></item><item><title>Prime Minister Netanyahu | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900085/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Looking back with Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu on his new book, “BiBi: My Story”. Also looking forward to his next government’s approach to Saudi Arabia (could we see an expansion of the Abraham Accords?); Israel’s position in the Russia-Ukraine war (will Israel’s posture change under his leadership?); and what he sees as the implications of events on the streets of Iran.
We spoke at an event hosted by The Streicker Cultural Center at Temple Emanu-El: https://streicker.</description></item><item><title>Mike Murphy on the Democrats' "Good Bad Night" | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900086/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900086/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, we go deep on deconstructing the mid-term results. We try to understand the implications for both parties heading into 2024. (And Murphy even tries to draw a connection between Richard Nixon and Mahatma Gandhi).
Mike Murphy has worked on 26 gubernatorial and US Senate races across the country, including 12 wins in Blue States. He was a top strategist for John McCain, Mitt Romney, Jeb Bush, and Arnold Schwarzenegger.</description></item><item><title>Israel’s Next Government - with Yaakov Katz | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900087/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 15:32:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yaakov Katz – Editor-in-Chief of The Jerusalem Post and a former advisor to Israeli Prime Minister Naftali Bennett – returns to our podcast.
Earlier, Yaakov Katz served as The Jerusalem Post’s military reporter and defense analyst. He is the author of &amp;ldquo;Shadow Strike: Inside Israel&amp;rsquo;s Secret Mission to Eliminate Syrian Nuclear Power&amp;rdquo; and co-author of two books: &amp;ldquo;Weapon Wizards - How Israel Became a High-Tech Military Superpower&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Israel vs.</description></item><item><title>Special Episode: "Taking the 5th" - Scenarios for Israel's next government | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900088/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 15:50:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900088/</guid><description>Podcast Description We join the team at Commentary Magazine for a discussion on scenarios for Israel&amp;rsquo;s next government coming out of this election (the 5th in 44 months!).
Subscribe to commentary magazine by going to: commentary.org
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Economic "Trilemma" - with Mohamed El-Erian | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900089/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Record inflation, another wake-up call out of Beijing, a new prime minister in the UK, overhang of supply chain shocks and massive fiscal and monetary stimulus from the pandemic, all against the backdrop of the Russia-Ukraine war, which shows no signs of abating.
What are the economic implications of all this? What should Central Banks be doing? Dr. Mohamed El-Erian returns to the podcast. He is President of Queens&amp;rsquo; College at Cambridge University.</description></item><item><title>Karl Rove's "Crystal Ball" | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900090/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 12:45:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900090/</guid><description>Podcast Description With less than 3 weeks to the mid-term elections, Karl Rove joins the conversation. Karl served as Senior Advisor to President George W. Bush and White House Deputy Chief of Staff. He was the architect of both of President Bush’s 2000 and 2004 presidential campaigns. He is the author &amp;ldquo;The Triumph of William McKinley&amp;rdquo; and also &amp;ldquo;Courage and Consequence&amp;rdquo;. He writes a weekly column for The Wall Street Journal.</description></item><item><title>'No off ramps for Putin' - with Fred Kagan | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900091/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 14:16:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900091/</guid><description>Podcast Description With increasing talk about nuclear threats, we have three questions in this episode:
What do we know from Putin’s past behavior that could inform how high up the ladder of escalation he is prepared to go? What are the next rungs up the ladder of escalation before the nuclear threat is real? As Putin moves up this escalatory ladder, what are the calculations of Zelensky, Europe’s leaders, and President Biden?</description></item><item><title>Cracks in Iran’s Theocracy - a view from a former CIA officer | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900092/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 12:45:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900092/</guid><description>Podcast Description We have all seen the images of women in cities across Iran burning their headscarves and cutting their hair in public to chants of &amp;ldquo;Death to the dictator.&amp;rdquo;.
The protests began after the September 13th death of 22-year-old Masha Amini. According to reports, Iranian morality police had accused Amini of violating laws mandating women cover their hair.
These events appear to have sparked a major public backlash against the Iranian regime.</description></item><item><title>BONUS EPISODE: Kol Nidrei...misunderstood - with Rabbi Meir Soloveichik | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900093/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 12:42:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yom Kippur, the Day of Atonement, begins in a few days. Kol Nidrei, is one of the most misunderstood parts of the Jewish high holidays &amp;ndash; and of the entirety of Jewish liturgy &amp;ndash; according to Rabbi Meir Soloveichik. He laid this out in a recent thought-provoking piece in The Wall Street Journal, which you can access here: https://tinyurl.com/44e4z7z8
Rabbi Soloveichik is the senior rabbi of Congregation Shearith Israel in Manhattan, the oldest Jewish congregation in the United States.</description></item><item><title>Putin's Panic Surge? With Richard Fontaine | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900094/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 13:07:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vladamir Putin has announced what he called a “partial mobilization” of up to 300,000 reservists.
According to reports, these reservists are basically former conscripts that will need training.
Meanwhile, commercial flights out of Russia are apparently selling out, fast.
The Russian Duma, on the other hand, is passing a law to clamp down on anyone evading their military service.
And then there was Putin’s seeming dangling of the nuclear threat again.</description></item><item><title>Mike Murphy on the Mid-Terms (&amp; the madness of polls) | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900095/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 12:28:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Between now and November, we will be taking a close look at the midterm election season, which &amp;ndash; for most voters &amp;ndash; is just kicking off now. If history is a guide, the first mid-term election cycle of a new president should result in the opposing party (the party not in the White House) scoring a wave of victories in Congress. How big will the wave be?
New polls suggest that there may not be much of a wave for Republicans.</description></item><item><title>Iran, Israel &amp; a Masterclass in US foreign policy - with Walter Russell Mead | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900096/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 12:10:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are we getting closer to or farther away from an Iran deal? Walter Russell Mead of The Wall Street Journal has been following developments closely. I wanted to check in with him. But I also wanted to talk to Walter about his big new and groundbreaking book, called “The Arc of a Covenant: The United States, Israel, and the Fate of the Jewish People.”
Walter has been immersed in writing this book for over a decade – it covers the history of the U.</description></item><item><title>The Hidden Jobs Crisis - with Nicholas Eberstadt | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900097/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900097/</guid><description>Podcast Description While the unemployment rate ticked up slightly to 3.7% in August from a low of 3.5% in July, job growth still remained well above the pre-covid trend. There are over 11 million job openings – that’s more than twice the number of unemployed people.
But according to a growing body of economics and social science research, the headline jobs numbers that we all track conceals a much bigger problem – the hidden crisis of able-bodied workers in their prime working age (25-54 years old), actually choosing to completely withdraw from the labor force.</description></item><item><title>Who by Fire - With Matti Friedman | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900098/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matti Friedman is one of the most thoughtful writers when it comes to all matters related to Israel, on the broader Middle East, and also on trends in the world of journalism. He is a monthly writer for Tablet Magazine and a regular contributor to The Atlantic.
His newest book is called “Who by Fire: Leonard Cohen in the Sinai.” Before that he published &amp;ldquo;Spies of No Country: Secret Lives at the Birth of Israel,&amp;rdquo; and before that &amp;ldquo;Pumpkinflowers: A Soldier’s Story of a Forgotten War,&amp;rdquo; which was chosen as a New York Times’ Notable Book and as one of Amazon’s 10 best books of the year, and was selected as one of the year’s best by Foreign Affairs Magazine.</description></item><item><title>The New Deal - Iran &amp; its nuclear program, with Mark Dubowitz | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900099/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 10:30:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900099/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is happening right now in Vienna with the negotiations over the future of Iran’s nuclear program? What was the significance of Putin’s recent trip to Iran? What is the nature of China’s relationship with Iran, and what can it tell us about Beijing’s grand strategy? And if Iran continues to build its nuclear program, what is Israel’s Plan B?
These are some of the questions we explore with Mark Dubowitz, who is the CEO of the Foundation for the Defense of Democracies, a nonpartisan think tank based in Washington, DC.</description></item><item><title>Zawahiri, Putin &amp; Pelosi - with Richard Fontaine | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900100/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 12:59:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why did Speaker Nancy Pelosi’s visit to Taipei get such outsized attention? She’s not the first US Speaker to travel to Taiwan.
Why did the killing of Ayman al-Zawahiri get so little attention? After all, he was one of the three most important figures in al-Qaeda&amp;rsquo;s leadership for decades.
And why the dwindling focus on the Russia-Ukraine war? Where does the war stand right now?
Richard Fontaine returns to the conversation.</description></item><item><title>The Summer of Shortages - with Scott Lincicome | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900101/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Air travel this summer seems broken.
On some days, major airlines have been canceling 10 percent of their flights. In normal times, it’s something like one in a hundred that are canceled.
How did this happen? Is there an explanation beyond just the obvious – which is the turbocharged rebound from the past two years of pandemic-induced turmoil in the airline industry?
Today’s guest thinks there’s something else going on that the post-covid travel summer has simply revealed.</description></item><item><title>Britain's Next Prime Minister | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900102/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 11:38:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900102/</guid><description>Podcast Description This next week will be among the most consequential in contemporary British politics. Ballots are sent out to Tory party members on August 1st, and they can begin voting right away. Whoever wins becomes Prime Minister in September, without first going through a General Election. So this next week is crucial for the two leading candidates to form final impressions before voting begins.
To help us understand the process, the candidates, and what this all means for the UK at home, the UK’s economy, and the UK in the world, we are joined by James Forsyth, the political editor of The Spectator magazine.</description></item><item><title>Nine Point One - with Mohamed El-Erian | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900103/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Inflation hit a staggering 9.1% over the last 12 months, rising 1.3% for the month of June. The increases were “broad-based,” as the Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS) put it, touching just about every aspect of our lives…especially food prices and energy prices.
In anticipation of these new numbers, we invited Dr Mohamed El-Erian back to the podcast. He is President of Queens&amp;rsquo; College at Cambridge University. Mohamed serves as part-time Chief Economic Advisor at Allianz and Chair of Gramercy Fund Management.</description></item><item><title>“The War on Fun” with Noah Rothman | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900104/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 15:43:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are there comparable periods in our history that can guide us through the current ‘“woke” debates? Is there precedent for this kind of thing burning out? Will it? How did we get to this point? And how long will it take?
That’s what we discuss today with Noah Rothman, whose new book, just released this week, is called “The Rise of the New Puritans: Fighting Back Against Progressives War on Fun.</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode: Lessons from the collapse of the Israeli Government | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900105/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 11:56:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan recently joined the Commentary Magazine podcast to share analysis on the current state of Israeli politics. We are posting that conversation here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Coming Political Crack-Up — with Mike Murphy | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900106/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 12:51:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900106/</guid><description>Podcast Description What have we learned so far about this election cycle, and what does it tell us about what’s likely to happen in the midterm elections of 2022, and the Democratic and GOP primaries for president in 2024?
Historically, California has often served as a movie trailer on our national political future &amp;ndash; &amp;lsquo;coming to a theater near you.&amp;rsquo; Richard Nixon started there, turning the Cold War threat into an election theme in his early political campaigns; Ronald Reagan transformed what we now think of as movement conservatism during his two terms as governor; and Proposition 187 was a California state ballot issue in 1994, before immigration became a national political issue (it helped get then-Governor Pete Wilson re-elected on the issue of immigration).</description></item><item><title>Saudi Arabia, Biden &amp; The Nobel Peace Prize – with Amb. Ron Dermer | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900107/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 14:27:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900107/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Biden administration has announced that the President will take his first trip to the Middle East as president. His first stop will be in Israel to meet with Israeli leaders and Palestinian President Mahmoud Abbas, before heading to Jeddah, Saudi Arabia, where he will meet with Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman.
The U.S.-Saudi relationship began nearly eight decades ago between FDR and King Ibn Saud. With varying degrees of tumult, the relationship has survived – and sometimes thrived – through 14 U.</description></item><item><title>100 Days: The Tide Turns Towards Putin | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900108/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900108/</guid><description>Podcast Description After the 100-day mark of the 2022 Russian war against Ukraine. we assess some grim facts of this war, and try to understand how they should inform what to expect in the next hundred days.
Richard Fontaine, CEO of the Centar for a New American Security (CNAS), returns to the conversation. Richard is a member of the Pentagon’s Defense Policy Board. CNAS is a bi-partisan foreign policy think tank in Washington, DC.</description></item><item><title>Revolution in Pro Sports Industry? With Jon Patricof | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900109/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 13:53:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900109/</guid><description>Podcast Description When it comes to the future of sports and entertainment, Jon Patricof is always trying to innovate and disrupt. He’s had the added challenge of launching a business from scratch on the eve of the pandemic.
Jon is the CEO and Co-Founder of Athletes Unlimited, a network of professional sports leagues. Launched in March 2020, Athletes Unlimited now operates leagues in pro women&amp;rsquo;s softball, volleyball, lacrosse, and basketball. By the end of this year, if current estimates hold, Athletes Unlimited will have conducted over 120 games that will be broadcast in over 150 countries.</description></item><item><title>What Does Putin Want Now? - with Fred Kagan | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900110/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 13:07:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900110/</guid><description>Podcast Description What are his objectives at this point in his war against Ukraine? And what are Ukraine’s objectives? What are US objectives? After all, the goals of different leaders in wartime often evolve based on battlefield developments.
Are objectives shifting right now before our eyes…for Putin, Zelensky, and the US and NATO? And has the likelihood that Putin would use a limited nuclear strike changed as his objectives have evolved?</description></item><item><title>An entrepreneur &amp; former Naval officer on Russia/Ukraine &amp; Global Supply Chains -- with Ami Daniel | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900111/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900111/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Israel we sit down with an entrepreneur and former Naval officer, who has built a company that has had to navigate the twin crises of Russia’s invasion of Ukraine and the maritime implications of cracks in global supply chains.
Ami Daniel comes to these crises as the co-founder and CEO of Windward, a maritime data, analytics and artificial intelligence company bringing transparency to what is among the largest but most opaque part of the global economy.</description></item><item><title>The Future of The Right - with Matthew Continetti | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900112/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 12:18:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Should we be surprised that there seems to be a renewed by bi-partisan consensus in response to Putin’s war? Are we back in a Cold War posture, both in policy terms and in our politics? Speaking of today’s politics, what can the past few decades of Republican politics and conservative ideas tell us about 2022 and 2024? According to Matthew Continetti, quite a lot. Matt Continentti is a senior fellow at the American Enterprise Institute, founding editor of The Washington Free Beacon, and a columnist for Commentary Magazine.</description></item><item><title>Putin’s Newly Shattered Norms - With Richard Fontaine | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900113/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is Putin crossing almost every line the West did not anticipate he would cross? What does this tell us about where he might might ultimately escalate to?
Richard Fontaine returns to the podcast to answer these questions and others. Richard is CEO of the Center for New American Security. He was recently appointed to the Defense Policy Board by the Biden Administration’s Pentagon leadership. Prior to working at CNAS, Richard was foreign policy advisor to Senator John McCain and worked on the Senate Armed Services Committee, at the State Department, at the National Security Council, and on the Senate Foreign Relations Committee.</description></item><item><title>That '70s Show - with John Podhoretz | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900114/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 12:51:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900114/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 1970s were a tragedy – inflation, rising crime and crumbling cities, American humiliation abroad from the Iranian hostage crisis and the Soviet invasion of Afghanistan, to Moscow’s geopolitical advances right in our backyard in Latin America. But here we are again, in the 2020s – with inflation surging to a four-decade high, a new crime wave and new decay in our cities, American humiliation in Afghanistan, ongoing Iran deal negotiations, and a new war launched by Russia.</description></item><item><title>A conversation with Ambassador Ron Dermer | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900115/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 13:33:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900115/</guid><description>Podcast Description The security situation continues to deteriorate in Israel &amp;ndash; tragic developments, including right in the heart of Tel Aviv. We continue to monitor developments and stay in close touch with Israeli family and friends. While Israel is a major focus of today’s conversation, the security crisis is not. We focus on the political impasse in Israel, which may be connected to the security crisis.
Today we sit down with Ambassador Ron Dermer, who served as Israel’s chief envoy to the United States from 2013 to 2021 – working closely with the Obama, Trump, and Biden administrations.</description></item><item><title>Paradox in US response to Russia? with Thomas Friedman of The New York Times | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900116/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 13:28:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Regardless of how or when the Russia-Ukraine war ends, is it possible to see the very early signs of a new geopolitical order taking shape? There are certainly some surprises, especially as it relates to Germany’s response to the crisis and – more broadly – the unity of Europe, and the overall scale of the economic response. Are there other new trends or global power centers we should be keeping an eye on?</description></item><item><title>Iran Nuclear Negotiations - The Origin Story, with Ambassador Eric Edelman | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900117/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900117/</guid><description>Podcast Description While we are all following the minute to minute developments in Russia-Ukraine, a new international deal with Iran on its nuclear program may be on the cusp of finalization. While there are still key details to be worked out, the broad contours are out there, and the implications are massive. So we wanted to have a conversation with an expert and policy practitioner that could walk us through the history of how we got here, and where it’s going.</description></item><item><title>5 Scenarios for Russia-Ukraine -- with Richard Fontaine | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900118/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900118/</guid><description>Podcast Description How could Russia-Ukraine escalate? How could it deescalate? Does Zelensky survive? Does Putin survive? Does China try to bail out Russia?
On this episode, we explore five scenarios with Richard Fontaine, who returns to the podcast. Richard Richard Fontaine is the CEO of the Center for a New American Security (CNAS), a bi-partisan foriegn policy think tank in Washington, DC. Prior to joining CNAS, Richard was foreign policy advisor to Senator John McCain and worked at the State Department, the National Security Council, and on the staff of the Senate Foreign Relations Committee.</description></item><item><title>What Xi is learning from Putin's war - with Matt Pottinger | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900119/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 13:54:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900119/</guid><description>Podcast Description As Russia has become isolated globally, a senior Russian Foreign Ministry official was asked if Moscow has anyone left in its corner, anywhere in the world. Her response: “Of course, we have them. Look at the reaction of world giants. Those who do not pretend to be giants, but are real giants. For example, it is China. You can see this reaction, can’t you?”
So what exactly is going on between Xi Xingping and Vladamir Putin as tensions escalate between Russia and the West over Russia’s invasion of Ukraine?</description></item><item><title>How Putin turns this around - with Congressman Mike Gallagher | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900120/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 13:55:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is Putin winning or losing? It looks like his war effort is not going according to plan, and that he underestimated Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky, the resistance of the Ukrainian military, and the unity of the international response. But could Putin quickly turn things around? What would that look like?
Congressman Mike Gallagher brings his perspective. Gallagher served for seven years on active duty in the United States Marine Corps, including two deployments to Iraq.</description></item><item><title>Fog of War - with Fred Kagan | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900121/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 18:09:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vladimir Putin may be unpredictable, but his direction seems to be clear. That’s the view of our guest today, Fred Kagan, who is a return guest.
As of what we know now, February 25th, there are at least 1,100 Russian casualties in Ukraine, and Russian forces are entering Kiev. President Biden has announced new sanctions, but oil and natural gas are still exempt from sanctions, and Russia is still part of the SWIFT BANKING SYSTEM.</description></item><item><title>With all eyes on Putin, enter Iran — a conversation in Jerusalem | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900122/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900122/</guid><description>Podcast Description While the world is watching every development on the Russia-Ukraine border, the United States and Iran may be close to a deal on Iran’s nuclear program. To help us understand what could happen next, Yaakov Katz – Editor-in-Chief of The Jerusalem Post and a former advisor to Israeli Prime Minister Naftali Bennett – joins the podcast.
How does the increasing likelihood of an agreement between the U.S. and Iran change Israeli calculations?</description></item><item><title>Israel's "Radical" move to the political center — and lessons for the rest of us | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900123/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 14:35:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900123/</guid><description>Podcast Description One theme of these 2020s is the polarization ripping through the US and other democracies around the world. Every day there’s a new story. Is there any way out of it?
Dr. Micah Goodman thinks so. He’s been studying the Israeli model of consensus as an antidote to polarization.
Micah is on speed-dial of several of the leaders of Israel’s new centrist coalition government. This Government is like nothing else in Israel’s history…or anywhere else for that matter.</description></item><item><title>Hollywood, China &amp; Cold War 2, with The Wall Street Journal’s Erich Scwartzel | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900124/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 15:30:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900124/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this podcast, we spend a lot of time discussing the rising threat from China and Cold War 2. We’ve hosted Matt Pottinger (episode #28), Josh Rogin (episode #17), and Admiral Stravidis (episode #44). We’ve also done an episode on the future of the movie industry, with John Podhoretz (episode #16).
But what do China – and specifically Cold War II – and Hollywood have to do with one another?</description></item><item><title>Putin-Ukraine Escalation: Lessons from an Obama Pentagon official &amp; a NY Times columnist - with Evelyn Farkas &amp; Bret Stephens | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900125/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 15:19:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is it too late to deter Russia from invading Ukraine? It certainly seems that way. And while it should be obvious that it does matter, at least as far as US interests are concerned, we are struck by how many pundits and political actors are questioning the stakes. We have received these questions in response to our recent episodes on the Russia-Ukraine crisis – the conversations with Walter Russell Mead and Richard Fontaine.</description></item><item><title>Anti-Semitism’s Enablers with Bret Stephens of The New York Times | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900126/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anti-semitism was tragically back in the news in recent days with the hostage-taking at the Beth Israel synagogue in Colleyville, Texas. But was this event covered the way it should have been? Barely.
And this tells us a lot about anti-Semitism during these times. Is this period different? Have we entered a ‘new normal’ for anti-Semitism? Is it just the extremes or are there now more enablers?
Bret Stephens, Pulitzer Prize winning columnist for The New York Times, joins us.</description></item><item><title>“Back in the USSR” with The Wall Street Journal’s Walter Russell Mead | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900127/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900127/</guid><description>Podcast Description In these conversations, we’ve talked a lot about tensions on the Russia-Ukraine border. But what we haven’t talked about is whether Putin is actually trying to re-assemble the former Soviet Union, whether the US and NATO are prepared to arrest his march, and whether Putin has successfully driven a wedge between the US and Europe.
What are the stakes for us?
Walter Russell Mead joins us. He is the Global View columnist for The Wall Street Journal.</description></item><item><title>How does a war with China start? With Admiral James Stavridis | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900128/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900128/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this podcast series, and in many other discussions and debates in think tanks and in the media, we often speculate about the likelihood of a kinetic conflict with China – is it inevitable? Or is it highly unlikely? But today we want to consider how a war would actually start, however grim this topic may be. It’s often hard to visualize what the trip wires would be. Admiral James Stavridis co-authored an entire book with Elliot Ackerman on the subject.</description></item><item><title>From Baby Boom to Baby Bust - with Nicholas Eberstadt | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900129/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900129/</guid><description>Podcast Description China is poised to pass one of the great demographic inflection points” – that’s according to the Financial Times. The inflection point the FT is referring to is that of diapers for the elderly growing into a larger market than diapers for infants. China won’t be the first. As far back as a decade ago in Japan, adult diapers started outselling infant diapers. What does that tell us about demographics, not just in China, but about the developing world as a whole?</description></item><item><title>Revisiting The New Inflation - with Mohamed El-Erian | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900130/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900130/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Covid-19 recession technically ended in April 2020. At two months, it was one of the shortest economic recessions in history. Since then, we have experienced record inflation. Last summer, we sat down with Mohamed El-Erian, who was an early voice warning about the coming inflation, how to understand it, and what its implications could be. But were the inflationary trends already in place prior to the pandemic? Did the covid response policies of governments here and abroad accelerate those trends?</description></item><item><title>Revisiting China’s Great Wall of Steel - with Matt Pottinger | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900131/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900131/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we are re-posting some of our episodes from 2021 that are most relevant right now. We’ll start with Matt Pottinger on recent developments in China. China’s borders have been sealed for almost two years. And those borders will be closed for the foreseeable future. That, obviously, is a result of the pandemic; but, is there a larger grand strategy at play? For decades now, China’s coupling with western economies has been the dominant theme of the global economic landscape - beginning with China’s 2001 accession to the World Trade Organization.</description></item><item><title>How Omicron Stunned The Scientific Community - With Scott Gottlieb | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900132/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 16:43:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900132/</guid><description>Podcast Description What about Omicron has most surprised the scientific community? What does it tell us about vaccines and where we’re heading? These are among the big questions we have for Dr. Scott Gottlieb, former Commissioner of the FDA and author of The New York Times Bestseller: “Uncontrolled Spread: Why COVID-19 Crushed Us and How We Can Defeat the Next Pandemic”. Scott currently serves on the boards of Pfizer, Illumina, Aetion, and Tempus.</description></item><item><title>Russia: In decline or on the march? with Richard Fontaine | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900133/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 16:35:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Russia poses a threat to Ukraine, again. But what about Russian President Putin’s threat to the unity of Europe, and what do recent developments tell us about global perceptions of America&amp;rsquo;s geopolitical strength? Is Russia a declining power or is Russia on the march? Could it be both?
Our guest, Richard Fontaine, is CEO of the Center for American Security. He was formerly the top foreign policy advisor to Senator John McCain, deputy staff director on the Senate Armed Services Committee, and an official of the US State Department and National Security Council.</description></item><item><title>The American College Crack-Up - with Niall Ferguson | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900134/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 13:46:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900134/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this decade we may finally experience a true crack-up in higher education. There have been comparable periods on American college campuses in the past (in the 1960s and 1980s, for example).
But our guest today, historian Niall Ferguson, believes what’s happening now is on a whole other level. Niall is doing something about it &amp;ndash; he’s starting a new university. Niall argues that parents &amp;ndash; who had enriching and intellectually diverse experiences when they went to college &amp;ndash; don’t fully appreciate that their own children will experience something completely different when they go off to university.</description></item><item><title>Lessons for the 2020s - With Historian Niall Ferguson | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900135/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900135/</guid><description>Podcast Description The first of our two-part conversation with Naill Ferguson is on applied history’s lessons of the 1920s and the 1970s&amp;hellip;for the 2020s.
Niall is a historian and senior fellow at the Hoover Institution at Stanford University, and he previously taught at Harvard, NYU and Oxford. He’s the managing director of Greenmantle, a macroeconomic and geopolitical advisory firm. Niall is also the author of 17 books including “The Square and the Tower: Networks and Power, from the Freemasons to Facebook” and “Doom: The Politics of Catastrophe”.</description></item><item><title>Dan Senor’s New Podcast - Call Me Back | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900136/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 19:18:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to our new podcast, “Call Me Back”, where we try to zoom out from minute-to-minute news and look back to how we got here, what we can learn from earlier decades and where we might be going in these roaring and raging 2020s.
In each episode, I’ll call a friend who is deeply immersed in some of the most transformative issues of our time.
Broadly speaking, I want to focus this podcast on this decade we&amp;rsquo;re in, the 2020s, because it strikes me that we’ll look back at the 2020s as one of the most consequential decades in modern history - from inflation and unprecedented fiscal and monetary policies, the technological transformation driven by AI, blockchain, and life sciences, to the rise of China and Cold War II, to declining American engagement in the Middle East and parts of Central Asia - all against the backdrop of culture wars, public safety breakdowns, and, of course, a public health crack-up as we come out of the pandemic.</description></item><item><title>The Political Fallout from Covid19 - with Matthew Continetti | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900137/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900137/</guid><description>Podcast Description The recent electoral outcomes in Virginia, New Jersey, New York City, Buffalo, Minneapolis and other areas across the country were as much to do with the pandemic &amp;ndash; and the economic and cultural shocks from the pandemic &amp;ndash; as anything. Was it a political blip or some kind of realignment? Where does the Democratic Party go from here? And what about the Republican Party? What does it mean for Joe Biden and Donald Trump?</description></item><item><title>Vaccines: A New American Success Story? — with The Wall Street Journal’s Gregory Zuckerman | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900138/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 13:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900138/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have we revolutionized vaccine development? What does this mean for our lives and our health well beyond the vaccine for Covid-19? Could this kind of life sciences revolution only happen in America? And what about Operation Warp Speed? Is it a model for future public-private partnerships to solve big problems?
Greg Zuckerman of The Wall Street Journal joins the podcast to discuss his new and fascinating book, “A Shot to Save the World: The Inside Story of the Life-or-Death Race for a COVID-19 Vaccine.</description></item><item><title>IS THIS THE END OF C-19’s BEGINNING? - with Yale University’s Nicholas Christakis | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900139/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900139/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the middle of the pandemic, Dr. Nicholas Christakis released a sweeping book, called “Apollo’s Arrow: The Profound and Enduring Impact of Coronavirus on the Way We Live”. In it, he drew on scientific, medical, and sociological research, and assessed the transmission of the virus, responses worldwide, and prognosis for the pandemic’s end, including some bold predictions. The paperback edition is just out with some new material.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Merits of Merit - with Adrian Wooldridge of The Economist | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900140/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900140/</guid><description>Podcast Description During the pandemic, standardized tests were suspended in an entire range of educational institutions. Will these changes be temporary or permanent? More than 600 of these institutions switched from a mandatory to optional test for the 2020-21 application season, and many just flat out refused to accept a test at all in their application process. According to the editor in chief of the Princeton Review, “That is a tectonic change for many schools.</description></item><item><title>A New Crime Wave? - With Jason Riley | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900141/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 13:54:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900141/</guid><description>Podcast Description According to The New York Times: “The United States experienced its biggest one-year increase on record in homicides in 2020, according to new figures released by the FBI, with some cities hitting record highs.” And as for 2021, while we don’t yet have complete data, it so far appears that this homicide surge has continued well into this year as well. So, tragically, this isn’t going away soon.</description></item><item><title>Presidents and Pandemics - with Tevi Troy | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900142/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 15:06:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are we living in peak politicized times? One test that pundits and the media frequently point to as Exhibit A is how our elected leaders have responded to the current pandemic. Just about every move by our current president, his predecessor, or governors in different states, and mayors and even county health commissioners &amp;ndash; they all get instantly analyzed in a political frame.
Is this new? Are there nakedly political motives in various actions on public health?</description></item><item><title>A Rosh Hashanah Special: Business Principles from the Book of Genesis | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900143/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900143/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this podcast, we’ve talked to a lot of policy-makers, pundits, professionals and practitioners about big picture trends they are observing and experiencing as a result of the pandemic.
Today, however, we are going more micro. We&amp;rsquo;ll talk to a venture capitalist about his portfolio of start-ups, and how those companies have been impacted by changes in the way we work and live, and what they tell us.</description></item><item><title>A Post-Delta World — with Dr. Sid Mukherjee | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900144/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 18:43:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900144/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is the pandemic fight winnable or are we going to keep chasing these variants forever? And What does this mean for our lives and our economy?
As we were all gearing up for a roaring return to normalcy, the Delta variant has tempered enthusiasm. Before Delta, we fought a virus and thought we may have won by developing a vaccine&amp;hellip;quickly (THANK YOU Operation Warp Speed, and thank you to the ecosystem of life science start-ups and large pharma companies, and to the years and years of massive investment in the sciences that made all of this possible).</description></item><item><title>Delta Politics - with Mike Murphy | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900145/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900145/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Pandemic has either caused a crack-up in our politics or accelerated the crack-up that was well under way. And just when it looked like things were stabilizing, the politics of Covid have evolved along with the Delta variant. Ground zero for how this is playing out right now is California.
California is home to approximately 40 million people and the 5th largest economy in the world. It’s about to have an election on whether to re-call its incumbent governor, Gavin Newsom.</description></item><item><title>Afghanistan &amp; The New Geopolitics - With Fred Kagan | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900146/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 18:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900146/</guid><description>Podcast Description While the world watches America’s chaotic withdrawal from Afghanistan, there’s enormous potential for human catastrophe — in the weeks, months and years ahead. At best, the future of Afghanistan is uncertain.
But what about the future of America’s role in the world? How does it impact the geopolitical landscape? What are the strategic implications for the West? What does it mean for China, Taiwan and Japan? For Russia? For Turkey?</description></item><item><title>China’s Great Wall of Steel? - with Matt Pottinger | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900147/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900147/</guid><description>Podcast Description China’s borders have been sealed for well over a year now. And those borders will be closed for the foreseeable future. That, obviously, is a result of the pandemic; but, is there a larger grand strategy at play?
For decades now, China’s coupling with western economies has been the dominant theme of the global economic landscape - beginning with China’s 2001 accession to the World Trade Organization.
But that’s been changing.</description></item><item><title>The New Inflation - with Mohamed El-Erian | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900148/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 14:39:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900148/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Covid-19 recession technically ended in April 2020. At two months, it was one of the shortest economic recessions in history. Since then, however, some economists and market practitioners have been screaming from the hilltops about the risk of inflation. That’s because the US Government injected trillions of fiscal and monetary stimulus into the economy - the highest levels in history - and the US Government and governments around the world are still at it.</description></item><item><title>Delta... This is New York! | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900149/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 15:34:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900149/</guid><description>Podcast Description This was supposed to be the summer that we returned to normal, here in New York City and in every major city around the world. Right?
But now there’s increasing speculation that it might not happen, because of the Delta variant, and other variants that may hit us from the mutating virus.
How should our government and public health leaders respond? How should we respond?
We wanted to sit down with frequent Post-Corona guest John Podhoretz for a midsummer check-in on where we are with the City’s return.</description></item><item><title>Unexpected Presidential Advisors - with Gary Ginsberg | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900150/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 16:19:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who do presidents, prime ministers and business leaders listen to in the midst of managing a crisis? It’s a question that’s always interested me, from my time in government and business and also as a moon-lighting student of history.
I thought about that a lot during the covid pandemic. On this podcast series, we’ve talked about how the formal channels in our governments performed these past 18 months. But how about those unofficial channels from outside the government that wind up shaping our leaders&amp;rsquo; thinking and approach to world-changing events.</description></item><item><title>Social Decay and The Pandemic - with Yuval Levin | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900151/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900151/</guid><description>Podcast Description The coronavirus pandemic was a public health crisis and an economic crisis, but was it also a social crisis? Will we look back at Covid19 as being a catalyst for unifying our society, tearing it apart, or simply accelerating trends that were already in the works long before March of 2020?
Yuval Levin is one of the most prolific and influential thinkers on the subject of the health of our society - pre… and post corona.</description></item><item><title>Blackstone’s Jonathan Pollack on Real-Estate Post Corona | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900152/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 17:42:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Many have been surprised that areas of the real estate market are booming, Post Corona. So what do we know about the pandemic’s impact on an exodus from some cities, and the growth of other cities?
One of the ways that I have learned on this limited series podcast is from our top flight guests, but also from our listeners. A business practitioner - an operator or investor - will hear one of our experts on the pod and get a hold of me with an alternative analysis; it’s like I get to crowdsource ideas from our listeners.</description></item><item><title>Naftali Bennett - Who Are You? | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900153/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 14:35:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900153/</guid><description>Podcast Description Naftali Bennett - Who Are You? Today we’re doing a special convention tied to the news. Politics in Israel is moving fast. It’s not necessarily about the Coronavirus, but it’s important in our geopolitics.
As of today, Israel may be on the cusp of forming a new coalition government, composed of 7 parties from across the ideological spectrum - from Naftali Bennett’s Yamina Party and the New Hope party on the Right, through Yair Lapid’s party in the center, to the Labor and Meretz parties on the Left.</description></item><item><title>Tom Cotton on the Lab Leak Hypothesis of Covid19 | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900154/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 16:51:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900154/</guid><description>Podcast Description The source of SARS-CoV-2 has been a mystery. One theory that was initially met with a scathing response from many in the media and some in the scientific community was that SARS-CoV-2 might have leaked from a research lab in Wuhan, Hubei in China - the Wuhan Institute of Virology.
The leading voice elevating the need to investigate this possible scenario back in February of 2019 was U.S. Senator Tom Cotton (R-AR).</description></item><item><title>Is The Problem In Israel Rooted in 1967 or 1948? | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900155/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 12:56:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900155/</guid><description>Podcast Description When I was in Israel a few weeks ago, a number of the Israelis I interviewed marveled at how quickly things had gone back to normal in Israel, Post-Corona. One of those guests, Yonatan Sagiv - the novelist - told me that we’ll know we’re back to normal when Israelis have to resume dealing with their pre-pandemic problems. Well, over these past 10 days, one conflict lit right back up in a tragic way - Israel’s off-again, on-again war with Hamas.</description></item><item><title>"God and the Pandemic" | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900156/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 12:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900156/</guid><description>Podcast Description News just out of the CDC has created fresh opportunities for normal, communal time together, indoors — just like we did pre-Corona. One of the rituals I have missed over the past year has been attending synagogue. But long before the Covid-19 pandemic, participation in organized religion - across all walks of religious life - was on the decline. Americans had become less engaged in religious institutions, whether it was regular attendance or membership and donations to their local congregation.</description></item><item><title>Post Corona Has Arrived - And This Is What It Sounds Like | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900157/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 16:04:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900157/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we’re doing something… different.
After 15 months of avoiding business travel, I boarded a plane to attend meetings in Israel. When I landed, it felt more like I boarded a DeLorean and time-traveled ahead to the era of Post Corona - a land far, far away.
WIth 85% of Israelis, 16 and older, inoculated, and with hospitals emptying out, it was clear that as far as Israelis are concerned - the pandemic is now just another chapter in history.</description></item><item><title>Is China Turning Crisis Into Opportunity? With Josh Rogin | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900158/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 18:49:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900158/</guid><description>Podcast Description China is in the midst of a global vaccination campaign. According to published reports, China’s Government is supplying 10 times as many doses to other countries as it is to citizens in its own country. China’s vaccination campaign is currently engaging 45 countries spread across multiple continents around the world. Why? What is China getting in return? And should the US also be engaged in vaccine diplomacy?
This is just one of many ways in which the Pandemic has upended geopolitics as we know it.</description></item><item><title>Will We Ever Go To The Movies Again… And Does That Matter? | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900159/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 18:51:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900159/</guid><description>Podcast Description That phrase - going to the movies - that shared experience in a movie theater full of strangers already makes me nostalgic, like listening to vinyl records.
Before the pandemic, the movie theater business was an 11-billion dollar industry in the US alone. In 2020, there were approximately 40,000 screens in 5,798 theaters that employed over 115,000 people.
Then, of course, in March of 2020, like all communal entertainment experiences, they were all shut down.</description></item><item><title>Zoom University: Is Covid The Ultimate Higher Education Disruptor? | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900160/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 16:53:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900160/</guid><description>Podcast Description When we think about industries that immediately got hardest hit during the pandemic, the images that come to mind include restaurants, travel, theater, sports and - higher education. In the US alone, higher education is almost a three-quarter-of-a-trillion dollar sector.
To help us understand what the disruption and the coming transformation might look like, we sit down with my friend Daniel Pianko. Dan has a long venture investing career in the higher education and training sectors.</description></item><item><title>The Covid Presidency with Maggie Haberman | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900161/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 18:57:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900161/</guid><description>Podcast Description What was the impact of Covid19 on the political landscape? What will it mean for elected leaders who governed during this past year?
Today we sit down with someone who knows something about covering a president during a pandemic that consumed his presidency.
For the entirety of the Trump administration, Maggie Haberman was a White House correspondent for The New York Times. She joined The Times in 2015, and soon found herself covering Donald Trump’s unlikely campaign.</description></item><item><title>Vaccination Nation: Is our Post Corona future unfolding now in Israel? | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900162/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900162/</guid><description>Podcast Description So far more than 70 percent of Israelis, ages 16 and older, have received at least one dose of the vaccine, and many of them two jabs.
How has Israel done this? Well, Israel’s prime minister negotiated with Pfizer to obtain millions of vaccine doses early. Israel paid a premium for this upfront supply, but also agreed to provide the company with indispensable clinical data, made possible by Israel’s digital health infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Will We Do Better Next Time? | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900163/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 20:23:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is there any good news? Are there any lessons from the crisis that should give us some optimism about how we contend with future pandemics? That’s what we try to untangle today with science journalist Jim Meigs. Jim helps us think about the promise of public-private partnerships that gave birth to Operation Warp Speed, as well as the new critical infrastructure we are building for vaccine manufacturing and hopefully distribution, and how we discern the public health news we get from political leaders, public health authorities and the media to inform our decisions during a crisis.</description></item><item><title>John Dickerson on The Presidency Post Corona | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900164/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900164/</guid><description>Podcast Description Will a new American president lead us to a post-Corona return to normal? Or has the American presidency become an impossible job? It is, according to 60 Minutes correspondent John Dickerson, “The Hardest Job In The World”.
Has the American presidency finally met its match in a global pandemic?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bret Stephens on Geopolitics Post Corona | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900165/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 18:08:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900165/</guid><description>Podcast Description It seems like analysts of foreign affairs and super power politics are always worrying that “the world is a mess”. But has the international order - to the extent it existed in recent years - become even more disorderly due to the pandemic? What effect has covid had on Great Power politics?
As a new president assembles his national security team and develops a grand strategy, I thought it would be good to sit down with Bret Stephens of the New York Times to take a quick tour around the world and talk about China, Russia, Europe and the Middle East.</description></item><item><title>When IS Post Corona, anyway? Part 2 - Turning the Corner | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900166/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900166/</guid><description>Podcast Description How will we know when we actually arrive at the Post-Corona phase? This is the second part of a two part conversation on this question, the first of which was when we looked at Israel (Vaccination Nation). Today, we’ll talk about the US &amp;ndash; when we will arrive at post-corona and what is standing in our way?
To help us understand what is happening in the US, we welcome Scott Gottlieb, who served as the 23rd commissioner of the Food and Drug Administration.</description></item><item><title>Is New York Over? Part 3 - Crime and the City | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900167/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 19:10:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan speaks with president of the Manhattan Institute, Reihan Salam, and deputy director of legal policy at the Manhattan Institute, Rafael Manguel, about the role crime will play in slowing, or even halting, the City’s Post-Corona recovery.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>When IS Post Corona, anyway? Part 1 - Vaccination Nation | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900168/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 18:58:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900168/</guid><description>Podcast Description How will we know when we actually arrive at the Post-Corona phase? Well, THE milestone along the way will be getting entire populations vaccinated. One country may show us the way - Israel, which is on track to vaccinate its entire population by the end of March.
To understand how did Israel become&amp;hellip; Vaccination Nation, we welcome Yonatan Adiri, who is the Founder and CEO of Healthy.IO, a fast-growing digital health start-up, headquartered in Tel Aviv.</description></item><item><title>How Will History Judge 2020? | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900169/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 22:04:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan sits down with Niall Ferguson, a historian and senior fellow at the Hoover Institution, to discuss how history will remember 2020.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is New York Over? Part 2 - Broadway | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900170/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 15:26:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan speaks with John Podhoretz, Editor-in-Chief of Commentary Magazine, to discuss the hotly debated question: &amp;ldquo;Is New York over?&amp;rdquo; On this episode of Post Corona, Dan asks John to help us understand the short history of Broadway’s economic boom and where it goes from here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is New York Over? Part 1 - The Subway | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900171/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900171/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan invites Reihan Salam and Nicole Gelinas of the Manhattan Institute to discuss the hotly debated question: &amp;ldquo;Is New York over?&amp;rdquo; On this episode of Post Corona, Dan and his guests explore how subways play a role in the city&amp;rsquo;s future.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Billy Beane on the future of sports | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900172/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 22:22:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Billy Beane, Executive Vice President of the Oakland Athletics, joins Dan to discuss the future of sports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Adam Grant on the future of work | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900173/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900173/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam Grant, a professor of organizational psychology at Wharton, joins Dan to discuss the future of work.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Derek Thompson of The Atlantic on the Post-Corona workforce | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900174/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 13:38:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900174/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the first episode of Post Corona, Dan Senor invites The Atlantic&amp;rsquo;s Derek Thompson to discuss the future of the American labor market.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Post Corona Trailer | Call Me Back - with Dan Senor</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4441900175/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2020 18:30:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4441900175/</guid><description>Podcast Description How Covid 19 will transform our world - indefinitely.
Hosted by Dan Senor.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>