<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hot Mess with Alix Earle on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/hot-mess-with-alix-earle/</link><description>Recent content in Hot Mess with Alix Earle on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/hot-mess-with-alix-earle/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Keeping Up With Kristin | Hot Mess with Alix Earle</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7653060001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7653060001/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST AVAILABLE ON SPOTIFY AND YOUTUBE) This week Alix sits down with her best friend and roommate, Kristin. The two discuss their differences, living together, drama, mean girls, and other details about their friendship. They even reveal some things they’ve never told each other before.
It’s also Art Basel week in Miami and Kristin has a collaboration with Fontainebleau. Alix, Kristin, Braxton, and the rest of their friends bring the cameras to the event and show what really happens at Art Basel.</description></item><item><title>Alix vs. Acne | Hot Mess with Alix Earle</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7653060002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7653060002/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST AVAILABLE ON SPOTIFY AND YOUTUBE) Today Alix addresses one of her most highly-requested topics…acne and skincare. She admits to having struggled with acne since middle school and her skin taking a toll on her mental health. Alix’s first experience with acne started in 5th - 6th grade. She went to a Catholic school where you were not allowed to wear makeup. She tells a story of secretly wearing concealer to cover up her pimples and then being forced to wash her face by a rude teacher.</description></item><item><title>Meet The Earles | Hot Mess with Alix Earle</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7653060003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7653060003/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST AVAILABLE ON SPOTIFY AND YOUTUBE) On this episode of Hot Mess, Alix heads home to New Jersey for Thanksgiving. She takes us down memory lane telling stories about her old high school, having to go back and forth between the houses of her divorced parents growing up, and working at Hazel Boutique as a sophomore. Alix even alludes to having a crisis about not knowing if she still wants to live in Miami.</description></item><item><title>Social Media, Secrets, and a Scholarship | Hot Mess with Alix Earle</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7653060004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 05:13:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7653060004/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST AVAILABLE ON SPOTIFY AND YOUTUBE) This week, Alix heads back to the University of Miami (for the last time). This time, she’s teaching a college class. Alix’s favorite class during her time at school was Social Media Marketing, taught by professor Bolton. Following her online success, he asked her to come back and guest lecture to share her knowledge with the new students. The cameras come with her and we get a chance to learn some of Alix’s tips and tricks for breaking the internet.</description></item><item><title>The End of NFL Man | Hot Mess with Alix Earle</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7653060005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7653060005/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST AVAILABLE ON SPOTIFY AND YOUTUBE) This week, Alix surprises NFL Man with a trip for his birthday. She reveals what has been going on the past three months since she first updated us on her situationship.
The two of them jet off to a tiny island in the Bahamas where they reveal how their vacation has unfolded. Big Al &amp;amp; NFL Man debrief their getaway, take a trip to a private island, and show the behind the scenes of the romantic surprises that were planned.</description></item><item><title>Anxiety: From Hospitals to Healing | Hot Mess with Alix Earle</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7653060006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7653060006/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST AVAILABLE ON SPOTIFY AND YOUTUBE) This week Alix opens up about her struggles with anxiety. She speaks in detail about the first time she fainted, her first panic attack, and even going to the emergency room. Alix shares the tips she’s learned to take her out of that place and live a happy and adventurous life. Alix also answers your questions in another What Would Alix Do segment.</description></item><item><title>Halloween Hangxiety | Hot Mess with Alix Earle</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7653060007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7653060007/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST AVAILABLE ON SPOTIFY AND YOUTUBE) This week it’s Halloween and Alix is bringing you with her. She sits down with one of your most requested guests, Hannah Knight, to discuss the wild times they had on Halloween during college. They recount their trips down to a swingers festival, hijacking a pirate ship, and getting messed up tattoos.
After venturing down memory lane, Alix takes you to two wild Halloween parties this year.</description></item><item><title>He Cheated But I Love Him | Hot Mess with Alix Earle</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7653060008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7653060008/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST AVAILABLE ON SPOTIFY AND YOUTUBE) For the first time online, Alix shares the sad intricacies of her first heartbreak. She details the on and off relationship she shared with an older guy, referred to as “Chad”, and the mistakes they made along the way. She remembers a time she caught him cheating…or the many times&amp;hellip; and the shocking events that transpired after. She reflects on how her past insecurities lead her to accept Chad’s destructive behavior and offers the wisdom she’s gained in hindsight.</description></item><item><title>Cockroaches and Tailgates | Hot Mess with Alix Earle</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7653060009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7653060009/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST AVAILABLE ON SPOTIFY AND YOUTUBE) This week it’s Alumni Weekend at the University of Miami and Alix is taking you with her. The Casa Amor girlies are back together to discuss the secrets of their time living in their viral cockroach-infested home. They spill stories of STDs, babies, and even paranormal activity caught on their security camera.
Alix brings the camera to the tailgate, unveiling the dirty truths of frat parties and college life.</description></item><item><title>Earle Girls vs Paris | Hot Mess with Alix Earle</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7653060010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7653060010/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST AVAILABLE ON SPOTIFY &amp;amp; YOUTUBE) In this week’s episode of Hot Mess, Alix jets off to Paris and reunites with her sister, Ashtin, who&amp;rsquo;s studying abroad. They reveal the behind the scenes of fashion week, boys, and their sisterly differences - Alix is the anxious, high-strung, quick-thinking sister while Ashtin is the slow-walker that always takes her time. They even recount physical altercations from their youth, including Alix throwing a straightener at Ashtin and giving her a bloody nose.</description></item><item><title>Overcoming My Eating Disorder | Hot Mess with Alix Earle</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7653060011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7653060011/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST AVAILABLE ON SPOTIFY &amp;amp; YOUTUBE) Join Alix and her high school bestie Isabella as they reminisce on the evolution of their friendship, and the chaotic memories they’ve created together over the years. They recall all of the “firsts” they shared including stealing from their parent’s liquor cabinets and experiencing their first hangover. Being long distance friends, they share the hardwork and commitment it takes to maintain their relationship from two different states.</description></item><item><title>My Sorority Nightmare | Hot Mess with Alix Earle</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7653060012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7653060012/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST AVAILABLE ON SPOTIFY &amp;amp; YOUTUBE) Welcome to Hot Mess with Alix Earle! In the spirit of sorority recruitment season, Alix is taking you back to her freshman year at the University of Miami. For the first time, Alix shares the details of her traumatic rush experience that almost resulted in her transferring to another school. Watch as Alix takes you through the recruitment process and shares the hard lessons she’s learned along the way - the most important being that you don’t need Greek life to find your people.</description></item><item><title>Just Friends? | Hot Mess with Alix Earle</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7653060013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7653060013/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST AVAILABLE ON SPOTIFY &amp;amp; YOUTUBE) Welcome to Hot Mess with Alix Earle! We are starting things off by addressing the question everyone has been asking, “does Alix have a boyfriend?” She opens up about how she met NFL man, their first date, navigating public controversy and their current relationship status. Hot Mess is all about providing an authentic glimpse into Alix&amp;rsquo;s life, and that includes introducing you to her friends and family.</description></item><item><title>Podcast Trailer | Hot Mess with Alix Earle</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7653060014/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 16:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7653060014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Premieres Sept 21st 2023. Join your favorite hot mess, Alix Earle, as she invites you to listen in on a weekly recap of her life revealing all the in-depth, exclusive details that has everyone watching, talking, and wanting more. For the first time ever, Alix will be letting you in on what is actually happening, beyond her trending TikToks. From friendships to family, relationship updates to rumors, traveling and navigating life after college, get ready for all the behind-the-scenes details that you’ve been waiting for.</description></item></channel></rss>