<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>NVIDIA on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/categories/nvidia/</link>
        <description>Recent content in NVIDIA on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 09:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/categories/nvidia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>NVIDIA - NVIDIA Keynote at COMPUTEX 2023</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3001600002/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001600002/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript (calm music plays)
[Voice Off-Screen] I am a translator, transforming text into creative discovery,
turning movement into animation
and infusing words with emotion.
(speaks foreign language)
[Voice Off-Screen] I am a healer,
exploring the building blocks that make us unique,
discovering new threats before they happen.
And searching for the cures to keep them at bay.
I am a visionary
creating new medical miracles
and unlocking the secrets of our sun</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>NVIDIA - GTC 2023 Keynote with NVIDIA CEO Jensen Huang</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3001600001/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001600001/</guid>
        <description>For nearly four decades
Moore’s Law has been the governing dynamics of the computer industry
which in turn has impacted every industry.
The exponential performance increase at constant cost and power has slowed.
Yet, computing advance has gone to lightspeed.
The warp drive engine is accelerated computing and the energy source is AI.
The arrival of accelerated computing and AI is timely
as industries tackle powerful dynamics
sustainability
generative AI</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>NVIDIA - GTC 2023 Keynote with NVIDIA CEO Jensen Huang - Español</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/es/post/3001600001/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/es/post/3001600001/</guid>
        <description>Durante casi cuatro décadas,
la Ley de Moore ha sido la dinámica rectora de la industria informática,
que a su vez ha impactado a todas las industrias.
El aumento exponencial del rendimiento a costo y potencia constantes se ha desacelerado.
Sin embargo, el avance informático ha ido a la velocidad de la luz.
El motor warp drive es computación acelerada y la fuente de energía es IA.
La llegada de la computación acelerada y la IA</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>NVIDIA - GTC 2023 Keynote with NVIDIA CEO Jensen Huang - Português</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/pt-br/post/3001600001/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/pt-br/post/3001600001/</guid>
        <description>Por quase quatro décadas,
a Lei de Moore tem sido a dinâmica governante da indústria de computadores,
que por sua vez impactou todos os setores.
O aumento exponencial do desempenho a um custo e potência constantes diminuiu.
No entanto, o avanço da computação foi para a velocidade da luz.
O motor dessa transformação é a computação acelerada, e a fonte de energia é a AI.
A chegada da computação acelerada e da AI é oportuna à medida</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>NVIDIA - GTC 2023 Keynote with NVIDIA CEO Jensen Huang - 한국어</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ko/post/3001600001/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ko/post/3001600001/</guid>
        <description>거의 40년 동안 무어의 법칙이 컴퓨터 산업의 지배 역학이 됐으며, 그로 인해 모든 산업에 영향을 미쳤습니다. 일정한 비용과 전력에서 기하급수적으로증가하던 성능은</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>NVIDIA - GTC 2023 Keynote with NVIDIA CEO Jensen Huang - 日本語</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ja/post/3001600001/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ja/post/3001600001/</guid>
        <description>約 40 年間 ムーアの法則はコンピューター産業を動かし あらゆる産業に影響を与えてきました 一定のコストと電力での性能向上はスローダウンしていますが コ</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>NVIDIA - GTC 2023 Keynote with NVIDIA CEO Jensen Huang - 简体中文</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/zh-hans/post/3001600001/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/zh-hans/post/3001600001/</guid>
        <description>近四十年来 摩尔定律一直是引领计算机行业动态发展的重要规律 而计算机行业又影响着各行各业的发展 在成本和功耗不变的情况下性能的指数级增长已经放缓 然</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>NVIDIA - GTC 2023 Keynote with NVIDIA CEO Jensen Huang - 繁體中文</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/zh-hant/post/3001600001/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/zh-hant/post/3001600001/</guid>
        <description>近四十年來 摩爾定律主導了電腦產業發展 而電腦產業也影響了各個產業 在成本和動力不變的情況下原先呈指數級增長的表現，也逐漸放緩 然而，運算技術則是以</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
