<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Short History Of on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/short-history-of/</link><description>Recent content in Short History Of on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/short-history-of/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Agatha Christie (Repeat) | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820126/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Retaining the title of the “Queen of Crime” to this day, Agatha Christie is the best-selling novelist of all time. Across 66 novels, 14 short-story collections, and 20 stage plays, she depicted the evil lurking in the hearts of ordinary people. But how did this homeschooled daughter of a privileged English family learn so much about poisons, psychopaths and murder? What in her personal life informed such a suspicious view of ordinary people?</description></item><item><title>J.R.R Tolkien | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820001/</guid><description>Podcast Description J.R.R Tolkien is one of Britain’s most beloved authors, famous for creating the fantasy world ‘Middle Earth’ through his novels ‘The Hobbit’ and the ‘Lord of the Rings’ trilogy. What started out as a bedtime story for his young children, now captivates millions of fans across the world, who long to join his memorable characters on their epic adventures. But how did Tolkien rise from a humble Birmingham childhood to become one of the most respected literary figures of all time?</description></item><item><title>The Colosseum | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Voted one of the seven modern wonders of the world, Rome’s Colosseum is an instantly recognizable building. Constructed by Emperor Flavian in the first century AD as a gift to his people, and still standing almost two millennia later, it has a rich and fascinating history. Films such as Gladiator and Spartacus popularize its reputation as home to brutal gladiator battles, but what is the real story behind the Colosseum?</description></item><item><title>Winston Churchill | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Winston Churchill is one of the most recognizable figures of the 20th Century. Voted in 2002 as ‘the greatest Briton’, he’s remembered for his unfailing leadership throughout the Second World War, as he steered Britain through its darkest hour to eventual victory. But what is the real story behind Churchill? How did the rise of Hitler thrust him into the spotlight? What sort of controversy surrounded the famed politician?</description></item><item><title>Highwaymen | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820004/</guid><description>Podcast Description For centuries, stories have been told about highwaymen - dangerous rogues who attacked unsuspecting travellers in the dead of night, demanding their money or their life. These robbers have been romanticised into myths, plays, films, and songs. But what’s the truth behind the legends? Who were the real men - and sometimes women - who risked death sentences for the contents of a purse? How did authorities respond to highway robbery?</description></item><item><title>Abolition of The British Slave Trade | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820005/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the mid-17th Century, Britain dominated the Slave Trade, shipping over 3 million enslaved Africans across the Atlantic. Conditions on board slave ships were inhumane, and large numbers of enslaved men, women, and children died en-route. However, during the 18th and early 19th centuries, certain individuals started to speak up and demand an end to slavery. So who were these courageous pioneers, brave enough to challenge the status-quo? How did they fight the establishments?</description></item><item><title>Charles Dickens | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Charles Dickens is considered one of the greatest novelists of the Victorian Age. His works shone a light on prevalent issues of his era, such as poverty, disease, and inequality, and called for widespread social change. Since Dickens’ time, his books have been translated into 150 languages, and have never been out of print. But how did a boy from Portsmouth turn into one of the world’s most celebrated literary figures?</description></item><item><title>The Gunpowder Plot (Repeat) | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820007/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820007/</guid><description>Podcast Description To mark Guy Fawkes night in England, Noiser brings you this episode from the archive of Short History Of… The Gunpowder plot is an epic tale of adventure and murderous revenge, a detective story complete with secrets, aliases, even an anonymous letter of betrayal. But who was really behind it? What drove the conspirators to attempt such an audacious act of terrorism? This is a Short History of the Gunpowder Plot.</description></item><item><title>Magna Carta | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Magna Carta is one of the most enduring documents from the Middle Ages. Reluctantly signed by King John at Runnymede in 1215, it forever changed society and politics in Britain, and the rest of the world. Magna Carta has been credited with inspiring the US Constitution and Bill of Rights, and providing the basis for democracy across the globe. But what does Magna Carta actually say? What events led to its creation?</description></item><item><title>Jane Austen | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820009/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane Austen is arguably the most famous female writer in history. Her novels have gone on to inspire countless films, plays, and dramas all over the world, and have been translated into almost 50 different languages. But how did an 18th Century woman create stories that are still loved today? What makes her characters so timeless? And, while we know all about her heroes and heroines, what do we know about the author herself?</description></item><item><title>Congo River | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820010/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820010/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Congo River is the world’s deepest and most powerful waterway. In its basin, a wilderness bigger than Alaska, natural resources abound - oil, gold, diamonds, rubber. But this river, more than any other, is also linked with some of the darkest times in human history – with slavery, war and corruption. So what do we know of the early communities who lived on its shores? Why did it take Europeans so long to explore the river?</description></item><item><title>Margaret Thatcher | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820011/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Margaret Thatcher was one of the most controversial figures of the 20th Century. Praised by some as a fearless leader and feminist icon, and despised by others as a heartless politician, the Iron Lady caused divisions wherever she went. But why did Britain’s first female Prime Minister inspire such extreme hatred? What policies did she implement, how did they affect the communities of Britain? And what, if anything, is her legacy today?</description></item><item><title>Boston Tea Party | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820012/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820012/</guid><description>Podcast Description In December, 1773, hundreds of angry Bostonians charged into the harbor at Griffin’s Wharf, and tossed over 300 chests of tea into the icy waters below. This lawlessness marked the culmination of what many Americans viewed as decades worth of oppression and exploitation by the British. Ultimately leading to the American War of Independence, this nonviolent protest has become one of the most pivotal moments in American history. But what circumstances led to the Boston Tea Party?</description></item><item><title>Fukushima Nuclear Disaster | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820013/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820013/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2011, Japan was hit by the worst earthquake in the country’s history. Enormous tremors caused devastation all throughout Japan, and the tsunami that followed wreaked further havoc. But the damage didn’t end there. 200 km north of Tokyo, the Fukushima Daiichi Nuclear Power Plant was in danger. It had been so severely damaged that there were fears of a full-scale, global, nuclear melt-down….
But how close did the world really come to nuclear disaster?</description></item><item><title>Joan of Arc | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820014/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joan of Arc is a historical superstar, a peasant who rose above her rank and gender to help free France from foreign occupation. Claiming to be acting under the orders of saints and angels, she became a symbol of national freedom. But how did a near-illiterate teenage girl win the hearts and minds of soldiers and citizens alike? What was behind her angelic visions? And why was she abandoned to a brutal fate at the age of just nineteen?</description></item><item><title>Suez Canal | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820015/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820015/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Suez Canal is one of the world’s most famous waterways - connecting the Red Sea to the Mediterranean, and opening up trade between the East and the West. But ever since its legendary construction in 1869, the Suez Canal has been at the centre of conflict and controversy. Why does a ditch in a desert spark years of political crises? Who helped turn a pharaoh’s dream into a reality?</description></item><item><title>Marilyn Monroe | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820016/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marilyn Monroe was one of the most famous screen actors of all time. Known for her charisma and beauty, her private life and turbulent health made headlines throughout her career, and her early death cemented her iconic status. But how was she shaped by her disrupted childhood? Did she change Hollywood – or did it destroy her? And why does her legend still inspire and exert such power, 60 years after her death?</description></item><item><title>The Sutton Hoo Ship Burial | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820017/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820017/</guid><description>Podcast Description The discovery at Sutton Hoo of the ship burial of an Anglo-Saxon king and his lavish treasure is one of the greatest archaeological finds on English soil. But who was the man considered worthy of such a splendid burial? Why was there no trace of human remains? What lies beneath the other mounds on the site? And why bury a body in a ship? This is a Short History of the Sutton Hoo Ship Burial.</description></item><item><title>Charlie Chaplin | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820018/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820018/</guid><description>Podcast Description The first truly global celebrity, Charlie Chaplin was once the most famous man in the world. The king of the silent movie, over the course of 82 films his wistful slapstick saw him light up the silver screen like no one else. But how did he leave behind the extreme poverty of his London childhood? What’s the truth about his complicated love life? And how did personal and political conflict threaten to derail one of the most celebrated careers in entertainment history?</description></item><item><title>Women’s Football | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820019/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Football is the most popular sport in the world, and is played anywhere from pitches marked out in desert dust, to warzones with helmets for goalposts. But it’s still predominantly a male sport. So what about the roots of women’s football in the UK? How did social change in the First World War contribute to its sudden growth? And after a catastrophic ban from the FA in 1921, how did the women’s game rise from the ashes?</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Real Survival Stories - Abandon Ship (Part 1 of 2) | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820020/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Noiser presents a brand-new podcast: Real Survival Stories. Hosted by John Hopkins, the show brings you astonishing tales of ordinary people thrust into extraordinary survival situations. In this taster episode, we meet Matt Lewis - a rookie sailor who goes looking for adventure&amp;hellip; and finds it. Joining the crew of a deep sea fishing trawler, Matt is on board as the vessel sails out of Cape Town. But far out in the South Atlantic, a polar storm will catch them all unawares.</description></item><item><title>The Battle of Britain | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820021/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820021/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the summer of 1940, the Battle of Britain saw 3,000 airmen risk their lives to defend British shores from the Nazis. But as the pilots battled overhead, what was life like for those supporting them on the ground, and the people of Britain they sought to protect? What was Hitler’s objective, and how did the British react? And what was the secret to defeating the formidable Luftwaffe? This is a Short History of the Battle of Britain.</description></item><item><title>The Great Depression | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820022/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Great Depression was the worst and deepest peacetime economic shock of the twentieth century. It affected millions of lives, redefined global trade, and contributed to the drift towards the Second World War.But how were the seeds of this financial disaster sown in the First World War? What was the cost to ordinary people? And how did America and the wider world dig itself out of its financial hole?</description></item><item><title>The French Resistance | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820023/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820023/</guid><description>Podcast Description During the dark years of the Nazi occupation, many French and Allied citizens risked and sacrificed their lives fighting against their oppressors. Their networks undermined the Nazis through intelligence, sabotage and guerilla tactics, and eventually grew into a huge clandestine force ready to help liberate their own country. But who were these activists? How much damage did they inflict on the occupiers? And what happened to those who fought – and those who collaborated – when the war was finally over?</description></item><item><title>Richard the Third | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820024/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Richard the Third was the last English king to die in battle. A key figure in the Wars of the Roses, he is also prime suspect in the enduring mystery of the Princes in the Tower. Shakespeare’s classic villain, he is immortalized as an anti-hero, cunning and monstrous. But is his reputation fair? What was his route to the throne, and what led to his famous demise on the battlefield?</description></item><item><title>Hadrian’s Wall | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820025/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nineteen hundred years ago, Hadrian’s Wall was built to defend against the northern tribes, and mark the extent of the Roman empire in Britain. But it also performed functions of trade and communication. Entire communities, of people from all over the Roman Empire, lived and worked in its shadow. But how did the Romans undertake such an extraordinary feat of architecture? What was life like for those who built it?</description></item><item><title>The Wright Brothers | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820026/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820026/</guid><description>Podcast Description As long as humans have observed creatures in flight, we have dreamed of taking to the skies ourselves. But Wilbur and Orville Wright were determined to be the ones to turn the dream into reality. So what did they need to learn from the early aviation pioneers who preceded them? And how did these two bicycle makers with no college education succeed where others had failed? This is a Short History of The Wright Brothers.</description></item><item><title>The Golden Age of Athens | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820027/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820027/</guid><description>Podcast Description While the Roman Republic was still in its infancy, the Greek city-state of Athens rose from the ruins of war with the Persians to become the most beautiful and powerful in the region. During this Golden Age, many Athenian citizens enjoyed unprecedented freedoms in the world’s first democracy. Architects and engineers designed buildings of unparalleled sophistication, while writers, philosophers and scientists created works that still resonate today. And after shining so brightly, Athens’ rapid decline is a lesson in how great civilisations rise and fall.</description></item><item><title>Female Spies of World War Two | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820028/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820028/</guid><description>Podcast Description During World War Two, dozens of British-trained women were deployed as spies and saboteurs, to infiltrate behind enemy lines in Nazi-controlled France. Ranging from housewives to countesses, they were trained as secret agents, and played critical roles to aid the war effort. But who were these women, and how did they find their way into espionage? What did they do undercover, and what were the consequences of capture? And how did those who made it home adjust to life when the war was won?</description></item><item><title>The Renaissance | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820029/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820029/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Renaissance of the 15th and 16th centuries was a time of rediscovery. With Florence as its epicentre, it saw a revival of the art, culture and philosophy of ancient Greek and Rome, triggering huge shifts in creativity and thought. But what prompted such a hugely influential movement? Who drove its development, and how did its ideas spread with such unprecedented speed? And, if it weren’t for the great thinkers, artists and inventors of the Renaissance, would we still be living in the Dark Ages?</description></item><item><title>Thomas Edison | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820030/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Thomas Edison was one of history’s greatest inventors, who gave the world not only electric light but other landmark innovations in sound recording and moving pictures. He accumulated more patents in his lifetime than any other, and filled over 4000 notebooks with his work. So, how did this ordinary, home-schooled boy from the American mid-West overcome ill-health and hearing loss to change the world? To what extent was he a lone genius, and how much did he rely on the work of others?</description></item><item><title>Angkor | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820031/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Built by the Khmer kings centuries ago, Angkor in modern Cambodia had a footprint bigger than present-day New York. But after it fell into ruin, much of its unique architecture and intricate carvings were swallowed by the jungle. So, who raised this vast city, and why? What caused their civilisation to fall? And how were parts of it maintained, right up to the present day? This is a Short History Of Angkor.</description></item><item><title>The Soviet Union, Part 2 of 2 | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820032/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Despite its troubled infancy and the hardship faced during World War 2, in the second half of the 20th century the USSR became one of the world’s two superpowers. How did it manage this turn-around? What did its rise mean for its people and the rest of the world? And how did the young nation that shaped so much of the 20th century’s geopolitics eventually come crashing down? This is the second in a special 2 part Short History of… the Soviet Union.</description></item><item><title>The Soviet Union, Part 1 of 2 | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820033/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820033/</guid><description>Podcast Description From its initial creation in 1922, the Soviet Union was perhaps the most ambitious political experiment in human history. But how did this superpower come about? And in its first decades, how did its founding principles of equality transform to fit a nation that became synonymous with tragedy, poverty, suppression and terror? This is the first in a special 2-part Short History of the Soviet Union. Written by Dan Smith.</description></item><item><title>Alexander the Great | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820034/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Though he ruled for just 13 years, Alexander the Great is as famed for his hedonistic lifestyle as his military genius. But how did he become one of the best known military leaders in history? What inspired such loyalty among his troops? And what drove this young man in his endless quest to conquer the known world? This is a Short History of Alexander the Great. Written by Linda Harrison.</description></item><item><title>The Crown Jewels | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820035/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820035/</guid><description>Podcast Description The British Crown Jewels is a priceless collection of items gathered over eight turbulent centuries. Consisting of 100 objects decorated with 23,000 gemstones, it’s held at the Tower of London, protected by guards and high-tech security. But why did one thief put the crown jewels down his trousers? Which king managed to lose his own crown? And why is one diamond so controversial that it is not invited to the coronation of King Charles III?</description></item><item><title>The Blitz | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820036/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820036/</guid><description>Podcast Description From September 1940, Germany’s Luftwaffe subjected Britain to an intense bombing campaign lasting more than eight months. Around 43,000 civilians were killed, with many more injured or made homeless. But what led to the onslaught, and why could it not be stopped? How effective was Hitler’s campaign in achieving his aims? And how did the people of Britain react to this massive disruption to their daily lives and to the ever-present threat of death?</description></item><item><title>The Wild West | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820037/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Think of the Wild West, and you’ll imagine cowboys, shootouts, bank robberies and saloons. But it was also a time of massive resettlement, new technology and communications. But what the white settlers’ westward migration mean for the native people who had lived on the land for centuries? What inspired so many to move west in the first place? And if the era only lasted a few decades, what makes it so iconic to Americans and the rest of the world?</description></item><item><title>British Castles | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820038/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820038/</guid><description>Podcast Description For over 600 years, castles played a leading role in the story of Britain. From the Norman Conquest to the English Civil War, they are woven into the tapestry of British history. But when did they start to be built, and why? How did their architecture evolve? And why did they fall out of fashion, leaving a landscape littered with crumbling ruins? This is A Short History Of… British Castles.</description></item><item><title>Muhammad Ali | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820039/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820039/</guid><description>Podcast Description From the day he burst onto the scene, Muhammad Ali changed boxing history. But he also influenced the American civil rights movement, the perception of Islam, the view of the war in Vietnam, and the self-branding of athletes themselves. So how did his beliefs affect his career? What drove him to keep fighting for so long – even when boxing itself was taking away the gifts that made him famous?</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Detectives Don’t Sleep - Murder in Paradise (Part 1 of 2) | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820040/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820040/</guid><description>Podcast Description From Noiser, comes the brand-new podcast Detectives Don’t Sleep. The show takes you beyond the police tape to shadow the real detectives who worked history’s most intriguing cases. In this taster episode, we’re in the Bahamas in 1943. One of the wealthiest men in the islands, Sir Harry Oakes, has been murdered - bludgeoned and burned in his mansion. The prime suspect is Oakes’ son-in-law, Count Alfred de Marigny.</description></item><item><title>The Dinosaur Rush | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820041/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820041/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Edward Cope and OC Marsh began their race to identify and name new species of dinosaur in the 1870s, palaeontology was still a new discipline. Before these two wealthy men entered the field, just eight species had been identified in North America. In two decades, between them they added 136 more. But how did they manage to produce such a vast body of research? And why was their earlier friendship replaced by a bitter professional feud?</description></item><item><title>Frida Kahlo | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820042/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Frida Kahlo is as much a modern icon for her personal flair as she is for her paintings. But how did her style develop, and what did she intend it to communicate? What was so subversive about her work, and the subjects she chose to portray? And why is she such an enduring figurehead for feminists, women with fertility issues, the queer community, and those living with disabilities and chronic pain?</description></item><item><title>St Patrick | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820043/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Though St Patrick is honoured by millions of revellers worldwide every year, few know more about him than the popular myths concerning shamrocks and snakes. The real story of St Patrick reads like an adventure story, involving kidnapping, enslavement, and daring escapes. But how did his commitment to spreading the word of God lead him to become the embodiment of all things Irish? This is A Short History of… St Patrick.</description></item><item><title>The Trans-Siberian Railway | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820044/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820044/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Trans-Siberian railway is the longest train line in the world, spanning 5700 miles, seven time zones, and straddling two continents. Though today’s passengers on the week-long journey can enjoy relative luxury, the route has a dark past. Who were the labourers who built it, enduring horrific conditions? How did the railroad provoke a war? And what part did the train line play in the bloody conflicts of the twentieth century?</description></item><item><title>The Bayeux Tapestry | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820045/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Since it was created 900 years ago, the Bayeux Tapestry has survived war, revolution and the ravages of time. This fragile piece of linen, almost seventy metres long, depicts the events leading up to the Norman invasion of England. But who created it, and why? What do its graphic scenes of battle and cruelty reveal about life, death and warfare in the middle ages? This is a Short History of the Bayeux Tapestry.</description></item><item><title>The Real Robinson Crusoe | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Daniel Defoe’s 1719 novel Robinson Crusoe is one of the most widely published books in history. This story of a man stranded alone on an island is said to be second only to the Bible in its number of translations. But who was Defoe’s inspiration for creating one of the best-known protagonists in literature? And what led to this real-life sailor spending years of his life cut off from human contact?</description></item><item><title>The Mona Lisa | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820047/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Leonardo da Vinci’s Mona Lisa is the most famous painting in the world. 500 years old and just 77x53cm in size, it is kept behind bulletproof glass in the Louvre museum in Paris, where it draws 10 million visitors a year. But how did a small portrait find global fame? Who is the woman in the painting, and why is the world so intrigued by her smile? This is a Short History Of the Mona Lisa.</description></item><item><title>The Partition of India | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820048/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820048/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1947, the British divided up its former colony of India into two provinces. What followed was confusion, chaos, and an unprecedented wave of sectarian violence that left up to a million dead. 15 million more were forced to flee their homes. So why was the country broken up? What prompted the ferocious backlash? And how do the events of 75 years ago still haunt the region, its residents and the diaspora?</description></item><item><title>D.B. Cooper | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820049/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820049/</guid><description>Podcast Description At approximately 8:13 p.m. on November 24th, 1971, a hijacker exited Northwest Airlines flight 305 at an altitude of 10,000 feet, carrying just a case, a bagful of money, and a parachute. The subsequent investigation became one of the largest and strangest in the FBI’s history. But was what the true identity of the man who called himself D.B. Cooper? And could he still out there, living among us?</description></item><item><title>Agatha Christie | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820050/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Retaining the title of the “Queen of Crime” to this day, Agatha Christie is the best-selling novelist of all time. Across 66 novels, 14 short-story collections, and 20 stage plays, she depicted the evil lurking in the hearts of ordinary people. But how did this homeschooled daughter of a privileged English family learn so much about poisons, psychopaths and murder? What in her personal life informed such a suspicious view of ordinary people?</description></item><item><title>The Irish Potato Famine | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820051/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Between 1845 and 1852, Ireland suffered an appalling famine after the repeated failure of the potato crop, its national staple. But though caused by a natural blight, a combination of ancient prejudices, simmering tensions and political short-termism turned a national emergency into a disaster for the ages. So why did the authorities in Westminster seem to wash their hands of Ireland during its time of need? How did the Irish people respond to their adversity?</description></item><item><title>Las Vegas | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820052/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Best known for its world-class casinos and lavish hotels, the desert city of Las Vegas, Nevada has a darker side, too. For decades, connections to organised crime tarnished its reputation. Now, Las Vegas attracts tens of millions of tourists every year, many of whom come to gamble. But did games of chance really drive the transformation of this small, dusty desert town? And will it ever shed its persistent nickname of Sin City?</description></item><item><title>Shakespeare | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820053/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820053/</guid><description>Podcast Description No single writer has shaped the way we speak and think more than William Shakespeare. Whether we’re being cruel to be kind, wearing our hearts on our sleeves, or spotting the green eye’d monster — it’s almost impossible to use the English language without quoting him. But who was Shakespeare? What vaulting ambition drove a young writer from a sleepy town to stardom in London? Was he born great or did he have greatness thrust upon him?</description></item><item><title>The Christmas Truce of 1914 (Repeat) | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820054/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820054/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s Christmas eve, 1914. On the Western Front, a British soldier peers out across No Man’s Land. A sound catches his attention – not artillery fire, but music. The enemy are singing Silent Night. The Christmas Truce of 1914 remains a unique historical anomaly. But how did these sworn enemies set down their weapons and meet as friends? What does the truce reveal about the First World War? This is a Short History of the Christmas Truce.</description></item><item><title>Pocahontas | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820055/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pocahontas is probably the best known Native American in history. But the true story of her life has been eclipsed by a fictionalised version, played out as a romance between an intrepid English captain and a wild native princess. So what is known about the real Pocahontas, and her life before the arrival of the white colonisers? How did she spearhead a period of truce between her tribe and the Europeans?</description></item><item><title>Abraham Lincoln | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820056/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Abraham Lincoln’s life reads like an American folk tale. The story of a boy born into poverty, whose drive and determination saw him become the most powerful man in the nation. But how did he navigate a path for a youthful country so deeply divided over slavery? What was his role in the devastating civil war? And how did one man attract such public adoration and murderous wrath all at the same time?</description></item><item><title>The Rosetta Stone | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820057/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820057/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1799, French soldiers in Egypt unearthed what would become one of the world’s most famous artefacts. After a desperate race to decipher its symbols, the Rosetta Stone provided the key to understanding Egyptian hieroglyphs, casting new light on the culture and history of this lost civilisation. But why was the Rosetta Stone made in the first place? How did it end up in the hands of the French occupiers, thousands of years after it was created?</description></item><item><title>The Tower of London | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820058/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820058/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Tower of London has been a symbol of the authority and power of the British crown for almost a thousand years. Established by William the Conqueror, the iconic building has served as a palace and a prison; a safe and an armory; a seat of leadership and a site of torture and execution. But why was it built in the first place? How did it evolve? What are the stories of its residents, willing or otherwise?</description></item><item><title>Easter Island | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820059/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820059/</guid><description>Podcast Description First inhabited by the Rapa Nui people a thousand years ago, Easter Island is best known for its hundreds of giant stone statues. But what inspired a group of ancient Polynesian explorers to settle in such a remote spot in the South Pacific? How did they almost bring their own community to the point of collapse? And as ancient traditions meet with modern tourism, what is the future for the Rapa Nui people?</description></item><item><title>Vincent Van Gogh | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820060/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vincent van Gogh was one of the most important and influential figures in the history of art. Though he created thousands of drawings and paintings, his was a life of commercial failure, instability and unhappiness. But who was Van Gogh before he discovered his passion for art? What caused him so much suffering? And who were the people who supported him right up to his tragic death at the age of just 37?</description></item><item><title>The Conquistadors | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820061/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820061/</guid><description>Podcast Description From the end of the 15th century, the Conquistadors changed the face of the Americas. Invading first the Caribbean and Mexico, they then plunged on into the rest of the continent and plundered the Pacific seaboard. So what do we know of these Europeans and their quest to expand a burgeoning empire? And who were the indigenous people that resisted invasion, negotiated with strangers, and fought off barbarians? This is a Short History of the Conquistadors.</description></item><item><title>Albert Einstein | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820062/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Albert Einstein overhauled our understanding of the universe—from the sub-atomic level to beyond the edges of the cosmos. Today his ideas are in evidence everywhere, from televisions and GPS systems, to our understanding of black holes and the Big Bang. But who was Einstein as a person? What were his theories that upended established scientific beliefs? And how did his work inadvertently contribute to some of the 20th century’s most devastating acts of warfare?</description></item><item><title>The Great Train Robbery | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820063/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820063/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Great Train Robbery of 1963 saw a gang of career criminals stage a daring heist of the multi-million pound cargo of a travelling Royal Mail train. The investigation that followed spanned many years and covered the globe. But how did the idea of the crime come about? What went into the planning, and who were the key players? And did any of them truly get away? This is a Short History of The Great Train Robbery.</description></item><item><title>Cleopatra | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820064/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820064/</guid><description>Podcast Description The last of the Ptolemaic Pharoahs, the enduring legend of Cleopatra has captivated imaginations for centuries. Though some write her off as a manipulative femme fatale, her competence as a ruler restored her country to a world superpower. But what were the early experiences that shaped her? How did she form both political and personal alliances with two great Roman generals? And what is the true story of her dramatic death?</description></item><item><title>The Conquest of Everest | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820065/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Standing over 29,000ft above sea level, the peak of Everest is the highest point on the planet. To the sherpa people of the Himalayas it is sacred, and to foreign adventurers, it is the holy grail of climbing. But what did it take to reach the summit? Was it expertise and endurance—or simply better equipment? What was sacrificed to plant a flag on top of the world? This is a Short History Of the Conquest of Everest.</description></item><item><title>The Mongol Empire | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820066/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820066/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the late Middle Ages, the Mongol Empire became the largest the world had ever seen. At its peak, maybe 100 million people lived under its banner, led by the Great Khans of the Asian steppe. But what unified the first disparate, nomadic clans? Who was the real Genghis Khan, and how did his empire fair after his death? And what caused the downfall of this once seemingly unstoppable civilisation?</description></item><item><title>The Real Peaky Blinders | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820067/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Between the 1890s and 1910s, the British city of Birmingham was in the grip of a gang: the Peaky Blinders. Their crimes – from stone-throwing and petty assault to murder – were unpredictable and senseless, and the police seemed powerless to stop it. So what’s the true story behind the legend that inspired the hit TV series? Were they really champions of the working class, their activities underpinned by codes of loyalty and morality?</description></item><item><title>Queen Elizabeth the Second, Part 2 of 2 (Repeat) | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820068/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 23:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820068/</guid><description>Podcast Description To mark the passing of the Queen, Noiser brings you this episode from the archive of Short History Of… As the Queen’s family life became more complex, the relationship between palace and press intensified. But balancing the need for security and privacy against her very public responsibilities was never simple. So who was the real woman beneath the crown? How did she respond to the dark years of her reign, or the grief of losing her beloved husband?</description></item><item><title>Queen Elizabeth the Second, Part 1 of 2 (Repeat) | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820069/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820069/</guid><description>Podcast Description To mark the passing of the Queen, Noiser brings you this episode from the archive of Short History Of… Spanning seventy years, Queen Elizabeth II’s reign saw the world change beyond recognition. And from her earliest public appearances representing the King to her roles as sister, wife, mother and mother-in-law, she was never far from the headlines. But what was life like for the young princess, who dreamed of a baby brother to take the throne instead?</description></item><item><title>The Wars of the Roses, Part 3 of 3 | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820070/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820070/</guid><description>Podcast Description After the death of King Edward IV, the heir to the throne, Edward V, is left under the protection of the late king’s brother Richard. But what lay in store for the 12 year old king? Will Richard honour his brother’s will? And when the Wars of the Roses finally end, how do the rival houses of Plantagenet unite once and for all? This is part three of a special three-part Short History of the Wars of the Roses.</description></item><item><title>The Wars of the Roses, Part 2 of 3 | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820071/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820071/</guid><description>Podcast Description With his father Richard of York’s head now on a spike, Edward’s determination to snatch the crown from Henry VI is stronger than ever. But how will he build support for his cause and assert his rights? Can he outmanoeuvre the formidable Queen Margaret, who will stop at nothing to see her own son on the throne? And is there any way to heal England’s bitter rifts and create a lasting peace?</description></item><item><title>The Wars of the Roses, Part 1 of 3 | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820072/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Almost 600 years ago, two rival branches of the ruling house of Plantagenet dragged England into unprecedented bloodshed in what became known as the Wars of the Roses. But what were the causes of the conflict? Who were its key players, the powerful men and women who wreaked such havoc on the country? And how did one couple unite the warring factions and bring an end to the carnage?</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Napoleon | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820073/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Noiser presents Napoleon, a new podcast examining the life and times of one of history’s most intriguing figures. You’ve heard the name Napoleon Bonaparte. But who was he, really? How did he become the most powerful man on Earth? And why didn&amp;rsquo;t he stop, even once he had it all? A Noiser production, written by Jeff Dawson. Search ‘Napoleon’ wherever you get your podcasts and hit follow to listen to the rest of the Napoleon story.</description></item><item><title>The Spanish Armada | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820074/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820074/</guid><description>Podcast Description The defeat of the Spanish Armada by the English navy is often recounted as a ‘David and Goliath’ tale in which one tiny country overcame a huge and formidable empire. It secured the continuance of Protestant rule in England and was a defining moment in the reign of Queen Elizabeth I. But why did this confrontation ever take place? Was England’s success due entirely to its naval prowess, or did other factors play a part?</description></item><item><title>Stonehenge | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820075/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Older than the pyramids and just as cryptic, the prehistoric British site of Stonehenge has dominated its landscape for thousands of years. But what is Stonehenge? A celestial clock? An ancient computer to predict eclipses? Was it a temple, a cemetery, or a site of execution? And who were the people who lived and died to create this Stone Age masterpiece? This is a Short History of Stonehenge. Written by Jo Furniss.</description></item><item><title>Amelia Earhart | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820076/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820076/</guid><description>Podcast Description As one of the great pioneers of air travel, Amelia Earhart was the first woman to fly solo across the Atlantic. She pushed aviation technology to its limits, broke countless records, and became world-famous for her skill, bravery and determination. But what prompted her to dare to take to the skies despite the overwhelming risks? Who was the real person behind the legend? And what happened on her final fateful flight—an enduring mystery that has spawned countless conspiracy theories?</description></item><item><title>Marco Polo | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820077/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820077/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the thirteenth century, Marco Polo spent decades travelling the world. His adventures took him from his home in Venice as far east as the Yellow Sea, where he was a valued courtier of the legendary Mongol emperor Kublai Khan. Later, in prison, he wrote the world’s first travel book. But how did his name become synonymous with adventure? What compelled him to stay away for so long? And why is his story still remembered almost eight centuries later?</description></item><item><title>The Spartans | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820078/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820078/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 480BC, the Spartans secured their place in history when 300 of their soldiers fought to the death against the mighty Persian army at Thermopylae. Their reputation for brutal decisiveness and simple living have been admired for thousands of years. But what about the darker side of Spartan ideology, a society that culled weak babies, forced children to fight, and enslaved its neighbours? Was Sparta really a utopia? Or was Aristotle right when he said that Spartans simply made men into machines?</description></item><item><title>Machu Picchu and the Inca Trail | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820079/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Covering thousands of miles in the Andes, the Inca Trail was the backbone of the ancient empire, connecting the millions of people who lived under its rule. The jewel in its crown, Machu Picchu, was recently named one of the seven wonders of the modern world. But who were the Incas? What was the purpose of their complex road system? And why did they build a stone citadel on a mountain ridge, only to abandon it a century later?</description></item><item><title>The Great Fire of London | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820080/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820080/</guid><description>Podcast Description In September 1666, the Great Fire of London consumed hundreds of acres of houses, shops, churches, and government buildings. But what effect did politics and memories of a recent civil war have on the spread of the fire, and the hunt for someone to blame? And once the flames had died down, how did the people of the city rebuild what they’d lost? This a Short History of the Great Fire of London.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Real Outlaws - Ned Kelly | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820081/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 09:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820081/</guid><description>Podcast Description From Noiser, Real Outlaws is the new podcast that travels back in time to when rouges and bandits followed a code all of their own. In this taster episode, we&amp;rsquo;re on the trail of Ned Kelly - The Australian legend without equal. But what&amp;rsquo;s the truth behind the myth? Search ‘Real Outlaws’ wherever you get your podcasts and hit follow to never miss an episode. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Queen Elizabeth the Second, Part 2 of 2 | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820082/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820082/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the Queen’s family life becomes more complex, the relationship between palace and press intensifies. But balancing the need for security and privacy against her very public responsibilities is never simple. So who is the real woman beneath the crown? How does she respond to the dark years of her reign, or the grief of losing her beloved husband? And as she approaches her Platinum Jubilee, how will history remember her reign?</description></item><item><title>Queen Elizabeth the Second, Part 1 of 2 | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820083/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Spanning seventy years, Queen Elizabeth II’s reign has seen the world change beyond recognition. And from her earliest public appearances representing the King to her roles as sister, wife, mother, and mother-in-law, she is never far from the headlines. But what was life like for the young princess, who dreamed of a baby brother to take the throne instead? How did she modernize an ancient role to fit a changing world, while managing a family so often overshadowed by scandal?</description></item><item><title>The Terracotta Army | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820084/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820084/</guid><description>Podcast Description After its initial discovery in 1974, the Terracotta Army became the unofficial eighth wonder of the world. Comprising an estimated 8,000 statue warriors buried as part of the First Emperor of China’s tomb complex, experts are still unearthing its secrets. But what was the purpose of so many clay soldiers? How were they made, and by whom? And what do we know about the Emperor considered so important that his death demanded a project on this scale?</description></item><item><title>Chernobyl | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820085/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820085/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1986, the Chernobyl power plant became the site of the worst nuclear disaster in history. Poisonous radiation caused over 100,000 casualties, and cost billions of dollars to clean up. Even now, the exclusion zone is one of the most polluted and heavily-patrolled regions in the world. But what caused the catastrophe in the first place? Why did the Soviet Union try to keep it a secret? And what is its lasting impact on the region, and the wider world?</description></item><item><title>Henry VIII | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820086/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820086/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1509, at just seventeen years old, Henry VIII was crowned King of England. Over the next four decades, he would burn through six marriages, bankrupt his nation, and vandalise his country’s cultural heritage in his quest for supreme power. But how did England’s most eligible bachelor degenerate into a bloated despot, and one of the worst husbands in history? Was the king a psychopath, or a complex character who dragged Britain from the Dark Ages into the modern era?</description></item><item><title>Pearl Harbor, Part 3 of 3 | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820087/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820087/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the smoke clears after the Japanese attack on Pearl Harbor, the blame game begins. President Roosevelt knows that military and intelligence heads must roll, but questions remain about who should be held to account. So what were the longer term consequences of the attack? How did life change for Japanese-Americans, and what fates awaited the Japanese servicemen on their return? And as the memory of Pearl Harbor fades, what lessons were learned?</description></item><item><title>Pearl Harbor, Part 2 of 3 | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820088/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chaos reigns in the immediate aftermath of the Japanese attack on Pearl Harbor. While the true extent of the damage to personnel and fleet is still uncertain, those on the ground work tirelessly to help the wounded. But what is the response of those in charge? What are the stories of servicemen who face incredible odds to save their vessels, retaliate, or flee? And who were the people who risked their lives to save others?</description></item><item><title>Pearl Harbor, Part 1 of 3 | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820089/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820089/</guid><description>Podcast Description On December 7th 1941, the Japanese attack on Pearl Harbor, Hawaii, changed the course of the Second World War. Forcing the United States into a conflict they were reluctant to enter, the attack killed over 2,500 people. But was it an act of aggression, or desperation? How did the Japanese pull off such an audacious stealth attack? And how were the Americans so unprepared? This is episode 1 of a special 3-part Short History of Pearl Harbor.</description></item><item><title>The Russian Revolution | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820090/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820090/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1917, revolution changed Russia forever. Putting an end to 300 years of the Romanov dynasty, it made way for what ordinary Russians believed would be a fairer, more egalitarian system. But what sparked the rebellion? What was it like to witness the collapse of the autocracy? And once the smoke had cleared, what happened to the promise of a new socialist utopia? This is a Short History of the Russian Revolution.</description></item><item><title>The Titanic | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820091/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820091/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Titanic was the largest moveable object in history: almost 900 feet long, and holding over two thousand passengers. But just four days into its maiden voyage, a collision with an iceberg was enough to send her to the bottom of the Atlantic Ocean. So what made the famously ‘unsinkable’ ship anything but? Who was responsible for so many deaths? And what was it like to witness the disaster first hand?</description></item><item><title>The Vikings | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820092/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Viking exploration changed the course of history in the northern hemisphere. As raiders and pirates, they dominated the seas of northern Europe for centuries. Their fearless and brutal reputations struck fear into hearts from Constantinople to Canada, while their folklore and mythology continues to inspire to this day. But who were the mortal men and women behind the immortal legends of the Norsemen? This is a Short History Of the Vikings.</description></item><item><title>The Knights Templar | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820093/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820093/</guid><description>Podcast Description For almost two hundred years, the Knights Templar were one of the most fearsome military forces in the world. Despite their strict vows of individual poverty, the Order was a global financial powerhouse, with valuable holdings across Europe and the Middle East. Even today, the myth of the Templars endures. But who were the men who devoted themselves to the mysterious order? And how did such a powerful international organisation find itself suddenly brought down?</description></item><item><title>Prohibition | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820094/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820094/</guid><description>Podcast Description For thirteen years from 1920, the manufacture, sale, and transportation of alcoholic drinks was banned in the USA. The age of prohibition was a rowdy time: enlivened by jazz and wild parties; darkened by violence and lawlessness. But how did it come about? Who were its heroes and villains? And how did it change the face of the country it sought to purify? This is a Short History of Prohibition.</description></item><item><title>The Watergate Scandal | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820095/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820095/</guid><description>Podcast Description When five men are caught inside a Washington DC office block in June 1972, it’s noted in police records simply as a ‘burglary’. So how does this bungled break-in go on to unravel a web of corruption and conspiracy, shatter America’s trust in its leadership, and topple President Richard Nixon, the most powerful man in the world? This is a Short History of the Watergate Scandal. Written by Jo Furniss.</description></item><item><title>The Suffragettes | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820096/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820096/</guid><description>Podcast Description While British women had been requesting the right to vote for decades, in the early 1900s, the Suffragettes refused to take no for an answer. But despite their PR expertise, as their methods became more violent, theirs was a movement that divided the nation. But what radicalized them? Were they revolutionaries? Terrorists? Or simply an oppressed majority with no legitimate way to protest? This is a Short History of the Suffragettes.</description></item><item><title>The Berlin Wall | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820097/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820097/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the border between the Western world and the Soviet Union, the Berlin Wall was a symbol of the Cold War. Starting out as a simple barbed wire fence, it would grow in scale and complexity to become a 27-mile concrete edifice, incorporating watchtowers, trenches, electric fences, and landmines. But what was its purpose? How did it impact the people whose city it divided? And what did it take, in the end, to bring it down?</description></item><item><title>The Ottoman Empire | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820098/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820098/</guid><description>Podcast Description For over six hundred years the Ottoman Empire ruled swathes of the Middle East, North Africa, and Southern Europe. As an Islamic superpower centred on what is now Turkey, theirs is a story of surprising alliances and enemies, trade, war and progress. But who were its leaders? How did it become so powerful? And after its eventual collapse, what legacy did it leave behind? This is a Short History of the Ottoman Empire.</description></item><item><title>The Underground Railroad | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820099/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820099/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Underground Railroad helped up to 100,000 enslaved people to freedom. It was America’s first civil rights movement, operated by Black and white people united in their abhorrence of slavery. But how was it established? Who were its passengers, and the people risking everything to assist them? And what part did it play in America’s descent into civil war? This is a Short History of the Underground Railroad. Written by Kate Simants.</description></item><item><title>Apollo 13 | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820100/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820100/</guid><description>Podcast Description April 13th, 1970. 200,000 miles from Earth, three astronauts are approaching lunar orbit when they hear a noise. Deep in the spacecraft, a tiny wiring fault has caused an entire oxygen tank to explode. Now, it’s a race against time to save the lives of the crew of Apollo 13. It could have been the worst disaster in the history of manned space exploration. So how did things go so wrong?</description></item><item><title>Bonnie and Clyde | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820101/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Forged by the Great Depression, Bonnie and Clyde became icons of lawlessness, thrilling and shocking America with their crime sprees and doomed romance. But what drove them to lives of such violence? And with the full might of the police against them, how did it all end? This is a Short History of Bonnie and Clyde. Written by Danny Marshall, with thanks to Paul Schneider, journalist and author of Bonnie and Clyde – The Lives Behind The Legend.</description></item><item><title>Ernest Shackleton | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820102/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Antarctica, October 1915. 1200 miles from civilisation, Ernest Shackleton watches from the ice as his ship finally crumples. To survive, he and his 27 men must now undertake an epic, death-defying journey, amid impossibly harsh conditions. Shackleton’s expedition is one of history’s greatest tales of human endurance. But what went so badly wrong? And with no hope of rescue, how will they make it home to tell the tale?</description></item><item><title>The Christmas Truce | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820103/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820103/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s Christmas eve, 1914. On the Western Front, a British soldier peers out across No Man’s Land. A sound catches his attention – not artillery fire, but music. The enemy are singing Silent Night. The Christmas Truce of 1914 remains a unique historical anomaly. But how did these sworn enemies set down their weapons and meet as friends? What does the truce reveal about the First World War? This is a Short History of the Christmas Truce.</description></item><item><title>The Roman Republic | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820104/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820104/</guid><description>Podcast Description March 15th, 44BC. Despite ill omens, Julius Caesar approaches the Theatre of Pompey. But the men inside have sworn an oath. To save the Republic from the hands of this self-styled ‘perpetual dictator&amp;rsquo;, Caesar must die. But where did the Republic start? How did it transform Rome from a small town into a superpower? And what made its government, so determinedly against autocracy, pass the tipping point into a dictatorship?</description></item><item><title>The Pirate Queen | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820105/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820105/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s November 28th, 1809. The Imperial fleet in Tung Chung Bay is aflame. But the crew of Zheng I Sao’s ship watch on and cheer. This is the greatest victory of the Pirate Queen, scourge of the South China Sea. At its peak, her fleet was more than twice the size of the Spanish Armada. But who was Zheng I Sao? How did she become one of the most successful pirates of all time?</description></item><item><title>Pyramids | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820106/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sakkara, Egypt, 2,630BC. A man stands atop a structure of dizzying height as the final block grinds into place. For Imhotep, it is the culmination of his life’s work: a mountain made by man. He checks the joint while his workers wait in silence. Then, he gives a barely perceptible nod. It is done. Imhotep’s pyramid is the first, but more will come. Bigger pyramids, more beautiful pyramids, tombs filled with treasure, chambers inscribed with complex, sacred writings.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Real Pirates | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820107/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820107/</guid><description>Podcast Description New Noiser Release. Starting today, unpack the epic dramas of history’s most infamous buccaneers. Real Pirates takes you right into the heart of the action with immersive storytelling and pulse-racing tales, charting the lives of the legendary men and women who roamed the oceans. Who really were they? What was life really like? Listen to an exclusive clip from the first episode right here, then search and follow Real Pirates for new episodes every Monday!</description></item><item><title>William Wallace | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820108/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Despised by the English, mistrusted by the Scottish nobles, and revered by his countrymen: William Wallace is synonymous with the battle for Scottish freedom. But scratch away at the legend, and even the most basic details are disputed. Where he was born, who he married, and what he did after his famous battle at Stirling Bridge. Thanks to the brutal nature of his death, he doesn’t even have a grave.</description></item><item><title>The Samurai | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820109/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820109/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a bloody battle on September 22nd, 1877, Saigo Takamori and his loyal warriors pause on a hillside overlooking Kagoshima. They’ll never surrender, but they’re wounded, exhausted, and massively outnumbered, and Saigo already knows how this will end. Because his noble Samurai army aren’t just fighting the Emperor’s gun-wielding forces. They’re fighting progress itself. And that’s a battle they cannot win. But were the Samurai really a class of elite martial artists, driven by unbreakable codes of chivalry and loyalty?</description></item><item><title>Introducing: History Daily - The Vote of Susan B. Anthony | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820110/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2021 10:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Introducing History Daily, the new show from Noiser, co-produced with Airship. Host Lindsay Graham (American Scandal, American History Tellers) takes you back in time to explore a momentous moment that happened ‘on this day’ in history. Find and follow &amp;lsquo;History Daily&amp;rsquo; wherever you get your podcasts to get your daily dose of history. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+. Now available for Apple and Android users.</description></item><item><title>The Gunpowder Plot | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820111/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820111/</guid><description>Podcast Description One night in November 1605, a man is discovered underneath England’s Houses of Parliament. And he’s got enough gunpowder with him to reduce it to rubble, with the King, his sons, and the entire government inside it. The Gunpowder plot is an epic tale of adventure and murderous revenge, a detective story complete with secrets, aliases, even an anonymous letter of betrayal. But who was really behind it? What drove the conspirators to attempt such an audacious act of terrorism?</description></item><item><title>Rosa Parks | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820112/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820112/</guid><description>Podcast Description By the time she died in 2005, Rosa Parks was known around the world as an icon of activism. Her act of defiance one ordinary Thursday afternoon in Montgomery, Alabama catapulted her to the forefront of the battle for racial equality in America. But what was her story before that fateful moment in 1955? What course did her life take afterward? This is a Short History of Rosa Parks.</description></item><item><title>Alcatraz | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820113/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cloaked in secrecy, discussed by even the most hardened criminals as a place of terror, US Penitentiary Alcatraz is the most feared institution in the American penal system. From 1934 to 1963 more than 1500 prisoners pass through its gates, including Machine-Gun Kelly and Scarface himself, Alphonse Capone. But how did this island rock capture the public imagination? What was life really like inside? This is a Short History of Alcatraz.</description></item><item><title>The Maya | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820114/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820114/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1511, a Spanish lifeboat makes land on the Yucatán coast in modern-day Mexico. Thirteen days ago, the crew&amp;rsquo;s caravel was wrecked on a reef. But their adventure is far from over. Now, they are about to become some of the first Europeans to make contact with the Maya. Custodians of an ancient civilisation, at one time tens of millions of Maya people inhabited a swathe of the Americas.</description></item><item><title>The Moon Landing | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820115/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820115/</guid><description>Podcast Description After multiple coups by the Soviet Union, astronaut Alan B. Shepard has just become the first American in space. But this is only the beginning. Now, NASA have the moon in their sights, but it&amp;rsquo;s still a long way off. For either the USA or the USSR to succeed, they&amp;rsquo;ll need newer and better technology. The 1960s are about to become the defining decade in space exploration. Who will touch down first on Earth&amp;rsquo;s nearest neighbour?</description></item><item><title>The Space Race | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820116/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Humanity has always looked to the heavens, pondering what is really out there. But how did space travel turn from fantasy into reality? In the aftermath of World War Two, a group of scientists from Nazi Germany arrives in the United States. Their task? To kickstart America&amp;rsquo;s space program. Meanwhile, in the Soviet Union a covert team of engineers begins work on a series of rockets and satellites. The starting gun has been fired.</description></item><item><title>The Black Death | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820117/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820117/</guid><description>Podcast Description In October 1347, a ghostly fleet of trading ships docks at a port in Sicily. The crew members – dead already, or well on their way – bear bubonic plague. The ‘Great Pestilence’ will ravage the populations of three continents over the next decade. What changes to society will result from this, the most devastating pandemic in history? How will people make sense of the terrible scenes before them?</description></item><item><title>Tutankhamun | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820118/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820118/</guid><description>Podcast Description In November 1922, in Egypt&amp;rsquo;s Valley of the Kings, a young water boy called Hussein Abdul Rasoul makes a remarkable discovery. A set of stone steps lies concealed beneath the desert sand - a staircase leading to a long-lost tomb. The mummified pharaoh within will capture the imagination of generations to come, becoming the very embodiment of Ancient Egypt. What do we know of this boy king and his premature end?</description></item><item><title>Pompeii and the Vesuvius Eruption | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820119/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820119/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happens when a volcano erupts just six miles from a bustling city? In 79 AD Mount Vesuvius is regarded as a source of bounty by those who live in its shadow. But one of history’s most infamous natural disasters soon unfolds. How did the lucky ones make their escape? And how did this Roman settlement become such an extraordinary archaeological site? This is a Short History of Pompeii and the Vesuvius Eruption.</description></item><item><title>The California Gold Rush | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820120/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820120/</guid><description>Podcast Description On January 24th, 1848, a carpenter from Coloma plunges a hand into the American River and pulls out gold. This discovery triggers an explosion of findings, as people flock to the region seeking fortune and reinvention. But what were the chances of striking gold? What obstacles did would-be prospectors encounter along the way? And did the rush to the American West ever really end? This is a Short History of the California Gold Rush.</description></item><item><title>Blackbeard the Pirate | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820121/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820121/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the early 18th century, one man makes his name as the most notorious pirate of all time. The legend of Edward Thatch has spawned television shows, novels, and major motion pictures. Stories abound of his wild eyes striking fear into enemy hearts, of the six pistols strapped to his chest, and of his arrival in battle with his jet-black beard set ablaze. But how much is fact and how much fiction?</description></item><item><title>The Cuban Missile Crisis, Part 2 of 2 | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820122/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820122/</guid><description>Podcast Description On October 16th, 1962, John F. Kennedy discovers that the Soviet Union has successfully planted ballistic missiles on Cuban soil. The United States is now in Moscow&amp;rsquo;s crosshairs. How will the President respond? How far will Khrushchev and Castro push him? This is a Short History of the Cuban Missile Crisis, Part 2. Written by Joel Duddell. With thanks to Philip Brenner, Professor Emeritus at the American University School of International Service.</description></item><item><title>The Cuban Missile Crisis, Part 1 of 2 | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820123/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820123/</guid><description>Podcast Description In October 1962, three men – Kennedy, Khrushchev, and Castro – hold the fate of the planet in their hands. A dispute over Soviet missiles in Cuba spirals out of control. Officials in the USA and the USSR prepare for a war that would end life on Earth as we know it. How exactly did it come to this? And just how close will the world come to nuclear Armageddon?</description></item><item><title>The Gladiators | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820124/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820124/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the first-ever episode of Short History Of… we take a trip back in time to Ancient Rome, to discover the bizarre and barbaric world of the gladiators. But who were these mysterious warriors? And how much truth lies behind the legends? Take your seat in the Roman Colosseum, the games are about to begin. This is a Short History of the Gladiators. Written by Addison Nugent. With thanks to Dr.</description></item><item><title>Trailer: Short History Of... | Short History Of...</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7918820125/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 21:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7918820125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week, Short History Of&amp;hellip; gives you a front-row seat as history’s most extraordinary moments play out right before you. You’ll be up close with the gladiators and the Mongols, unearthing the Terracotta Army, setting sail in Blackbeard’s pirate ship, watching on as the Cold War hots up. These are the stories beyond the headline names, stories that are amazing because they really did happen. Hit follow for weekly episodes.</description></item></channel></rss>