<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Pirate of Prague on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-pirate-of-prague/</link><description>Recent content in The Pirate of Prague on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 08:01:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-pirate-of-prague/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bottom of the Barrel | 8 | The Pirate of Prague</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8878010009/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8878010009/</guid><description>Podcast Description After 18 months in a notorious Bahamian prison, Viktor walks free. But he’s still being hunted. The Czechs put him on trial in absentia. Trapped in the Bahamas, Viktor is shunned. For so long a self-promoting, globetrotting high roller, he seems to have disappeared from public view. Where is he? Where’s all that money? And will he ever face justice?
The Pirate of Prague is an Apple Original podcast, produced by Blanchard House.</description></item><item><title>The Seven Stages of Grief | 7 | The Pirate of Prague</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8878010008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8878010008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Still reeling from the failed deal, investors begin to believe that Viktor may have double-crossed them. US Law enforcement also sets its sights on Viktor, investigating criminal allegations of a bribery scheme. Viktor is banged up in the Bahamas, fighting extradition to the U.S.&amp;nbsp;
The Pirate of Prague is an Apple Original podcast, produced by Blanchard House. Follow and listen on Apple Podcasts.
apple.co/pirate
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Vallpaper! | 6 | The Pirate of Prague</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8878010007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8878010007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Viktor and his investors await the Azeris’ approval of the oil deal they hope will trigger the ultimate payday. They bend over backwards to keep key officials onside.&amp;nbsp;
The Pirate of Prague is an Apple Original podcast, produced by Blanchard House. Follow and listen on Apple Podcasts.
apple.co/pirate
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>In Bed With Baba | 5 | The Pirate of Prague</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8878010006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8878010006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Just days after his swanky Christmas party in Aspen, Viktor starts recruiting his high-flying guests for his next grand plan: getting control of the state-owned oil company of Azerbaijan. With promises of eye-watering returns, Viktor sweet-talks a group of elite investors into putting up big bucks, including a Wall Street billionaire and one of Washington’s most respected politicians.&amp;nbsp;
The Pirate of Prague is an Apple Original podcast, produced by Blanchard House.</description></item><item><title>Lifeless Cay | 4 | The Pirate of Prague</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8878010005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8878010005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mired in a bribery scandal and wanted by the Czech authorities, Viktor flees to the Bahamas with his young family and a large sum of cash. In the exclusive resort of Lyford Cay, he starts to spend it in earnest.&amp;nbsp;But he’s already got his eye on his next deal—a deal he hopes will catapult him into the ranks of the mega-rich.&amp;nbsp;
The Pirate of Prague is an Apple Original podcast, produced by Blanchard House.</description></item><item><title>The Three Vaclavs | 3 | The Pirate of Prague</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8878010001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 08:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8878010001/</guid><description>Podcast Description With the old Czech communists ousted, Viktor finds his one true talent— making money. Lots of it. He rapidly amasses a vast fortune by persuading fellow citizens to invest with him so he can hoover up valuable state assets. But when rumors about his business start flying, Viktor finds himself caught up in a scandal involving some of the country’s top politicians—and a spy.&amp;nbsp;
The Pirate of Prague is an Apple Original podcast, produced by Blanchard House.</description></item><item><title>The Best Student Harvard Ever Had | 2 | The Pirate of Prague</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8878010002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 08:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8878010002/</guid><description>Podcast Description How it all started: After escaping communist Czechoslovakia, the wily young Viktor orchestrates a trip to America by posing as a physics prodigy. Taken in by a generous college professor, Viktor then runs off with the man’s wife and talks his way into Harvard. Returning to Prague just as communism is imploding, Viktor spots an opportunity that will change his fortunes forever.&amp;nbsp;
The Pirate of Prague is an Apple Original podcast, produced by Blanchard House.</description></item><item><title>The Party | 1 | The Pirate of Prague</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8878010003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8878010003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Christmas 1997. Viktor Kožený, a charismatic financial whiz kid from the former Czechoslovakia, throws a lavish party at his $20-million mountaintop mansion in Aspen. It’s so excessive that even his super-rich neighbors are blown away. But what they don’t realize is that their charming host is about to take them for the ride of their lives.&amp;nbsp;
The Pirate of Prague is an Apple Original podcast, produced by Blanchard House.</description></item><item><title>Introducing The Pirate of Prague | The Pirate of Prague</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8878010004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8878010004/</guid><description>Podcast Description A charming young Czech promises staggering returns. An entire country’s oil industry is up for grabs. America’s top investors want in. Sounds too good to be true? Damn right it is.&amp;nbsp;
This is a story of private jets, $20,000 dinners, and suitcases stuffed with cash. It’s also a tale about the collapse of communism, the free-for-all that followed, and the birth of the oligarchs. And it’s a story of plain-old human greed.</description></item></channel></rss>