<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/two-ts-in-a-pod-with-teddi-mellencamp-and-tamra-judge/</link><description>Recent content in Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 18:05:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/two-ts-in-a-pod-with-teddi-mellencamp-and-tamra-judge/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>TWOTS Take on San Francisco | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850381/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 18:05:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850381/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi and Tamra and Two Ts in a Pod are hitting the road and going live. Find out the special guests that will be on stage with them and why it’s a girls night out you dont want to miss.
Get your tickets now at ticketmaster.com.
January 25th at Palace of Fine Arts, San Francisco!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A+ for Participation (RHOBH &amp; RHOM Recap) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850379/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850379/</guid><description>Podcast Description There has been a lot of talk about Sutton’s drinking over the years, and people are now talking about it this season
Then, Crystal may be on the season but she needs to start speaking up! No participation trophy for her.
Plus, do the ladies agree with Kiki about how much Lisa talks about Lenny?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Hard Episode to Swallow (RHOP &amp; RHOSLC Recap) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850380/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850380/</guid><description>Podcast Description The RHOSLC reunion looks are here and it's giving... rainbow!
Teddi and Tamra breakdown this week's RHOSLC and RHOP episodes. Plus, Tamra has a bone to pick with someone from the Vanderpump Rules cast...
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Ts Presents: Ay Por Favor: Brofessor’s of the Year | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850378/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850378/</guid><description>Podcast Description Your favorite besties are back as they revisit their FIRST EVER live show in Boca Raton, Fl last weekend and all the fun they had. Alexia and Marysol can barely contain their excitement as they weigh in on Taylor Swift being named Time’s Person of the Year and their predictions with her relationship to Travis Kelce. They also dish on Taylor’s bestie, Selena Gomez’ new relationship with Benny Blanco and how they feel she needs to prioritize her happiness.</description></item><item><title>TTTT Takeover with TOM SANDOVAL &amp; TOM SCHWARTZ | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850377/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850377/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Four Ts are together and leaving no crumbs behind!
Teddi and Tamra don't hold back as they hit Tom and Tom with the hard-hitting questions everybody wants to know.
For Part 2 of this interview, listen to Everybody Loves Tom!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Phantom of the Opera… Featuring Julia (RHOBH &amp; RHOM Recap) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850376/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850376/</guid><description>Podcast Description Denise is back on RHOBH and the Two Ts question if she's trying to get her diamond back. Plus, is Sutton trying to fill Lisa Rinna's shoes?!
Then, Julia is singing opera while Alexia was making excuses to avoid being roommates.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Xanax, Bathtubs &amp; Pies (RHOP &amp; RHOSLC Recap) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850375/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850375/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is Teddi being replaced?! The ladies are setting the rumors straight!
Then, is Meredith running the show from behind the scenes on RHOSLC? And is Robyn protecting Juan and his cheating on RHOP?!
Plus… we all have had bad license pictures, but Teddi and Tamra might take the cake on this one!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Two Jersey Js with Jackie Goldschneider and Jennifer Fessler | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850373/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 17:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850373/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two Housewives, two BIG personalities, Two Jersey J's! Jackie Goldschneider and Jennifer Fessler join the Two T's family to spill some east coast tea! From menopause to making the most of your 40's and 50's.
Follow these fabulous women as they navigate family, friendships, and even frenemies! Chasing that spark in your life, motherhood, men, good sex, and finding satisfaction in everything.If being a Real Housewife feels overwhelming at times, be a friend to one.</description></item><item><title>Two Ts Presents: Ozempic Opposites Attract | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850374/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 15:12:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850374/</guid><description>Podcast Description The housewives universe is exploding with the use of Ozempic so Jackie and Jenn dive right into what makes them compete opposites on their views of the drug.
Jenn gets real about how she landed in the hospital from taking semiglutides. And Jackie shares her fears and worries about Jenn using it.
The ladies don’t hold back and discuss it ALL on our first episode of Two Jersey J’s!</description></item><item><title>Two Ts on the Town | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850370/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 20:54:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850370/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi and Tamra have had an eventful week filled with red carpets, housewives and tons of tea to spill!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Blast from the Beverly Hills Past (RHOBH &amp; RHOM Recap) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850371/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850371/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two former Beverly Hills housewives make an appearance in this week’s episode.. Then, if Kyle isn’t allowed to have a judgment, then why is Sutton allowed to have judgment about Kyle’s new lifestyle?
Plus, Teddi and Tamra question Larsa’s comments towards Guerdy. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>You’re dressed like a pickle (RHOP &amp; RHOSLC Recap) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850372/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850372/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been a couple weeks since BravoCon, but has Teddi and Tamra’s relationship changed since?? Then, the drama on RHOP feels childish… who is keeping track of followers on Facebook?!
Plus, the Two Ts weigh in on Lisa and Whitney’s argument on RHOSLC. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Ts Presents: Ay Por Favor: Love Hath No Fury… | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850369/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850369/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tune in as your favorite besties catch up on their Thanksgiving activities, dish on Linda Evangelista and finding love when you’re of a “certain age”, and share their hot take on the latest allegations against Sean Combs, aka Puff Daddy/P. Diddy/Diddy/Love/Puffy etc. BTW - If you’re in South Florida, be sure to catch Alexia and Marysol at the Studio at Mizner Park, LIVE on Saturday 12/9. Tickets on sale at ticketmaster.</description></item><item><title>Name 'Em, My Love (RHOBH &amp; RHOM Recap) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850368/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850368/</guid><description>Podcast Description Looks like we have a new housewives catchphrase thanks to Sutton... NAME 'EM!
The ladies are loving Erika’s authenticity on this season of RHOBH, but is Sutton suddenly insufferable?
Then on RHOM, is Adrianna jealous of Alexia’s new lifestyle? And why are we fighting over farts?!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Quiet Woman isn’t so Quiet (RHOP &amp; RHOSLC Recap) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850367/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850367/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Two Ts break down the latest headlines, including a former RHOC cast member seen with John Janssen, Lenny’s fiancé’s encounter with Teddi at BravoCon, plus, our very own Tamra is on Variety’s 40 Top Most Powerful Women list! Then, they dive into this week’s RHOP and RHOSLC.
It’s all on a new episode of Two Ts! See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>TWOTS Flashback: RHOBH 111 &amp; 112 | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850364/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850364/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi is out sick, but RHOBH OG Camille Meyer joins Tamra to recap season 1 episodes 11 &amp;amp; 12, and it’s the ultimate throwback.
What was Camille’s friendship with Kyle really like and are they still friends? Plus, did Camille always want to be on the show? Listen to a new TWOTS Flashback to find out! See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Only 6 Hours… (RHOBH &amp; RHOM Recap) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850365/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850365/</guid><description>Podcast Description After watching this week’s RHOBH, we can’t tell if we like this new Erika or miss the old Erika.
Then, Teddi has a confession to make and it is about Garcelle…
Plus, we have to discuss Larsa’s reaction to Guerdy’s cancer diagnosis.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What’s in the Vida Tequila? (RHOSLC &amp; RHOP Recap) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850363/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850363/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi may be under the weather but she is coming in hot with her opinion on Monica’s mom, Linda.
Also, should Lisa Barlow pursue a career in rapping? Plus, which housewife of Potomac is Tamra most alike?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ay Por Favor: Lo Que Pasa en Vegas… | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850362/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850362/</guid><description>Podcast Description Your favorite Miami Housewives are back and still buzzing from BravoCon as they discuss the highs, the lows and LOTS of behind the scenes chisme you won’t get anywhere else *fire emoji*. They also get personal as they answer some burning questions from their AMAZING fans about RHOM, life on and off the show, and of course, their friendship. So pour those cockies and make sure they’re filled to the rim, because this one is a doozy!</description></item><item><title>Two Ts Getting the Tea with ALEX BASKIN | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850360/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850360/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex Baskin, the executive producer of RHOBH, RHOC, Vanderpump Rules, Botched and more, joins the Two Ts to discuss all the behind the scenes of the housewives franchise! (The guy in charge!)
Then, Teddi and Alex dig into why Teddi was fired!
Plus, Alex shares a unique perspective on Scandoval!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Take Your Pants Off (RHOBH &amp; RHOM Recap) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850359/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850359/</guid><description>Podcast Description The ladies of Beverly Hills go to Magic Mike… looks like wearing pants is not the move.
Then on RHOM, is Lisa moving too fast with her boyfriend after her split from Lenny?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Ts Getting the Tea with HIBISCUS | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850356/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 06:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850356/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Masked Singer revealed a housewife… Tune in to find out who it is! See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>That’s A Low Blow (RHOSLC &amp; RHOP Recap) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850357/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 20:10:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850357/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s RHOSLC tugged at our heartstrings! Teddi and Tamra feel for Monica and her situation with her mom.
Also, was it a low blow to comment on Lisa’s age?!
Plus, is Teddi a little biased while watching RHOP after talking to Robyn at BravoCon?? The ladies break down the season premiere.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What Happens in Vegas, Doesn’t Stay in Vegas | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850358/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 21:19:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850358/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Two Ts are back home to recap BravoCon. Who had to sneak out of the Two Ts party to avoid their cast mates?
Plus, Which househusband was the life of the party?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Shep Rose: Live from BravoCon (Southern Charm) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi is joined by her childhood friend, Shep Rose! Have Teddi and Shep ever kissed???
Shep explains why he won’t ask Brynn Whitfield on a date and what kind of partner he is looking for.
Plus, Shep explains why men cheat…
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kelly Bensimon: Live from BravoCon (RHONY) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850002/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kelly tells Teddi what her biggest regret is from her time on the show.
Plus, she teases RHONY Legacy and we are already counting down the days!!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Larsa Pippen and Marcus Jordan: Live from BravoCon (RHOM) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850003/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Larsa and Marcus talk about their love, Traitors and the new season of RHOM. Plus, is Larsa still mad at Teddi? Tune in to find out…
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nicole Martin: Live from BravoCon (RHOM) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850004/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi starts off the podcast by helping Nicole pick out a name for Baby No. 2! Plus, Nicole is not holding back and answers all of Teddi’s questions about Season 6 of Miami.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Robyn Dixon: Live from BravoCon (RHOP) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850005/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi tells Robyn which one of her castmates snubbed her at BravoCon.
Plus, Robyn opens up about her marriage to Juan.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dorinda Medley: Live from BravoCon (RHONY) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850006/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dorinda and Teddi find out that they are disliked by the same person…. Will they make it nice with this housewife at BravoCon?
Plus, Dorinda gets us excited for RHONY Legacy!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Frank Catania and Brittany Mattessich: Live from BravoCon (RHONJ) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850007/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850007/</guid><description>Podcast Description The newly engaged couple is here! Frank and Brittany tell the Two Ts all the wedding details they have so far.
Plus, do Frank and Brittany or Larsa and Marcus have more sex?? See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Erin Lichy: Live from BravoCon (RHONY) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850008/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 21:14:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi is stirring the pot and tells Erin who called her a fake snake. Plus, Erin says who she is most nervous to run into at BravoCon. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kyle Richards: Live from BravoCon (RHOBH) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850009/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi and Kyle breakdown BravoCon so far including who Kyle is least looking forward to seeing.
Plus, Kyle opens up how she really feels towards Mauricio and Emma Slater’s relationship.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Caroline Brooks: Live from BravoCon (RHODubai) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850010/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 06:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850010/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Two Ts are stirring the pot yet again at BravoCon… Caroline Brooks heard what one of her castmates had to say about her and is here to set the record straight.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chanel Ayan: Live from BravoCon (RHODubai) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850011/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 05:34:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chanel Ayan is heated after watching the RHONY reunion and has her cousin, Ubah’s back!
Then, she shares who she thinks are the fake snakes on RHONY.
Plus, Jeff Lewis crashes the podcast. Find out what he is heated about…
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Caroline Stanbury and Sergio Carrallo: Live from BravoCon (RHODubai) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850012/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 04:21:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Caroline Stanbury and Sergio Carrallo are here to tell us what to expect on Season 2 of Dubai.
Plus, Caroline gives her opinion on the newest addition to the franchise.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jackie Goldschneider &amp; Jennifer Fessler: Live from BravoCon (RHONJ) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850013/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 01:55:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850013/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Jersey J’s join Teddi for a BIG announcement!!
Plus, they weigh in on the BravoCon panels changing last minute.
Everything you're missing at BravoCon, is on our pod! See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dave Quinn: Live from BravoCon | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850014/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 22:09:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dave Quinn has the inside scoop on Ramona Singer his take on the reality reckoning.
Everything you're missing on in Vegas, is on our pod! See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Whitney Rose &amp; Angie Katsanevas: Live From BravoCon (RHOSLC) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Whitney tells the truth about her marriage to Justin and how they are doing today, Angie K sets the record straight on her husband, and they give their honest opinion on Monica and Meredith.
Everything you're missing at BravoCon, is on our pod! See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Monica Garcia: Live from BravoCon (RHOSLC) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850016/</guid><description>Podcast Description The newest RHOSLC housewife sits down with the Two Ts live from BravoCon and opens up about her relationship with her mother, who she trusts the most on the show and more!
Everything you're missing at BravoCon, is on our pod! See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Ts Getting the Tea with LUANN DE LESSEPS (Part 3) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 19:27:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850017/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Countess is back with the TWOTS!
Luann weighs in on the latest Ramona news and shares advice she has for Shannon Beador.
Plus, which Bravolebrity is Luann trying to get set up with at BravoCon this weekend?! See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tam-Rat (RHOBH &amp; RHOM Recap) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850018/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Snitches don’t get stitches… they get tattoos in Beverly Hills! Is Kyle right about jinxing your marriage by getting your husband’s name tattoo’d? Plus, Tamra reveals a tattoo she got for her ex.
Ay por favor! What’s going on with Alexia and Marysol this season on RHOM?! Is their friendship on the rocks?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Old Cackling Hag (RHONY &amp; RHOSLC Recap) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi is getting to the bottom of the meaning behind “old cackling hag” and calling PK Kemsley for his expertise. Then, is Andy getting backlash for casting influencers on the new RHONY?
Plus, Eddie Judge crashes the pod. Are him and Tamra still in the honeymoon phase? Find out what he has to say about watching back RHOC!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Ts and an E | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850020/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 19:26:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850020/</guid><description>Podcast Description RHOC’s Emily Simpson dropped in to help the Two Ts recap the latest headlines… and it’s juicy!
Who JUST started drama with Tamra on Instagram??
And what is the latest with Tamra and Jenn?!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ay Por Favor: The Internet is a Scary Place | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850021/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is off to a spOoOky start as the Brofessor’s talk about Halloween and the ghost in Marysol’s home - QUE MIEDO! They also discuss Britney Spears’ latest memoir and the bombshells dropped about her previous relationship with Justin Timberlake...Plus Sofia Vergara and Bad Bunny low-key flirting on Instagram, and a daughter giving her father the silent treatment for not coughing up cash for her lavish wedding - QUE MALCRIADA!</description></item><item><title>Teddi’s in the Hot Seat (RHOBH Recap) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 20:31:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi is back in the Clubhouse and Tamra is giving her sh*t for her shadiness.
Then, the Two Ts are back to recap the Season 13 premiere of RHOBH. Are you ready to see all the drama unfold this season?!?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Don’t Call Me Sweetie (RHONY Recap) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 04:35:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850023/</guid><description>Podcast Description From Bethenny’s celebrity dinner to Lisa and Erika at the club… we got all the headlines in today’s show!
Also, is it just us or did Ubah come in too hot at the reunion?! Plus, find out what the ladies think of RHONY this season. Who do they think was the star of the season?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Am I the Drama? (RHONY &amp; RHOSLC Recap) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 05:25:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850024/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Two Ts are finally back together and better than ever, but apparently the podcast causes problems… Are we the drama?!
Then, are the women of RHONY hiding their lives? What’s the point of being a housewife if you’re not going to be open?
Plus, is Monica making a scene just for the cameras on RHOSLC? Or is she always this outrageous?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ay Por Favor: Tremendo Bombshell | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850025/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850025/</guid><description>Podcast Description If this episode were a person, Will Smith would more than likely slap them, because Alexia &amp;amp; Marysol go IN on Jada's memoir. But that's not all...tune in as Alexia and Marysol share their thoughts on the latest RHOM Season 6 trailer, Tamra telling Andy Cohen to STFU during the RHOC reunion and so much more...
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Judge Returns (RHOC Reunion Part 2) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850026/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Was Shannon really the “most authentic” this season? Did filming with John ultimately lead to the end of her relationship?
Plus, was Tamra out of line for snapping at Andy?
The RHOC reunion conversation continues…
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Judge Returns (RHOC Reunion Part 1) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850027/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 01:46:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tamra’s back and here we go! The reunion came in hot and Tamra’s fired up to talk about it.
What REALLY went down between Tamra and Heather? And what did Tamra think of her behavior this season? Then, Tamra explains the backstory of her friendship with Jenn and how it all went sideways. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>First Class Sandwich (RHONY &amp; RHOSLC Recap) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 19:19:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are the ladies of RHONY too invested in Jessel and Pavit's love life? Are the husbands getting too involved? Teddi and Emily are invested in Pavit's trip to Vietnam to earn points.
Then on RHOSLC, Angie and Shawn's relationship is shown in a better light. And, Is Linda crossing the line telling Monica how to raise her daughters? See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Pour Some Lemonade On Me | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850029/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 00:27:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850029/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are analyzing the RHOBH and RHOM trailers and revealing secrets.
Shannon is getting treatment after her DUI arrest, but what does it mean for the future Tres Amigas shows? Should she continue?
Plus, what in the world is going on with that Jenn Pedranti post?!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Stop the Shaman (RHONY &amp; RHOSLC Recap) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850030/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are Teddi and Emily spoiling their children. How much is too much? Can the shamans and sound baths please come to an end? We’ve seen (and heard) enough!
Plus, is Meredith trying to stay out of drama in SLC by not naming names? Or is it making matters worse! See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ay Por Favor - Cuffing Season | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850031/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fall is in the air, y el cuerpo lo sabe… Alexia and Marysol dish on a few of the latest saucy celeb sightings that have everyone buzzing, Leo DiCaprio’s dating dilemma, and Mick Jagger’s plans for his fortune once his ‘stone’ stops "rolling".
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We're All Sh*t Stirrers | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850032/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 19:22:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi and Emily are breaking down the biggest Bravo headlines .
Bethenny Frankel and NeNe Leakes controversial interview, Tom Sandoval shirtless in his podcast ad, and the extremely confusing RHONY reunion looks. Plus, who texted Emily trying to ruin her marriage?!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Ts Getting the Tea with SANYA RICHARDS-ROSS | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850033/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sanya Richards-Ross is clearing up those RHOA rumors! Is the network rebooting the franchise with a new cast? What do the current ladies think?
Then, Sanya opens up about her miscarriage, why she decided to share her experience on the show and how she felt finding out she’s pregnant again.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Just Try the Salad (RHOC Recap) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850034/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850034/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's the RHOC season finale! And, Teddi is to blame for Tamra’s fight with Heather.
Are Heather and Tamra two alphas going at it for top dog??
Plus, where’s Teddi's orange?! She's been on this season more than Vicki! See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Don't Talk Sexy to Me (RHONY &amp; RHOSLC Recap) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850035/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850035/</guid><description>Podcast Description There's drama in Jersey, and Teddi and Emily Simpson are dishing!
Jessel's making her checklist and sharing it twice! But, this cell phone debacle is getting out of hand.
Plus, is Monica forcing relationships with the other Housewives in RHOSLC?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Pastor Bailey (RHOC Recap) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850036/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tamra and Jenn are back to square one with their arguments about Ryan... is this getting old?!
Is Heather simply mean? Or is she just unaware?
Plus, Vicki came in HOT! Was she out of line with her comments about Ryan?!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>From Erin to Karen (RHONY &amp; RHOSLC Recap) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850037/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily Simpson has entered the chat and she's not holding back!
Teddi and Emily dig into this week’s RHONY and made a shocking correlation -- Shane walked so Pavit can run! Also, did Erin go from Queen Bee to… a Karen?
It’s starting to get icy on RHOSLC but we’re all wondering how Angie got herself a snowflake?
Plus, Emily gets real and settles rumors about her fitness journey and fitting into the OC Housewife standards.</description></item><item><title>Ay Por Favor: Squirrel Talk | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850038/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 04:38:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Your favorite housewives let loose as they dish on Ben getting caught in a very affectionate embrace with the wrong Jen, Taylor and another ‘swift’ transition to another man, and Sopranos star Drea De Matteo joining Only Fans… Ay Dios Mio!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Breaking News from the OC | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850039/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 21:22:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi, Tamra and Cynthia are discussing the shocking breaking news regarding Shannon Beador.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Snuffleupagus (RHOC Recap) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850040/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 04:18:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi gets very emotional detailing her recent biopsy and melanoma. The ladies of RHOC are in Mexico and the drama is coming in HOT! It’s always a good time when Vicki's around! But, who’s the ultimate pot stirrer this episode? Hint: it starts with a T and ends with Amra! See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ice Ice Angie (RHOSLC Recap) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850041/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why are Heather and Meredith trying to ice Angie out this season?!
Teddi thinks Whitney has changed…is she catering to the fans rather than being her true self?
And, the fashion in Salt Lake City needs to be discussed. Teddi and Tamra reveal their best and worst dressed lists!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Long Lost Cousins (RHONY &amp; RHOA Recap) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850042/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 02:02:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tamra is back from filming the RHOC reunion! In a shocking discovery, she has a cousin she didn't know about... and it's a housewife!
We have one word to describe this week's RHOA …AWKWARD!
Plus, are the girls just really jealous of Kandi? What were Ralph’s motives? And, Teddi and Tamra critique the moment Drew serenaded Ralph... eek!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Ts Getting the Tea with JESSEL TAANK | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850043/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jessel Taank is setting the record straight on a ton of rumors!! Did she move to NY just to be on the show?? Is her marriage on the rocks? What REALLY happened at the Rainbow Room red carpet?
Plus, Jessel and Teddi have an honest discussion about their struggles with IVF.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Blame It on the Alcohol | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850044/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Before jumping into this week's RHOC recap, Teddi and Cynthia discuss Atlanta! Did Kandi go too far with Drew? Does someone hype up Marlo before her confessionals?
Then, RHOC is back in Mexico which means… Tequila!
Drunken words are sober thoughts – we’re looking at you, Emily!!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Salty as Ever | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850045/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850045/</guid><description>Podcast Description RHOSLC is back!
Teddi and Tamra reveal why they love the new housewife... Jen Shah's fired assistant, Monica! Mary is back but why is she listed as "Meredith's Friend"?!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Titillating | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850046/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 02:30:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi addresses a rumor going ‘round…
And, we deep dive into a Housewives husband getting boo'd at a softball game... Teddi and Tamra are breaking down all the headlines!
Was it just us or was there a lot of cleavage at the RHOA reunion?! Plus, Erin is the ultimate pot stirrer on RHONY!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ay Por Favor: Living La Dolce Vita? | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850047/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850047/</guid><description>Podcast Description The besties are back for more, this time it’s all eyes on Italy, as Alexia and Marysol discuss Kanye getting caught with his pants down on a river taxi in Venice, and a clip that has gone viral of an Italian wedding where the groom exposes his “bride to be” for infidelity - in front of all their guests. Mamma Mia - QUE ESCANDALO! See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>We Were On A Break | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850048/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 22:21:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi and Cynthia need a lesson from Heather Dubrow on manifesting...
And what does it mean to be on a “break”?! Was Ryan in the wrong?
Then, Teddi made an appearance on last night's RHOC and she’s stirring the pot, to say the least!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Dirtiest Reunion That Hasn't Happened Yet | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850049/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 01:50:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Everyone saw Taylor Armstrong's paparazzi moment... Now she's calling in to tell her side of the story!
RHOA has come to the end, but what are Teddi and Tamra's thoughts on Drew and Ralph's relationship?
Plus, Teddi gets emotional while discussing Jessel and Sanya opening up about miscarriages and IVF.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bet It All on Blonde with ERIKA JAYNE | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850050/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi and Tamra are live from Las Vegas with Erika Jayne! What REALLY happened with the Fox Force Five group text?
Does she miss Lisa Rinna on the new season of RHOBH?
Is Erika seeing a new man? And, she gives us an update on Tom! Plus, Erika addresses the comments about her menopause weight loss. It’s the tell all of tell alls. What happens in Vegas, stays on the Pod!</description></item><item><title>No Tacos for You | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850051/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850051/</guid><description>Podcast Description RHOC is serving up the juicy drama!
Teddi and Cynthia’s opinions have changed about Ryan!! Do you agree?
They also have a bone to pick with Shannon…
Plus, Cynthia reveals who she almost hired as her assistant! See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Show Me Your Best O | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850052/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Crappie Lake has come to an end, RHOA is almost at the finish line, and RHONY is just getting started!
Find out which RHONY star Tamra relates to and why.
And, in a turn of events... Let's hear Teddi &amp;amp; Tamra give their best O’s.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Wasted, But Not Naked | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850053/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 01:57:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi and Tamra share their OPINIONS on Bethenny Frankel's interview with Rachel Leviss. As a result, Tamra reveals what "naked wasted" really means.
Then, what does Tamra think of Lala Kent's shade towards this season of RHOC?
And, could it be Kenya's last season on RHOA?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ay Por Favor: Great Minds (Sometimes) Think Alike | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850054/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Grab those cockies and make sure they’re stiff - your favorite housewives are back for more chisme in spanglish. This episode is off to a HEATED start as Alexia &amp;amp; Marysol chime in on Britney Spears’ divorce from Sam Asghari, Doja Cat dissing her (declining) fan base, how Rachel Leviss (aka Raquel) needs to Vander-PUMP the breaks on wanting to cash in on Scandoval, y mucho mas!
See omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>Hand Jobs are so 2003 | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850055/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 22:49:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850055/</guid><description>Podcast Description RHONY keeps on delivering! But, this week had us questioning… are hand jobs in or out?
Find out why Whitney cried watching this week’s RHONY.
Then, we visit Atlanta and Crappie Lake.Why didn’t Martell pay for Sheree’s Birthday Dinner?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Every Rose Has Its Thorn | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850056/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:59:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Whitney Rose is jumping in the TWOTS hot seat and she is spilling all the SLC tea.
Find out which SLC Housewife blocked her and who she goes up against in the upcoming season. And, is there truth to the rumor that Whitney and Justin’s marriage is in trouble!?
Plus, whose sex scenes were worse — Whitney or Tamra’s?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Ts Getting the Tea with GINA KIRSCHENHEITER | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850057/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gina vs Shannon
Gina vs Heather
Gina’s getting in to it and giving her side of the story!
What’s true and what’s fake news?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nipple Licker | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850058/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi has a bone to pick with Cynthia... She threw some shade on another podcast!
Teddi and Cynthia break down Vicki's non-negotiables in the latest RHOC episode. Whose nipple would Cynthia lick?! Plus, a lot went down between Andy Cohen and Jeff Lewis on WWHL last night and we have the inside intel! See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trimming the Bushes | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850059/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 01:15:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850059/</guid><description>Podcast Description RHONY is a breath of fresh air! Is it healthy to stay friends with your ex?
The drama between Marlo and Drew on RHOA continues… whose side are you on? The Twots agree we need Cynthia back as a regular!!
Plus, a certain headline has the Twots revealing whether trimmed bushes are in or out. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ay Por Favor: From Lenny to Lizzo | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850060/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Your favorite bro’s are finally back together, to serve up some hot goss! Marysol and Alexia catch up over their recent romantic getaways with their beaus right before sharing their thoughts on Lenny Hochstein’s engagement, Gerard Pique moving his mistress into his home, Ariana being a Grande homewrecker, and finish off with Lizzo and the banana show fiasco. Prepare yourselves, porque EL CHISME ESTA BUENISIMO!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Tricky Vicki | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850061/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 00:26:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi weighs in on Vicki's WWHL appearance and it’s a questionable review. Cynthia spills hot tea revealing what she knows about Drew and LaToya. Eddie Judge is doing all the dirty work on this week's RHOC! He needs to hold an orange!
Plus, Ryan’s leopard collar… we have some thoughts.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Big Orange Popsicle | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850062/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 19:03:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Let’s talk RHONY! Was it ok for Jenna to leave Erin’s house in the middle of the night? Teddi relates to this all too well and has some thoughts…
Are we still loving Crappie Lake? The Twots are divided.
Plus, Tamra tells a story about a Popsicle no one saw coming…
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Congrats to Your Mistress | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850063/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:23:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lenny Hochstein is engaged… yet, still married?!
And, Tamra unfollows another Housewife. Woah.
Plus, the RHOA reunion seating chart is here!Why is Kandi in the 3rd seat again? The Twots have their theories.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lyons, Testicles &amp; Bravo Oh My! | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850064/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jenna Lyons fan club alert!! Teddi and Tamra are loving Jenna on RHONY!
Find out which RHONY newbie is a combination of Teddi and… Heather Dubrow!
ATL is getting spicy. The Twots deep dive in to what actually happened between Drew and LaToya. Did they really make out?
Plus, we don't want Crappie Lake to end! Should Bravo make shows with less drama and more fun!?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>When Tamra Gives you Lemons… | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850065/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 22:01:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tamra is back from WWHL and she’s got A LOT to say. What did Jenn and Ryan do that made her cringe? Should Vicki get her orange back??
We also have to address Teresa and Tamra wearing the same outfit…
Plus, details on a hate text Teddi sent… or did she?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Watch Me NeNe | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850066/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cynthia is responding to NeNe Leakes! Are they still friends? And how does she feel about what NeNe said?!
The drama between Jenn, Tamra and Heather continues this week on RHOC.
Cynthia questions if there are any other hotties in the OC besides Ryan. Plus, Teddi is shocked by all the waxing. And, a slip and slide means one thing... Tamra's top is for sure coming off!
See omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>Ay Por Favor: Peter Covers for Marysol | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850067/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alexia’s son, Peter sits in for Marysol while she’s away renewing her vows - AY QUE CUTE!
In this special episode, Peter and Alexia discuss deep family issues. From his feelings about growing up on tv, to their reactions when they first watched Cocaine Cowboys, and all the hard lessons learned along the way.
But wait, just because Marysol isn’t around doesn’t mean there won’t be any CHISME! This momma - son duo dish on everything from Hailey Bieber thirst traps, to Jonah Hill’s ex posting personal text messages, to Joe Manganiello’s cold Birthday wish for Sofia Vergara foreshadowing their recent split, y mucho mas con madre y hijo!</description></item><item><title>Don’t Throw a Napkin at Me!! | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850068/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850068/</guid><description>Podcast Description The episode is finally here — the Napkin Throw!
Find out why Cynthia wasn’t too happy with Tamra.
Is it better to be best friends with the Housewives Villain or to stay far, far away? Teddi and Cynthia discuss.
Plus, Teddi ran into one of Cynthia's RHOA castmates and it didn’t go over too well… See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>New York State of Mind | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850069/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850069/</guid><description>Podcast Description After 2 years, RHONY is BACK!!
New girls, new drama… it’s New York!!
Is Erin the new Bethenny Frankel?
Was cheese gate the dumbest thing ever?
Can YOU eat 5-6 bananas a day?
The Twots pick their favorite and least favorite newbie.
And, of course, we visit Crappie Lake and it does not disappoint.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Threesomes, Tiffs and Talking Sh** | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850070/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:24:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tamra found herself in a very sh*tty situation this morning and she’s coming in hot!
RHOA is getting goooood!
Finally, Drew is back in the mix and Teddi and Tamra dissect her emotional fight with Sheree.
Plus, the Twots worry that Kenya’s new fling, Roi, might be in it for the wrong reasons…
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Don’t Mess with Mama Bear | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850071/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 22:55:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi is completely outraged!! Find out why you don’t want to mess with her today.
RHOC is getting better each week! Teddi and Cynthia are loving Tamra and Shannon back together, but what’s up with Heather’s pity party?
And of course, we need to discuss what Garcelle said on WWHL…
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Ts Getting the Tea with ERIN LICHY | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850072/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850072/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a two year hiatus, RHONY is back and on fire with a brand new cast! Erin Lichy joins the Twots to spill the tea on the season premiere.
Which OG RHONY Housewife took Erin out to lunch?!
Plus, Erin compares the new cast to the OG cast and you’ll never guess which two Housewives are related!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>In Twots We Trust | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850073/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 01:09:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850073/</guid><description>Podcast Description The least trustworthy Housewives... experts compiled a list, find out if Teddi and Tamra agree. The truth will be revealed.
There’s a rumor that Margaret Josephs is she scared of Louie and is refusing to film with him… we go directly to her to get you your answer.
Plus, we break down the first two episodes of Crappie Lake. Find out what made Teddi and Tamra pee their pants laughing.</description></item><item><title>Ay Por Favor: Ask Us Anything (Otra Vez) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850074/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pour yourself a cockie - It’s time for another episode of ‘Ask Us Anything’, where Alexia and Marysol take turns answering some saucy questions from beautiful listeners like you. This time, they answer questions and offer advice on friendships, relationships, mental health, y mucho, mucho mas.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Not the D*ck Pic, Please | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850075/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850075/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a shocking turn of events, Teddi is asking for an olive branch from Heather.
Teddi and Cynthia unpack the Jennifer d*ck pic drama… do you believe her?
Plus, Cynthia shares what she got from a random man at a gas station. Eww!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The BIG Elephant in the Room | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850076/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 01:22:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850076/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Twots are back from some much-needed time off, but that didn't stop the Bravo news cycle! Yes, we are addressing the BIG elephant in the room… Kyle and Mauricio. Speaking of the D word… Kim and Kroy called off their divorce?
Plus, we’re getting some OC tea from Tamra.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ay Por Favor: Pásame el Menthol! | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850077/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 03:17:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hold the cockies and grab the vivaporu, because the ladies are back for more (this time with a cold - pardon the stuffiness). In this episode, they talk about a “new” dialect of English &amp;amp; Spanish (aka spanglish), more Shakira/Pique drama, out of pocket concert goers y mucho mas. Para que vean, not even a cold can keep your favorite housewives away from a little chisme.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Block or Mute? | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850078/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:09:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cynthia Winfrey (aka Cynthia Bailey) is reporting for duty and spilling the tea on which Housewives she muted on Instagram. Eek!!
RHOC is getting juicy!! Was Tamra stirring the pot and was Heather condescending by saying Taylor's play is "cute"? Plus, what does everyone do in Cynthia's house that drives her absolutely nuts?!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Teddi Turned Down | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850079/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 21:54:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850079/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a never-ending feud, Tamra tells Teddi someone does NOT want her at the Tres Amigas show. Tamra teases why this season is the BEST of RHOC ever.
Then, we head to Atlanta… Did the Twots uncover signs of Drew and Ralph’s split in this episode? Did they *Already Know*?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Ts and a FRANK | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850080/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Frankly, RHONJ Reunion left us with many MANY questions. So, our favorite (ex) husband, Frank Catania, is clearing the air.
Let’s be Frank, we uncover the truth behind Bo Dietl, Teresa, the Gorga’s, and Margaret. What’s really going on with Frank and Louie? Find out what happened when they met up recently. On a lighter note, is Frank still living with David?
AND, who will get married first — Frank or Dolores?</description></item><item><title>The Final CUT | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850081/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 20:39:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850081/</guid><description>Podcast Description We hate to see CUT go, but why isn’t Shannon apologizing to Tamra too? And, in a shocking change of opinion, we are totally loving Emily this season!
Cynthia Bailey gives us all the BTS of being an actress and how “hoohaas” come in handy. Would she be a better teacher than Heather?
Plus, we find out from Cynthia which RHOA housewives will NEVER be friends again!!
See omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Separation Anxiety with Larsa and Marcus | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850082/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Larsa Pippen and Marcus Jordan have Separation Anxiety. They finally found each other and now they're ready to be brutally honest with you about life, love, sex, and 16 year age gaps!
Larsa and Marcus share their private thoughts about being in the public eye. What is life really like at home with the Pippen/Jordan's? They won't hold back about all the juicy things happening, even when it’s about them- their friends- and even their haters.</description></item><item><title>Overrated Housewives | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850083/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 00:47:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tamra is setting the record straight about her beef with Teresa. And, this is the last time she’s ever going to talk about it! Teddi and Tamra dissect this week’s RHOA and it wasn’t all that Gucci. If not for Kandi this season, there would be nothing! Plus, the Twots chime in on Kenya wanting to have another baby. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>PI’s and Pop Tarts | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850084/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 01:14:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tamra shares the REAL story behind her sit down with Shannon.
With zero resolution amongst the cast, the final episode of the RHONJ Reunion left the Twots sad. Should Melissa and Teresa be put on pause? Can Teresa be on the show WITHOUT Louie?!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>F*ck a Duck | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850085/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tamra’s emotions are running high in this week’s RHOC episode. And the moment we all have been waiting for… Shannon and Tamra confront each other at lunch. We dissect it all!!
Plus, RHOA continues to be divided and Cynthia has answers as to why and how it can be fixed.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ay Por Favor: Settle Down | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850086/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alexia and Marysol share stories of their mother’s journeys to the US from Cuba. The chisme gets hot as they dish on Hollywood's favorite ‘viejos verdes’ (Al Pacino &amp;amp; Robert De Niro) and their expecting girlfriends, whether or not it's too soon for Kanye to be introducing his kids to his latest love, and Lionel Messi making his move to Miami’s MLS team.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>The Gnat Rat | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850087/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 01:56:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850087/</guid><description>Podcast Description What’s really happening in the OC with David and Lesley Beador? Eek, it’s not good.
Why was WWHL more interesting than this week’s RHOA?
Find out why the Twots are not pleased.
We want to see Kandi activated!!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Watch What Happens to Tamra | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850088/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 18:51:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850088/</guid><description>Podcast Description With her first episode back on RHOC, Tamra is filled with a bunch of emotions!
Tamra gives us all the BTS of WWHL from last night including all the Teresa drama.
Dorinda had something to say about Tamra’s tagline and confronts her about it.
Plus, the Twots give their take on the Vanderpump Rules finale. Their take will surprise you.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>RHOC Season 17 Premieres | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850089/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tamra has returned and does not disappoint!! The new RHOC season is ON and Tamra is back in FULL FORCE! Teddi’s got Cynthia Bailey subbing in to breakdown the first episode.
Sandy living in the casita, the most awkward hug ever between Tamra and Shannon, and the new girl, Jennifer.
And in a BH sidebar, how does Teddi feel about Cynthia’s friendship with Camille and Denise? Uh oh…</description></item><item><title>Master Manipulator | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850090/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850090/</guid><description>Podcast Description RHONJ Reunion Part 2 was even messier than the first! Nobody is taking ownership, especially Teresa, who is playing the blame game on everyone else. We are OVER it.
And, what is with those prank calls? Was it a set up with Margaret’s son? They happen more often than you think in the Housewife universe, and the Twots explain why.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Photo worth a Thousand Words | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850091/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 23:54:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850091/</guid><description>Podcast Description RHOC’s new season is premiering this week, and drama is ALREADY brewing. We’re getting to the bottom of that photo of Shannon and David Beador.
And, why does premiere week have Tamra feeling totally stressed?
Plus, something is missing from RHOA this season. Do they need a cast shake up... maybe Kim Zolciak?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Queen of Denial | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850092/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Find out why the first episode of the RHONJ Reunion has the Twots worried about the show's future. The anger and aggression between Melissa and Teresa is getting so INTENSE. Is Teresa the Queen of Denial? Plus, Rachel and Danielle’s fight has taken center stage, but do we even care?! The Twots give their *opinions* on if they should even return.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Don’t judge a book by its cover | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850093/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 23:04:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tamra’s OC intro is revealed! It’s hot and it’s feisty!
The TWOTS debate which housewife is the voice of reason for ATL and the OC? Their answer will shock you.
Plus, we get the tea on who Erika Jayne’s mystery guy really is.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ay Por Favor: Ask Us Anything | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850094/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get to know Alexia &amp;amp; Marysol like never before. They’ll answer questions about their friendship, their relationships with their hubbies, cultural traditions, beauty secrets, y mucho, mucho mas! Per usual, cockies strictly enforced. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>This is Hairy | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850095/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 01:25:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jersey, Jersey, Jersey… WOW!
Teddi and Tamra are unhinged after watching the RHONJ Reunion trailer. The Twots are dissecting every crumb!!
And what about Teresa’s wedding?! The hair… the drama… and all the lies!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Matchmaker | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850096/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 01:36:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former EP of both RHONJ &amp;amp; RHOA, Carlos King, is here and he has a bone to pick with the Twots.
As we recap RHOA, find out what role Carlos played in Kim Zolciak meeting Kroy. PLUS, what REALLY happened between Kenya and Martell in those DMs.
And, thoughts on the future of RHONJ and if it includes Teresa, Melissa or… neither.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Ts Getting the Tea with ANDY COHEN (PART TWO) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850097/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850097/</guid><description>Podcast Description The King is here dishing everything!! Everything!! Tamra and Teddi confront Andy for firing them.
Lisa Rinna, Teresa Guidice, Kyle Richards, LVP, Mary Cosby, Denise Richards, Caroline Manzo, Garcelle Beauvais, Kim Zolciak, Phaedra Parks, John Mayer… we’re talking about it ALL.
Plus, we play a game of Plead the Fifth that will have your jaw on the floor!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Ts Getting the Tea with ANDY COHEN (PART ONE) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850098/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 02:54:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850098/</guid><description>Podcast Description The King is here dishing everything!! Everything!! Tamra and Teddi confront Andy for firing them.
Lisa Rinna, Teresa Guidice, Kyle Richards, LVP, Mary Cosby, Denise Richards, Caroline Manzo, Garcelle Beauvais, Kim Zolciak, Phaedra Parks, John Mayer… we’re talking about it ALL.
Plus, we play a game of Plead the Fifth that will have your jaw on the floor!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Rumor Mill | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850099/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850099/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Twots are mentioned in Andy’s new book and they are responding.
What really happened between Vicki and Tamra that night of WWHL? What did Andy actually tell Tamra the day she was fired? Then, rumors galore in Atlanta &amp;amp; NJ.
Teddi and Tamra give their take on who is right and who is wrong between Kenya and Martell.
Plus, a nasty one about Melissa is finally revealed but why on earth does Teresa involve her kids in it?</description></item><item><title>Ay Por Favor: Mo’ Money, Mo’ (Relationship) Problems | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850100/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Proud Mama, Alexia talks being extra protective of her boys and the women they date and Marysol opens up about past relationships and breaking the toxic cycle that so many people get stuck in. Pero, that’s not all…
This episode's gets saucy as they dish on Bennifer 2.0 and the car door slam heard around the world, Taylor’s swift shift to another lover, Kim Zolciak-Biermann being “tardy” to pay her taxes, y mucho mas.</description></item><item><title>I am your Mother, you listen to Me | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850101/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sandy and Vicky (aka the Twots’ Moms!!) are here!!
Ever wonder who raised Teddi and Tamra? What the Twots were like as kids? How Tamra and Sandy are so open with each other about their sex lives? How Vicky dealt with Teddi’s alter ego?
And, would Sandy and Vicky ever entertain joining The Real Housewives Mom Edition? And if so, what their taglines would be? See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Three Ts and a Shannon Beador | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850102/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:08:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850102/</guid><description>Podcast Description The *new* Tres Amigas are here!! Taylor Armstrong and Shannon Beador join the Twots.
We’re talking threesomes, BBLs, and even exes.
What really happened between Shannon and John Janssen before and after the breakup? Are they back together?
Plus, Taylor reveals a very weird Bravo Con interaction that involved Jen Shah.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Big D’s: Divorce, DMs and Drama | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850103/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 03:31:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kim Zolciak files for divorce from Kroy… what’s the real reason? The RHOA premiere was SPICY! Ralph filming without Drew, Courtney vs Kandi and Martell sliding into Kenya’s DMs… so much to dissect!
Then, we head over to Jersey. In a stunning turn of events, the Twots actually feel some sympathy for Teresa and it’ll shock you as to why.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Ts Getting the Tea with CARY DEUBER | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850104/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 01:51:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850104/</guid><description>Podcast Description RHOD’s Cary Deuber is in the hot seat today and the Twots are grilling her!!
Will RHOD ever return?
Who was the worst castmate to work with?
What’s the beef between Brandi and Stephanie?
Which *famous* celeb has she slept with?
This, and so much more!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Teddi Gets Naked | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850105/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi bares all and why you need to too…
The RHONJ reunion outfits are out! Who gets best dressed and who looks like they belong in a Disney movie?
Plus, find out why the Twots are worried about Frank Cantina.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ay Por Favor: Damage Control | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850106/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alexia and Maryol get candid talking about some of their biggest regrets from being on screen and what they would've done differently!
The chisme continues when they discuss Kylie Jenner and beauty standards, latin pop's unexpected yet expected hot new couple, and whether or not there's trouble in paradise for Cristiano Ronaldo and Georgina Rodriguez. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Ts Getting the Tea with RAMONA SINGER | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850107/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850107/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Ramona Coaster is here!!
Ramona is glowing and word on the street is she’s dating! Find out who, why, when and where.
Plus, we’re dishing on Legacy, UGT, and Kenya Moore.
Get ready because it’s Turtle Time!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Napkin Slap | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850108/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 00:52:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Finally!! The OC trailer is here!! Tamra tells us everything including details behind that napkin slap.
Find out why Erika Jayne paid a visit to Teddi.
Plus, Teddi and Tamra analyze the shift in Teresa in this week’s RHONJ episode. Why so nice to Melissa? Was it all just fake?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Ts Getting the Tea with MARLO HAMPTON | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850109/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 20:38:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tamra competed on Family Feud this weekend — RHOC vs RHOA! But WHY ON EARTH was John Janssen (Shannon’s ex) there?! Tamra fills us in… Then, we get all the RHOA tea from one of our favorite peaches, Marlo Hampton!
She didn’t hold back on the new season and which housewife she “activated” the most. Plus, who is the most selfish on her cast? She tells us.
See omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>The B*tch is Back!! | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850110/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 01:13:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tamra spilled the beans outing Teddi’s past Hollywood hookup with a VERY famous celebrity.
Plus, Teresa is coming for Tamra and Teddi once again and Tamra is not happy. Find out why.
Speaking of Teresa, NJ is getting so messy. Was she in the wrong bringing up Antonia?! We breakdown this week’s episodes of RHONJ and UGT.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ay Por Favor: Bienvenidos Al Show | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850111/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ay For Favor! No first episode is complete without a proper backstory! Get up close and personal as these besties of over 20 years revisit the wild Miami nights and heartwarming moments that made their friendship what it is today. Alexia &amp;amp; Marysol get into the "chisme" (gossip). From Kendall Jenner + Bad Bunny's relationship, to Shakira vs. the media and SNL making history. So grab a glass and make yourself a stiff one (unless you're driving or listening at work), because your favorite housewives have lots to spill!</description></item><item><title>Two Ts Getting the Tea with ALEXIA NEPOLA and MARYSOL PATTON | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850112/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850112/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s time to grab your cockies!! Alexia and Marysol give all the BTS of RHOM and UGT and they are serving up some serious tea. Which OG Miami Housewife do they wish came back?
Are Marysol and Alexia speaking to Adriana?
What happened to the infamous Clase Azul bottle in Thailand?
Plus, get ready because these spicy Miami housewives are coming out with a podcast of their own!! Ay Por Favor!</description></item><item><title>Hangxiety | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850113/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 01:32:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850113/</guid><description>Podcast Description What’s Hangxiety and why does Teddi have it?
Plus, the most embarrassing Coachella stories ever.
We’re answering all your questions about Tamra’s sex chair plus Vicki Gunvalson and the Twots’ original casting stories.
Get ready to laugh your a** off!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Luck of the Irish | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850114/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 02:23:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850114/</guid><description>Podcast Description RHONJ headed to Ireland but this trip was not lucky. Was Melissa invited to Teresa’s wedding only out of obligation? The Twots takes sides about Jennifer admitting to leaking info to the coffee reader.
Then, we jump over to Thailand for UGT only to see Pepsi cry! How sad.
Also, you don’t want to miss Teddi and Tamra’s limericks they created for each other!!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Two Ts Getting the Tea with MAURICIO UMANSKY | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850115/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 22:32:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Your favorite BH husband is here!!
We’ve all seen the headlines… trouble in paradise?? Why was Kyle spotted not wearing her engagement ring? Mauricio explains. Find out which ex he misses and which he would prefer never comes back to RHOBH ever again.
Plus, some real estate advice you didn’t know you needed until now.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>One tequila, two tequila, three tequila, FLOOR! | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850116/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850116/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Twots are dissecting this week’s headlines — one of which includes Tamra!
Why was this week’s UGT episode all about Tequila?!
And is Gizelle a producer?
One thing is for sure, Pepsi is a STAR!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Ts Getting the Tea with CAROLINE MANZO | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850117/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 20:44:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850117/</guid><description>Podcast Description The (ex) Housewife, The Myth, The Legend… Caroline Manzo is here!!
Caroline responds to UGT drama, Brandi’s tweets, and her own future with RHONJ.
You don’t want to miss this.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Coffee Beans and Pizza Gate | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850118/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 03:01:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Between Pizza Gate and Louie crying, RHONJ is bringing out all the Gym, Tan and DRAMA!
Find out why Teddi and Tamra have a bone to pick with that coffee bean reader. What’s the realdrama with Dina and Dolores? And, could this be the last we see of Frank? The Twots weigh in!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sh*t Stirring Twots | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850119/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 00:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850119/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Twots are answering your burning questions and let’s just say, they are definitely stirring the pot!!
Teddi and Tamra are giving their unfiltered take on
RHONJ’s Pizza Gate, why Teresa is mad at them and if Teddi and Camille will ever be in the same room together again.
You’ll need a glass of champagne for this one — it’s that juicy!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mellencamp: From BH to OC | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850120/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 01:57:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is Teddi moving to the OC?! What does this mean for the Twots?
What’s going on with Leah on UGT? We are so confused. And, are we about to see BFFs Alexia and Marysol fight?! Uh oh!
Plus, we’re recapping Jersey and we simply can’t get over Luis holding Melissa’s hand!!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Porsha Show | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850121/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 03:40:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Three UGT Eps. Two Crocs.
Only one Pepsi.
The Twots reveal their first impressions of the new season of RHUGT in Thailand. One thing is for sure — Porsha is stealing the show!
Plus, we tackle some Housewife Headlines — and yes, we are discussing Shannon’s new guy!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Keep calm and go to Vegas (with your husband) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850122/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850122/</guid><description>Podcast Description The husbands are in the hot seat!! Edwin Arroyave, Eddie Judge and Shane Simpson reveal all.
How did the show affect their marriage?
What is the key to getting through the tough times and those *dry spells*?
Oh, and should Teddi, Tamra and Emily do Only Fans?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Ts Getting the Tea with EMILY SIMPSON | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850123/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 18:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850123/</guid><description>Podcast Description The OC &amp;amp; BH are bringing the party to VEGAS!
Emily Simpson and Tamra address the beef they had when they first met and how they got to where they are today.
Plus, we get all the juicy scoop on Noella, Taylor Armstrong and a taste of what the new season will be like.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Waxes, Whoppers and WWHL | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850124/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 23:13:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850124/</guid><description>Podcast Description New Jersey is as explosive as ever!!
Should Teresa have invited Melissa’s mom to the wedding??
What’s the deal with Danielle and her brother?
Is Jennifer Aydin responsible for Teresa’s wedding hair?
How painful was it to watch John Fuda’s chest be waxed?
Then, we get into the final episode of the RHOM reunion. Who was the weakest link?!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Ts Getting the Tea with CANDIACE DILLARD BASSETT | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850125/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 23:15:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Not today Titties!!
It is a love fest when the Twots meet Candiace!
Imagine you go to Thailand with your mortal enemy and it gets filmed for TV. Spoiler Alert: Gizelle + Candiace on RHUGT is going to be juicy!
Plus, we get the dirty scoop on RHOP and her current relationship status with Gizelle and why she thinks Robyn is the ultimate undercover chess player.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Why such small couches? | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850126/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850126/</guid><description>Podcast Description We have never seen Andy so fired up at a reunion before!
Do we believe Larsa truly had sex 4 times a night for 23 years?! Also, was it just us, or was the entire cast of RHOM shoved onto two tiny couches for the reunion?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Ts Getting the Tea with RACHEL FUDA | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850127/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 22:50:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rachel Fuda may be a NJ newbie but she’s serving the tea piping hot! Does she hold a grudge against Jennifer Aydin for calling out her nose job?
Who is the most toxic on the cast? Is she getting along with Danielle? Oh and, we’re calling Rachel out on her Finsta! #BravoLover1234
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Way We Bugle | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850128/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850128/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Elton John Oscar Party was filled with Housewives including Lisa Rinna, Kyle Richards, Jill Zarin and Dorit Kemsley. But, one of their outfits had us doing a double take!!
We’re tackling headlines, answering your need to knows and recapping RHONJ.
One thing we can all agree on… the new girls are bringing the heat to NJ!!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Housewives Guide to Narcissism | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850129/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850129/</guid><description>Podcast Description The tea is piping hot recapping RHONJ &amp;amp; RHOM.
Did Gia accidentally insinuate that Luis is the problem? And, do the Twots agree?
Between Marysol’s bedazzled blow horn, Larsa’s lip licking and all the yelling, we are exhausted after watching the RHOM reunion!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tea Time! Part II with MELISSA GORGA | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850130/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Melissa is confronting the TwoTs about something they did. How will they respond?
We’re talking RHONJ and how this is one of the most stressful seasons ever for Melissa. Is reconciliation with Teresa even possible??
For Part 1 of this interview, listen to On Display with Melissa Gorga!
Link: tinyurl.com/mvbynaaf
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>4 Times a Night?! | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850131/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850131/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Twots are loading up on champagne to dissect the RHOP reunion! Find out what Teddi and Tamra would like to say to Chris Bassett now AFTER watching. Juicy headlines! How does Larsa have sex 4 times a day?! Finally, do you like your own IG and Tik Tok posts?! Oh, Tamra…
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Scandoval of the Century | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850132/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 23:53:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850132/</guid><description>Podcast Description We interrupt this program to dive into the biggest hot topic of the year.
Vanderpump Rules. Raquel (Rachel??). Sandoval. Schwartz. Ariana.
There is so much to talk about and Twots are giving you their hot take!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Ts Getting the Tea with CHRIS BASSETT | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850133/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 20:09:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850133/</guid><description>Podcast Description The RHOP reunion was beyond dramatic so Chris Bassett (Candiace’s husband) is here to clear the air.
What really happened with Gizelle?
What are his thoughts on Juan and Robyn?
When are Candiace and Chris having kids?
And, this is only the start of where the TWOTS are taking this!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tamra Grudge | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850134/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 01:32:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850134/</guid><description>Podcast Description A certain NJ Housewife has some harsh words for Tamra… We are devastated. Ralph and Drew announce their divorce.
And, of course we recap Miami and Jersey.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Melissa enters the Group Chat | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850135/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 00:53:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850135/</guid><description>Podcast Description After our Jacqueline Laurita episode, a current Housewife has come forward with some facts… and receipts!
Was the RHOP reunion a boring snooze fest or did you love it?
And of course, the Twots discuss new Housewife rumors and the upcoming RHUGT season in Thailand.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Adriana, what the… ??? | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850136/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 20:29:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adriana… what are you doing?! Talk about an analogy gone wrong!!
Find out why the Twots believe Jennifer Aydin is moments away from exploding.
Also, should Pamela Anderson be a Housewife?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Ts Getting the Tea with JACQUELINE LAURITA | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850137/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 23:24:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850137/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s the juiciest Twots episode ever!
Jacqueline Laurita does not hold back!
We’re talking Teresa, Melissa, Dina, Caroline, Danielle, Luis, both Joe’s and SO much more…
Get ready because we are diving in deep to RHONJ.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We like our Housewives Messy | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850138/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 23:55:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850138/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a HOT MESS in Housewives world!!
Jen Shah in prison.
Eminem goes after Robyn and Gizelle.
Joe Gorga’s Bahamas run in with Joe Giudice.
And, the RHOP Reunion is finally here. Should a married man be in a hotel room with a single woman?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Ts Getting the Tea with STEPHANIE HOLLMAN | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850139/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850139/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is up with these RHOD reboot rumors? We get all the answers.
Where do things stand with Stephanie and LeeAnne Locken? Plus, Stephanie reveals her dream Ultimate Girl’s Trip cast.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sex Chairs &amp; Scandals | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850140/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 03:35:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi reveals if Denise texted her back. Will it shock you? Between Braunwyn’s Vegas “wedding” and Brandi Glanville’s scandal, we have a lot to talk about.
Then, we’re recapping NJ &amp;amp; Miami. Teddi slides into a certain Miami housewives DMs and we have all the details.
Plus, we get an update on Tamra’s sex chair.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Getting the Tea with MARGARET JOSEPHS | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850141/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Grab your iced coffee in a wine glass and sit down with Margaret Josephs!! We are getting all the juicy BTS on the new season of RHONJ. Does she regret going to Teresa’s wedding? Does she have hope for Teresa and Melissa? This doesn’t even begin to cover how deep we’re going.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Will She Text Back? | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850142/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 02:50:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Breaking News: Teddi texts Denise.
Is a mended friendship in their future??
RHONJ is back and it’s coming in hot. Are Melissa and Teresa doomed forever?
Plus, our thoughts on the New NJ Housewives! Who are we loving? And who, not so much.
And of course, we recap the heat coming in from Miami!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Watch What Happens Robyn | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850143/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 04:51:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Robyn on WWHL was a major YIKES! What does this mean for her future on Potomac?
RHOP Finale was a bust. Why is Ashley Darby buying a house with her ex’s LLC?? Are you as confused as we are?
Plus, Tamra dishes on a whirlwind weekend with Margaret Josephs and Dorinda Medley!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Birds of a Feather flock Together | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850144/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 21:49:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850144/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a doozy this SLC Reunion! Is Heather playing the victim? Is Whitney the only one keeping it real??
Once again, Miami is doing the most!
We don’t understand why Alexia is so upset with Nicole.
And then Todd and Anthony go at it… something is up!
But more importantly, who is in the wheelchair?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Double Dipping | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850145/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 04:33:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why is everyone double dipping? Over it!
Jill Zarin has Tamra fired up… again. And would Tracy Tutor make a good housewife?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Most Hated Housewife | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850146/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 23:31:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850146/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Most Hated Housewife award goes to… (listen to find out!)
But, who is the most hated husband?? That’s for you to decide!
Plus, recapping Potomac. Should Ashley Darby get back together with Michael?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OnlyFans and Naked Billboards | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850147/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 01:34:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi is going to be naked on a billboard?!
RHONJ taglines are out and we are rating them and adding our hot take.
Plus, our first glimpse at the Potomac reunion outfits. Find out who topped our most fashionable list and who missed.
And, should Eddie Judge join OnlyFans?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Blue Eyes | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850148/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Meghan King talks threesomes… woah!
Does Karen have it out for Robyn? Is Juan cheating on Robyn?
And who is blue eyes?
Plus, recapping RHOP and it’s juicy!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CABO WABO (with Kyle Richards) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850149/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 03:57:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi is in Cabo with Kyle Richards’ for her birthday trip! Kyle is in the hot seat answering ALL of our burning questions including why she distanced herself from the RHOBH ladies this year and how she feels about a Legacy show for Beverly Hills.
Plus, Tamra contemplates joining OnlyFans to spy on another housewife.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>And we’re blocked again… | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850150/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 22:48:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who blocked Teddi this time??
RHOP reunion seating chart is out and Gizelle is in the first seat but should she be?
And, the engagement party of the year… we are dying over Nicole’s party!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Who’s the Queen of Potomac?? | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850151/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 04:34:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is Charisse the Queen of Potomac? The Twots dissect this week’s RHOP episode and one thing we can all agree on… Mia is messy!
Plus, we’re diving deep into this week’s headlines. Shannon’s ex is dating… who?!
And Teddi settles a nasty rumor about Kyle.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Teddi has an Anxiety Attack | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850152/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 00:59:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi’s anxiety is running high and she’s experiencing it in real time. The Twots dig deep into Shannon Beador’s break up… Is his “one-week-after-filming-ended” breakup suspicious?
SLC finale left us bored… yawn. Miami is heating up, wow Lenny!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Belly Flop | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850153/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 01:56:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850153/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tamra is back and she gives us an update on her new belly button! RHUGT cast reveal! Has Teddi spoken to Lisa Rinna? And, how SLC will be different next year.
Plus, is Miami taking over Potomac’s highly coveted honor of being Teddi’s top franchise?!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>6.5 Years | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850154/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 00:37:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Covering all the breaking news! Jen Shah is sentenced to 6.5 years in prison. What does it mean for the future of RHOSLC?
Lisa Rinna announces she’s leaving the franchise! Who is going to step it up in her absence — Denise? LVP? Brandi?
And then, Miami and SLC going strong. Don’t miss the recap of this week’s episodes.
Real Housewives is the gift that keeps on giving.</description></item><item><title>Cheater, Cheater, Pumpkin eater | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850155/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 05:38:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brandi Glanville jumps in to recap Miami and Potomac.
Brandi knows a lot about cheating scandals on reality TV… so what’s her take on Lenny and Lisa? It will shock you.
Plus, more theories on who gave Heather Gay that black eye… we just can’t get over it!!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two T’s Getting the Tea with EVA MARCILLE | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850156/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eva made a massive mistake…and divulges all right here right now!
Hint: it involves Andy AND Porsha.
Plus, Eva and Tamra reminisce over the Berkshires and reveal unbelievable RHUGT BTS. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two T’s Getting the Tea with EBONI K. WILLIAMS | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850157/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850157/</guid><description>Podcast Description Order in the court! Court is in session with Eboni and Two T’s!!
Curious why RHONY didn't had a reunion last season? Are Leah and Eboni on speaking terms? Where do things stand today with Eboni and Ramona?
The Twots discover who is innocent and who is guilty as charged.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Beauty is in the EYE of the beholder | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850158/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 03:35:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850158/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ok, is Heather’s black eye real? We just don’t get it…
Find out why RHOM may be our favorite franchise… Ever.
And in breaking News — SLC Reunion looks are out AND a RHONJ trailer has been released… Merry Christmas to us!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Drunk Dial w/ Erika Jayne and Cynthia Bailey | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850159/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 03:46:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850159/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a few glasses of champagne, the Twots are revved up about this week’s Housewife Headlines. They were compelled to call the Housewives themselves live on air!! That’s right, Erika Jayne and Cynthia Bailey chime in LIVE on their very own headlines. Can we also make it through a recap of RHOP, RHOM and SLC?? You’ll have to tune in to find out.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Two Ts Getting the Tea with LUANN DE LESSEPS (part 2) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850160/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850160/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Countess is here and she’s not holding back!
Luann and Bethenny are feuding and the TWOTS get all the tea!
Who blocked who, who unfollowed who, and why?! This drama is real.
Plus, Luann serves up some major tea on RHONY Legacy.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why You Gotta Be So Mean?! | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850161/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 22:12:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850161/</guid><description>Podcast Description RHOM has finally returned and this season is hot hot hot!!
There’s trouble in paradise aka Miami Paradise… with Lenny and Lisa! Was Lenny’s hot mic moment even a hot mic? The Twots have theories…
And why is having a mortgage a bad thing?!
Plus, "I’m not mean"!!
Is Nicole mean???!!!!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>My Ride or Die | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850162/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 03:58:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850162/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happens in Vegas…. Doesn’t stay in Vegas.
Tamra was there with Melissa Gorga AND Brandi Glanville… find out what went down.
Plus, the Twots are tackling the hottest housewife headlines. Between Lenny Hochstein and Jen Shah, some people are better off not being on Twitter and Instagram.
And, of course we’re recapping SLC &amp;amp; RHOP!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Ts getting the Tea with ANGIE KATSANEVAS (RHOSLC) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850163/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 16:31:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850163/</guid><description>Podcast Description This ‘friend of’ is READY for her snowflake!!
Angie K reveals the BTS of the moment Jen Shah poured champagne all over her head… and let’s just say there is A LOT to discuss.
Plus… the good, the bad and the ugly of the SLC Housewives. Angie isn’t holding back and neither are the Twots! Buckle up!!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Schadenfreude in the SLC and RHOP | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850164/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 06:59:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850164/</guid><description>Podcast Description Messy messy … these Housewives are getting messy!!
SLC, we’re pouring Champagne on people’s heads and Zen Jen isn’t so Zen after all.
Who will be holding snowflakes next year?
Also, STILL no black eye?!!
Topic of the day — are threesomes marriage killers?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We’re Unfollowed and Sweet James shows up! | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850165/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 00:58:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Awkward encounter????
Tamra runs into Sweet James (RHOC’s Noella’s ex husband) at Jingle Ball and she’s dishing it ALL!!
In other news, one housewife has decided to unfollow the Twots. UH OH!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Ts and a Badass B | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850166/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 05:06:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850166/</guid><description>Podcast Description THE TEA!!!! With Brandi Glanville in the hot seat, this is one of the juiciest Twots ever.
Who was the rudest person at Bravo Con?
Find out.
Will she return to RHOBH??
Find out.
Status of Brandi’s relationship with Kim Richards???
Find out.
But most importantly, Teddi &amp;amp; Tamra get an update on Brandi’s dating life as she reveals the greatest celebrity sex she’s ever had and if she will ever get married.</description></item><item><title>Party in the R-H-O-P | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850167/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 01:17:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Was it really a party in Potomac? Or was it a complete disaster?
Drinks were flying. Candaice is crying. And Karen is getting a birthday she’ll never forget. Who’s to blame?! The Twots weigh in!!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Champagne Problems | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850168/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 22:03:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two T’s in a Pod = Double Trouble… especially when champagne is involved!!
Teddi is reliving WWHL with her dad. And we are answering your questions LIVE.
Does the Fox Force Five still exist? Are the Twots Team Mia or Wendy? And SO MUCH MORE.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Twots Tackling Tough Terrifying Questions | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850169/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850169/</guid><description>Podcast Description The TWOTS answer YOUR questions… no matter how hard and difficult they are.
Fox Force 5… OC legacy… Even Jen Shah…
No holds barred.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MIA: Missing In Action | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850170/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 02:26:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lets dive right in to RHOP and it’s soooo messy!!
Peter Thomas. Uh Oh….
The Twots have some very strong thoughts.
Hey, SLC — can we get rid of the choir already?! Do we even like the SLC Husbands??!!!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Real Housewife Lifesaver | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850171/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850171/</guid><description>Podcast Description Whitney Rose from SLC is an honorary Twot!! After a whirlwind weekend at BravoCon, our three BFFs are catching up and getting REAL.
Teddi continues to share her cancer journey. She’s prioritizing health hoping everyone will do the same! Thanks to 23andMe, Teddi, Tamra and Whitney dive headfirst in to their Housewife DNA.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Who's not my friend here? Raise your hand. | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850172/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 20:03:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850172/</guid><description>Podcast Description SLC is heating up and we are here for it!! Does Lisa have any friends? Is Angie H trying to earn her snowflake?
One Twots has a very shocking discovery about a SLC Housewife… and it involves LVP.
RHOP… one is fooling around with a Summer House regular and we have all the tea!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The REAL Ugly Truth | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850173/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:13:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850173/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tears.
Arguments.
Heartbreak.
Things we wish we could Do Over after I Do.
And then , the D word… DIVORCE.
Teddi and Tamra get real admitting what happened off screen in their marriages when the Housewives cameras weren’t rolling.
Oh, A Cougar we love!
Teddi is in NYC for WWHL with… JOHN MELLENCAMP! It hurts so good!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Finstas and Elves on a Shelf | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850174/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 19:47:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850174/</guid><description>Podcast Description SLC husbands are sooooo dicey!! Why are they so thirsty?? Is Angie H. really behind it all? Plus, a health update from Teddi and she reveals all about the upcoming WWHL with the legend himself, her dad, John Mellencamp!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Twitter Takedown | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850175/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850175/</guid><description>Podcast Description RHOSLC and RHOP serving piping hot tea!! Heather and Whitney feud, Angie Harrington DRAMA, and Ashley Darby in general… Oh, and Rinna deactivated her Twitter account… what does it mean?!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trick or Treat with Cynthia Bailey | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850176/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 23:58:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850176/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cynthia Bailey joins the Two T's to celebrate Halloween TWOTS style.
Teddi and Cynthia address the big rumor that they are both joining the next season of RHOBH.
Cynthia gets emotionally sharing the details of very recent divorce. Plus, a TREAT...BTS from BravoCon and RHUGT you can only hear here!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>For Richards or Poorer?? | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850177/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 23:46:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850177/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lifestyles of the Richards and Famous.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Liquid Courage | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850178/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850178/</guid><description>Podcast Description Of course!!!!! According to WWHL this week, Tamra is the life of the party!!
The Lisa Rinna drama continues and we’ve got it all!
Breaking news, who’s following who on Instagram and behind the scenes Bravo Con drama only the TWOTS will divulge! And, is Gizelle the new bone collector?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The D Word: DENISE | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850179/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 20:56:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Let's talk about Denise. The TWOTS have SO MANY thoughts.
The TWOTS reveal who may be leaving BH and who will return.
Teddi gets spotted by TMZ after lunch with another housewife...
The Fox Force Five Shakeup Breakup...Tamra reveals why this is a good thing!
Teddi gives a health update.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Party in Potomac | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850180/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi gives an update about her skin cancer and has strong opinions about sharing these types of stories.
Let’s discuss the controversial DM! And break down the divorce drama, Teddi and Tamra know what’s up. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Recapping the Con | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850181/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 19:59:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850181/</guid><description>Podcast Description The TWO Ts are back from BravonCon and telling all!
They’re giving us the after hours stories, squashing rumors, and all the BTS tea you can sip. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Reasonably Potomac with Gizelle, Robyn, Candiace and Dr. Wendy | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850182/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850182/</guid><description>Podcast Description Potomac is finally back!! Teddi’s favorite in the HOUSEWIVES franchise!!
Things get heated between Teddi , Gizelle, and Robyn.Will this become a feud or a friendship???
We get an update on Gizelle’s dating life and what the girl’s really think of Mia’s online behavior?? EEK!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>B*tch I am the Peach! with Marlo Hampton | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850183/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850183/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marlo tells us what she’s learned and how she’s feeling after being REAL for one full season.
She’s giving us all the spicy energy we know and love her for!!
Plus, who does she want back on Atlanta??
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Are you for REAL in The O.C.?! with Tamra, Shannon, Emily and Gina | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850184/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 17:26:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850184/</guid><description>Podcast Description Let’s dig in to the divorce drama with Shannon… OMG!
Can Shannon and Tamra help mend Teddi and Vicki’s tumultuous relationship?
Plus, Gina and Emily give us all the tea of new season of the OC!!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jersey Girls are Unforgettable with Dolores, Jackie, Jennifer and Teresa | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850185/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 13:34:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850185/</guid><description>Podcast Description The truth serum was flowing strong today!!
Jennifer spills all the drama from this season and Teresa reveals details from her wedding day! (Including the goods on the Gorga’s)
Dolores tells us about her new boyfriend and he’s filming so we will see it all on screen!
This episode will have you fist pumping all the way down to the shore!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CHANELling our inner Diva with Chanel Ayan | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850186/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 16:31:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850186/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chanel is not shying away from throwing shade at her fellow cast-mates. PERIOD. DOT.
Find out who is too preachy and who needs to stay off Twitter.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The OG of NJ with Caroline Manzo | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850187/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850187/</guid><description>Podcast Description She’s the MANZO!
The OG of NJ is here and she’s not afraid to speak her mind.Yes, we talk about Teresa!
She’s unfiltered, raw, and wild!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Miami is always a good idea with Lisa Hochstein, Adriana de Moura and Julia Lemigova | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850188/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850188/</guid><description>Podcast Description BravoCon got Hot Hot Hot when the Miami ladies showed up!! We need tea about Lisa’s single life. Plus, lots of BTS intel on the new season! All that’s missing is a mojito!!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Real Housewives Kids with Gia Giudice, Frankie Catania and Riley Burruss | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850189/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850189/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Real Kids of NJ and Atlanta are spilling the tea!
Do Frankie and Gia belong together? Has Gia spoken to The Gorgas?? Plus, Riley is the longest running housewife “kid” and she’s telling us everything! See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>90210 has entered the Group Chat!!!! | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850190/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 06:09:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850190/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the midst of the craziest reunion ever, Kyle, Erika and Sutton are live with us from BravoCon! As Dorit would say, they are looking CHIC! As we would say, WE ARE SPILLING MASSIVE TEA!
Dig in to Diana’s drama and Rinna and Erika were boo’d at BravoCon! What the…!!!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Gym, Tan, Jersey Husbands | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850191/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 05:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850191/</guid><description>Podcast Description Your favorite Husbands are here… Frank, Evan, Joe Gorga and Joe Benigno and they are NOT holding back!!
Joe dishes on all the family drama and we are shook!! Plus, find out which of these husbands has a special ringtone for their other half!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>From SLC to NYC with Lisa Barlow | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850192/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 18:25:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850192/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adventures at BravoCon continue! This one could use a little SALT!
We’ve got inside details from the infamous hot mic moment…a Relationship status update with Meredith…and, a lot of thoughts on Jen Shah. Lisa is putting the rumors to rest!
Grab your Diet Coke because we’re getting SALTY.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Words: ANDY COHEN | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850193/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 15:58:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850193/</guid><description>Podcast Description There is only one way to start BravoCon and that’s with the man, the myth, the legend… ANDY COHEN!!
The guy who FIRED Teddi…
The man that started it all… LIVE from BravoCon!! See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Housewives and the City | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850194/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 15:43:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850194/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Con is on!!!! BravoCon Time! They’ve just landed and the Twots already have JUICY stories aplenty!
It begins with Teddi sitting next to this Housewife on the plane to NYC and takes off from there!!! (Hint: she wore fancy pants.)
And honorary Twot, Justin Anderson helps break down the BH reunion!!
The drinks are flowing…the tea is spilling…this one is coming in HOT so you better buckle up!</description></item><item><title>Prenups, Painful Partings and Potomac | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850195/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 19:56:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850195/</guid><description>Podcast Description Potomac… here we go!
RHOP is finally back and the tea is overflowing!! RHOA Drew Sidora jumps in to dissect it all!
Is it the d word for Ashley Darby??To divorce or not to divorce, that is the question! Ashley Darby… what is happening?!
Plus, Teddi has one thing in common with Ashley Darby… and it involves Vikki Gunvalson. Uh oh….
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cold as Ice | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850196/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850196/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s our 100th episode!! What better way to celebrate than with the RHOBH reunion trailer — Kyle is crying, Dianna doesn’t say a word, and Kathy and Rinna go at it.
Plus, SLC is in AZ and the tears are a plenty!Will Lisa and Meredith ever make up?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What in the Rinna?! | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850197/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 22:05:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850197/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the Twots prep for Bravo Con… they have noticed something significant… RINNA!! What happened?
Speaking of Rinna, this week’s BH finale was just… wow. Garcelle’s green lipstick, Sutton’s Bumble Match, and the fight over Birkins!!
Also… Teddi may have broken her va jay jay.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two T’s Getting the Tea with TERESA GIUDICE | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850198/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850198/</guid><description>Podcast Description Namaste Bitches!!Teresa Giudice is all TWOT and bothered and she’s bringing her BFF Melissa with her.
Will Teresa and Tamra resolve the beef they have with each other?
Find out how Ramona really screwed up Teresa’s wedding, which RHONJ OGs she’d want to come back, and if she really had sex 5 times a day on her Honeymoon…
This is one you just can’t miss.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>SALT in a wound | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850199/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 22:44:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850199/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s ON…RHOSLC returns!!
Do we forgive Lisa’s hot mic moment? Was her apology even an apology??
Teddi has a shocking connection to one of the new housewives that you must hear for yourself! See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sending Blessings and Prayers | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850200/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 01:50:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850200/</guid><description>Podcast Description WOAH! You can cut the BH tension with a knife!!!! Lisa Rinna…in the right or oh so wrong!?How bad was Kathy’s melt down? Is this really all because of 818 tequila?!
90210 is a hot mess but we’ll always have Popeye’s.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What happens in Vegas… Immediately goes on Air | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850201/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 01:19:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850201/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi is back from Vegas and oh boy is she dishing some juicy stories from the weekend!!
RHOA has come to an end and we have mixed emotions. Teddi has one revelation about Ralph (Drew’s Husband) that you don’t want to miss.
Buckle up, RHOSLC starts this week and the Twots are ready!!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Real Husbands | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850202/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 17:58:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850202/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s Vegas baby!! So we flew in Drew Sidora and she is coming in hot from Atlanta. She brought along a special guest, her husband Ralph, so Teddi grabbed Edwin and it’s on… fire!!!!!!
We’ve got recaps, mishaps, all the haps and PLENTY of booze.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two T’s getting the Tea with WHITNEY ROSE | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850203/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850203/</guid><description>Podcast Description Will you accept this rose? Or does ever ROSE have it’s thorns? Let’s talk RHOSLC!!
There’s some drama between Whitney Rose and Heather… Whitney is somehow now friends with Lisa…. And she’s gong on Ultimate Girl’s Trip!
There is so much to unpack… Plus, we got all the scoop on Jen Shah and Mary Cosby.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>I Have the Receipts! | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850204/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:36:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850204/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a (not) shocking turn of events… David Beador is… getting a divorce?!
RHOA is back with night 2 of the reunion.. Are you team Kenya or team Marlo?
One thing is for sure… Marlo brought receipts!!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Watch What Aspens | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850205/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 00:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850205/</guid><description>Podcast Description WOW… RHOBH! Aspen will never be the same.
Kathy’s sweat pants. Kendall Jenner’s Tequila. Erika’s earrings. Kyle’s hats.
But more importantly, WHAT A CLIFFHANGER!!
There is so much to discuss… you’ll just have to listen now.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Ts Getting the Tea with SHEREE WHITFIELD | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850206/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 00:20:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850206/</guid><description>Podcast Description We have a housewife WITH fashions joining the Twots and she is serving up some serious tea!!
Sheree Whitfield is telling us all —the infamous She by Sheree website crash, the truth about Tyrone and which special guy she’s flirting with now!!
Who gon' check me, boo?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Little Bird Told me… | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850207/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 00:55:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850207/</guid><description>Podcast Description Seriously… what was up with all those birds?! We are jumping right into the RHOA reunion! The seating chart was puzzling… why was Kandi on the end?? The Twots give their expert theories.
And, good news — it only took 14 years. There is a website WITH fashions!!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lions, Tigers and Reunions, OH MY! | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850208/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 20:57:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850208/</guid><description>Podcast Description RHOBH is filming their reunion as we speak!! Who will sit next to Andy? Which housewife doesn’t show up? We dissect allllllll the rumors.
Speaking of Beverly Hills… Things are getting HOT and STRESSY in Aspen.
Teddi had a turning point with RHOA… find out which housewife she is REALLY starting to love. Finally, will we ever get our She by Sheree fashions?!
Dubai has come to an end.</description></item><item><title>Two T’s Getting the Tea w/ SERGIO CARRALLO | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850209/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850209/</guid><description>Podcast Description The drama is SERGing!!
Fresh off Part 1 of the Dubai reunion, the housewife… we mean, husband… everyone is talking about is HERE!!!!
Teddi quizzes him on sex education, soccer and Tiki Tiki.
We STANbury this Husband!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Vacation Nobody Wanted w/ Drew Sidora | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850210/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 20:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850210/</guid><description>Podcast Description Reunited and it feels so (not) good. It’s the Dubai reunion and it is dicey! The ladies are bringing the heat so we brought back Drew Sidora to break it all down!
Speaking of break downs… OOOF!! The BH trip to Aspen is already off to a rocky start. Can they recover?? We’re not sure…
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>It’s Icy in Salt Lake w/ Drew Sidora | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850211/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 23:59:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850211/</guid><description>Podcast Description We DREW upon her expertise as we dig into these juicy housewife headlines…
RHOA’s Drew Sidora can completely relate to what Erika Jayne is going through.
OH BOY! The RHOSLC trailer is out and WOW!!!!
What’s up with Heather’s black eye? Is Jen Shah really guilty? Let’s unpack. It. All…
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>90210 | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850212/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 02:42:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850212/</guid><description>Podcast Description Real Housewives of Beverly Hills...
Teddi and Tamra are reviewing the timeline of all the recent news.
Our hearts go out to Garcelle and her son, Jax.
Then...
Vikki said what about Tamra??!!! Oh boy...Tamra responds.
We are feeling kinda MEH on the Dubai finale but at least we will get to see the CROWN at the reunion!
Of course, the Twots are recapping ATL… tune in for the fashion without fashions!</description></item><item><title>Two T’s Getting the Tea with LESA MILAN | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850213/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850213/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lesa is more!
We're going one on one with Real Housewives of Dubai star Lesa Milan Hall.
From Nip Slips, the Reunion, to where do things stand between Lesa and Caroline Stanbury now. Plus, we go over all the reunion looks and Lesa tells us how she really feels about that crown…
We're getting to it all TWOTS style.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The "Meaning" of Life | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850214/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 02:39:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850214/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi wants to talk. She's going one on one with you to talk LVP.
Teddi and Tamra discuss Lisa Rinna's video statement and what it all “means". Did Tamra know about Vicky's new pod with Kelly? Let's gets the tea.
Plus, we're recapping Atlanta...
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sipping on some Bailey’s! | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850215/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 19:23:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850215/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cynthia Bailey is here spilling everywhere!
We get the inside scoop on Teresa’s wedding and what that hairdo looked like in person!! Plus, Cynthia tells us what went down between her and Kenya at the wedding.
Cynthia opens up about her mom being diagnosed with breast cancer and how important it is to get mammograms regularly and prioritize our health.
And of course, we recap Dubai… Chanel Ayan’s story touched us all.</description></item><item><title>MAYER of the Year | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850216/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 00:53:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850216/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dubai reunion serving looks! Who was best dressed?? And worst? The Twots debate Caroline Brooks’ crown.
We all agree on one thing this week… Dorit’s daughter Phoenix stole the show!!
Fun fact: John Mayer is on Raya and his picture features one of our very own Twots…
Plus… Tamra has a Ouija board story thats giving us chills!
Eeeek!!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>It’s a Family Affair | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850217/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 01:32:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850217/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Twots are sipping champagne breaking down the juiciest Housewives stories.
Dorit and Mauricio?!! That’s a headline we didn’t see coming… Teddi weighs in on her two BFFs.
Should Melissa leave RHONJ in the midst of all her family drama??
Plus, Tamra’s ex, Simon, is single and CUT Fitness is closing... oh my!
And, a RHOA debate the Twots can’t agree on — how do you feel about Sanya’s husband!</description></item><item><title>Say Yes to the Dress | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850218/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 00:22:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850218/</guid><description>Podcast Description Breaking news: Tamra and Teresa had the same wedding dress designer!! Who wore it best - Tamra or Teresa?! You be the judge!! Are Melissa and Joe stronger than ever? Or are they putting on a brave face?
This week’s RHOBH was filled with lots of drama, tears and Melissa Etheridge!!
Plus, Teddi and Tamra decide which BH husband they’d rather be married to…
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Big Hair, Don’t Care | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850219/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 23:08:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850219/</guid><description>Podcast Description This wedding will go down in Hairstory!!
The wedding we have all been waiting for… Teresa and Luis tie the knot and it did not disappoint!
The Hair.The Bridesmaids.Dorinda. Alexia. Phaedra. Cynthia. Kenya. Chanel. Jackie. Dolores. Jennifer. Jill. Margaret. Phaedra.Gone Missing: Dina, Melissa and Joe.
So… Is it really all rainbows and butterflies inside the Love Bubble?! We think not.
Then we go to Jamaica with the ATL Housewives… are couples trips ever a good idea?</description></item><item><title>Is this Reality?? | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850220/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 16:29:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850220/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi had a very weird dream last night… and our dear Vicki was in it.
We are recapping it ALL — Atlanta, Dubai, Beverly Hills… our cup runneth over!
Plus, which Dubai Housewife reminds Teddi of herself.
But one thing we simply cannot handle… the sound of Sutton making chicken salad… HELP!!!!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Twots, Texting feuds, European tours | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850221/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 23:02:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850221/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi and Jim Edmonds are going at it! We don’t know whether to cringe, cry or get out the popcorn!
Tamra dishes on her European vacation!
Taylor Armstrong is back but this time she’s holding an orange. How does Tamra feel about her new cast-mate??
Plus, find out which Housewife is declining to be on the pod. Hint: she’s thirsty.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Long Live the KING | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850222/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 23:41:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850222/</guid><description>Podcast Description Meghan King is a TWOT.
Teddi shares a massive bombshell of a DM that she received and it shocks Meghan to her core…
As if that’s not enough, Meghan is recapping BH and Dubai with us…
There is so much to dissect… Caroline Stanbury’s Wedding to Sergio, PK and Dorit’s argument and uh…. Sutton’s date. Can we please talk about that cat sweater??!
But there is one thing Teddi and Meghan can agree on… Vicki!</description></item><item><title>Life’s A Peach | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850223/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 21:17:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850223/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hot hot Housewives Headlines
Why is Kathy Hilton tweeting out her number?!
Is Phaedra returning to RHOA?
Also, Tamra has a gut feeling that ?????? will return to BH… can you guess who it is??
And, of course we are recapping RHOA. Marlo is sureeee bringing the drama!! Is she earning her peach or is it starting to get too ridiculous??
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mean Dirty Housewives | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850224/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 00:05:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850224/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tamra is giving us all the scoop from New York!WWHL BTS…so juicy!Seeing Sutton!! Tamra’s spilling so much tea!
We are sad to see Ultimate Girls Trip S2 come to an end. So many tears, shirt dresses and canoes. Our takeaway: Brandi is Queen
BH was the messiest of them all… oh man… this episode was rough!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>All Rise... The Judge is Back in Session! | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850225/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 02:38:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850225/</guid><description>Podcast Description Things are getting REAL...AGAIN!!!
And...she's back in the OC!!
Tamra is heading back to the Real Housewives of OC and she's telling us EVERYTHING!! (including all that drama with Jill...)
How does Eddie, Tamra's husband, feel about filming again??!!
And, let's talk about a threesome that won't happen... Vicki, Teddi and Tamra...eek.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Brandi, You're a Fine Girl... What A Good Wife You Would Be… | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850226/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850226/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brandi Glanville joins the TWOTS to recap Girls Trip! Oh What a Trip it is!
We're going for it...talking Bravo Con Flirtations and Brandi and Taylor's relationship TODAY.Teddi and Tamra ask Brandi about their "eyebrows". Plus, who Brandi prefers Teddi or Tamra.
And, Brandi has a new song dissing a lot of housewives...
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tiny Hats and Shady Words | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850227/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 00:39:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850227/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you Team Sutton or Team Diana???
BH is so MESSY!
Erika apologizes…Everyone has a crush on Garcelle’s … son! Eek Diana keeps licking her lips and wearing tiny hats…Kyle kisses Maurico’s Dad…
And, we are still snoozing through Dubai. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SHAHking | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850228/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 02:26:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850228/</guid><description>Podcast Description Did you think we were avoiding you????!!! Nah! The TWOTS are fired up and dishing all the dirt.
Jen Shah...OH MY...what do we think? Teddi discusses Kyle...is she biased because it's her best friend? You be the judge.
Dubai...are you bored...the TWOTS are a tad bored.
Atlanta - YES YES! Gimme More!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Happy 4th of July! | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850229/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850229/</guid><description>Podcast Description See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tamra gets Naked… again | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850230/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 16:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850230/</guid><description>Podcast Description Girls Trip…Tamra gets naked, Dorinda gets mad, Garcelle throws shade at Teddi &amp;amp; Tamra. And, we thought we were friends again!!
You aren’t a good Housewife if you don’t have receipts… and Tamra shows them all.
Plus… is Diana the villain we all wanted?! The Twots chime in!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Eyebrows, OH MY! | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850231/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 01:49:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850231/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tamra is back on TV and she’s here telling all! It wouldn’t be a housewives trip without Vicki going to the hospital, Brandi having one too many glasses of wine and Dorinda making it NICE at Blue Stone Manor!
If you’re feeling like a little tea…you’ve come to the right place!
And then… the eyebrows… Super-fan / Celeb Hairstylist, Justin Anderson is joining in.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Vicki Gunvalsonning for Teddi | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850232/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 01:20:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850232/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vicki said, "I don't know Teddi Mellencamp but I don't like Teddi Mellencamp"
hmmmmmm
Teddi responds.
Plus, Justin Sylvester is filling in for Tamra… he used to be Kyle Richards’ assistant and boy does he have all the tea from when RHOBH first started….
Between Teddi, Justin and all the truth serum, this pod is out of control!!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two T’s getting the Tea with DREW SIDORA | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850233/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850233/</guid><description>Podcast Description DREW is spilling all the peachy tea!
Drew’s relationship with her husband is the center of the drama on RHOA… what’s going on when the cameras are off!!??
Plus, is therapy every Monday the key to success!
Lastly… Where are the receipts?!!!
And is Marlo going to lose her peach??
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>I’ll have a “Glam-Light” | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850234/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 23:46:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850234/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi unfollowed Vicki… the TWOTS tell you why. Tamra is in NYC with all the RHUGT ladies!! What’s up with those kissing videos of Tamra??
We are recapping all things Atlanta and debating donating clothes and dating people in prison.
Plus, Dorinda surprises the TWOTS to address rumors during Housewife Headlines.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>9 Year Itch | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850235/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 00:13:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850235/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tamra&amp;rsquo;s been married 9 years! &amp;nbsp;Let's relive that iconic OC wedding special and reveal BTS you never knew.
Is she still friends with all her bridesmaids? And what about Teddi?!
Is it completely outrageous to travel with your glam squad?! (Ha!) The Twots discuss.&amp;nbsp;
RHOBH is about to get real goooood and real messy &amp;hellip; Hi Erika!
And Dubai&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s still making us snooze. But, would you keep the goat?</description></item><item><title>WTH in the ATL | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850236/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 16:15:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850236/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who gave Teddi covid?!
A listener asked the TWOT's how much plastic surgery they have had?&amp;nbsp; Appropriate question?? Probably not...but they answered!
A little OC drama when Kelly Dodd called in while Tamra was a guest on Jeff Lewis'....EEK!
Atlanta Recap:&amp;nbsp; We need help from all the social sleuths out there...are Sheree and Tyrone still together?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two T's getting the Tea with LARSA PIPPEN | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850237/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850237/</guid><description>Podcast Description This interview is PIPPEN hot with the tea!!
Tamra is nervous because Larsa has a bone to pick with Teddi!!!! Find out why this Miami Housewife is mad at Teddi. Will they resolve their issues??&amp;nbsp;
Plus, where do&amp;nbsp;Larsa&amp;nbsp;and Scottie stand today? And will she ever get married again?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lovely Lois and Fiesta de Housewives | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850238/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850238/</guid><description>Podcast Description Let's all take a moment to honor Lois.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Then, let's join the ladies on the trip to Mexico on Diana's jet but even a private plane can't stop the drama between Sutton and Crystal.How do we all feel about Real Housewives of Dubai?&amp;nbsp; Is it boring?&amp;nbsp; The TWOTS weigh in and it may not be pretty.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>BTS BS | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850239/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 02:09:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850239/</guid><description>Podcast Description First up the MTV Awards...Hear all about why Sutton was not friendly to the TWOTS and how Teresa and Tamra made up. Some housewives seating drama.&amp;nbsp; (one housewife sat down which made another leave) Then, after the show...the TWOTS went to Tom Tom and Teddi's telling all about her talk with LVP. As if this wasn't enough, the TWOTS went to WANGO TANGO and one 'reality star' was quite rude.</description></item><item><title>OC Goodbyes and Hello Dubai | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850240/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 00:50:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850240/</guid><description>Podcast Description Will the Twots survive the MTV Movie Awards&amp;hellip;. It could get dicey!
In the meantime&amp;hellip;
The premiere of DUBAI is finally here!! Money, big yachts and loads of champagne - just how the Twots like it!!
In a shocking turn of events&amp;hellip; Teddi is impressed by Garcelle on RHOBH this week!! Find out why the Twots think she earned her paycheck&amp;hellip;
Plus&amp;hellip; did Shannon spill the beans about the RHOC cast next season?</description></item><item><title>Two T’s Getting the Tea with MONIQUE SAMUELS | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850241/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850241/</guid><description>Podcast Description This Ex-Potomac Housewife isn&amp;rsquo;t holding back and we are LOVING it!!
She tells us all about her dramatic exit from housewives, why she refused to do RHUGT and addresses her &amp;ldquo;alleged&amp;rdquo; beef with Andy.
But most importantly&amp;hellip; does she talk to Candiace after that infamous brawl?? Her hilarious response may shock you&amp;hellip;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Drama in the Desert | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850242/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 15:44:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850242/</guid><description>Podcast Description What better way to make sense of the madness on RHOBH then to go straight to the source.&amp;nbsp; Teddi texted Crystal to understand what was happening in La Quinta and bringing that info to you.&amp;nbsp;
Longtime friendships are struggling b/c of BTS drama.
Then, we head to Atlanta for even more drama. The Twots are officially invested!!
The Twots make a discovery about the marriage counselor&amp;hellip; did you know?</description></item><item><title>Two T’s Getting the Tea with LEAH MCSWEENEY | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850243/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850243/</guid><description>Podcast Description Princess Leah
Teddi has some beef with Leah McSweeney and they are going to hash it out!&amp;nbsp; (Are they????). This Twitter war has a hilarious ending&amp;hellip;
Why didn&amp;rsquo;t RHONY have a reunion last season???&amp;nbsp; Why???? Leah is here to tell us what happened during filming AND most importantly, what happened after.&amp;nbsp;
Leah shocks us with the Housewife she isn&amp;rsquo;t speaking to&amp;hellip;
Leah joins the TWOTs to talk running around naked with tiki torches to our own mental health and everything in between!</description></item><item><title>Two T’s Getting the Tea with FRANK CATANIA | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850244/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 17:49:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850244/</guid><description>Podcast Description Let&amp;rsquo;s Be Frank.
This is quite frankly the best episode ever!! Our first Husband, Frank Catania is joining the Twots straight from David&amp;rsquo;s House and&amp;hellip; IT&amp;rsquo;S NICE!!!!
Did Frank ask Dolores for permission before moving in with her ex?? Is David really dating Luis&amp;rsquo; ex?! This is crazy!!!! But we love it.
For the TWOTS when it rains it pours!! It&amp;rsquo;s the RHONJ reunion!! How are Dolores and Frank after that infamous &amp;ldquo;Buzz&amp;rdquo; comment?</description></item><item><title>It wasn't good enough for Erika... | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850245/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 23:40:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850245/</guid><description>Podcast Description Life's a Beach&amp;nbsp;The Twot's are at the Beach!&amp;nbsp;
They are live from Teddi's Beach House (The one that Erika wouldn't stay at...but it's good enough for Tamra!)&amp;nbsp;
Jersey finale is over and Andy is MAD. No one has ever seen him this mad!!&amp;nbsp;
Atlanta is serving us some realllly shady Tea...Peachy Tea!&amp;nbsp;
BH is getting better and better!&amp;nbsp;
Tamra has a surprise for Teddi!&amp;nbsp; They're having lunch with...TAYLOR ARMSTRONG!</description></item><item><title>Two T’s Getting the Tea with CARLOS KING | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850246/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850246/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is he really the King??!?!?
Who knows Housewives better than the guy who knows how the secret sauce is made?Behind every good Housewife is a&amp;hellip;&amp;nbsp;Producer!
The TWOTS are not letting Carlos King off the hook without getting some major BTS.&amp;nbsp; (he produced RHONJ and RHOA)
Teddi confronts Carlos because he recently threw some shade right at her!&amp;nbsp; OHHHHH....AWKWARD
Carlos is dishing about Teddi's firing, a craft services shocker, his favorite housewife, and his views on The Ladies of the View!</description></item><item><title>Neck and Neck | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850247/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 01:12:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850247/</guid><description>Podcast Description Talk about breathing down someone's neck&amp;hellip; Teddi's talking about her neck deep situation.
Tamra gets very emotional about her relationship with another Real Housewife.&amp;nbsp; (And we're feeling for her....)&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
If this isn't enough, we're recapping BH and it's getting HOT.&amp;nbsp; Teddi's talking about all her former castmates and puting a rumor to rest about Dorit's home invasion.&amp;nbsp;Plus, come on Frank...get your own house!&amp;nbsp; What's goin' on?!&amp;nbsp;Wow...our tea cup runneth over!</description></item><item><title>Two T’s Getting the Tea with JACKIE GOLDSCHNEIDER | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850248/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850248/</guid><description>Podcast Description She has a heart of Gold-schneider!
RHONJ fan favorite,&amp;nbsp;Jackie Goldschneider&amp;nbsp;has realized it&amp;rsquo;s time to sit down with the TWOTs.
She&amp;rsquo;s prepping us for the&amp;nbsp;rest of the finale by telling us if she thinks Melissa should have been a bridesmaid, how last season almost destroyed her family and insight on the tension between Teresa and the rest of the cast.
Plus the Twots asked her&amp;hellip; did she get the Vicki?</description></item><item><title>Tamra's Back Travelin' with the Housewives on Girls Trip | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850249/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 00:42:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850249/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tamra's going on Girls Trip and the trailer is HERE.&amp;nbsp; Tamra reveals what Eddie is NOT GOING TO BE HAPPY ABOUT, Vicki heads to the hospital and we find out who was overserved. Plus, Atlanta premieres...New Jersey Reunion is on...and the drama is delicious.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Ts Getting the Tea with CRYSTAL KUNG MINKOFF | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850250/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850250/</guid><description>Podcast Description Crystal clear!&amp;nbsp; Tam and Crystal went full twinsies in the same dress and it bonded them for life.
Teddi and Crystal have been friends for years, but that makes things real awkward when Teddi confronts her about being &amp;ldquo;different&amp;rdquo; on TV than IRL.
We learn who is bringing the drama this season.
And of course, Kiss Marry Kill BH edition.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Thirsty TWOTs in NAPA | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850251/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850251/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Twots are tipsy again. Tamra has lost her mind after being mistaken for&amp;hellip; another housewife!!!&amp;nbsp;
Even while away the recaps will stay.
Jersey and OC&amp;hellip; here we go.&amp;nbsp;
The OC Reunion has ended and the TOWTs make their guesses on who will be invited back next season. Do you agree?!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two T’s Getting the Tea with LISA RINNA, KYLE RICHARDS AND ERIKA JAYNE | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850252/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 02:39:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850252/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi and her besties Rinna, Kyle and Erika are sipping champagne and we stuck microphones in their faces.
The BH gals are spilling shocking amounts of tea aka Champagne. They are dishing so much dirt we had to get the bleep button out!
And we play kiss, marry, kill with each others husband&amp;rsquo;s AND Ex&amp;rsquo;s!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Snoozy Reunion | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850253/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 17:18:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850253/</guid><description>Podcast Description OC wasn&amp;rsquo;t a trainwreck&amp;hellip; it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a hot mess&amp;hellip; there was no drama&amp;hellip; it was dull!! The Two T&amp;rsquo;s don&amp;rsquo;t sugarcoat&amp;hellip;
Teddi and Tamra are doing fashion reviews &amp;mdash; best and worst dressed at the reunion. Their worst dressed pick could cost them their jobs&amp;hellip;
Also&amp;hellip; We CAN&amp;rsquo;T with Teresa. Why is she a grumpa-saurus??
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two T’s Getting the Tea with CAROLINE STANBURY | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850254/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 21:43:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850254/</guid><description>Podcast Description We &amp;ldquo;Stan&amp;rdquo;bury this new housewife!!
This former Lady of London is back at it on Real Housewives of Dubai. She&amp;rsquo;s spilling tea and giving us the inside scoop on the new Housewife franchise and she does not disappoint.
Plus, how did she meet her hunky husband?? And will they have kids?? Could this approach work for you?! She tells all&amp;hellip;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Watch What Happens W T F | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850255/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 22:16:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850255/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why isn&amp;rsquo;t Heather following her fellow Housewives??? What&amp;rsquo;s up with that! Why does Garcelle feel she is closer to Kathy than her own sister Kyle?? Hmmmm&amp;hellip;.
The TWOTS address these oddities and telling all about a very strange Watch What Happens Live episode!
Are you team Teresa or Marge?&amp;nbsp; Pick a side as the tea is being spilled everywhere.
Plus, Teddi unfollowed a fired housewife this week&amp;hellip; and tells us the juicy reason why!</description></item><item><title>Two T’s Getting the Tea with DOLORES CATANIA | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850256/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850256/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dolores&amp;nbsp;yourself a favor&amp;hellip; Catan-ia how quickly you need to listen to this episode.
Dolores&amp;nbsp;spills on the absurd reason why she was excluded form Teresa&amp;rsquo;s engagement party.
Then, she admits she still overwhelmed by what happened at the RHONJ reunion&amp;hellip; She has not recovered from it!
At a very low moment for Teddi,&amp;nbsp;Dolores&amp;nbsp;reached out and was unbelievably kind. Teddi for the first time shares the details behind that conversation.</description></item><item><title>Housewives on Mt. Rushmore | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850257/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 17:23:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850257/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fired Housewives are on Fire....right?!?!?!&amp;nbsp;Using Bethenny Frankel's Housewives Mt. Rushmore as inspo...the TWOTS name who they think deserves a spot on Mt. Rushmore.
As they dig in to this weeks RHOC, Tamra thinks it's just mean girls vs sad girls...do you agree?!?!?
And, Housewives breaking news... we're breaking down the just released trailer for RHOBH!!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>When Teddi’s away, Braunwyn will play | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850258/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 16:27:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850258/</guid><description>Podcast Description Braunwyn Windham&amp;nbsp;is filling in for Teddi while she is out for spring break and the tea is steaming hot. We&amp;rsquo;re talking name changes, significant others, the truth behind her relationship with Noella, and Tamra and Braunwyn&amp;rsquo;s bond.&amp;nbsp;
Braunwyn is such an epic guest host, we made her an honorary Twot!
(Oh, and we&amp;rsquo;re recapping NJ &amp;amp; OC too!)
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two T’s Getting the Tea with KANDI BURRUSS | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850259/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850259/</guid><description>Podcast Description I want Kandi!! RHOA fan favorite, Kandi Burruss is joining the Twots. Kandi explains why being in the Big Brother house was way harder than Housewives.&amp;nbsp;
Kandi had concerns that this season of Atlanta would feel lack luster without two of the OG housewives but she was pleasantly surprised. Find out why!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two T’s Getting the Tea with LUANN DE LESSEPS | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850260/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 17:48:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850260/</guid><description>Podcast Description Luann&amp;nbsp;gives an honest and vulnerable explanation of her less than desirable appearance on stage the other night.
Plus, there is obviously major breaking news in the RHONY world&amp;hellip;&amp;nbsp;Luann&amp;nbsp;explains what&amp;rsquo;s happening and whether or not she&amp;rsquo;ll be involved.
Luann&amp;nbsp;tells the ladies were she stands with Bethenny and Dorinda.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Twots are Talking | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850261/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 01:18:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850261/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tamra is setting the record straight about her relationship with Shannon. Speaking of the OC&amp;hellip; Teddi and Tamra are digging deep and they are totally coming around on one of the women&amp;hellip; and are actually starting to like her!!&amp;nbsp;
On to New Jersey&amp;hellip; why was Teresa in such a bad mood?!?
Plus the Twots tell all about the iHeartRadio Music Awards and all their celeb spotings!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Two T’s Getting the Tea with RHOM’s NICOLE MARTIN | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850262/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850262/</guid><description>Podcast Description The TWOTS can't focus on what Nicole Martin has to say because they are blinded by the bling this Miami Housewife is rockin'!&amp;nbsp;
He put a ring on it, lucky for us, so Nicole is dishing on her engagement and upcoming wedding. She reveals WHO made the wedding guest list and who isn&amp;rsquo;t helping plan her wedding.&amp;nbsp;
Nicole is giving our Thirsty Twots all the RHOM gossip, juice, and dirt they need!</description></item><item><title>Two T’s getting the Tea with MARGARET JOSEPHS | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850263/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 16:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850263/</guid><description>Podcast Description Margaret Josephs is in the hot seat ready to dish.
Teddi confronts her about a not so sweet tweet.
Will Marg be invited to Teresa&amp;rsquo;s wedding?&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;
Margaret must choose between Jen and Teresa&amp;hellip; who would she pick for a Girls Trip?
And what happened to those pigtails?
The Twots are getting all the NJ tea.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Its Getting Hot in Here | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850264/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 17:20:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850264/</guid><description>Podcast Description While the TWOTS are discussing OC things get so heated that Tamra had to get Kelly Dodd on to get her opinion.
Kyle insisted that Teddi go to the doctor this week and likely it saved Teddi&amp;rsquo;s life.
Could it save yours?
Is Evan Goldschneider (RHONJ - Jackie&amp;rsquo;s Husband) the male version of Teddi??!! You decide!&amp;nbsp;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>This is Salty!! | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850265/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 23:27:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850265/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ok...so before we get to the SLC Reunion&amp;hellip; here's some TEAAAAAAAAAA.
Teddi bumped in to a REAL HOUSEWIFE at Catch this weekend&amp;hellip; and that Housewife had a real bone to pick with Teddi!!&amp;nbsp; And it was ON!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Back to the Reunion&amp;hellip; dramatic or snoozefest?!?!?!&amp;nbsp;
And, the question we all need to know&amp;hellip; Will Tamra return to RHOC?!??!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two T’s getting the Tea with CYNTHIA BAILEY | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850266/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850266/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cynthia Bailey is incredible!! She shared so much juicy juice with the Twots - you need to listen immediately.&amp;nbsp;
#1 She got Vicki&amp;rsquo;d
#2 What her biggest regret is from RHOA
#3 Which Housewife supported her the most during Celebrity Big&amp;nbsp;Brother&amp;nbsp;
#4 Why are you still reading this?
Listen now!!!!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Overserved Twots | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850267/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 03:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850267/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Twots are tipsy and you're the beneficiary!! The Twots are filled with truth serum as they recap Miami, OC and NJ.&amp;nbsp;
We&amp;rsquo;d love to tell you all the highlights but the entire hour is Twots filled tea spilling!!&amp;nbsp;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two T’s Getting the Tea with RHOM’s GUERDY ABRAIRA | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850268/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 20:22:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850268/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our Guerdyian Angel!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We got a hot mic!! | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850269/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 00:43:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850269/</guid><description>Podcast Description It seems like you’re either Team Lisa or Team everybody else.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Nose Knows | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850270/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 03:05:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850270/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Twots are doing a deep dive on whether or not you should admit if you’ve had “work done”. Housewives…. You aren’t fooling anybody!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>It’s all relative | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850271/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 20:56:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850271/</guid><description>Podcast Description Breaking news!!! Tamra is related to TWO of the SLC stars. All will be revealed.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Miami Vice | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850272/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 04:29:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850272/</guid><description>Podcast Description Miami finale did not disappoint. The TWOTs are dishing on this amazing ep. The drama was intense. The TWOTS cried, laughed and were in shock.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rub a Dub Dub | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850273/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 04:23:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850273/</guid><description>Podcast Description Was it #goals or cringy.com when Eddie and Tamra had their bathtub makeout sesh? Well, RHOSLC’s Whitney and Justin have topped it. If you like cheesy bedroom nude love scenes, this podcast is for you.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hot to Twot | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850274/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 21:53:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850274/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nothing like a wet lunch in Miami!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>You thirsty?? | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850275/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 20:44:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850275/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’ve got the tea on RHOC, RHOM &amp;amp; RHONJ.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two T’s Getting the Tea with MELISSA GORGA | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850276/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 20:15:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850276/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad-choices at https://www.iheartpodcastnetwork.comSee omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>First is the Worst | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850277/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 05:53:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850277/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi’s back!! Uh Oh, that means she was the first eliminated from the Big Brother House.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Let your Hair do the Talking (with Justin Anderson) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850278/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 08:07:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850278/</guid><description>Podcast Description NJ is back! And it does not disappoint! Teresa’s new boyfriend is our hot topic … is he hot or in hot water???!!!!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Here comes the King (w/ Meghan King) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850279/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:19:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850279/</guid><description>Podcast Description All hail the King! Meghan is here and not holding back!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two T’s Getting the Tea with RHOM’S ALEXIA ECHEVARRIA NEPOLA | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850280/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 01:53:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850280/</guid><description>Podcast Description This entire episode is so juicy and there is so much tea… You’re just going to need to listen!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>ONE OF THE TWOTS is joining Celebrity Big Brother… | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850281/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 02:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850281/</guid><description>Podcast Description Listen Now!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ripped from the Headlines | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850282/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 20:58:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850282/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andy Cohen reveals his favorite Housewife Mother-In-Law and one of the TWOTS is super mad.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two T’s Getting the Tea with DORIT KEMSLEY | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850283/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 20:03:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850283/</guid><description>Podcast Description We love some Dorit OHS!! The TWOTS are going one on one with Dorit Kemsley.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Party Pooper | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850284/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 04:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850284/</guid><description>Podcast Description Every party has a pooper, that&amp;rsquo;s why we invited you.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two T’s getting the Tea with VICKI GUNVALSON | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850285/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 20:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850285/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vicki Gunvalson is here, sharing her side, and telling all.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bienvenido a Miami | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850286/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 18:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850286/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s getting Hot in Here (IN MIAMI)! Are we team Todd or not? While it&amp;rsquo;s getting a bit frigid and creepy (IN UTAH) as discuss Seth at his own Birthday! And what is going on in The OC? Heather vs Shannon!?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Fired Housewives answering all your questions as only Ex-wives can | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850287/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 21:17:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850287/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Two T&amp;rsquo;s are answering your questions and nothing is off limits. Who is the biggest Housewives Diva? You won&amp;rsquo;t believe what Teddi and Tamra say!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Housewives Hot Messes | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850288/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 20:11:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850288/</guid><description>Podcast Description Meghan’s split. Vicki’s Ex gets engaged. Andy gets messy!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two T’s getting the tea with DORINDA MEDLEY | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850289/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 04:15:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850289/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a perfect medley….
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Brandi (You’re a Fine Girl) | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850290/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 03:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850290/</guid><description>Podcast Description Everyone needs a little Brandi for the Holidays! Brandi Glanville joins the Two T’s to talk Miami &amp;amp; OC.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>It’s Not All Diamonds and Rosé | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850291/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850291/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ex’s are best but so are authors who have interviewed almost every Housewife. Author Dave Quinn wrote “Not All Diamonds and Rosé: The Inside Story of The Real Housewives from the People Who Lived It” and he is spilling the tea with the two T’s.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Keeping it REAL | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850292/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 02:58:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850292/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tamra and Teddi are coming in hot while talking about Miami. The shade is everywhere on our trip to the OC&amp;hellip; and burrrrr things are frigid in Salt Lake City!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two T's Getting The Tea From PORSHA WILLIAMS | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850293/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850293/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tamra and Teddi are joined by Former Real Housewives of Atlanta Star Porsha Williams. Was she fired or did she leave on her own?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sushi-Gate | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850294/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 23:40:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850294/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do you spend $36,000 on sushi, Heather? And, who is paying for that!? Tamra SHOCKS Teddi with some inside information about her own Housewives expenses. We disect Mary&amp;rsquo;s apology even questioning why did it look like a Party invitation.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two T's Getting the Tea from KYLE RICHARDS | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850295/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850295/</guid><description>Podcast Description Like never before, Kyle Richards is here telling all.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>UTAH Brouhaha | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850296/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 20:50:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850296/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi and Tamra are not holding back as they discuss Salt Lake City! Why is Mary so Scary??? Are you Team Mary or Team Whitney?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ex's Do It Best | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850297/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 21:59:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850297/</guid><description>Podcast Description Introducing Two T’s in a Pod&amp;hellip; OC’s Tamra Judge and BH&amp;rsquo;s Teddi Mellencamp are united and it feels so good. T and T are spilling so much tea you could fill an ocean!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Real-Time Crime | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850298/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 22:44:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850298/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you obsessed with solving crimes? Are you a sleuth for the truth with a self-awarded PHD in unsolved mysteries? Do you believe you should be giving an FYI to the FBI?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Scheana Shaying her Secrets | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850299/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850299/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vanderpump Rules star Scheana Shay is joining Teddi live from Las Vegas. The new mom is letting us in on secrets from the new season of Vanderpump Rules including the drama surrounding Brock and why she sheds a lot of tears in the upcoming episodes.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mom Life is Hard | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850300/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850300/</guid><description>Podcast Description The #Imomsohard Moms, Kristin and Jen, join Teddi to answer all your pressing mom questions, parenting question, is your husband making you crazy questions. Nothing is TMI for these ladies.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Teddi Gets Real about her Return to Real Housewives of Beverly Hills | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850301/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 00:19:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850301/</guid><description>Podcast Description Garcelle called her &amp;ldquo;Annoying&amp;rdquo; and a &amp;ldquo;GNAT&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip;.let&amp;rsquo;s see how Teddi feels about that&amp;hellip;my goodness&amp;hellip; Kyle Richards joins Teddi as they talk about it all!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>All the Tea on An Unorthodox Life | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850302/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 04:40:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850302/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi is joined by Batsheva Haart from the Netflix hit show An Unorthodox Life.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Doctor Doctor | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850303/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 20:15:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850303/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our health has become the top priority.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Teddi Shares Her Story | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850304/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 04:19:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850304/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s on everyone&amp;rsquo;s minds again. Covid, the Delta Variant, and Teddi is revealing it happened to her. Fully vaccinated with a breakthrough case and she&amp;rsquo;s sharing her story.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>40 and Fabulous | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850305/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 04:54:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850305/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi is turning the big 4-0. What better way to celebrate than a surprise serenade from Teddi’s Dad. Plus, find out why he missed her birth!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Check into the Hilton | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850306/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 04:15:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850306/</guid><description>Podcast Description Beverly Hills housewife Kathy Hilton joins Teddi and is spilling ALL the Tea! Kathy is calm and a great mediator amongst the housewives, but will she get sucked in to the drama especially with her sister!? Teddi wants to know how Kathy really feels about joining the show and why she didn&amp;rsquo;t tell Paris and Nicky about it.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Asset Management | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850307/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850307/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jana Kramer joins Teddi to talk about her &amp;ldquo;Mommy Makeover&amp;rdquo; aka &amp;ldquo;boob job&amp;rdquo;. Also, did you see this the botox blunder that went viral? Beauty blogger Whitney Buhu showed you every details of her botox gone wrong. It was described as a droopy eyelid but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t quite do it justice. Even after what she went through, she may get botox again. WHAT?!?!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dorit So Sweet | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850308/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850308/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi and Dorit are talking and telling all.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Crystal Clear | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850309/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850309/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi reveals that she is the reason for new Beverly Hills Housewife Crystal Kung Minkoff. Crystal joins Teddi to tell all. Crystal talks about the warrant out for her arrest and the friendliest fellow housewife.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Housewives Reunited and It Feels So Good | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850310/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 17:30:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850310/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kyle Richards is here answering your questions and calls. Nothing is off limits. LVP is on the top of our list of topics.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Moms are dealing with a lot of S**t! | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850311/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 16:37:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850311/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tori Spelling and Witney Carson
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Good Doctor | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850312/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 01:09:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850312/</guid><description>Podcast Description You asked&amp;hellip;we answered. You asked about the effectiveness of the vaccine, side effects from the second shot, getting back to normal life, how long will we be wearing masks, and so much more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Princess Diaries | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850313/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 01:15:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850313/</guid><description>Podcast Description Like everyone else on the planet, we&amp;rsquo;re talking about Oprah&amp;rsquo;s interview with Harry and Meghan.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Introducing This is Paris | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850314/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850314/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join Paris Hilton each week as she speaks candidly with her friends and family, the hottest in movies, music, and television, innovators, creators, newsmakers, and icons. Paris will sit down for edgy, in depth conversations with a multitude of unexpected guests.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Fake Famous &amp; #FreeBritney | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850315/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 05:02:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850315/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you seen Fake Famous? What is Fake Famous? Teddi is discussing this fascinating film with the director and producer. Teddi is also obsessed with &amp;ldquo;Framing Britney Spears&amp;rdquo;. We are breaking it down from every angle.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Side Parts, Skinny Jeans &amp; Sex | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850316/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850316/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi is joined by E!&amp;rsquo;s Carissa Culiner to discuss an assortment of important topics.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Momma Knows Best | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850317/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 02:15:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850317/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mom tips and Mom advice from some badass Mom Bosses
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Good Binge | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850318/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850318/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wondering what to watch? What’s hot? What’s not? What’s the Must See Show? We will tell you.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Waiting Til the Last Minute | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850319/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 01:02:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850319/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dancing with the Stars Cheryl Burke and Project Runway designer Matt Sarafa join Teddi.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Teddi Mellencamp Talks with Jillian Michaels | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850320/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 17:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850320/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi and Jillian address their “feud”.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Little Ditty 'bout | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850321/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 22:43:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850321/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi’s dad John Mellencamp joins Teddi to co-host this episode.
It is their first interview together...ever!
What does this music legend think about his daughter appearing on Real Housewives of Beverly Hills? How does he feel about her public friendships and feuds?
This is an in-depth heartfelt conversation between a dad and a daughter who just happen to be an icon and a “real housewife”.
Learn more about your ad-choices at https://www.</description></item><item><title>Teddi Tells All | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850322/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 05:37:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850322/</guid><description>Podcast Description Was she fired? What happened? Why isn't Teddi returning to the Real Housewives of Beverly Hills?
Guest co-host former Bachelor Bob Guiney will ask Teddi....EVERYTHING.
It's quite shocking how Teddi found she wasn't returning to the show. Hear the story and how she feels about it.
Will we ever see her on TV again?
Which housewife did she reach out to?
What did Andy say to her?
Will she remain friends with the other ladies?</description></item><item><title>Teddi Responds | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850323/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2020 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850323/</guid><description>Podcast Description Please listen to a special episode of Teddi Tea Pod. In this episode, we have a conversation about All In. I’ll answer your questions about what ALL IN is and what we do.
Learn more about your ad-choices at https://www.iheartpodcastnetwork.comSee omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why Ya Gotta Be So Mean? | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850324/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850324/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi has been encountering painful bullying online.
And they are going after the kids.
We bring in a cyber bullying expert to give everyone advise on how to handle it.
And, Rebecca Black from "Friday Friday" fame helps Teddi by sharing her own story of cyber bullying
Learn more about your ad-choices at https://www.iheartpodcastnetwork.comSee omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Waking Up to a Nightmare | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850325/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850325/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi woke up at 1am and looked at her instagram to find more than 100 comments with death threats. People are saying her kids getting hurt is the karma she deserves.
Teddi tries to cope with it all and discusses with her friend Matt how to handle it.
Teddi realizes how resilient kids are through it all. Slates finger is fully recovered, Cruz has a cool cast, and Doves surgery went really well.</description></item><item><title>Love for Dove | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850326/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850326/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s the day of Teddi’s sweet baby Dove’s surgery.
Teddi has decided to share the complete story
Dove’s doctor joins Teddi as the family prepares to endure this challenging ordeal.
Other friends join Teddi to ease her concerns and help her get through it.
Learn more about your ad-choices at https://www.iheartpodcastnetwork.comSee omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bitch Better Have My Money | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850327/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 03:58:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850327/</guid><description>Podcast Description We have two money and financial experts to give us all much needed help.
Jean Chatzy and Lynn Richardson don't sugarcoat the situation but they do offer practical ideas you can use.
Spend less and know what you are spending money on. Figure out what is important.
Jean gives Teddi tips that are effective to save money.
Lynn advises couples about how to stop arguing over money. Multiple streams of income are likely necessary.</description></item><item><title>Hope Floats | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850328/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 04:26:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850328/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi is bringing in a team of experts for a discussion about staying hopeful right now.
Can we find optimism, hope, positivity? Does it even exist right now?
Anxiety is at an all time high, you can't sleep at night, you're exhausted.
We can't solve everything but we have enlisted the best to try to help and ease your stress and worries, find a little calm, and make things just a little bit easier.</description></item><item><title>Back to School | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850329/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850329/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi opens up about baby Dove’s upcoming surgery. And then, It’s on everyone’s minds... kids and school.
Should kids go back to the classroom? Are kids really able to learn virtually from home? How do parents make the right decisions?
Teddi’s team of experts discuss every aspect, answering all the tough questions as they sort through this Impossibly complicated issue.
Learn more about your ad-choices at https://www.iheartpodcastnetwork.comSee omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Gone Girl | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850330/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 04:39:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850330/</guid><description>Podcast Description After breaking down all the recent celebrities breakups, now it’s time for Teddi and Dr. V to help us with the situation at home.
Should you stay together? Should you head your separate ways?
Can these marriages be saved?
Learn more about your ad-choices at https://www.iheartpodcastnetwork.comSee omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Breaking Down the Breakups | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850331/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 14:07:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850331/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi’s back.
Why are so many celebrities getting divorced? We are dishing the details
Teddi opens up about Her daughter Slate’s injury after an accident.
Teddi reveals what “closet time” is and how it might help you at home
Learn more about your ad-choices at https://www.iheartpodcastnetwork.comSee omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>ABCs of CBD | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850332/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 05:08:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850332/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shayna Taylor joins Teddi to offer her expertise about CBD, easing anxiety, diet and of course life as Ryan Seacrest’s girlfriend.
Learn more about your ad-choices at https://www.iheartpodcastnetwork.comSee omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nanny Knows Best | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850333/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 04:48:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850333/</guid><description>Podcast Description Not your average Jo.
The parenting advice we all need!
Learn more about your ad-choices at https://www.iheartpodcastnetwork.comSee omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Teddi's Back | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850334/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 04:27:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850334/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stitchless and hormonal, Teddi Mellencamp returns to tell us everything about the birth of Dove, nursing after a "boob job", intimacy after birth and in quarantine, the kids and so much more. Plus, staying calm during so much uncertainty. Guest host Tanya Rad joins Teddi as well as special guest Marriage and Family Therapist Jennie Marie Battistin.
Learn more about your ad-choices at https://www.iheartpodcastnetwork.comSee omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Due Date with Kristin Cavallari | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850335/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850335/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi is about to give birth any minute Kristin Cavallari talks birth and babies with Teddi and they are really telling it like it is
Learn more about your ad-choices at https://www.iheartpodcastnetwork.comSee omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hit Me Baby, One More Time | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850336/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850336/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi’s baby will be here very soon ... what does that mean for her marriage?
Will they ever have sex again?
Forget sex, Will they ever sleep again ?
Find out why morning dates can save your relationship.
We’re doing some marriage boot camp of our own with Dr. V.
Learn more about your ad-choices at https://www.iheartpodcastnetwork.comSee omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Heart Attack | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850337/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850337/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's almost Valentine's Day so it's time to talk about....Sex.
Teddi and the fabulous Dr. Viviana Coles (Married at First Sight) are answering your questions about relationships, intimacy and sex. Their candid answers can help even a non-believer let Cupid's arrow open up your heart.
Learn more about your ad-choices at https://www.iheartpodcastnetwork.comSee omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Catching the Love Bug | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850338/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850338/</guid><description>Podcast Description February is the month of love. Teddi and her panel of love experts are here to help us understand love, romance, relationships and sex. Can they solve our heartbreak and heartache, lack of sex, and love problems in time for Valentine's Day? Teddi has the answers to give you the love story you want!
Learn more about your ad-choices at https://www.iheartpodcastnetwork.comSee omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Co-Parenting Co-Operation with Lala Kent | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850339/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850339/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vanderpump Rules star Lala Kent and her fiance Randall join Teddi to reveal how they handle co-parenting with Randall's Ex and how Lala became best friends with Ambyr. Co-parenting started out messy but they were able to turn it around. They also detail their wedding planning and when will they have kids.
Plus, Lala reveals a Vanderpump Pregnancy Pact.
Teddi brings on expert Kati Morton to help assist everyone sorting out co-parenting and how to do it successfully.</description></item><item><title>Why Worry? | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850340/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850340/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi sits down with an expert panel to break down when to worry about our children’s worries and how worrisome it all truly is!
Award winning author of You Are a F*cking Awesome Mom, Leslie Bruce and Adolescent Psychotherapist Susan Zinn lend their expertise and advice to help us understand children with stress and anxiety.
Learn more about your ad-choices at https://www.iheartpodcastnetwork.comSee omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Shape of Things to Come | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850341/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850341/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi starts the new year off ALL IN. She's guiding us with her expertise and enlisting support from Biggest Loser coach Erica Lugo. Erica shares her powerful story with Teddi and everyone is inspired.
And, if you want a Revenge Body listen as Teddi works with Autumn Calabrese to get us all in shape.
Learn more about your ad-choices at https://www.iheartpodcastnetwork.comSee omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>All In 2020 | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850342/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 05:23:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850342/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ed Mylett is a PEAK PERFORMANCE EXPERT and he is here with Teddi to help us all achieve our goals in 2020.
Scrubbing In Host, Tanya Rad joins her friend Teddi to talk about the power of a Vision Board and why we need to start the year with a clear focus of what we want.
And, anything is possible with Cherie Healey and she wants you to know anything is possible.</description></item><item><title>We Should Talk About This | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850343/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850343/</guid><description>Podcast Description Real Housewives of New Jersey star Jackie Goldschneider shares her personal journey with Teddi of coping with and living with an extreme eating disorder. The women are bonded when Jackie reveals the extreme ups and downs of living with and recovering from Anorexia.
Our friend, Jess Clarke then joins Teddi to talk about how her struggle with diet connected to sports led her to walk to be an advocate for women combating this all too common disease.</description></item><item><title>The Grieving Process | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850344/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850344/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi shares with us the heartbreaking story of the loss of their family pet.
She breaks down and opens up about what happened to their beloved Khaleesi. Everyone experiences grief throughout their life and we lean on expert David Kessler to guide us through techniques to survive the grief.
Learn more about your ad-choices at https://www.iheartpodcastnetwork.comSee omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Under the Influence | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850345/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 09:55:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850345/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is Social Media our best Frenemy? Are we spending too much time scrolling, double tapping and swiping? What does it take to be an influencer? Are influencers a more honest form of advertising? Should we be FaceTuning, Vscoing, Photoshopping, and Filtering? Are we altering reality too much? Should we be panicking about our kids and social media?
Learn more about your ad-choices at https://www.iheartpodcastnetwork.comSee omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Are You KIDding Me? | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850346/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850346/</guid><description>Podcast Description What do you think of someone who doesn't want children?
Teddi explores this and it's a growing trend. She talks to Mary, a woman who simply doesn't want kids. Why is there so much shame and judgement? Why is it embarrassing or considered weird?
Teddi asks Professor Amy Blackstone, who studies childlessness and the childfree choice, to share her knowledge and expertise. Filmmaker Maxine Trump joins in about her new documentary TO KID OR NOT TO KID.</description></item><item><title>Addicted to... .with Cameron Douglas and Jason Wahler | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850347/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850347/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cameron Douglas discusses addiction, his time in prison, his relationship with Dad Michael and what the future looks like.
Jason Wahler discusses his relapse on The Hills and why it happened and what he’s doing about it.
They both give thoughtful advice to those suffering from addiction themselves or within their family.
Learn more about your ad-choices at https://www.iheartpodcastnetwork.comSee omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cheater Cheater Pumpkin Eater with Brandi Glanville | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850348/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850348/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi and Brandi unravel all aspects of cheating
Brandi has her own personal experience and is not afraid to share her thoughts
Why does it happen?
Do men cheat more than women?
Do people cheat even if the relationship is good?
Why do people cheat with the nanny?
They talk with the owner of westside nannies to understand what an appropriate and inappropriate relationship is with your nanny</description></item><item><title>Fear Factor | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850349/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850349/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi unravels the mystery of Fear.
Whether you are afraid of the dark or afraid of death, we are discovering why we are afraid.
If you are filled with anxiety or simply afraid of mice, Teddi is answering why.
With experts and those who seem to have no fear, we answer why are we afraid.
Learn more about your ad-choices at https://www.iheartpodcastnetwork.comSee omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>She's Having a Baby | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850350/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 04:07:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850350/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi conceived naturally after struggling with infertility with her first two children. She opens up and breaks down sharing her story and the heartwrenching details.
Teddi then learns from her guests their stories and their journey. Sadie, single and over 30 decided to freeze her eggs. Michelle, 46 and a cancer survivor, used a sperm donor and is pregnant with her first. Julia, multiple miscarriages and now has triplets!</description></item><item><title>Breaking Bad | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850351/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850351/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teddi is breaking down, breaking apart, breakups. If you are going through a breakup, you must listen. If you are stuck in a relationship that isn't ideal, you must listen.
Kathryn Woodward Thomas is with us giving us the answers. She invented CONSCIOUS UNCOUPLING and we learn what it really is and why it works. We have experts here to give you the real help you need. How do you get through it?</description></item><item><title>Don’t Fall In Love with a Narcissist | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850352/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 04:46:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850352/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is narcissism? What does the term really mean?
Who has it and what do you do if you fall in love with them?
Teddi and narcissism expert Dr. Ramani explore it, explain it and evaluate what the heck we should do it about it. Learn more about your ad-choices at https://www.iheartpodcastnetwork.comSee omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What is NXIVM? | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850353/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 04:37:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850353/</guid><description>Podcast Description Catherine Oxenberg joins Teddi and guest co-host Sam Rubin. She explains her daughter's role in NXIVM and how she was instrumental in getting her out and holding the guilty responsible. She fought to save her child. Sam &amp;amp; Teddi then discuss Terrance Howard's "interesting" red carpet interview.
And the age old debate of how to discipline your child. Learn more about your ad-choices at https://www.iheartpodcastnetwork.comSee omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Down the Rabbit Hole | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850354/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 04:14:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850354/</guid><description>Podcast Description Could an open marriage actually work? What is swinging?Thomas Middleditch says it saved his relationship!Teddi goes down this rabbit hole with a couple of swingers. Then we step all over the idea of a foot fetishWhy is everyone sucking on toes?Is it safe? Is it a turn on?Let’s get the answers.
Introducing Teddi Mellencamp and the Teddi Tea Pod on iHeartRadio.
Learn more about your ad-choices at https://www.iheartpodcastnetwork.comSee omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>Teddi Tea Pod Trailer | Two Ts In A Pod with Teddi Mellencamp and Tamra Judge</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7949850355/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 08:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7949850355/</guid><description>Podcast Description Check out Teddi Tea Pod on iHeartRadio or wherever you get your podcasts!
Learn more about your ad-choices at https://www.iheartpodcastnetwork.comSee omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>