<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Carrie Jade Does Not Exist on SWIEST - Transcripts 路 Screenplays 路 Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/carrie-jade-does-not-exist/</link><description>Recent content in Carrie Jade Does Not Exist on SWIEST - Transcripts 路 Screenplays 路 Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 06:00:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/carrie-jade-does-not-exist/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Episode 6: Finding Samantha | Carrie Jade Does Not Exist</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3369310001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 06:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3369310001/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2022, Carrie Jade Williams disappeared out of sight. After years of travelling around Ireland befriending and then scamming vulnerable women, Kat's investigation came out and Carrie Jade's house of cards fell apart. So... where is "Carrie Jade" now? In this episode, Sue Perkins and Katherine Denkinson speak to some of the people who knew Carrie Jade the best and then they try to hear her side of the story.</description></item><item><title>Episode 5: The Fraud | Carrie Jade Does Not Exist</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3369310002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 06:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3369310002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sue Perkins and Katherine Denkinson delve into Carrie Jade's mysterious life to find out what compels a compulsive liar and investigate the ramifications that Carrie's lies had on the people who once trusted her.
To keep up with the podcast, follow us on social media @carriejadepod and If you have a story to share, email us at carriejadedoesnotexist@gmail.com
The finale of Carrie Jade Does Not Exist comes out on Thursday 30th November.</description></item><item><title>Were there other women? | Carrie Jade Does Not Exist</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3369310003/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3369310003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Since releasing the first episodes of Carrie Jade Does Not Exist, we've heard a variety of unaired stories about Samantha and her many different lives, but could there be even more to the story than we can see? If so, we want you to get in touch.
To keep up with the podcast, follow us on social media @carriejadepod and If you have a story to share, email us at carriejadedoesnotexist@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Episode 4: The Mother | Carrie Jade Does Not Exist</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3369310004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 06:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3369310004/</guid><description>Podcast Description So far we've met Lucy Fitzwilliam the therapist, Carrie Jade the activist, Lucy Hart the au pair, Claudia Bronwyn the bridesmaid, and Rebecca Fitzgerald the autism therapist. But before all of these identities, there was just one woman, Samantha.&amp;nbsp;
In this episode, Sue Perkins and Katherine Denkinson uncover the true story of Samantha Cookes, a woman whose life was changed by an unimaginable tragedy.
To keep up with the podcast, follow us on social media @carriejadepod and If you have a story to share, email us at carriejadedoesnotexist@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Episode 3: The Surrogate | Carrie Jade Does Not Exist</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3369310005/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 06:00:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3369310005/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Lucy Hart, a smiley 26-year-old from the UK arrived in Tullamore Ireland in 2014, she seemed like the perfect au pair. But the truth behind Lucy's life before she became an au pair spanned two countries, three children and a long history of lies.
In this episode, Sue Perkins and Katherine Denkinson hear stories from the women who hired Lucy to look after their children and dive deep into a story stranger and darker than anybody could have predicted to investigate the woman behind the identity of Lucy Hart.</description></item><item><title>Episode 2: The Therapist | Carrie Jade Does Not Exist</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3369310006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 06:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3369310006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who would you entrust your children with? How would you feel if you found out that the woman looking after your kids wasn't qualified to provide the therapy she claimed to be an expert in?
In this episode, Sue Perkins and Katherine Denkinson meet Lucy and Rebecca, mysterious child therapists who moved to small towns in Ireland claiming to be therapists for disabled children. But Lucy and Rebeca weren't who they said they were, and the story behind the 'therapy' they provided was much darker than anybody could have predicted.</description></item><item><title>Episode 1: The Activist | Carrie Jade Does Not Exist</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3369310007/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 06:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3369310007/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2021, Carrie Jade Williams posted a video saying she was being sued by her AirBnB guests for the disability aids in her home. She went viral on TikTok, won a prestigious literary essay competition, and branded herself as a disability activist living with Huntington's Disease. But Carrie Jade wasn't who she said she was.
In Episode 1, Sue Perkins meets Katherine Denkinson, the journalist who uncovered the astounding truth behind the real life of Carrie Jade Williams.</description></item><item><title>Carrie Jade Does Not Exist | Carrie Jade Does Not Exist</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3369310008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 11:48:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3369310008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Carrie Jade Does Not Exist is the story of how one woman, who took on over six different identities, infiltrated the lives of vulnerable people, and lied her way into gaining their trust. This six-part series hosted by Sue Perkins and journalist Katherine Denkinson will tell the story of how Carrie built up a picture-perfect persona and scammed her way into the literary world until she finally got tangled up in her very own web of lies.</description></item></channel></rss>