<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ireland Crimes and Mysteries on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/ireland-crimes-and-mysteries/</link><description>Recent content in Ireland Crimes and Mysteries on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 19:00:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/ireland-crimes-and-mysteries/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Christmas Nightmare: The Whelan Family Tragedy. | Ireland Crimes and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3388540014/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 19:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3388540014/</guid><description>Podcast Description A Christmas Nightmare: The Whelan Family Tragedy&amp;quot; delves into the heart-wrenching events of Christmas Eve in 2008, forever marking the lives of the Whelan family. In a chilling arson attack that unfolded within the festive warmth of their rented farmhouse, just a mile from her parents home in Windgap, Co. Kilkenny, a loving mother, Sharon Whelan, and her two young daughters, Zarah 7 and Nadia 2, lost their lives in a devastating blaze, but what was initially thought to be a tragic accident turned out to be something far more sinister.</description></item><item><title>The Forgotten Girl: Mary Boyles Story | Ireland Crimes and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3388540001/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 19:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3388540001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to Ireland Crimes and Mysteries, This episode delves into the haunting and unresolved mystery surrounding the disappearance of Mary Boyle in Cashelard, County Donegal, Ireland, in March 1977.
In this episode, we embark on a journey through the windswept landscapes and tight-knit communities of Co.Donegal, where the mysterious vanishing of Mary Boyle has left an indelible mark on the region&amp;rsquo;s history. Join us as we navigate through the intricate web of clues, theories, and unanswered questions that surround this perplexing case.</description></item><item><title>The Curious Case of Peter Bergmann | Ireland Crimes and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3388540002/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 19:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3388540002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to the Ireland Crimes and Mysteries Podcast, In this episode, we will be talking about the intriguing and unexplained case of Peter Bergmann, whose lifeless body washed ashore on the beach in Rosses Point, Sligo, on June 16th, 2009.
We will talk about the perplexing events surrounding Peter Bergmann&amp;rsquo;s final days, exploring the mysterious decisions that led him to the shores of Sligo. Who was Peter Bergmann, and why did he choose to vanish in such a puzzling manner?</description></item><item><title>The Disappearance of a Legend: Shergars Story | Ireland Crimes and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3388540003/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 19:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3388540003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to The Disappearance of a legend:Shergars Story, a podcast that unravels the captivating tale of one of Ireland&amp;rsquo;s most famous and enduring mysteries. In 1983, the world was left stunned when the champion racehorse Shergar was kidnapped from the Ballymany Stud in County Kildare.
Join us as we journey back in time to explore the events surrounding Shergar&amp;rsquo;s disappearance, the baffling ransom demands and the investigation that followed.</description></item><item><title>Beyond the Trees: Imelda, Liam and Father Joes Story. | Ireland Crimes and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3388540004/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 18:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3388540004/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode &amp;ldquo;Beyond the Trees: Imelda, Liam and Fr Joes Story&amp;rdquo; takes you deep into the heart of a chilling and devastating series of events that unfolded in the peaceful countryside of Whitegate, Co Clare in 1994.
We delve into the horrifying events that claimed the lives of Imelda Riney, her 3 year old son Liam and young curate Father Joe Walsh at the tranquil Cregg Wood. At the center of this gruesome tale is Brendan O&amp;rsquo;Donnell, the man whose actions forever shattered the tranquility of the community and opened a scar that will never heal on the families left behind.</description></item><item><title>Fatal Encounter: Karen Buckleys Story. | Ireland Crimes and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3388540005/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3388540005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to &amp;ldquo;Fatal Encounter: Karen Buckleys Story&amp;rdquo; a podcast that explores one of Scotland&amp;rsquo;s most shocking and heart-wrenching criminal cases. In 2015, the vibrant city of Glasgow became the backdrop for a crime that shook an entire community and left the two nations, that of Scotland and Ireland in disbelief. This gripping episode introduces you to Karen and talks about her life and untimely death, She was a young Irish nursing student with a promising future.</description></item><item><title>The Missing Pieces: Annie McCarrick | Ireland Crimes and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3388540006/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3388540006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join us on a journey into the heart of Ireland&amp;rsquo;s most perplexing unsolved mystery. In 1993, Annie McCarrick, a vibrant and adventurous young woman, vanished without a trace somewhere in the picturesque land of Ireland. In this podcast, we delve deep into the case, exploring the events leading up to her disappearance, the investigation that followed, and the enduring questions that continue to baffle investigators and haunt those who loved her.</description></item><item><title>Uncovering the Maamtrasna Massacre: Ireland’s Forgotten Tragedy | Ireland Crimes and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3388540007/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3388540007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can you imagine the terror and chaos of having your close-knit community in the remote Irish village of Maamtrasna turned upside down by a gruesome crime? Experience this gripping tale from 1882 as we unravel the horrific attack on the Joyce family and the chilling aftermath that provoked fear and suspicion among locals, ultimately leading to a controversial trial under the newly passed Prevention of Crimes Act. Welcome to a world where tales of dark mysteries and unjust convictions come alive.</description></item><item><title>Echoes of Absence: The Mysterious Vanishing of Dean Roche | Ireland Crimes and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3388540008/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3388540008/</guid><description>Podcast Description What if you found yourself entangled in a web of mystery, questioning the very fabric of reality? Step into the chilling narrative surrounding the baffling vanishing of Dean Roche, a 31-year-old man from Kilkenny. As we journey through the murky details of that fateful day on March 22, 2015, we find ourselves delving into a world where the line between accident and sinister plot blurs. Join us as we take an agonisingly close look at the eerie circumstances surrounding Dean&amp;rsquo;s vanishing - an abandoned car, a string of break-ins, and cryptic eyewitness accounts that raise more questions than answers.</description></item><item><title>Whispers in the Shadows: The Tragic Story of Raonaid Murray | Ireland Crimes and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3388540009/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3388540009/</guid><description>Podcast Description What if the person who took away your dreams, your ambitions, and your life was a like a ghost, leaving no traces behind? This is the haunting tale we unfold in our latest episode of Ireland Crimes and Mysteries. We transport you to 1999 and the untimely death of Raonaid Murray in South Dublin who was found lifeless in a shadowy walkway at just 17 by her own sister.</description></item><item><title>Chasing Darkness: The Tragic Tale of Elizabeth Plunkett and Mary Duffy | Ireland Crimes and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3388540010/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3388540010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to &amp;ldquo;Chasing Darkness: The Tragic Tale of Elizabeth Plunkett and Mary Duffy,&amp;rdquo; where we dive deep into the harrowing tale of the 1976 murders of these two 23 year old women. On that tragic night, the lives of Elizabeth and Mary were abruptly taken by the ruthless hands of John Shaw and Geoffrey Evans, two fugitives fleeing the English police. As news of the horrific crimes spread, fear and uncertainty gripped the communities in Co Galway and Co Wicklow as well as the country as a whole.</description></item><item><title>From Bond Girl to Headlines: The Celine Cawley Story | Ireland Crimes and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3388540011/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3388540011/</guid><description>Podcast Description What if the glitz and glamour of a Bond girl&amp;rsquo;s life suddenly turned into a chilling tale of tragedy and crime? That&amp;rsquo;s the unsettling journey we&amp;rsquo;re about to embark on as we peel back the layers of a chilling case that has marked Ireland&amp;rsquo;s history - the death of former model and Bond girl, Celine Cawley. The echoes of suspicious events leading up to Celine&amp;rsquo;s untimely demise still resonate - inconsistent alibis, secret text messages, and the haunting screams that still ring in the wind of the quiet seaside village of Howth.</description></item><item><title>Justice Denied: The Unsolved Mystery of Father Niall Molloy’s Death | Ireland Crimes and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3388540012/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3388540012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Could a passion for horses, a financial blunder, and an alleged affair lead to a tragic end? This unmissable episode takes you on a chilling journey into the mysterious and unsolved case surrounding the death of Father Niall Molloy . As we unravel the threads of deception, a darker picture emerges - an ill-fated financial arrangement, a missing will, and an infamous murder trial ending in an acquittal due to lack of evidence.</description></item><item><title>Into Thin Air: The Disappearance of Jojo Dullard | Ireland Crimes and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3388540013/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3388540013/</guid><description>Podcast Description What really happened to Jo Jo Dullard on that fateful night in 1995? Join us as we retrace the chilling story of her disappearance and reveal the latest developments in the case. Born in Cuffsgrange, Kilkenny, Jo Jo was known for her strong spirit and kind heart. But when she missed the last bus from Dublin to Kilkenny but after getting a bus to Naas, Co Kildare she made the fateful decision to hitchhike home.</description></item></channel></rss>