<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Australian True Crime on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/australian-true-crime/</link><description>Recent content in Australian True Crime on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 17:03:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/australian-true-crime/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Shortcut: The ex-bikie enforcer who turned to mental health advocacy | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100339/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 17:03:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100339/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Brent Simpson is a former sergeant-at-arms for the Bandidos Motorcycle Club.
Considering his childhood was marked by poverty, physical and sexual abuse, it's almost easy to imagine how he found community and connection within the bikie gang.
What is hard to imagine, however, is how someone could leave that club and commit their life to mental health advocacy - a path Brent has not only embarked on but continues to do so.</description></item><item><title>The ex-bikie enforcer who turned to mental health advocacy | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100340/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 17:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100340/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brent Simpson is a former sergeant-at-arms for the Bandidos Motorcycle Club.
Considering his childhood was marked by poverty, physical and sexual abuse, it's almost easy to imagine how he found community and connection within the bikie gang.
What is hard to imagine, however, is how someone could leave that club and commit their life to mental health advocacy - a path Brent has not only embarked on but continues to do so.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: My father the underworld crime figure | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 17:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100001/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Frank La Rosa and his wife Kim were murdered at a Welshpool (WA) factory on June 13, 2008.
Along with being a convicted heroin importer and notorious underworld figure in Western Australia, Frank La Rosa was also a father to three children.
Lisa Mahoney is one of those children.</description></item><item><title>My father the underworld crime figure | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 17:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Frank La Rosa and his wife Kim were murdered at a Welshpool (WA) factory on June 13, 2008.
Along with being a convicted heroin importer and notorious underworld figure in Western Australia, Frank La Rosa was also a father to three children.
Lisa Mahoney is one of those children. She joins us on this episode of Australian True Crime to discuss the collateral damage her father's actions have had on her own life and the lives of many others.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: The international cult that has a presence in Australia | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100003/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 17:02:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100003/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Founded in 1972, "The 12 Tribes" presents itself as a welcoming religious sect. However, the accounts from those who have managed to escape tell a very different story.
The group maintains global locations and communities, including two communities in NSW: Katoomba and Picton.
Our guest for this episode is Tim Elliiott.</description></item><item><title>The international cult that has a presence in Australia | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100004/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 17:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100004/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Founded in 1972, "The 12 Tribes" presents itself as a welcoming religious sect. However, the accounts from those who have managed to escape tell a very different story.
The group maintains global locations and communities, including two communities in NSW: Katoomba and Picton.
Our guest for this episode is Tim Elliiott.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: The young law student who began robbing TABs - Part 2 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 14:58:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100005/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
This is the second part of a two part series with our guest, Arthur Bolkas.
In his late teens and early twenties, Arthur was pulling double duty as a promising young law student and an armed robber.
We discovered at the end of part one that Arthur was eventually captured after a very dramatic car chase through the streets of a busy inner Melbourne suburb.</description></item><item><title>The young law student who began robbing TABs - Part 2 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 14:58:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100006/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the second part of a two part series with our guest, Arthur Bolkas.
In his late teens and early twenties, Arthur was pulling double duty as a promising young law student and an armed robber.
We discovered at the end of part one that Arthur was eventually captured after a very dramatic car chase through the streets of a busy inner Melbourne suburb.
We now pick up our conversation with Arthurs memories and reflections from his sentencing, incarceration and life after prison.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: The young law student who began robbing TABs - Part 1 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100007/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 17:02:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100007/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
We're going back to the "stick ups" this week with Arthur Bolkas.
He's a Criminologist, actor, public speaker and proud father of two.
However, before he was all of these things, he was a very promising young law student, and a flamboyant armed robber.
Part two of this two part series will be released later on this week.</description></item><item><title>The young law student who began robbing TABs - Part 1 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100008/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 17:00:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100008/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
We're going back to the "stick ups" this week with Arthur Bolkas.
He's a Criminologist, actor, public speaker and proud father of two.
However, before he was all of these things, he was a very promising young law student, and a flamboyant armed robber.
Part two of this two part series will be released later on this week.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: The surge of violence in Victoria's illicit tobacco market | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 17:02:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100009/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Over the past eight months, more than 30 tobacco stores in Victoria have fallen victim to a series of fire bombings due to a burgeoning turf war. Marta Pascual Juanola is a crime reporter for The Age, and has written a series of stories on Victoria's illegal tobacco industry.</description></item><item><title>The surge of violence in Victoria's illicit tobacco market | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 17:00:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the past eight months, more than 30 tobacco stores in Victoria have fallen victim to a series of fire bombings due to a burgeoning turf war. Marta Pascual Juanola is a crime reporter for The Age, and has written a series of stories on Victoria's illegal tobacco industry.
She joins us on this episode of Australian True Crime to talk about the increasing violence in this industry, and the surprisingly big players involved.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: Falling in love with a prisoner sentenced to life | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100011/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 17:01:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100011/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Ashleigh (not her real name) is a kind of woman we've all heard about many times, but don't often get to hear from.
A couple of years ago, Ashleigh received a letter from an inmate who is serving a life imprisonment conviction for his involvement in a double murder.</description></item><item><title>Falling in love with a prisoner sentenced to life | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100012/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 17:00:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ashleigh (not her real name) is a kind of woman we've all heard about many times, but don't often get to hear from.
A couple of years ago, Ashleigh received a letter from an inmate who is serving a life imprisonment conviction for his involvement in a double murder. They soon fell in love with each other.
Ashleigh joins us today to talk about their relationship, about the realities of courtship under the ever-present eye of corrections, and about her hopes for the future.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: The Man Who Wasn't There | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 17:02:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100013/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
In 2011, A young indigenous man by the name of Zak Grieve was sentenced to life in prison for a murder he didn't commit.
The murder of Ray Niceforo was commissioned by his former partner Bronwyn Malyschko, and carried out by her son Chris Malyschko and accomplice Darren Halfpenny.</description></item><item><title>The Man Who Wasn't There | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100014/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2011, A young indigenous man by the name of Zak Grieve was sentenced to life in prison for a murder he didn't commit.
The murder of Ray Niceforo was commissioned by his former partner Bronwyn Malyschko, and carried out by her son Chris Malyschko and accomplice Darren Halfpenny.
Grieve was originally supposed to be an accomplice to the murder too, but changed his mind on the night.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: Where is Australia getting its crystal meth? | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100015/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 17:01:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100015/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Australia tops almost every other country when it comes to our consumption of meth, with billions of dollars of it arriving at our shores each year.
Investigative journalist Conor Woodman joins us on this episode to detail exactly where all of this methamphetamine is coming from, the destructive path it takes to get into Australia, and the steps we can take for harm minimisation.</description></item><item><title>Where is Australia getting its crystal meth? | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100016/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 17:00:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Australia tops almost every other country when it comes to our consumption of meth, with billions of dollars of it arriving at our shores each year.
Investigative journalist Conor Woodman joins us on this episode to detail exactly where all of this methamphetamine is coming from, the destructive path it takes to get into Australia, and the steps we can take for harm minimisation.&amp;nbsp;
Conor Woodman’s book “Meth Road” is available now, and can be purchased here.</description></item><item><title>Re-Issue: Annette Mason: Journey to an Inquest - #42 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 13:01:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100017/</guid><description>Podcast Description November 2023 marks the 34th anniversary of the brutal murder of Toowoomba teenager, Annette Mason. For today's episode, we revisit one of our earliest episodes of Australian True Crime which featured an interview with Annette's sister, Linda Mason.
For Support:&amp;nbsp;
Lifeline &amp;nbsp;on 13 11 14
13 YARN on 13 92 76 (24/7 crisis support phone line for Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander peoples)
1800RESPECT: 1800 737 732
GET IN TOUCH:</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: Convincing your husband to murder your ex | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100018/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 17:01:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100018/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Even though Biannca Edmunds didn't pull the trigger, Victorian homicide detectives pursued her for years with the belief that she was responsible for the death of her ex partner, Michael Caposiena.
In 2016, Caposiena was murdered by Edmunds' then-husband, Glen Cassidy. Cassidy himself died that night, due to the self-defence efforts of Caposiena.</description></item><item><title>Convincing your husband to murder your ex | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100019/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 17:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Even though Biannca Edmunds didn't pull the trigger, Victorian homicide detectives pursued her for years with the belief that she was responsible for the death of her ex partner, Michael Caposiena.
In 2016, Caposiena was murdered by Edmunds' then-husband, Glen Cassidy. Cassidy himself died that night, due to the self-defence efforts of Caposiena.
Court Reporter for ABC News Melbourne, Kristian Silva, joins us this on episode to break down this bizarre and tragic assassination attempt.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: The Girl in Cabin 350 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100020/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 17:02:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100020/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Gwenda McCallum was young, single and determined to squeeze every drop out of life when she arrived in Sydney in 1949. Mere weeks later, she found herself in the company of some extremely unsuitable men. After one night of partying, Gwenda awoke on board an ocean liner.</description></item><item><title>The Girl in Cabin 350 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100021/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 17:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gwenda McCallum was young, single and determined to squeeze every drop out of life when she arrived in Sydney in 1949. Mere weeks later, she found herself in the company of some extremely unsuitable men. After one night of partying, Gwenda awoke on board an ocean liner. 24 hours later, she vanished.
Our guest today, Gideon Haigh, puts an inspiring amount of work and care into seeking the truth for long forgotten women into his books.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: The Real Romper Stomper | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 07:49:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100022/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
The current rise of Antisemitism and “White Power” groups in Australia is not unprecedented.
In fact, as recently as 1992, Russell Crowe’s career was launched by his role as a brutal skinhead in the seminal Australian film Romper Stomper.
Andrew Kirby is one of the men that movie was about and he joins us to talk about Neo Nazism in Australia, and his subsequent internal journey to reform.</description></item><item><title>The Real Romper Stomper | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 07:47:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100023/</guid><description>Podcast Description The current rise of Antisemitism and “White Power” groups in Australia is not unprecedented.
In fact, as recently as 1992, Russell Crowe’s career was launched by his role as a brutal skinhead in the seminal Australian film Romper Stomper.
Andrew Kirby is one of the men that movie was about and he joins us to talk about Neo Nazism in Australia, and his subsequent internal journey to reform.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: This Criminologist may challenge your views on the Criminal Justice System | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100024/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 17:01:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100024/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Lauren Humby brings a perspective on the criminal justice system that many of us may struggle with.
However, she is anything but misinformed. Not only is Lauren an academic with decades of research in the field, she is also victim of several sexual assaults dating back to her early childhood.</description></item><item><title>This Criminologist may challenge your views on the Criminal Justice System | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100025/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 17:00:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100025/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Lauren Humby brings a perspective on the criminal justice system that many of us may struggle with.
However, she is anything but misinformed. Not only is Lauren an academic with decades of research in the field, she is also victim of several sexual assaults dating back to her early childhood.</description></item><item><title>Robert Berchtold's reign of terror on the Broberg family - True Crime Compendium | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100026/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 06:49:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100026/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is an unlocked episode of Australian True Crime Plus. To access all ATC Plus episodes, plus ad free and early listening of all Australian True Crime episodes, you can subscribe on Apple Podcasts.
The story of Robert Berchtold's double kidnapping of Jan Broberg is so bizarre and tragic, that you may find it unbelievable.
In the 1970s, Jan Broberg was kidnapped twice by family friend, Robert Berchtold. First when she was 12, and again when she was 14.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: The Brutal Upbringing that Prepared Susan Norman to be a Prison Guard | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100027/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 17:01:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100027/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Susan grew up in the UK, enduring years of highly abusive relationships at the hands of her mother and her pimp husband.&amp;nbsp;
In her thirties, she moved to Australia and begun working at Brisbane's infamous Boggo Road prison.&amp;nbsp;
At the prison, she handled everything from breaking up fights to initiating new prisoners, drug busts and suicide attempts.</description></item><item><title>The Brutal Upbringing that Prepared Susan Norman to be a Prison Guard | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 17:00:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100028/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Susan grew up in the UK, enduring years of highly abusive relationships at the hands of her mother and her pimp husband.&amp;nbsp;
In her thirties, she moved to Australia and begun working at Brisbane's infamous Boggo Road prison.&amp;nbsp;
At the prison, she handled everything from breaking up fights to initiating new prisoners, drug busts and suicide attempts.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: Lynn's Law: The Murder of Lynn Cannon and the Call for Reform | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100029/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 02:35:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100029/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Lynn Cannon, an adored Perth mother of two, was brutally murdered by her ex husband Paul Cannon in late 2022.
The day before she was murdered, Paul learned she was in a new relationship.
Under false pretences, he convinced her to come to his house the next day.</description></item><item><title>Lynn's Law: The Murder of Lynn Cannon and the Call for Reform | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100030/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 02:34:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lynn Cannon, an adored Perth mother of two, was brutally murdered by her ex husband Paul Cannon in late 2022.
The day before she was murdered, Paul learned she was in a new relationship.
Under false pretences, he convinced her to come to his house the next day. An argument escalated, prompting neighbours to call the police.
Despite multiple calls to 000, police took an hour and 15 minutes to arrive.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: Being the head police officer during the Cabramatta heroin crisis | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100031/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 17:01:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100031/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Alan Leek is a retired member of the New South Wales Police Service, in which he served for 34 years.&amp;nbsp;
In the early 1990s, Alan was rewarded for his excellence in management. When he was made the head police officer in Cabramatta, it was at the time the largest heroin distribution point in the country, a growing political flashpoint and spiraling ever faster, out of control.</description></item><item><title>Being the head police officer during the Cabramatta heroin crisis | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100032/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 17:00:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alan Leek is a retired member of the New South Wales Police Service, in which he served for 34 years.&amp;nbsp;
In the early 1990s, Alan was rewarded for his excellence in management. When he was made the head police officer in Cabramatta, it was at the time the largest heroin distribution point in the country, a growing political flashpoint and spiraling ever faster, out of control.
The unique set of challenges that beset Cabramatta from the late 1980s created a criminal and cultural misery unlike anything else Australia had seen at the time.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: My father murdered my baby and he’s not in jail | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100033/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 17:01:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100033/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
In October 2019, Natalie Sands, her children and her mother suffered an unthinkably brutal attack at the hands of her father. Natalie was doused in petrol and set alight by her father. Despite being able to escape her burning house with burns to 75 percent of her body, she watched helplessly as her five year old son, Orlando, and mother Antoinette, perished.</description></item><item><title>My father murdered my baby and he’s not in jail | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100034/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 17:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100034/</guid><description>Podcast Description In October 2019, Natalie Sands, her children and her mother suffered an unthinkably brutal attack at the hands of her father. Natalie was doused in petrol and set alight by her father. Despite being able to escape her burning house with burns to 75 percent of her body, she watched helplessly as her five year old son, Orlando, and mother Antoinette, perished.
After leaving the scene, her father drove to the local Tamworth police station and handed himself in.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: How did this Australian die in South African police custody? | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100035/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 17:01:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100035/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
In 1995, Adrian Pendergast accepted an exciting job opportunity in South Africa. Less than a week after he got there, he was found dead in a jail cell.
For almost 30 years, his family have been trying to understand what happened and how he died. But it seems that everything new that they learn, it only leads to more questions.</description></item><item><title>How did this Australian die in South African police custody? | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100036/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 17:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100036/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1995, Adrian Pendergast accepted an exciting job opportunity in South Africa. Less than a week after he got there, he was found dead in a jail cell.
For almost 30 years, his family have been trying to understand what happened and how he died. But it seems that everything new that they learn, it only leads to more questions.
Our guest today is Adrian's younger sister, Courtney. Courtney only got to know her older brother until she was 15.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: Drug dealing, car theft and escaping prison. This was Nathan's life. | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100037/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 09:08:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100037/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Our guest today, Nathan Crisfield, embodies a story of duality like no other.
From Albury, He was born into a tumultuous home life, with his father taking him under his wing at an early age to steal whatever they could off the back of trucks.</description></item><item><title>Drug dealing, car theft and escaping prison. This was Nathan's life. | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100038/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 09:08:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100038/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Our guest today, Nathan Crisfield, embodies a story of duality like no other.
From Albury, He was born into a tumultuous home life, with his father taking him under his wing at an early age to steal whatever they could off the back of trucks.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: The high school music teacher who preyed upon his students | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 18:01:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100039/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Anna is a fabulous, vivacious woman who seems to have lived many lifetimes. But the deeper we get into the business of why she joins us on Australian True Crime, the darker forces that drives people like Anna and their fast paced lives becomes more apparent.</description></item><item><title>The high school music teacher who preyed upon his students | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 18:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anna is a fabulous, vivacious woman who seems to have lived many lifetimes. But the deeper we get into the business of why she joins us on Australian True Crime, the darker forces that drives people like Anna and their fast paced lives becomes more apparent.
For many years, Anna was trying to cope with the fact that she'd been preyed upon by a teacher, Trenton John Wickers, and the matter had never felt resolved in any way.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: If your abuser is a cop, will the police still protect you? | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100041/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 01:39:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100041/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Mary (not her real name) is a recently retired Victoria Police officer.
Mary's husband and father of her two children committed serious family violence for many years. He was also a Victoria Police officer - a very high ranking one.
Mary joins us to tell us about the attempts she and her children have made to have their allegations of family violence fully investigated by Victoria Police.</description></item><item><title>If your abuser is a cop, will the police still protect you? | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100042/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 01:38:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mary (not her real name) is a recently retired Victoria Police officer.
Mary's husband and father of her two children committed serious family violence for many years. He was also a Victoria Police officer - a very high ranking one.
Mary joins us to tell us about the attempts she and her children have made to have their allegations of family violence fully investigated by Victoria Police.
In 2021, Victoria Police announced the formation of a specialist unit to investigate cases of family violence involving its own employees.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: Australia's sex trafficking rings hiding in plain sight | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100043/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 01:33:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100043/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Sex trafficking of overseas women to Australia is far more widespread than you may believe.
The Sex Work industry can be one of empowerment and autonomy for many workers. On this episode however, we discuss its dark corner controlled my organised crime and exploitation.
Investigative journalist Nick McKenzie joins us to discuss the major sex trafficking rings he exposes in his documentary "</description></item><item><title>Australia's sex trafficking rings hiding in plain sight | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100044/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 01:33:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sex trafficking of overseas women to Australia is far more widespread than you may believe.
The Sex Work industry can be one of empowerment and autonomy for many workers. On this episode however, we discuss its dark corner controlled my organised crime and exploitation.
Investigative journalist Nick McKenzie joins us to discuss the major sex trafficking rings he exposes in his documentary "Revealed: Trafficked".
"Revealed: Trafficked" can be streamed now only on Stan.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: What happened to Ray and Jennie Kehlet? | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100045/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 18:01:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100045/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Ray and Jennie Kehlet's much loved Great Dane, Ella, wandered alone and dehydrated into a caravan park in Sandstone, WA in March 2015.
The phone calls that resulted from local police scanning Ella's microchip alerted both Ray and Jennie's families to the fact that something had gone terribly wrong during their latest adventure.</description></item><item><title>What happened to Ray and Jennie Kehlet? | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100046/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 18:00:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ray and Jennie Kehlet's much loved Great Dane, Ella, wandered alone and dehydrated into a caravan park in Sandstone, WA in March 2015.
The phone calls that resulted from local police scanning Ella's microchip alerted both Ray and Jennie's families to the fact that something had gone terribly wrong during their latest adventure.
Eight years and one inquest later, many questions still remain.
Ray's brother Dave joins us on this episode of Australian True Crime to tell us the story of the last eight years from his perspective.</description></item><item><title>The Murder of Katie Rackliff - True Crime Compendium | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100047/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 18:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100047/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the story of the unlikely killer who hid in plain sight in the tiny and terrified community of Camberley for two years. This is an unlocked episode of Australian True Crime Plus. To access all ATC Plus episodes, plus ad free and early listening of all Australian True Crime episodes, you can subscribe on Apple Podcasts.
If you have been affected by anything discussed in this episode you can contact:</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: The multinational effort to bring Cecilia Haddad's killer to justice - Part 2 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100048/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 08:03:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100048/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
This is episode 2 of a 2 part series on the murder of Cecilia Haddad, and the multinational effort to bring her killer to justice.
Journalist Ashlea Hansen joins us again to discuss the trial of Mario Marcelo Santoro, the unusual witnesses called to testify, and his shocking confession.</description></item><item><title>The multinational effort to bring Cecilia Haddad's killer to justice - Part 2 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100049/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 08:02:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100049/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is episode 2 of a 2 part series on the murder of Cecilia Haddad, and the multinational effort to bring her killer to justice.
Journalist Ashlea Hansen joins us again to discuss the trial of Mario Marcelo Santoro, the unusual witnesses called to testify, and his shocking confession.
For Support:&amp;nbsp;
Lifeline &amp;nbsp;on 13 11 14
13 YARN on 13 92 76 (24/7 crisis support phone line for Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander peoples)</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: The multinational effort to bring Cecilia Haddad's killer to justice - Part 1 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100050/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 02:31:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100050/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
On the day Cecilia Haddad's body was discovered in Sydney's Lane Cove River, her ex partner Mario Marcelo Santoro was on a flight home to Brazil.
Our guest for today's episode, journalist Ashlea Hansen, has been following this story for the very beginning.
This episode is part 1 of a 2 part series on the murder of Cecilia Haddad, and the multinational effort to bring her killer to justice.</description></item><item><title>The multinational effort to bring Cecilia Haddad's killer to justice - Part 1 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100051/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 02:30:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100051/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the day Cecilia Haddad's body was discovered in Sydney's Lane Cove River, her ex partner Mario Marcelo Santoro was on a flight home to Brazil.
Our guest for today's episode, journalist Ashlea Hansen, has been following this story for the very beginning.
This episode is part 1 of a 2 part series on the murder of Cecilia Haddad, and the multinational effort to bring her killer to justice.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: Sarah's brave act that forever stopped a child predator | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100052/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 09:08:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100052/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Sarah spent decades explaining her self-destructive behaviour to people as a consequence of one terrible year of bullying in primary school.
Her abuser wasn't another child, but her principal, an elderly Catholic nun.
But while Sarah tried to overcome the trauma of that experience, and of one terrible incident in particular, by talking about it with friends and seeking counselling, it wasn't until she heard a line in a true crime podcast while driving her car that she realised the one detail she'd always kept to herself was the thing that was preventing her from healing.</description></item><item><title>Sarah's brave act that forever stopped a child predator | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100053/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 09:07:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sarah spent decades explaining her self-destructive behaviour to people as a consequence of one terrible year of bullying in primary school.
Her abuser wasn't another child, but her principal, an elderly Catholic nun.
But while Sarah tried to overcome the trauma of that experience, and of one terrible incident in particular, by talking about it with friends and seeking counselling, it wasn't until she heard a line in a true crime podcast while driving her car that she realised the one detail she'd always kept to herself was the thing that was preventing her from healing.</description></item><item><title>Re-Issue: The Fight to Bring an Alleged Pedophile Headmistress Back to Australia to Face Justice: Survivor Dassi Erlich's Story | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100054/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 18:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100054/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a re-issue of episode 99 from May 2019 2019
Dassi Erlich is living a life today she literally could never have imagined as a child. She couldn’t have imagined it because so much of what the rest of us take for granted was hidden from her by her parents and the other adults around her. Dassi and her six siblings were raised in the ultra-Orthodox Adass Israel community of Melbourne.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: Re-Issue: The Fight to Bring an Alleged Pedophile Headmistress Back to Australia to Face Justice: Survivor Dassi Erlich's Story | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100055/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 07:29:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100055/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
This is a re-issue of episode 99 from May 2019 2019
Dassi Erlich is living a life today she literally could never have imagined as a child. She couldn’t have imagined it because so much of what the rest of us take for granted was hidden from her by her parents and the other adults around her.</description></item><item><title>The disappearance of Susan Thomson leaves more questions than answers | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100056/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 18:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Susan Warren, 15 years old in the year of 1965, ran away with a man 8 years her senior, Arthur Thomson.
The next 34 years of her life are quite frankly, a complete mystery.
She had no friends, no community, and hardly any family contact.
In fact, her life was so isolated that when she went missing in 1999, there wasn’t a missing persons report with the police until 2006.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: The disappearance of Susan Thomson leaves more questions than answers | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100057/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:59:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100057/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Susan Warren, 15 years old in the year of 1965, ran away with a man 8 years her senior, Arthur Thomson.
The next 34 years of her life are quite frankly, a complete mystery.
She had no friends, no community, and hardly any family contact.</description></item><item><title>What you need to know to keep your child safe online | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100058/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 18:00:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100058/</guid><description>Podcast Description We return this episode with our guests Jon Rouse APM and Akhim Dev, answering your questions about the fight against online exploitation of children.
Akhim Dev is the creator of The Children In the Pictures, a documentary and podcast that looks into the amazing and unrelenting work of members at Task Force Argos, of which Jon Rouse was a founding member of.&amp;nbsp;
For those not in the know, Task Force Argos is a world renowned branch of the Queensland police force responsible for the investigation of online child exploitation and abuse, which you can learn more about from our previous episode.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: What you need to know to keep your child safe online | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100059/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 13:12:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100059/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
We return this episode with our guests Jon Rouse APM and Akhim Dev, answering your questions about the fight against online exploitation of children.
Akhim Dev is the creator of The Children In the Pictures, a documentary and podcast that looks into the amazing and unrelenting work of members at Task Force Argos, of which Jon Rouse was a founding member of.</description></item><item><title>Task Force Argos: The police who rescue children from online sexual exploitation | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100060/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 18:00:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Task Force Argos is a world renowned branch of the Queensland Police Service, responsible for the investigation of online child exploitation and abuse.
Our guests for this episode are Jon Rouse APM and Akhim Dev. Rouse was one of the founding members of the Argos Task Force, and Dev is a documentary film maker, whose film and podcast "The Children in the Pictures" featured the work of the Rouse's team.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: Task Force Argos: The police who rescue children from online sexual exploitation | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100061/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 12:22:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100061/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Task Force Argos is a world renowned branch of the Queensland Police Service, responsible for the investigation of online child exploitation and abuse.
Our guests for this episode are Jon Rouse APM and Akhim Dev. Rouse was one of the founding members of the Argos Task Force, and Dev is a documentary film maker, whose film and podcast "</description></item><item><title>Can We Be Real? - The Secrets! | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100062/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Introducing "Can We Be Real?" - our new podcast that delves deep into the realm of authenticity and vulnerability.
Join us as we encourage our listeners to share their most intimate secrets, creating an atmosphere of connection and openness.
In this episode, we're thrilled to unveil some of our favourite secrets shared by our incredible listeners so far. Prepare to be moved, entertained, and inspired as we explore the depths of human emotions and experiences.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: A "real life monster" from Australia's Great Depression | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100063/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 09:51:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100063/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
During the Great Depression, 32% of working age men were put out of work, with many of them resorting to drunken and violent lifestyles.
During this time, there was a significant spike in Australia's murder rate, with many so called "monsters" being birthed from the era.</description></item><item><title>A "real life monster" from Australia's Great Depression | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100064/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 09:50:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100064/</guid><description>Podcast Description During the Great Depression, 32% of working age men were put out of work, with many of them resorting to drunken and violent lifestyles.
During this time, there was a significant spike in Australia's murder rate, with many so called "monsters" being birthed from the era.
Michael Adams from the "Forgotten Australia" podcast, joins us to tell us the story of one of those "monsters", William Moxley.
Michael Adams' new book "</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: Unfinished Business - a survivor defies the odds of Australia’s Court System (Part 2) | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100065/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 12:28:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100065/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
This is part two of a two part series with our anonymous guest. If you haven’t yet listened to our previous episode, we highly suggest you go and listen to that one first.
Our guest is a recovering heroin addict, and in our previous episode, we delved into her early childhood years, and the chaos brought into her life at the hands of her mother.</description></item><item><title>Unfinished Business - a survivor defies the odds of Australia’s Court System (Part 2) | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100066/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 12:27:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100066/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is part two of a two part series with our anonymous guest. If you haven’t yet listened to our previous episode, we highly suggest you go and listen to that one first.
Our guest is a recovering heroin addict, and in our previous episode, we delved into her early childhood years, and the chaos brought into her life at the hands of her mother.&amp;nbsp;
Concurrently to that, however, there was something else happening in her life.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: Unfinished Business - a survivor defies the odds of Australia’s Court System (Part 1) | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100067/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 03:57:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100067/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Today's episode is part one of a two part series. Part two will be available this coming Thursday.
For reasons that will become apparent, our guest has chosen to remain anonymous.
Raised mostly in a single father household alongside her sister, our guest's upbringing was far from ordinary.</description></item><item><title>Unfinished Business - a survivor defies the odds of Australia’s Court System (Part 1) | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100068/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 03:57:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode is part one of a two part series. Part two will be available this coming Thursday.
For reasons that will become apparent, our guest has chosen to remain anonymous.
Raised mostly in a single father household alongside her sister, our guest's upbringing was far from ordinary. Her relationship with her turbulent mother added to the complexity of her early years, as her mother's attempts to be involved often resulted in further pain and confusion.</description></item><item><title>Introducing… They Walk Among Us | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100069/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 18:00:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever wondered if there is a dark side to your neighbour? The cashier at the supermarket? The delivery driver? The person that sleeps beside you?
Delving into UK cases that are scarily close to home, They Walk Among Us explores both, lesser-known crimes committed by seemingly ordinary people, along with examining the infamous cases that are splashed across the headlines. The award-winning podcast has been praised by The Guardian, which called the show “a cult hit”; The Financial Times, referred to it as “sharply written”, and The Evening Standard applauded They Walk Among Us and its “expertly understated storytelling"</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: Three days before her pregnancy was due, Krystal Fraser went missing | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100070/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 11:24:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100070/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
On the 20th of June, 2009, a heavily pregnant Krystal Fraser, 23 years old, checked herself out of hospital to go to a party in Pyramid Hill. A country town in the far north of Victoria.&amp;nbsp;
Krystal was intellectually disabled, and did not have any credit left on her phone to make any calls.</description></item><item><title>Three days before her pregnancy was due, Krystal Fraser went missing | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100071/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 11:24:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100071/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the 20th of June, 2009, a heavily pregnant Krystal Fraser, 23 years old, checked herself out of hospital to go to a party in Pyramid Hill. A country town in the far north of Victoria.&amp;nbsp;
Krystal was intellectually disabled, and did not have any credit left on her phone to make any calls. One of the last sightings of Krystal that night, was meeting an unknown, well dressed man, who was waiting for her at the Pyramid Hill train station.</description></item><item><title>Special Extra: Mark Bouris and Meshel Laurie talk True Crime | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100072/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 18:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Meshel recently went on Straight Talk with&amp;nbsp;Mark&amp;nbsp;Bouris, and a whole lot of their conversation was about true crime. So what we've done is edit together all of the true crime bits for an extra bonus episode this week. If you want to listen to their full episode, go check out "Straight Talk with&amp;nbsp;Mark&amp;nbsp;Bouris"&amp;nbsp;wherever you get your podcasts.
Straight Talk with Mark Bouris episode notes:
Meshel Laurie is a name that has become synonymous with intelligence, wit, and compassion.</description></item><item><title>The father and son who vanished in one of the most remote parts of Australia | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100073/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 18:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100073/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a story about a man and his young son, Brad and Bevin Simmonds, who disappeared out in Cape York 20 years ago.
How could an experienced fisherman's boat disappear without a trace in broad daylight? In good weather and calm seas? How could everything on board, all the gear designed to float in case it fell overboard, disappear with it, and never, ever show up or wash ashore?</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: The father and son who vanished in one of the most remote parts of Australia | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100074/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 04:04:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100074/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
This is a story about a man and his young son, Brad and Bevin Simmonds, who disappeared out in Cape York 20 years ago.
How could an experienced fisherman's boat disappear without a trace in broad daylight? In good weather and calm seas? How could everything on board, all the gear designed to float in case it fell overboard, disappear with it, and never, ever show up or wash ashore?</description></item><item><title>ATC Plus *UNLOCKED*: Ripple: A Long Strange Search for A Killer | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100075/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 18:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jim Cosgrove was a journalist until a song he made up for his nieces and nephews called ‘Mr Stinky Feet’ became the hit of the local book fair. He was persuaded to record it and now tours the US as a children’s entertainer. True Story.
&amp;nbsp;
It’s not the first time Jim’s allowed himself to be swept along by life’s current. During his childhood, a young man from his neighbourhood named Frank McGonigle disappeared without a trace.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: From Predatory Boys Homes to the Unforgiving Streets of Kings Cross | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100076/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 07:55:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100076/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Many of Australia's systems failed Glen Fisher during his adolescence.
Coming from a broken home, Glen had to endure a horrifying stint while in custody of the Daruk Training Center for Boys in Sydney's Penrith.
Not being able to return home, Glen was rejected and abandoned to the streets of Kings Cross.</description></item><item><title>From Predatory Boys Homes to the Unforgiving Streets of Kings Cross | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100077/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 07:55:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Many of Australia's systems failed Glen Fisher during his adolescence. Coming from a broken home, Glen had to endure a horrifying stint while in custody of the Daruk Training Center for Boys in Sydney's Penrith. Not being able to return home, Glen was rejected and abandoned to the streets of Kings Cross.
Over the past four decades, Glen has tirelessly fought to hold his abusers accountable and shed light on the pervasive issue of institutional abuse that plagued Australia.</description></item><item><title>War hero to war criminal, Nick Mckenzie reflects on exposing Ben Roberts-Smith | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100078/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 18:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100078/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2018, Ben Roberts-Smith, a decorated Australian war veteran who had won the Victoria Cross for his actions in Afghanistan, sued The Age, The Sydney Morning Herald and The Canberra Times.
The above newspapers had alleged that Roberts-Smith committed acts of war crimes, bullying and domestic violence.
The civil trial ended in July 2022 after 110 days of evidence and legal submissions. It was dubbed one of the largest and most important defamation cases in Australian history.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: War hero to war criminal, Nick Mckenzie reflects on exposing Ben Roberts-Smith | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100079/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 03:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100079/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
In 2018, Ben Roberts-Smith, a decorated Australian war veteran who had won the Victoria Cross for his actions in Afghanistan, sued The Age, The Sydney Morning Herald and The Canberra Times.
The above newspapers had alleged that Roberts-Smith committed acts of war crimes, bullying and domestic violence.</description></item><item><title>The silent suffering of a missing person's sibling | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100080/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 18:00:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tony Ryan's sister Marcia disappeared in 1996 after leaving her Melbourne home. Marcia told her family she was going on a road trip with her dog Ziggy to see their parents in Queensland. But as you'll hear from Tony, Marcia's car was found abandoned in the Latrobe Valley in Victoria with no sign of Marcia or Ziggy. Tony's been relentless in trying to find out what happened to Marcia, who was 33 when she vanished.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: The silent suffering of a missing person's sibling | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100081/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 07:57:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100081/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Tony Ryan's sister Marcia disappeared in 1996 after leaving her Melbourne home.
Marcia told her family she was going on a road trip with her dog Ziggy to see their parents in Queensland. But as you'll hear from Tony, Marcia's car was found abandoned in the Latrobe Valley in Victoria with no sign of Marcia or Ziggy.</description></item><item><title>Tina Greer's disappearance: Her daughter's fight for justice | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100082/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 18:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tina Louise Greer, 32, went missing from her Beechmont home in Queensland, January 18, 2012.
She had gone to visit her ex boyfriend, a Finks bikie by the name of Les "Grumpy" Sharman, and has not been seen since.
Despite being listed by a Queensland coroner and police as the primary suspect in Tina's disappearance, Les Sharman was never formally questioned by police. He then died in a car crash in 2018.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: Tina Greer's disappearance: Her daughter's fight for justice | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100083/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:48:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100083/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Tina Louise Greer, 32, went missing from her Beechmont home in Queensland, January 18, 2012.
She had gone to visit her ex boyfriend, a Finks bikie by the name of Les "Grumpy" Sharman, and has not been seen since.
Despite being listed by a Queensland coroner and police as the primary suspect in Tina's disappearance, Les Sharman was never formally questioned by police.</description></item><item><title>The woman helping families of the vanished in Australia | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100084/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 18:00:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nicole Morris started a website more than 16 years ago called Australian Missing Persons Register. It was something she began as a personal project but it soon turned into a valuable resource and advocacy platform for the families and friends of missing people in Australia.&amp;nbsp;
Now some of these cases and stories are in her first book VANISHED, told through the experiences of siblings with a missing loved one - the desperate searches in the first days, the Police investigations and, for many, the heartbreak as the years, even decades, go by with no news and no answers.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: The woman helping families of the vanished in Australia | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100085/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 04:02:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100085/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Nicole Morris started a website more than 16 years ago called Australian Missing Persons Register. It was something she began as a personal project but it soon turned into a valuable resource and advocacy platform for the families and friends of missing people in Australia.&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>The Heartbreaking Story This Crime Reporter Can't Forget | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100086/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 18:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100086/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2007 when Kate Kyriacou was a reporter for the Adelaide Advertiser, she took up a story of a missing woman named Glenys Heyward.
Glenys, 53, had been due to go on a holiday with her new partner. Instead, she went missing from her hometown of Mount Gambier, towards the Victorian border.
Nowadays, Kate is the Courier Mail's Chief Crime Reporter, and has since reported on many harrowing cases.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: The Heartbreaking Story This Crime Reporter Can't Forget | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100087/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 09:47:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100087/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
In 2007 when Kate Kyriacou was a reporter for the Adelaide Advertiser, she took up a story of a missing woman named Glenys Heyward.
Glenys, 53, had been due to go on a holiday with her new partner. Instead, she went missing from her hometown of Mount Gambier, towards the Victorian border.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: The Baby in the Suitcase | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100088/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 09:48:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100088/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Sarah Boyd immigrated from Scotland to Sydney in 1923. It was there, where she and an accomplice committed an unthinkable decision.
What's even more terrifying, is that it was a decision that wasn't uncommon for women living in Sydney, Australia at the time. In fact, it was one of only a handful of difficult options faced by many women.</description></item><item><title>The Baby in the Suitcase | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100089/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 09:48:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sarah Boyd immigrated from Scotland to Sydney in 1923. It was there, where she and an accomplice committed an unthinkable decision.
What's even more terrifying, is that it was a decision that wasn't uncommon for women living in Sydney, Australia at the time. In fact, it was one of only a handful of difficult options faced by many women.
BUY Tanya Bretherton's book The Suitcase Baby.
For Support:&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>Can We Be Real? | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100090/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100090/</guid><description>Podcast Description 🚨 NEW PODCAST ALERT 🚨
You are the first to find out about a new podcast project I've been working on and it's called "Can We Be Real?"
I've really missed connecting with you on a range of different topics and now every Tuesday we can catch up, share secrets, chat life and discuss taboo topics going on in the world. I would really love your support today...</description></item><item><title>The Meanest Man in Pentridge Who You've Never Heard Of | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100091/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 18:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100091/</guid><description>Podcast Description We continue on from last week's episode with a breakdown of a suspect believed to be the perpetrator of the 1941 Pay Car massacre.
That suspect's name is Lionel Charles Thomas. But don't get too used to it, because if there was one thing this guy loved, it was changing his name.
You'll have to keep your wits about you because over the course of this episode, as he lies cheats, murders, but also romances his way around Australia and New Guinea, Lionel will go by no less than three more names.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: The Meanest Man in Pentridge Who You've Never Heard Of | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100092/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 23:55:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100092/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
We continue on from last week's episode with a breakdown of a suspect believed to be the perpetrator of the 1941 Pay Car massacre.
That suspect's name is Lionel Charles Thomas. But don't get too used to it, because if there was one thing this guy loved, it was changing his name.</description></item><item><title>Unsolved: South Sydney's Forgotten Massacre | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100093/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 18:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100093/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the morning of December 8, 1941, three men operating a "Pay Car" in south Sydney were unknowingly heading into a brutal ambush.
This story, however, has been lost to history due to it taking place on the same day Pearl Harbour was attacked.
Michael Adams from the Forgotten Australia podcast is back with us for another historical Australian crime.
This is a part one of two part series.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: Unsolved: South Sydney's Forgotten Massacre | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100094/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 08:29:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100094/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
On the morning of December 8, 1941, three men operating a "Pay Car" in south Sydney were unknowingly heading into a brutal ambush.
This story, however, has been lost to history due to it taking place on the same day Pearl Harbour was attacked.
Michael Adams from the Forgotten Australia podcast is back with us for another historical Australian crime.</description></item><item><title>Leisl Smith is missing, and her family can not get a judge's verdict | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100095/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 18:00:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sandi Harvey has not seen her daughter Leisl Smith since 2012. At that time, Leisl was 23 years old. She was happy, healthy and working in her dream job caring for horses.
But it was horses that brought her into contact with James Church, a much older man with whom she fell in love.
After her disappearance, Sandi discovered Leisl's relationship with Church was one of cruelty and heartache.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: Leisl Smith is missing, and her family can not get a judge's verdict | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100096/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 07:42:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100096/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Sandi Harvey has not seen her daughter Leisl Smith since 2012.
At that time, Leisl was 23 years old. She was happy, healthy and working in her dream job caring for horses.
But it was horses that brought her into contact with James Church, a much older man with whom she fell in love.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: The ripple effects after your family is touched by an act of pure evil | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100097/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 09:18:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100097/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Our guest today is Boyd Unwin, a suburban tradie and father of three in his fifties, who's always thought of himself and his family as the epitome of normal and unremarkable.
Boyd has committed himself to understanding how he lost his daughter, Katie Haley, to her partner five years ago.</description></item><item><title>The ripple effects after your family is touched by an act of pure evil | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100098/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 09:09:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our guest today is Boyd Unwin, a suburban tradie and father of three in his fifties, who's always thought of himself and his family as the epitome of normal and unremarkable.
Boyd has committed himself to understanding how he lost his daughter, Katie Haley, to her partner five years ago. Boyd and his wife Tania are now raising the child their daughter shared with her murderer. And bit by bit, they'll have to explain to that child why neither of her parents can be with her.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: Setting the record straight on Christopher Dale Flannery, AKA Mr Rent-a-Kill | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100099/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 01:43:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100099/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Ray Mooney joins us again this week to tell us about his friend, Christopher Dale Flannery (AKA Mr Rent-a-kill).
Chris was a teenager when they first met in Pentridge Prison. Chris was not long out of the notorious Morning Star boys home in Victoria's Mt Eliza.</description></item><item><title>Setting the record straight on Christopher Dale Flannery, AKA Mr Rent-a-Kill | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100100/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 00:43:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ray Mooney joins us again this week to tell us about his friend, Christopher Dale Flannery (AKA Mr Rent-a-kill).
Chris was a teenager when they first met in Pentridge Prison. Chris was not long out of the notorious Morning Star boys home in Victoria's Mt Eliza. Over the following decades, they maintained their close friendship. While Ray Mooney went on to become a published author, playwright, director and educator, Chris went on to become Australia's best known hitman.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: From Pentridge to Playwright, Ray Mooney proves rehabilitation is possible | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100101/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 06:53:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100101/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Our guest today is Ray Mooney. He's in his seventies now, and for most of his life, he's been a celebrated writer of novels, plays, films, non-fiction books, and a university lecturer.
At a different time in his life, though, the only institution he was allowed inside of was the Bluestone College: The College of Knowledge, also known as Pentridge Prison.</description></item><item><title>From Pentridge to Playwright, Ray Mooney proves rehabilitation is possible | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100102/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 18:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our guest today is Ray Mooney. He's in his seventies now, and for most of his life, he's been a celebrated writer of novels, plays, films, non-fiction books, and a university lecturer. At a different time in his life, though, the only institution he was allowed inside of was the Bluestone College: The College of Knowledge, also known as Pentridge Prison. Ray Mooney was convicted of rape when he was 19, and today we hear Ray's story, which is extraordinary in its own right, not least because of the honesty and openness he's prepared to bring to it.</description></item><item><title>Modern day organised crime gangs in Australia | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100103/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 18:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anthony Dowsley has been a crime reporter at Melbourne's Herald Sun since 2004. In that time, he's covered everything from homicides, solved and unsolved, law and order reforms and police corruption.
We're very honoured to have him in to discuss one of his speciality topics: gang related crime in Australia.
In this episode we will get a snapshot of who's who in Australian bikie gangs, how they're linked to organised crime in other countries, and the biggest police Trojan Horse operation yet.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: Modern day organised crime gangs in Australia | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100104/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 19:02:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100104/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Anthony Dowsley has been a crime reporter at Melbourne's Herald Sun since 2004. In that time, he's covered everything from homicides, solved and unsolved, law and order reforms and police corruption.
We're very honoured to have him in to discuss one of his speciality topics: gang related crime in Australia.</description></item><item><title>Nancy &amp; Victoria: The Beaumaris Beach Mystery | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100105/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 18:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two young female tourists are staying in the same quiet spot in Tasmania…one disappears, never to be seen again and two years later, the other woman is brutally murdered.
The women are 26-year-old German Nancy Grunwaldt, reported missing on April 15th 1993. Getting around on a bike, she was spending some time at Beaumaris Beach, reading a book. What happened after that is a mystery…so far. Nancy’s never been found but she was declared deceased by the coroner in 2003.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: Nancy &amp; Victoria: The Beaumaris Beach Mystery | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100106/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 19:02:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100106/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Two young female tourists are staying in the same quiet spot in Tasmania…one disappears, never to be seen again and two years later, the other woman is brutally murdered.
The women are 26-year-old German Nancy Grunwaldt, reported missing on April 15th 1993. Getting around on a bike, she was spending some time at Beaumaris Beach, reading a book.</description></item><item><title>How Jeffrey Morgan went from serving 18 years in prison to becoming a community leader | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100107/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 18:00:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100107/</guid><description>Podcast Description When he was 12, Jeffrey Morgan ran away from his country NSW home to Redfern to stay with his mum. He thought his dad was being too strict and he wanted more freedom. This was the time in Redfern when the inner-city suburb was the centre of Aboriginal life and activism and it was a tough place.
Jeffrey spent a lot of time on the streets, getting involved in minor offences a s a means of survival – namely stealing food to eat - but eventually this escalated to stealing cars and then, robbing banks.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: How Jeffrey Morgan went from serving 18 years in prison to becoming a community leader | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100108/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 08:25:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100108/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
When he was 12, Jeffrey Morgan ran away from his country NSW home to Redfern to stay with his mum. He thought his dad was being too strict and he wanted more freedom. This was the time in Redfern when the inner-city suburb was the centre of Aboriginal life and activism and it was a tough place.</description></item><item><title>The Soldier On Podcast: Tiny Little Spark | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100109/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100109/</guid><description>Podcast Description For the last year or so, we've been working away on a very special project called The Soldier On Podcast.
Soldier On is an incredible not for profit organisation that delivers holistic support services for current and former Australian Defence Force (ADF) personnel.
We joined up with them to help share the remarkable stories of those they work with. Hosted by the wonderful Hugh Riminton, each episode you’ll hear a first-hand account of a life touched by involvement in the Defence industry.</description></item><item><title>I'm sorry I missed a brutal multiple murder | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100110/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 18:00:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our guest today is from Toowoomba in Queensland, and he thought he'd seen his fair share of violence and mayhem by the time he'd sobered up in his mid-twenties. On today's episode, we're talking about a terrible turn of events that landed him back in the middle of incredibly senseless violence, just as he was pulling his life together. On the evening of May 30th 2005, three teenage boys brutally murdered Michael Thompson, 30, and teenagers David Lyons and Tyson Wilson, both just 17.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: I'm sorry I missed a brutal multiple murder | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100111/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 10:17:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100111/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Our guest today is from Toowoomba in Queensland, and he thought he'd seen his fair share of violence and mayhem by the time he'd sobered up in his mid-twenties.
On today's episode, we're talking about a terrible turn of events that landed him back in the middle of incredibly senseless violence, just as he was pulling his life together.</description></item><item><title>How I changed after 37 years of addiction, drama and hopelessness | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100112/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 17:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Robyn Lewis’s life was, frankly, hectic and destructive for 37 years. Multiple addictions, trauma from a brutal childhood, crime…she was just trying to survive. Robyn had tried and tried to change her life and then something happened. Now she’s sharing her story with her community and now, with us, to show that change is possible.
And a note before listening - Our guests share their experience. Each person has their own way they deal with life.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: How I changed after 37 years of addiction, drama and hopelessness | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100113/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 07:27:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100113/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Robyn Lewis’s life was, frankly, hectic and destructive for 37 years. Multiple addictions, trauma from a brutal childhood, crime…she was just trying to survive. Robyn had tried and tried to change her life and then something happened. Now she’s sharing her story with her community and now, with us, to show that change is possible.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut: Why should we care about conspiracy theorists and so-called sovereign citizens? | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100114/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 08:07:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100114/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a "Shortcut" episode. It’s a shortened version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Is it that bad if people believe in conspiracy theories? According to our guests for this episode, at first it’s funny, irritating (we all had someone we know who was sharing things that seemed a bit off beam over the past three years) and seemingly ridiculous…until it’s not.</description></item><item><title>Why should we care about conspiracy theorists and so-called sovereign citizens? | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100115/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 07:56:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is it that bad if people believe in conspiracy theories? According to our guests for this episode, at first it’s funny, irritating (we all had someone we know who was sharing things that seemed a bit off beam over the past three years) and seemingly ridiculous…until it’s not.
SOS and Sandee are two women who live in outer suburban Melbourne and have day jobs and families but they have also been deep diving into the world of places and spaces where people who believe in conspiracy theories and have such a distrust in Governments that they don’t acknowledge the laws that we all have to adhere to…like having a driver's licence, paying council rates and there’s more.</description></item><item><title>Grace's Place: The Legacy of Anita Cobby | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100116/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 06:49:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100116/</guid><description>Podcast Description The night of February 2nd 1986 was when 26 year old Sydney nurse Anita Cobby was savagely murdered by a group of strangers. It has since been marked a turning point for Australian culture.
Today's conversation is with Anita's sister, Kathryn Szyszka. It's all about legacy - Anita's legacy, and the legacy of their parents, Grace and Garry Lynch.
A new facility has finally opened in Sydney to provide healing and restoration for children affected by violent crime.</description></item><item><title>We need to talk about complex trauma with Forensic Psychologist Dr Ahona Guha | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100117/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 01:07:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our guest for this episode is Dr Ahona Guha, a Melbourne-based Forensic and clinical psychologist. She works with survivors of abuse and those who live with trauma.&amp;nbsp;Ahona also works with perpetrators of harmful behaviours including sex offenders, stalkers and bullies.&amp;nbsp;
Ahona has written her first book RECLAIM: Understanding complex trauma and those who abuse.
Dr Ahona Guha’s views are her own.
MORE INFO:
Former Victorian prosecutor awarded $435,000 over exposure to sexual abuse material</description></item><item><title>Suicide Bombings and the Australian Federal Police | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100118/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 06:33:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100118/</guid><description>Podcast Description We've mentioned the Australian Federal Police (AFP) many times on Australian True Crime, but do any of us really know what they do?
Our guest today, David Savage AM, who reached the very top of the tree in that organisation, may change the way you think about the role of the AFP.
For one thing, his brilliant career was brought to a grinding halt when he was supposed to be protected by a bunch of Americans on a dusty road in Afghanistan.</description></item><item><title>The relentless work of rescuing children from online sexual abuse | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100119/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 17:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Father of two, Filmmaker and director of The Children in The Pictures, Akhim Dev joins us for this episode.
&amp;nbsp;
He was granted unprecedented access to TASKFORCE ARGOS, a Queensland Police team who are world leaders in rescuing children from online sexual abuse and catching the perpetrators like Shannon McCoole, a South Australian child protection worker revealed to be a child-sex offender and the administrator of a paedophile chat board with 45,000 members.</description></item><item><title>The hell of what happened to Trevor Tascas - a family’s story | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100120/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 17:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trevor Tascas was 27 years old when he suspiciously disappeared in October 2005 from an address in Whittington, a suburb of the regional Victorian city Geelong.&amp;nbsp;
His mum Pamela and sister Kirsty join us for this episode.
&amp;nbsp;
Trevor’s life was up and down and at the time of his disappearance - he was using and dealing drugs but still in sporadic contact with his family.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Investigators believe Trevor had been involved in a dispute with Lawrence Butler, the man he was sharing a house with prior to his disappearance.</description></item><item><title>How MAFS star Mishel Karen lost over $100k from an online love scam | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100121/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 17:00:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mishel Karen was a participant on season 7 of Married at First Sight Australia.&amp;nbsp;
Mishel didn’t find the love she was looking for on the show, and a quick google will tell you a lot about Mishel’s life since the show ended. She’s now an only fans star and so far, she’s still single.&amp;nbsp;
Mishel Karen became the victim of a sophisticated scam from Everrise Brokers, through which she lost a large amount of her own money and friends and relatives of hers lost money to after taking her advice to trust her scammers.</description></item><item><title>Special Extra: Beauty Break with Joanna from Adore Beauty | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100122/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 17:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the summer break, we played some beauty chat segments at the end of our episodes with Joanna Fleming from Adore Beauty.
We thought for everyone's convenience, we would collate them all together into this one episode. It's seriously a great refresher on all things skincare and makeup.
For a limited time only, use the code "truecrime15" for 15 dollars off orders over $75 at www.adorebeauty.com.au exclusions do apply.</description></item><item><title>How Clare became a victim and what happened next | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100123/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 17:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100123/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2008, Clare awoke in the.middle of the night to two violent men invading her house, demanding the code to her boyfriend's safe.
This episode is the story of Clare's life up until now. A story involving mental illness, drugs and abusive men. It's also a story of recovery, support and family.
If you have been affected by anything discussed in this episode you can contact:
Lifeline on 13 11 14</description></item><item><title>Tied Up: Alec Baldwin | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100124/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 01:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hello loves, we have another podcast recommendation for you, and this one is a bit of a crossover.
It is a pop-culture podcast called Tied Up, hosted by two friends of mine Sonia Jahshan&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;Simon Baggs.
I think this episode will be of particular interest to you, because they are talking about Alec Baldwin and whether or not he will face charges for that terrible shooting incident that took place on the set of his film, Rust.</description></item><item><title>Man Overboard, the Enduring Mystery of Andrew Witton | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100125/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 17:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Australian True Crime is back for 2023, and we begin this year with the story of Andrew Witton.
Andrew was a sailor, surfer and adventurer, who disappeared from his yacht in a remote stretch of the Pacific Ocean in 2007. He was sailing with another man at the time, Simon Golding. As far has Andrew's friends and family are concerned, Simon has yet to provide a satisfactory account of what happened to Andrew on that trip.</description></item><item><title>Hoaxed: Secrets and Lies | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100126/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 23:08:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100126/</guid><description>Podcast Description We're taking a little break over Summer and using this time to spotlight some of our favourite true-crime podcasts.
Introducing... Hoaxed, the new series from Alexi Mostrous and Tortoise, who brought you Sweet Bobby.
In 2014, two children told police a shocking story: that they were being abused by a Satanic cult; a cult headed by their father and by parents and teachers at their school in the wealthy London suburb of Hampstead.</description></item><item><title>One Minute Remaining: David Talley | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100127/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 23:30:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100127/</guid><description>Podcast Description We're taking a little break over Summer and using this time to spotlight some of our favourite true-crime podcasts.
This week we're showcasing Jack Laurence's podcast, One Minute Remaining.
Today's episode is the story of David Talley, the man serving an incredible prison sentence. David, like millions of others around the world, struggled with addiction, an addiction to crack cocaine. This addiction would drive David to make poor decisions, decisions that would see him fall into a cycle of prison time for petty theft to help pay for his habit.</description></item><item><title>Introducing True North True Crime | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100128/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 00:25:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100128/</guid><description>Podcast Description We're taking a little break over Summer and using this time to spotlight some of our favourite true-crime podcasts.
This week we're showcasing True North True Crime. On the night of February 17th, 2018, Ryan Shtuka attended a silent disco followed by an after-party at a house in Sun Peaks resort near Kamloops BC. No one has seen or heard from Ryan since the party. Nearly 5 years have gone by and the Shtuka family still needs answers.</description></item><item><title>Do Go On: The Tylenol Murders | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100129/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 00:31:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100129/</guid><description>Podcast Description We're taking a little break over Summer and using this time to spotlight some of our favourite podcasts.
Do Go On is a fact based comedy podcast hosted by Melbourne comedians Jess Perkins, Matt Stewart and Dave Warneke. Each week they take it in turns to report on a topic and have covered everything from the life of Dolly Parton to the Chernobyl Disaster, Argentina's Heist of the Century to The History of The Penis.</description></item><item><title>GUILT: Theories &amp; Rumours | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100130/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 23:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100130/</guid><description>Podcast Description We're taking a little break over Summer and using this time to spotlight some of our favourite true-crime podcasts.
This week we're showcasing Ryan Wolf's podcast, GUILT.
Show notes: On the 18th June 2012, beloved Pizza shop owner Jordan Voudouris was gunned down in cold blood, in Paeroa, New Zealand. To this day, his killers have never been caught.
In this Multi-Part Investigative Podcast Actor/Lawyer Ryan Wolf revisits Jordan's case in the search for answers.</description></item><item><title>One Minute Remaining: The Murdered Lottery Winner - Dorice Moore part 1 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100131/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 17:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100131/</guid><description>Podcast Description We're taking a little break over Summer and using this time to spotlight some of our favourite true-crime podcasts.
This week we're showcasing Jack Laurence's podcast, One Minute Remaining.
Show notes: Welcome to episode one of 'One minute remaining' - Today we start the story of Dorice Moore and Abraham Lee Shakespeare, a story that has layer after layer but that is nothing short of mind blowing.
I am not here to prove her innocent or guilty I am simply here to allow her to tell her side of the story.</description></item><item><title>Forgotten Australia: The Cairns Grenade Murders Part 3 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100132/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 17:02:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100132/</guid><description>Podcast Description We're taking a little break over Summer and using this time to spotlight some of our favourite true-crime podcasts.
This week we're showcasing Michael Adam's Forgotten Australia, with his three part Cairns Grenade Murders series.
Part 3: With the accused murderer of Holly Murphy and Kathleen Brown set to go to trial in April 1946, there's a series of shocking secret developments, including a bombshell letter that makes disturbing claims against Queensland's boys in blue.</description></item><item><title>Forgotten Australia: The Cairns Grenade Murders Part 2 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100133/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 17:01:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100133/</guid><description>Podcast Description We're taking a little break over Summer and using this time to spotlight some of our favourite true-crime podcasts.
This week we're showcasing Michael Adam's Forgotten Australia, with his three part Cairns Grenade Murders series.
Part 2: With Detective Senior-Sergeant Frank Bischof in Cairns, Bob Davis soon identifies the murderer. But how far can Bob be trusted? And what is Bischof offering?
To read an extract and get 26% off Michael's book Hanging Ned Kelly, you can visit this link here: https://affirmpress.</description></item><item><title>Forgotten Australia: The Cairns Grenade Murders Part 1 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100134/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 17:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100134/</guid><description>Podcast Description We're taking a little break over Summer and using this time to spotlight some of our favourite true-crime podcasts.
This week we're showcasing Michael Adam's Forgotten Australia, with his three part Cairns Grenade Murders series.
On a hot night in January 1946, two women were cold-bloodedly murdered with a grenade in the centre of Cairns. In this three-part special episode - based on the original police murder file - we take a deep dive into this callous crime, whose solution was frustrated not only by the underworld’s code of silence but also by the conduct of Queensland’s most infamously corrupt cop.</description></item><item><title>A Narelle Fraser Special: Why The Fallen? Part 2 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100135/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 12:35:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100135/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2017, 21 year old Zac Jones was drunk, on drugs, and driving recklessly in a car with four other passengers. Unable to control the vehicle, they horrifically crashed, but all remarkably survived.
This is part two of a two part series hosted by our dear friend, Narelle Fraser about the lives of Zac and his mother Jane. We will hear a side-by-side account from both Zac and Jane about how an educated, intelligent teenager from a loving family ended up falling so badly, and the astonishing ways in which both of their lives have changed since.</description></item><item><title>A Narelle Fraser Special: Why The Fallen? Part 1 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100136/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 12:28:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100136/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2017, 21 year old Zac Jones was drunk, on drugs, and driving recklessly in a car with four other passengers. Unable to control the vehicle, they horrifically crashed, but all remarkably survived.
This is part one of a two part series hosted by our dear friend, Narelle Fraser about the lives of Zac and his mother Jane. We will hear a side-by-side account from both Zac and Jane about how an educated, intelligent teenager from a loving family ended up falling so badly, and the astonishing ways in which both of their lives have changed since.</description></item><item><title>The Disappearance of Marjorie Norval | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100137/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 17:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marjorie Norval was a mould breaker. In the 1930s, she was a single, gregarious career woman, living in a hotel in the Brisbane CBD. She worked for the Premiere William Forgan Smith and his wife, which afforded her to live a lifestyle that was out of reach for most women in conservative Brisbane at the time. That lifestyle came to an abrupt end when she disappeared without a trace, one sunny day in 1938.</description></item><item><title>The make-up artist that helped put Rolf Harris in prison | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100138/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 17:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100138/</guid><description>Podcast Description The word most commonly used to describe Rolf Harris at the conclusion of his trial and his spectacular fall from grace was remorseless.
He still seemed utterly shameless as revelation after revelation rolled out in front of the world and his real character was exposed. We all got an inkling of the sheer entitlement felt by the man and of his expectation that he should be allowed to go on separating his private and public personas with the complete complicity of everyone around him because he was just so famous.</description></item><item><title>Don't Make a Fuss: It's Only the Claremont Serial Killer | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100139/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 17:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100139/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1990, social worker Wendy Davis had her dream job at what was then known as Hollywood Private Hospital in Perth. She was the senior grief counsellor in the palliative care unit. It was intense but rewarding work, and at 40 years of age, life was right on track for Wendy Davis.
But It was cruelly taken away from her on her youngest daughter's 11th birthday, when she was violently assaulted by a Telecom technician who was working at the hospital.</description></item><item><title>"Shotgun" Shannon O'Connell's childhood is her toughest opponent | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100140/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 17:00:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100140/</guid><description>Podcast Description "Shotgun" Shannon O'Connell is Australia's pre-eminent female boxer. One thing that is absolutely true, is that her toughest opponent is her childhood. She fights it everyday, as do her two brothers, with varying degrees of success. We were introduced to Shannon by a previous guest, Russell Manser from The Voice of a Survivor. He likes to say that boxing has saved more lives than church, and Shannon is definitely one of them.</description></item><item><title>The Stick Up with Russell Manser: The Many Lives of Mick Gatto | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100141/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 05:55:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our guest this week, Russell Manser, has an incredible podcast of his own called The Stick Up. Please enjoy this rare interview with Mick Gatto, and check out other episodes of The Stick Up wherever you get your podcasts. Show notes:
In this rare interview with ex-underworld figure Mick Gatto, you'll hear about his love for his family, passion for charity and the life altering moments that saw him lose two sons, and end up in jail.</description></item><item><title>Russell Manser Wins the Prize for Turning a Life Around | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100142/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 05:45:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Russell Manser is an extraordinary man. He's been in and out of prison since we was literally a child, and when he wasn't inside, he was robbing banks to support a raging heroin habit. As we know, lifestyle habits like that don't come out of nowhere. When Russell decided to face the truth of what had happened to him, it changed his life. Since then, he's changed many lives too.</description></item><item><title>A life stolen: Jake was 12 days old when the Frankston serial killer murdered his mum | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100143/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 06:18:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100143/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1993, Paul Denyer murdered Natalie Russell, Elizabeth Stevens and Deborah Fream in the Frankston area. Denyer had also stalked and terrified women - that’s one of the lesser known aspects of his horrendous offending.
Now 50, Denyer was sentenced to life in prison without parole, but the sentence was later appealed and reduced to a non-parole period of 30 years, meaning Denyer is eligible for release in 2023.</description></item><item><title>The Bali Bombings - Aussie Therese Fox’s incredible survival story | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100144/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 09:00:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100144/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our guests for this episode are Therese Fox and Megan Norris.
In 2002 friends Therese Fox and Bronwyn Cartwright travelled to Bali – it was a dream trip that the two Geelong nurses had saved hard for. It was Therese’s first trip overseas and away from her young children.
On October 12th Therese and Bronwyn decided to go out to Paddy’s Irish Bar for their last night in Bali.</description></item><item><title>The shocking life of the man who hanged Ned Kelly | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100145/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 00:20:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our guest for this episode is Michael Adams, host of the fascinating podcast Forgotten Australia.&amp;nbsp;
Michael is a master of deep diving into the archives to tell incredible stories most people have never heard of - many of them about crime and society. From historic news articles - even the smallest of briefs and the mere mention of a name, Michael brings old stories, scandals, oddities and the lives of intriguing people back to life.</description></item><item><title>Special Extra: We Need To Talk About The Handmaid's Tale | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100146/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 05:28:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100146/</guid><description>Podcast Description In celebration of the release of the brand new season of The Handmaid's Tale, we've invited a couple of friends over to chat about the series with. We're joined today by mega fan Joanna Fleming from Adore Beauty, and from the brilliant Eyes On Gilead podcast, Fiona Williams. So, why a special episode about The Handmaid's Tale on our true crime podcast feed? Well, Margaret Atwood, the author of The Handmaid's Tale famously said that there's no crime against women in the book, that hasn't actually been perpetrated against women in real life somewhere in the world.</description></item><item><title>What the jury didn’t hear in the trial of my brother’s killer | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100147/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 18:00:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lucy Wessell contacted Australian True Crime to tell her family’s story about the unforeseeable and tragic loss of her brother Andrew - who is remembered by them as a kind and gentle man who loved his family, animals, and nature. He was a seasoned traveller who had friends all over the world.
&amp;nbsp;
Andrew Drake was stabbed to death in 2019. Andrew, 29, died on the lawn of a house in Batemans Bay on the NSW South Coast, as his sister Penny desperately tried to save his life.</description></item><item><title>Re-Issue: The Unsatisfactory Case Of Matthew Leveson - #76 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100148/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 00:58:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100148/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a re-issue of episode 76 from November 2018
In November of 2016, a decade after his death, Michael Atkins finally agreed to tell police where he'd buried the remains of his young lover Matthew Leveson. Matt's tormented parents tell us the twisted tale as to why Atkins will never be convicted in connection with their son's death.
Show notes:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb</description></item><item><title>Re-Issue: The good old mental health defence. | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100149/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 17:50:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100149/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a re-issue of episode 216 of Australian True Crime.
Some of Australia’s most dangerous offenders aren’t housed in prisons because they were judged mentally unfit to stand trial. Dr Danny Sullivan is the Executive Director of Clinical Services at Thomas Embling hospital. It’s been home to some of Victoria's most dangerous people, including Masa Vuktotic’s killer Sean Price, Henry Hammond who murdered Courtney Herron and Bourke Street rampage driver James Gargasoulas.</description></item><item><title>A victim’s perspective of the mental impairment defence | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100150/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 06:15:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100150/</guid><description>Podcast Description David&amp;nbsp;Cammarata’s childhood best friend is currently a forensic patient in a secure psychiatric facility. He was found not guilty of the machete murder of his own brother at a suburban shopping centre and of stalking and attempting to murder David, because the judge believed he was suffering from severe mental illness when he committed the offences.
David and his family were terrorised for years before his former friend Jonathan was apprehended.</description></item><item><title>Re-Issue: The Crimes and Times of Uncle Jack Charles - #103 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100151/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 01:32:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100151/</guid><description>Podcast Description A repost of episode #103 In loving memory of Uncle Jack Charles. We send our deepest condolences to the people of the Boon Wurrung, Dja Dja Wurrung, Woiwurrung and Yorta Yorta nations on the loss of Uncle Jack Charles. Stolen from his loving family as a child, he embraced all with love and kindness and was a vital artist until the end.
---
Jack Charles, known respectfully and affectionately as Uncle Jack Charles is a survivor who has much to tell about life, starting from the impact of being one of the Stolen Generation; Indigenous children forcibly removed from their families as a result of various government policies.</description></item><item><title>Serial Killers at Truro | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100152/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 20:31:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Geoff Plunkett's book "Death Row At Truro" investigates the mythology around a case that is often bizarrely overlooking in Australian crime reporting. Geoff joins us today to discuss the seven week serial killing spree committed by Christopher Worrell and James Miller in 1970s Adelaide.&amp;nbsp;
For ad-free listening, early access and exclusive content, join Australian True Crime Plus on Apple Podcasts here: http://apple.co/australiantruecrime
CREDITS:
Host: Meshel Laurie. You can find her on Instagram&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>Cold Case: Marea Yann - Part 2 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100153/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 18:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100153/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is part 2 of our exploration into Marea Yann’s case and our guests are&amp;nbsp; Esther Yann and close family friend of Marea and her family, lawyer Frank Chen.
&amp;nbsp;
You know when someone says they’ll do anything they can to right a wrong…Frank Chen really meant it. And you’ll hear the extraordinary lengths he’s gone to so he can fulfil&amp;nbsp; the promise he made to Marea at her funeral that he would do all he could to bring her killer to justice.</description></item><item><title>Cold Case: Marea Yann | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100154/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100154/</guid><description>Podcast Description As we know, behind every cold case is a family, and 19 years after her shocking murder, Marea Yann’s family remains divided.&amp;nbsp;Tensions that were developing in the lead up to her death, were cast in stone during the murder trial in 2008 that resulted in an acquittal.
Some family members still believe the acquittal was appropriate and police never fully investigated alternative theories, while other family members believe it was a terrible miscarriage of justice and continue to pursue a second trial.</description></item><item><title>I lost my teens to heroin and sex work - Part 2 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100155/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 18:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100155/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you haven't listened to the first part of this story, you might want to go back and listen before diving into this episode. It contains a lot of background you need to know about Vanessa's own story, but it's also a unique insight into how one human being's life can be completely derailed by the intervention of another, particularly during childhood. Vanessa's story provides a perfect case study of what's known as the victim-offender overlap; which is to say most offenders of crime have been victims of crime first.</description></item><item><title>I lost my teens to heroin and sex work | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100156/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 18:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100156/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the first of a two part Australian True Crime special because Vanessa’s story just refused to be contained in a single episode. I’m sure you’ll agree it’s a story that shouldn’t be rushed. It’s not every day you have the opportunity to hear first hand how a well-behaved, studious, happy child, from a loving home found herself estranged from her family and living on the streets before her twentieth birthday.</description></item><item><title>The Particular PTSD of the Country Town Beat | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100157/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 18:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100157/</guid><description>Podcast Description Roger Eichler is a former country copper who served in NSW police from the 1990's. Like so many others, too many others, Roger eventually left the service on a medical discharge with debilitating PTSD. Roger Eichler has written a book on his experience as a country copper, it's called "The Price Of Protecting Others", and he joins us today to talk about it.
You can buy Roger's book here: https://www.</description></item><item><title>My Brother The Family Violence Victim | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100158/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 18:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100158/</guid><description>Podcast Description As Jeffrey Lindsell’s family and friends gathered around his hospital bed in the days after his house caught on fire, attention turned to his volatile on-off relationship with Amanda Zukowski. It seemed as though Jeffrey had been living in an abusive relationship and had been a victim of coercive control and intimate partner violence. They realised that although he’d been increasingly withdrawn during the two year relationship and was particularly reluctant to talk about her, he’d shared different things with each of them at different times, and when they put it all together a very disturbing picture emerged.</description></item><item><title>The 1998 Silk-Miller police murders: Jason Roberts found not guilty | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100159/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 18:00:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jason Roberts, 41 years old, was recently freed for the first time in twenty two years by the Supreme Court of Victoria. He was seventeen years old when two police officers, Sergeant Gary Silk and Senior Constable Rodney Miller were shot and murdered on Cochranes Road, Moorabbin, Victoria. Roberts was one of two who were convicted of the murders all those years ago. It's a very infamous case in Australia, and a very complicated one.</description></item><item><title>A “low-flying” barrister’s life and times working in the Magistrates’ Court | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100160/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 18:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100160/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Magistrates’ Court is the workhorse of the legal system, hearing both criminal and civil matters.&amp;nbsp;Magistrates’ Courts around Australia hear the vast majority of sentenced court cases - more than 90 per cent in fact.
Michael Challinger is a criminal barrister based in Melbourne and has been working in Victorian courts since 1975 – representing clients,&amp;nbsp;mostly in the Victorian Magistrates’ Court and Children’s Court. Michael’s&amp;nbsp;written a book called Mostly Guilty – which is funny….</description></item><item><title>Coroner Leveaaque Peterson on giving a voice for the dead | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100161/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 18:00:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100161/</guid><description>Podcast Description We've spoken a great deal on this show over the years about the work of our state coroners, and today we finally got to meet one. Leveaaque Peterson was appointed a coroner by the Victorian state government in February 2020, and throughout her career in the legal system has chosen to take on some big and uncomfortable challenges. We'll find out why she finds that kind of law interesting, and also, what being a coroner actually entails.</description></item><item><title>Should sex offenders keep their super? | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100162/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 18:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100162/</guid><description>Podcast Description Many offenders who remain incarcerated can use their superannuation upon release to return to their lives luxuriating in their super, whilst their survivors generally are unemployed due to the longstanding impact these horrendous crimes have had on them. Our guests today, Andrew Carpenter and Adam Washbourne, are some of the front runners calling on the government to reform the Bankruptcy&amp;nbsp;Act, so that child sex offenders’ superannuation can be used to help victim-survivors rebuild their lives.</description></item><item><title>No one is a monster: what a clinical psychologist thinks we should know about violence | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100163/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 03:27:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr Ahona Guha is a Melbourne-based Forensic and Clinical Psychologist.
&amp;nbsp;
Ahona works at pointy end of mental health and treatment - with people who have clinical presentations of harmful behaviours, trauma histories, and those who have offended against others&amp;nbsp;- sexual offences (including against children) violence, stalking, arson…
&amp;nbsp;
Dr Ahona Guha, DPsych works in the field of forensic psychology to understand offending behaviours such as stalking, sex offending and intimate partner violence with the intention of assessing risk and providing psychological treatment to people who offend;&amp;nbsp;thus contributing to community safety and the protection of victims.</description></item><item><title>Forced adoptions in Australia, could it happen again? | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100164/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 07:42:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100164/</guid><description>Podcast Description Australia in the mid twentieth century has a dark history of forced adoption. Women who did not fit the moral expectations of the time (usually those who were young and unmarried) had their children taken from them at birth, often with little to no information left behind for them to be reunited.
Our guest today, Lily Arthur, is one story of many, and it is an absolutely heartbreaking one.</description></item><item><title>The most unlikely drug runners you’ve probably never heard of - Short Cut | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100165/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 18:02:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100165/</guid><description>Podcast Description The bullet point version of today's episode of Australian True Crime.
There’s stories that get under the skin of people, especially journalists. And this story you’re going to hear about is unbelievable. And most of us have probably never heard about it. Enter author Sandi Logan, a former journalist and diplomat who followed the case of two older American women Vera 'Toddie' Hays and Florice 'Beezie' Bessire -&amp;nbsp;who were arrested in Australia in the 1970s for having almost 2 TONNES of hashish concealed in a camper van.</description></item><item><title>The most unlikely drug runners you’ve probably never heard of | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100166/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 18:00:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100166/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s stories that get under the skin of people, especially journalists. And this story you’re going to hear about is unbelievable. And most of us have probably never heard about it. Enter author Sandi Logan, a former journalist and diplomat who followed the case of two older American women Vera 'Toddie' Hays and Florice 'Beezie' Bessire -&amp;nbsp;who were arrested in Australia in the 1970s for having almost 2 TONNES of hashish concealed in a camper van.</description></item><item><title>Queensland's Crooked Kings | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100167/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 18:00:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matthew Condon is an Australian author and journalist who has published multiple books on the history of corruption in the Queensland police force and state government. Our conversation today covers the events that led up to, and following, the Fitzgerald enquiry, which lead to custodial sentences for three former senior QLD ministers, and for the police commissioner, Terry Lewis. Joh Bjelke-Petersen, the longest running QLD premiere, was also sacked and tried for perjury.</description></item><item><title>The murder of Tiahleigh Palmer with Courier-Mail Crime and Courts Editor Kate Kyriacou | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100168/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 18:00:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100168/</guid><description>Podcast Description A lot of us will remember&amp;nbsp; the haunting photo of beautiful 12-year-old Tiahleigh Palmer, who was murdered in 2015. However the path to the dark truth of what happened to Tiahleigh was long and shocking and not resolved until several years later.
Tiahleigh was living in foster care in Logan, Queensland with Rick and Julene Thorburn and their sons Trent and Joshua.
Kate Kyriacou, the Courier-Mail newspaper’s Crime and Courts Editor, has reported extensively on Tiahleigh’s death and the tragic full story that emerged.</description></item><item><title>Supporting Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander people in prison - Louise Lynch | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100169/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 18:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100169/</guid><description>Podcast Description A NOTE FOR LISTENERS – This episode discusses the issue of deaths in custody of Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander peoples.
&amp;nbsp;
Gamilaraay woman, Louise Lynch is the manager of Corrective Services NSW’s Aboriginal Strategy and Policy Unit. Louise first came to work in NSW prisons as a teacher more than 25 years ago and she’s dedicated her career to supporting Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander peoples in prison and, among many important initiatives, improving and embedding culturally appropriate training for staff in corrective services.</description></item><item><title>Cindy Gambino's passing with Megan Norris | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100170/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 18:04:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Megan Norris spent several years with Cindy Gambino in the wake of the murders of her three sons by their father, her ex-husband Robert Farquharson on Father’s Day 2005. They were working together on a book called ‘On father’s Day’.
&amp;nbsp;
They remained close and Megan joins Emily Webb to reflect on Cindy’s tragic death and the ultimate form of family violence.
&amp;nbsp;
You can pre order Megan Norris's upcoming book 'Messiah's Bride' here.</description></item><item><title>Vale Cindy Gambino - On Father's Day | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100171/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 18:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100171/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;nbsp;
It’s 17 years since Cindy Gambino’s ex-husband Robert Farquharson murdered their three sons, ten-year-old Jai, seven-year old Tyler and three-year old Bailey by deliberately driving his car into a dam on the side of the Princes highway, near Winchelsea, West of Geelong on father’s day in 2005.
&amp;nbsp;
Cindy Gambino died last week as the result of a medical emergency at her home in country Victoria. She was just 50 years old.</description></item><item><title>The 1960 Crime That Shocked Then-Innocent Australia | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100172/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 18:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Best-selling biographer and history author Peter FitzSimons has turned his attention to detailing the history of the Sydney Opera House - drama, scandals and even crimes. For this episode of Australian True Crime, Emily speaks to Peter about a crime linked with the Opera House and how it shocked the nation - the kidnapping and killing of Bondi schoolboy Graeme Thorne in 1960.
Peter’s book The Opera House is published by Hachette Australia.</description></item><item><title>An Absolute Bastard | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100173/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 18:08:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100173/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lindy Cameron,&amp;nbsp;journalist, award-winning author and publisher joins Meshel and Emily to talk about about Danny Deacon, who murdered his former partner Carlie Sinclair in Darwin.
&amp;nbsp;
Lindy’s co-written a book with her sister Fin J Ross called Toxic: Cold-blooded Australian murders full of Aussie cases of men, including Deacon (in a chapter called “An Absolute Bastard”)&amp;nbsp;and women who kill.&amp;nbsp;
&amp;nbsp;
Lindy's Book is Toxic: Cold-blooded Australian murders full of Aussie cases of men and women who kill</description></item><item><title>Women of Corrections - The Governor Faith Slatcher | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100174/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 19:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100174/</guid><description>Podcast Description Faith Slatcher is the Governor of Goulburn Correctional Complex in New South Wales but you’ll probably be more familiar with the part of this prison known as the Goulburn Supermax which manages high risk inmates including Australia’s “Pablo Escobar” Mostafa Baluch and Bassam Hamzy, boss of the violent crime gang Brothers 4 life. There’s also the never to be released inmates there like Malcolm George Baker who murdered seven people on NSW’s central coast in a spree killing in 1992 and Lindsay Robert Rose, killer of five people over a decade from 1984 to 1994.</description></item><item><title>Women of Corrections - The “Screw” - Angela Feeney | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100175/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 19:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100175/</guid><description>Podcast Description For this episode we meet Angela Feeney, a Corrections officer in NSW who's been in the job for 27 years. Angela has worked a lot with women inmates – it’s something she tells us she swore she’d never do.
&amp;nbsp;
Angela sheds&amp;nbsp;light on life inside prison including the circumstances she’s seen on the job that break her heart and she also gives her honest opinion on how Meshel and Emily would go if they went to jail.</description></item><item><title>Re-Issue: The Jaidyn Leskie Murder | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100176/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 07:09:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100176/</guid><description>Podcast Description RE-ISSUE: EPISODE #165.
The murder of 14-month-old Jaidyn Leskie is officially unsolved. Journalist and author Michael Gleeson explains the prosecution’s theory as to how he died and the many distractions that prevented his killer seeing justice.
Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.
Show notes for Episode 165:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
With thanks to Michael Gleeson from The Age and Sydney Morning Herald</description></item><item><title>Rowland Legg on the Bega School Girls and Jaidyn Leskie | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100177/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 07:05:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100177/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1997, fourteen month old Jaidyn Leskie was left by his young mum Bilynda Williams, with her boyfriend Greg&amp;nbsp;Domaszewicz while she went for a rare night out. She never saw her child again. That same year, two families awoke to discover their teenage daughters were missing after a routine camp out with their friends. They were by then, miles away, having been abducted by two troubled young men with no boundaries, and nothing to lose.</description></item><item><title>The Romance Myth with Alain de Botton | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100178/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 07:13:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100178/</guid><description>Podcast Description What does romance have to do with true crime? Anyone who's fallen prey to coercive control, stalking, cat-fishing or domestic violence will know that the fantasies we're taught about romance can be very damaging when it comes to resisting overbearing partners and recognising red flags. British philosopher and author Alain de Botton wrote the seminal book on the topic in 2016. It's called 'The Course of Love' and Meshel interviewed him way back then about the surprisingly inorganic and unrealistic origins of romance.</description></item><item><title>Your 14yo daughter shouldn't have a 19yo boyfriend. This is why. | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100179/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 18:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ashleigh Rae is confident, smart, witty and really charming company. All of that is a testament to her powerful survival spirit because she was taken advantage of at a very vulnerable time in her life. For those of us who have young girls in our care, what Ashleigh Rae has to say is invaluable.
&amp;nbsp;
If you have a true crime story, we’d love to hear it. You can send us a message on Facebook or Instagram or email us at hello@australiantruecrimepodcast.</description></item><item><title>A Stranger's Face in the Bathroom Mirror | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100180/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 02:37:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kay stepped out of her shower and into a nightmare that changed the way she lived her life forever. A brilliant storyteller, she also lets us in on the extraordinary unprofessionalism of the men who were assigned to assist her.
&amp;nbsp;
If you have a true crime story, we’d love to hear it. You can send us a message on Facebook or Instagram or email us at hello@australiantruecrimepodcast.com</description></item><item><title>You Might've Been Strangled | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100181/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 03:32:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Did you know a strangulation episode during a violent attack can kill months later? Even if it leaves no visible marks?&amp;nbsp;Many victims don't even realise they've been strangled. Betty Taylor is the CEO of the Red Rose foundation in Brisbane that works to address the high number of domestic violence related deaths and suicides in the community. One of their main areas of focus is educating the community and first responders about non-fatal strangulation.</description></item><item><title>Narelle Fraser - Surprise! | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100182/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 02:29:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100182/</guid><description>Podcast Description Narelle Fraser – Surprise!
So many of you have asked to hear Narelle again so here she is. You may remember I promised another episode with Rowland Legg this week and I haven’t forgotten but here’s the thing, due to unforeseen circumstance, Rowland can’t make our live show at the Yarraville club on April 8, so our old friend Narelle Fraser has agreed to step in for that one too.</description></item><item><title>Legendary Homicide Detective Rowland Legg | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100183/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 17:08:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100183/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rowland Legg was the lead homicide investigator on some of Australia's most notorious crimes including the murders of Jason Moran and his bodyguard Pasquale Barbaro at a suburban children's football game at the height of the Melbourne gang war in 2003, and the shocking murder of Mercina Helvagis as she tended her grandmother's grave at Fawkner Cemetery by serial killer Peter Dupas in 1997. He joins us as a guest on this week's podcast and he will join us live on stage at the Yarraville Club on April 8.</description></item><item><title>My Child is a Notorious Killer - Short Cut | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100184/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 22:39:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100184/</guid><description>Podcast Description The bullet point version of this week's episode of Australian True Crime. Two extended families continue to pay a heavy price for turning a blind eye to the disfunction in one household. A mother joins us to talk about the lead up to her child becoming a killer, and the aftermath so many people must live with for the rest of their lives.
If you are in immediate danger in Australia, call 000.</description></item><item><title>My Child is a Notorious Killer. | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100185/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100185/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two extended families continue to pay a heavy price for turning a blind eye to the disfunction in one household. A mother joins us to talk about the lead up to her child becoming a killer, and the aftermath so many people must live with for the rest of their lives. If you are in immediate danger in Australia, call 000.
There is help if you are experiencing family violence or coercive control.</description></item><item><title>Always Fighting: Criminal Defence Lawyer Bernie “The Attorney” Balmer | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100186/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 07:11:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100186/</guid><description>Podcast Description Melbourne criminal defence lawyer Bernie Balmer has represented some of Victoria’s most notorious identities like gangland matriarch Judy Moran, Mick Gatto and Mark “Chopper Read”, AFL and NRL players, past and present, and people you’ve probably never heard of, like the woman who stabbed to death the child she gave birth to, on an access visit, with the adoptive parents nearby.
&amp;nbsp;
He and his team are also known for representing some of the most vulnerable people, including children, who enter the court system each day.</description></item><item><title>Re-Issue: The Day They Blew Up The Police Station - The Russell Street Bombing | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100187/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 17:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100187/</guid><description>Podcast Description RE-ISSUE: EPISODE #98.
Retired Victoria Police Chief Inspector Rob Bailey has seen a lot over the course of his career. Among many other things, he was part of the legendary Victorian armed robbery squad in its heyday, and he was an eyewitness to what remains the most audacious attack ever carried out by the criminal underworld against Australian law enforcement, the bombing of Police Headquarters in Melbourne’s Russell Street.</description></item><item><title>Re-Issue: Amazing Tales from Special Ops with Doug O'Loughlin and Heath O'Loughlin | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100188/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100188/</guid><description>Podcast Description RE-ISSUE: EPISODE #16.
Doug O'Loughlin was a founding member of the Victorian Special Operations Group. His job was to deal with sieges, hostage situations, terrorist attacks and everything in between. Doug's son Heath has written a book about it and they both join us for a chat.
CREDITS:
&amp;nbsp;
Host: Meshel Laurie. You can find her on Instagram here and get her free monthly newsletter here.
&amp;nbsp;
Co-Host: Emily Webb.</description></item><item><title>The Detective’s Story: Damian Loone on the Disappearance of Cheryl Grimmer | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100189/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100189/</guid><description>Podcast Description Some of you may recognise the name and voice of this episode’s guest, It’s retired NSW Police Detective Sergeant Damian Loone who featured on Hedley Thomas’s extraordinary podcast The Teacher’s Pet. Damian investigated the 1982 disappearance of Sydney mum Lynnette Dawson for years, bringing the case to two coronial inquests. Lynette’s former husband Chris Dawson was charged with her murder in 2018 and is awaiting trial.
Damian features again in another major podcast that’s gripped listeners' attention worldwide.</description></item><item><title>The Detective’s Story: Frank Sanvitale on the Disappearance of Cheryl Grimmer | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100190/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100190/</guid><description>Podcast Description The disappearance of 3-year-old Cheryl Grimmer in 1970 has gripped listeners around the world due to the extraordinary BBC Sounds Podcast Fairy Meadow and our guest for this episode Frank Sanvitale is a big part of that podcast.
Now retired from the New South Wales Police, Frank has moved the wheels of justice further for Cheryl’s shattered family more than had ever been done in the more than 50 years since her disappearance.</description></item><item><title>The Disappearance of Cheryl Grimmer &amp; The 52-year Search for Justice. | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100191/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100191/</guid><description>Podcast Description On January 12th 1970, Three-Year-Old Cheryl Grimmer disappeared from Fairy Meadow Beach. While it’s technically one of Australia’s longest-standing cold cases, Cheryl’s family and the two highly respected former homicide detectives believe they know exactly what happened to her, and who’s responsible.&amp;nbsp;
&amp;nbsp;
Cheryl’s eldest brother, Ricky Nash, was the last person to see her on the day of her disappearance. Ricky joins us to discuss his fight to find justice for his baby sister.</description></item><item><title>Short Cut: Why The Whole Story Matters When Sex Crimes Go To Court. | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100192/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 23:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100192/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is an Australian True Crime short cut. It’s an abridged version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Why The Whole Story Matters When Sex Crimes Go To Court.
Criminologist Patrick Tidmarsh specialises in teaching police how to interview victims of sexual assault and sex offenders in the hope that he can have some positive impact in the pathetically low rates of conviction in that area.</description></item><item><title>Why The Whole Story Matters When Sex Crimes Go To Court. | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100193/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 13:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100193/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why The Whole Story Matters When Sex Crimes Go To Court.
Criminologist Patrick Tidmarsh specialises in teaching police how to interview victims of sexual assault and sex offenders in the hope that he can have some positive impact in the pathetically low rates of conviction in that area. He joins us to talk about his new book ‘The Whole Story’.
The Whole Story by Patrick Tidmarsh: www.booktopia.com.au/the-whole-story-patrick-tidmarsh/book/9781787331037.html
NEXT WEEK Terror Knocks in FNQ - A young man is woken in the dead of night by a terrfied woman at his door.</description></item><item><title>Gary Jubelin's Brilliant Career | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100194/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 08:48:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100194/</guid><description>Podcast Description Show Notes Ep 237 of Australian True Crime with Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
Former Detective Inspector Gary Jubelin of NSW police will be forever linked with the search for William Tyrrell. In this re issued episode of Australian True Crime, originally aired in 2020, we hear about some of the cases that made him a legend before he agreed to take on the one that ended his 34-year career and has him back in the headlines now.</description></item><item><title>William Tyrrell Update - Who Really Said What and When? | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100195/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 07:42:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100195/</guid><description>Podcast Description Show Notes Ep 236 of Australian True Crime with Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
&amp;nbsp;
Australia is haunted by its missing children and none more so than William Tyrrell. On November 16 NSW Police Commissioner Mick Fuller sensationally announced a breakthrough in the investigation. The headlines have been extraordinary and at times misleading. Here are the interviews behind those headlines.
&amp;nbsp;
Buy CSI
Told You Lies by Meshel Laurie here</description></item><item><title>Who Killed Canberra Grandmother Irma Palasics? | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100196/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 14:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100196/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 236:
&amp;nbsp;
On November 6, 1999, Canberra grandmother Irma Palasics was on the floor of her home.
&amp;nbsp;
Irma’s grandson John Mikita feels that the case is tantalisingly close to being solved but frustratingly, despite a few breakthroughs on the case and a $500,000 reward, no one has been arrested. Police believe that members of the Hungarian community in Melbourne can provide the vital clue to the identity of the people who killed Irma.</description></item><item><title>Mystery in The High Country | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100197/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:09:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100197/</guid><description>Podcast Description Show Notes Ep 235 of Australian True Crime with Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
Police are closing in on the truth behind the mysterious disappearance of elderly campers Russell Hill and Carol Clay, missing from Victoria’s high country for over a year now. They’re the latest in a long line of people who’ve met with unknown fates in the area.
&amp;nbsp;
Buy CSI
Told You Lies by Meshel Laurie here</description></item><item><title>What's Britney Spears Got to do with Australian True Crime? | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100198/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 13:15:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100198/</guid><description>Podcast Description Show Notes Ep 234 of Australian True Crime with Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
Brittany Spears’ story has had a profound effect on women around the
world whose basic rights have also been stripped away by partners and other
family members. We discuss the impact of her emancipation with Kat Foster from
the 50/50 Foundation which is working towards equal representation for women in
governance by 2030.
&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>Hedley Thomas’ own unsolved crime. | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100199/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100199/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 233
Hedley Thomas is an award-winning investigative journalist and podcast producer who brought us The Teacher’s Pet and The Night Driver podcasts. He is back with a new podcast series – Shandee's Story – where he goes back to the night of the 23-year old’s murder to find out who killed her and why.
For those of you not familiar with The Teacher’s Pet podcast, Hedley delved into the cold case of missing woman, Lynette Dawson, who disappeared on Sydney's Northern Beaches in 1982.</description></item><item><title>Prison Officer in Danger | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100200/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100200/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 232
It’s hard to imagine a job where you have to be vigilant all the time, being ready to attend to traumatic and unpredictable situations. But that’s what prison officers have to do every day. Social worker and therapist Bruce Perham has worked with hundreds of officers and he’s written a book called Code Blue: Prison Officer in Danger about trauma and PTSD in these first responders.</description></item><item><title>A 1942 cold case and cover up with Bob Marmion | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100201/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100201/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 231
There were only two unsolved murders in the state of Victoria in 1942, and they are heavily shrouded in mystery. These murders happened during World War II time, on the Bellarine Peninsula, in Queenscliff, in an area occupied by Australian troops who were patrolling and defending the coastline.
Early one cold, wintry morning in late May 1942, the bullet-ridden body of Army Driver Roy Willis was found on the side of the road.</description></item><item><title>Jack The Ripper Australian True Crime? | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100202/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100202/</guid><description>Podcast Description Show Notes Ep 230 of Australian True Crime with Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
Was a man convicted of murder in Australia in the late 19th Century also responsible for the Jack the Ripper murders in London?
Far from being a Ripper 'fan', author Garry Linnell is intrigued by Victorian history. In his new book ‘Devil’s Work’, he doesn't just retell the story we're so familiar with but uses it as a starting point to take us further into the social upheaval of the time, both in England and in Australia, where his suspect ended his days.</description></item><item><title>Noona Went to Jail | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100203/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100203/</guid><description>Podcast Description Show Notes Ep 229 of Australian True Crime with Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
Well I’ve said it before and I’ll say it again, some of the best people I’ve ever met have been to prison. Here’s another one. Catherine from Horsham went to jail, and she’s thoroughly lovely, in fact, I bet you can totally relate to her.
&amp;nbsp;
I'm a bit delirious with our endless lockdown I have to admit.</description></item><item><title>Organised crime loves supply chains | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100204/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100204/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 290 of Australian True Crime with Meshel Laurie &amp;amp; Emily Webb.
What does organised crime have to do with supply chains…and how is forensic science used to trace things like gold, diamonds and even food.
These were the questions I had for Western Australia based Cameron Scadding who is a Forensic and Analytical Chemist and founder and Managing Director of a company called Source Certain International.
Over the course of his career Cameron has worked on some fascinating and strange cases using&amp;nbsp;forensic science to help solve crime.</description></item><item><title>The Great Bookie Robbery and the Gamble of Crime with Andrew Rule | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100205/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100205/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 289 of Australian True Crime with Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb.
&amp;nbsp;
Andrew Rule, legendary crime writer is equally fascinated by the horse racing industry. His latest book, Chance: Of Grit and Gamblers and the Romance of Racing is about both! Today he joins us to talk about The Great Bookie Robbery of 1976.
&amp;nbsp;
&amp;nbsp;
Purchase Chance: Of Grit and Gamblers and the Romance of Racing Life &amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>Banquet: The Untold Story of Adelaide’s Family Murders with Debi Marshall | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100206/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100206/</guid><description>Podcast Description Show Notes Ep 228 of Australian True Crime with Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
Veteran journalist and True Crime author Debi Marshall joins us to talk about her new book, Banquet: The Untold Story of Adelaide’s Family Murders. It follows on from her Foxtel series and podcast, Frozen Lies.
You can subscribe to the podcast here.
You can buy the book HERE.
Buy CSI Told You Lies by Meshel Laurie here</description></item><item><title>Chapelwaite Special Extra Episode | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100207/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 21:54:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100207/</guid><description>Podcast Description Show Notes Ep 226 of Australian True Crime with Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
This is a special extra episode of ATC to celebrate the release of ‘Chapelwaite’, inspired by the Stephen King short story ‘Jerusalem’s Lot’ on Stan. You can sign up for your 30-day free trial at stan.com.au
&amp;nbsp;
&amp;nbsp;
Buy CSI Told You Lies by Meshel Laurie
In Paperback
As an ebook
As an audiobook read by Meshel</description></item><item><title>Dr Joanna Glengarry Forensic Pathologist | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100208/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100208/</guid><description>Podcast Description Show Notes Ep 225 of Australian True Crime with Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
Dr Joanna Glengarry studied for 8 years to be a surgeon but not long after completing her studies and entering the theatre she realised her true passion was forensic pathology. In her native Auckland, that meant another 5 years of formal study, just to get an introduction at the city mortuary. She was taken on as a Saturday volunteer.</description></item><item><title>Squizzy Taylor Australia’s first flashy Gangster | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100209/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100209/</guid><description>Podcast Description Show Notes Ep 224 of Australian True Crime with Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
Squizzy Taylor was Australia’s first flashy Gangster. He set the standard so many still try to emulate today. Squizzy courted the media, flaunted an extravagant lifestyle and never laid low. Historian Roy Malloy joins us to talk about the incredible exploits of Squizzy and his associates.
You can buy Roy’s book, Squizzy Taylor, The Forensics, The Man, The Vendetta, here.</description></item><item><title>Bikies, the Mount Panorama riots and the lure of the open road with Boris Mihailovic | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100210/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100210/</guid><description>Podcast Description Boris Mihailovic is a former outlaw motorcycle club member, a journo and magazine editor and writer, and author of three books - My mother Warned Me about Blokes Like Me, At the Altar Altar of the&amp;nbsp;Road Gods and The Wisdom of the Road Gods.
&amp;nbsp;
You can find out more about Boris and read his provocative musings at his website &amp;nbsp;borismihailovic.com Boris co-hosts a popular podcast&amp;nbsp;MotoPG.
&amp;nbsp;
Buy Meshel’s book “CSI Told You Lies” here.</description></item><item><title>New Hope for the Unidentified | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100211/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100211/</guid><description>Podcast Description Show Notes Ep 222 of Australian True Crime with Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
New Hope for the Unidentified
There are around 500 sets of unidentified human remains stored in mortuaries around Australia. There are also over 2000 people registered as long-term missing persons. No doubt, some of them are the same people, so why have none of these mysteries been solved?&amp;nbsp;There is new hope.
&amp;nbsp;
For more information about Australian Missing Persons -</description></item><item><title>Missing Suzie Lawrance | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100212/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100212/</guid><description>Podcast Description Suzanne Lawrance, known as Suzie, has been missing from Healesville, Victoria since February 7 1987 after walking home from a 21st birthday party at the town’s Memorial Hall.
We speak to Suzie’s family - Liz Westwood and Tony Lawrance and Suzie’s friends, Tracey Squires, Natalie Tulipano, Matthew Hughes and Glenn Taylor in this episode.
&amp;nbsp;
If you have any information that could help find out what happened to Suzanne Lawrance call Crime Stoppers on 1800 333 000 or report online at crimestoppersvic.</description></item><item><title>The Coffin Confessor spills people’s secrets from beyond their graves | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100213/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100213/</guid><description>Podcast Description CONTENT WARNING: this episode discusses suicide, sexual abuse and assault.
Private investigator and entrepreneur Bill Edgar had a traumatic childhood. Childhood sexual assault, life on the streets and a stint in Brisbane’s notorious Boggo Road Jail with some of Australia’s worst criminals, Bill found many ways to survive. In adulthood, Bill has built a loving home and family life with his wife Lara and their children and grandchildren.&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>The Abortion Clinic Murder and the High Court drama that followed | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100214/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 06:19:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100214/</guid><description>Podcast Description Show Notes Ep 219 of Australian True Crime with Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb:
On 16 July 2001, security guard Steven Rogers was shot dead at his workplace, a Fertility Control Clinic in East Melbourne. Clinical psychologist Dr Susie Allanson who worked at the clinic was on-sight that day and she joins us to tell us about it, along with lawyer Lizzie O’Shea who represented the clinic in the Supreme Court Case against protesters who'd harassed staff and patients for years before the crime.</description></item><item><title>Vale Sandra Pankhurst The Trauma Cleaner | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100215/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100215/</guid><description>Podcast Description Show Notes Ep 218 of Australian True Crime with Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
The legendary Sandra Pankhurst, made famous as The Trauma Cleaner in the brilliant book by Sarah Krasnostein, passed away last week. Although she battled health issues for some years, Sandra never lost her sense of humour, her incredible generosity or her capacity for love. She was genuinely one of the most loving human beings I’ve ever met.</description></item><item><title>Online Child Exploitation – Lux’s Destruction | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100216/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100216/</guid><description>Podcast Description Show Notes Ep 217 of Australian True Crime with Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
Australian journalist Eileen Ormsby literally wrote the book on the Dark Web. In fact, she’s written 7 books about it, but it was her first book, “Silk Road”, released in 2014, about the so-called eBay of hard drugs, that began the exposure of the darkest corners of the internet to the world.
A year after Silk Road’s release, Eileen sat in a courtroom looking at a man who was once the internet’s most wanted and illusive trafficker of violent child abuse material.</description></item><item><title>The good old mental health defence. | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100217/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100217/</guid><description>Podcast Description Show Notes Ep 216 of Australian True Crime with Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
Dr Danny Sullivan is the Executive Director of Clinical Services at Thomas Embling hospital, Melbourne's Secure Mental Health Hospital, which houses patients with varying levels of security clearance including some who've committed extremely violent acts, but who the court has deemed to ill to be held responsible. You can find out more about the work of Forensicare at https://www.</description></item><item><title>The Devil is in the detail. Where is Amber Haigh? | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100218/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100218/</guid><description>Podcast Description Show Notes Ep 215 of Australian True Crime with Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
Amber Haigh has been on the missing persons list since 2002. At that time, she was 19 years old, the mother of a newborn, residing in the NSW town of Young, with the parents of her former boyfriend, who were reportedly the last people to see her alive.
&amp;nbsp;
Shaun McMahon, from the True Blue Crime podcast joins us to tell us the chilling story of Amber’s disappearance.</description></item><item><title>Beenham Valley Update | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100219/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100219/</guid><description>Podcast Description Show Notes Ep 214 of Australian True Crime with Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
Many things have changed since Jamie Pultz and I last spoke about Kirra
McLoughlin’s death and the podcast it inspired, called Beenham Valley Road.
Most notably, we don’t have to use the pseudonym “Jason” when talking about her
partner anymore. That’s because Queensland’s Deputy Coroner named him as the
person responsible for her death last week in the inquest brought about in no</description></item><item><title>On the Trail of the Serpent | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100220/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 05:30:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100220/</guid><description>Podcast Description Show Notes Ep 213 of Australian True Crime with Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
Julie Clarke and her husband Richard Neville wrote the book On the Trail of the Serpent, The Life and Crimes of Charles Sobhraj upon which the
Netflix series The Serpent is based. Julie is our guest this week.
&amp;nbsp;
You can support us with a one-off contribution here.
You can become a patron here.</description></item><item><title>Short Cut Troll Hunter Ginger Gorman | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100221/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100221/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is an Australian True Crime short cut. It’s an abridged version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
Australian True Crime with Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
Ginger Gorman is an award-winning journalist and the author of Troll Hunter. She’s always had great passion for her work, and she’s been driven by equal parts creativity and curiosity. In 2011, those forces led her to a home in Far North Queensland to record an interview with a family.</description></item><item><title>Troll Hunter Ginger Gorman | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100222/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100222/</guid><description>Podcast Description Show Notes Ep 212 of Australian True Crime with Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
Ginger Gorman is an award-winning journalist and the author of Troll Hunter. She’s always had great passion for her work, and she’s been driven by equal parts creativity and curiosity. In 2011, those forces led her to a home in Far North Queensland to record an interview with a family.&amp;nbsp;It was meant to be a short radio piece about diverse families, but Ginger had no way of knowing that it would change her life and lead her into some of the darkest corners of the modern world.</description></item><item><title>My Father the Murderer | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100223/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100223/</guid><description>Podcast Description Show Notes Ep 211
Journalist Nina Young made a podcast documenting her search for the truth about her father. It’s called My Father the Murderer.
Nina uncovered much more than she could ever have imagined, and more than her mother Denise had ever wanted to know. Both Nina and Denise join us to talk about their impressions of the man in question, Allen Ladd and his crimes. We’ll also talk about the profound impact on their relationship of not talking enough about him for most of Nina’s life and then talking about little else for the last two years.</description></item><item><title>Short Cut My Father The Murderer | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100224/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100224/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is an Australian True Crime short cut. It’s an abridged version of this week’s more detailed full episode, which is also available on our feed.&amp;nbsp;
&amp;nbsp;
Journalist Nina Young made a podcast documenting her search for the truth about her father. It’s called My Father the Murderer.
Nina uncovered much more than she could ever have imagined, and more than her mother Denise had ever wanted to know.</description></item><item><title>Dr Ahona Guha works with stalkers | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100225/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100225/</guid><description>Podcast Description Melbourne-based forensic and clinical psychologist Dr Ahona Guha joins us to discuss her work with people who display abnormal behaviours from stalking to arson. You can ask Ahona questions on Instagram or Twitter
Like us on Facebook ​
Follow us on Instagram or Twitter
Support us on Patreon
Visit our Bookshop
Support this show http://supporter.acast.com/australiantruecrime.
Become a subscriber to Australian True Crime Plus here: https://plus.acast.com/s/australiantruecrime.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>With True Crime and Cocktails | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100226/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 13:44:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100226/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a special mother’s day edition if Australian true crime. Both Emily and Meshel have a favourite TV show they share with their 11-year-old daughters called “Superstore”. All four of them share the same favourite character – assistant manager Dina Fox, played by Canadian actress Lauren Ash, and would you believe it?&amp;nbsp;Lauren co-hosts her own True Crime podcast, called True Crime and Cocktails with her best friend who also happens to be her cousin, Christy Oxborrow.</description></item><item><title>Dimity Matters | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100227/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100227/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode we hear from Dimity about the night she was sexually assaulted by a stranger in 2019, the investigation from her perspective, why she chooses to speak about her experience and how she feels about it now. Most importantly though, we learn lots of other things about Dimity.
You can support us with a one-off contribution here.
You can become a patron here.
You can subscribe to Calm Ya Farm here.</description></item><item><title>Sex Crimes Investigations 2021 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100228/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 09:04:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100228/</guid><description>Podcast Description Detective Leading Senior Constable Brett Sniegowski takes us through the investigation into the 2019 sexual assault of Dimity, who joins us next week. We discuss the criticisms levelled at police by sexual assault victims and their families in the past and how investigators are working to improve their methods.
Thank you to Detective Leading Senior Constable Brett Sniegowski and Detective Inspector Juliann Goldrick, and thank to Victoria Police Media.</description></item><item><title>Inside the Real Animal Kingdom | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100230/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100230/</guid><description>Podcast Description Show notes for Episode 207:
Your hosts are&amp;nbsp;MeshelLaurie&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;EmilyWebb
With thanks to Joe Noonan.
“Breaking Ranks: An Amazing true Story of a cop on the line.”
Former Detective Joe Noonan’s time in Victoria Police happened to coincide with a very hectic period in history - the 1980s when a bloody battle raged between the armed robbery squad and the fearless armed robbery gangs of the day.
You can support us with a one-off contribution here.</description></item><item><title>Re Issue - Golden Age of Australian Armed Robbery | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100229/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100229/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bank robbers like Russell ‘Mad Dog’ Cox and Ray Denning were household names in Australia in the 1980s, when they brazenly escaped prison and taunted police for years. Author Mark Dapin joins us to talk about this period in Australian history.
Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.
Show notes for Episode 172:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
With thanks to Mark Dapin</description></item><item><title>Can Hard Cuddles End Family Violence? | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100231/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100231/</guid><description>Podcast Description Show notes for Episode 206:
Your hosts are&amp;nbsp;Meshel Laurie&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;Emily Webb
With thanks to James Harding and Steve.
For one family at least, connecting with James Harding’s Hard Cuddles organisation was the intervention that made the difference. Steve was fresh out of jail when he met James Harding. He was a convicted domestic abuser, helpless against his addiction, on the verge of losing his children and still blaming his partner for his troubles.</description></item><item><title>SOCIT Explainer with Narelle Fraser and her mentor Lorraine Blackwell | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100232/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 22:53:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100232/</guid><description>Podcast Description Narelle Fraser and her mentor Lorraine Blackwell discuss the beginning of Victoria Police’s SOCIT, the Sexual Offence and Child Abuse Investigation Teams , among other things. This was originally a Patreon-only episode but we’ve released it as a special companion episode to this week’s main show.
You can support us with a one-off contribution here.
You can become a patron here.
﻿Show notes for Episode 206:
Your hosts are&amp;nbsp;Meshel Laurie&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;Emily Webb</description></item><item><title>The System’s Victims | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100233/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 20:15:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100233/</guid><description>Podcast Description A mother from country Victoria wants us to know what it’s really like, day-by-day, for a family after they report their daughter’s rape by a family friend.
You can support us with a one-off contribution here.
You can become a patron here.
You can subscribe to Calm Ya Farm here.
You can visit the Calm Ya Farm website here.
﻿Show notes for Episode 205:
Your hosts are&amp;nbsp;Meshel Laurie&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;Emily Webb</description></item><item><title>Prison Forensic Psych | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100234/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100234/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ellery Kane’s life is non-stop crime. By day Ellery is a forensic psychologist and she evaluates prison inmates in California, most of whom have committed murder or another serious crime and have been in jail for a very long time, and are coming up for parole. Ellery’s the author of the detective thriller series featuring&amp;nbsp;Criminal Psychologist Olivia Rockwell and Detective Will Decker. The first book in this series is Watch Her Vanish.</description></item><item><title>Man Shot Dead In Stand Off – My Father | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100235/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100235/</guid><description>Podcast Description Travis Winks talks about the chain reaction of events that turned his normal, Queensland family into a tragic, sensational headline.
You can support us with a one-off contribution here.
You can become a patron here.
You can subscribe to Calm Ya Farm here.
You can visit the Calm Ya Farm website here.
﻿Show notes for Episode 204:
Your hosts are&amp;nbsp;Meshel Laurie&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;Emily Webb
With thanks to Travis Winks.
Shattered, 67 days to a family’s Self-Destruction</description></item><item><title>Phia's Brother Corey Was No Angel. | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100236/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100236/</guid><description>Podcast Description Phia Power’s brother Corey wasn’t exactly a model citizen, but should that make us any less interested in seeing justice for his murder?&amp;nbsp;
You can support us with a one-off contribution here.
You can become a patron here.
﻿Show notes for Episode 203:
Your hosts are&amp;nbsp;Meshel Laurie&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;Emily Webb
With thanks to Phia Power.
Like us on&amp;nbsp;Facebook&amp;nbsp;​
Follow us on&amp;nbsp;Instagram&amp;nbsp;or&amp;nbsp;Twitter
Support us on&amp;nbsp;Patreon
Visit our&amp;nbsp;Bookshop
Listen on&amp;nbsp;Apple Podcasts
Listen on&amp;nbsp;Google Podcasts</description></item><item><title>Barrenjoey Road - Update - #193 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100237/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100237/</guid><description>Podcast Description Neil Mercer and Ruby Jones are still investigating the crimes of Neville Tween, who stalked Sydney’s Northern Beaches without apparent impunity in the 70s and 80s. He trained up dozens of other sex offenders and released them into the community too. How did he get away with so much for so long? The unsolved disappearance of Trudy Adams was just the beginning. The book, Barrenjoey Road is out now, through ABC books.</description></item><item><title>The Husband Poisoner - #192 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100238/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100238/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sydney experienced a noticeable uptick in homicides post WWII, and as police made more and more arrests the startling truth emerged. Women represented a much higher proportion of offenders than ever before and their MO struck fear into husbands nation wide.
&amp;nbsp;
Dr Tanya Bretherton joins us to discuss the phenomenon and her book, THE HUSBAND POISONER
﻿Show notes for Episode 192:
Your hosts are&amp;nbsp;Meshel Laurie&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;Emily Webb
With thanks to Dr Tanya Bretherton</description></item><item><title>The Unsolved Frankston &amp; Tynong North Murders - #191 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100239/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100239/</guid><description>Podcast Description Author Brian Willams is back with another deep dive into crime - this time the baffling Tynong and Frankston North Serial Killings that are still unsolved 40 years since the discovery of&amp;nbsp;three female murder victims who were ritualistically concealed in Victorian bushland.
We also spoke to Brian for Episode #59 about his book about serial killer Martha Needle .
Show notes for Episode 191:
Your hosts are&amp;nbsp;Meshel Laurie&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;Emily Webb</description></item><item><title>The Vanishing Criminal - #190 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100240/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100240/</guid><description>Podcast Description There was a time in Australia where crime was hectic - armed robberies, a racket in stolen goods like stereos that could be sold quickly, an explosion in the heroin trade, shocking gun crimes including at Hoddle Street Melbourne, Strathfield Plaza in Sydney and Port Arthur in Tasmania .&amp;nbsp;
Even former Prime minister&amp;nbsp;the late Bob Hawke and his family were directly touched by the impacts of the drug trade when he and then wife Hazel spoke to the nation about their daughter’s heroin addiction.</description></item><item><title>Stalking Claremont - #189 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100241/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100241/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Claremont Serial Killer. Bret Christian is a journalist from Perth, in fact he's a newspaper owner and he's been following the Claremont serial killer case from the very beginning. Now, after sitting through every day of the trial he's written the definitive book, Stalking Claremont, and he joins us exclusively to talk about it.&amp;nbsp;
I've read it and it's great. It's a very intense story, especially when you think about what a great mystery it was for so long.</description></item><item><title>Lynne McGranger (Yes, it's Irene!) | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100242/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 23:53:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100242/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi friend. We're back next week with all new Australian True Crime but in the meantime, please give our new show Calm ya Farm a try. It’s a short drop of practical wisdom from unlikely gurus. This one is Home and Away’s Irene!
More calming ideas at our website.
Thank you to Uncle Jack Charles for the Acknowledgement of Country.
How do YOU #CalmYaFarm? Leave us a voice message via our Speakpipe!</description></item><item><title>Spotlight Series: Stalking Australia: She ain't no Mary Poppins | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100243/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 06:11:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100243/</guid><description>Podcast Description Another instalment of our Spotlight series, where we showcase one of our favourite podcasts.
Stalking is prevalent in Australia.&amp;nbsp;There are hundreds of cases reported every year.&amp;nbsp;These people’s existence have been besieged by a stalker. Survivors often are voiceless and have no place to tell their stories.&amp;nbsp;This podcast is giving a voice to these victims.&amp;nbsp;A place to tell their stories.&amp;nbsp;Hopefully we can help others who are in this terrible situation to fight back.</description></item><item><title>Spotlight Series: Still Not Asking For it - Episode 2 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100244/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 06:59:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100244/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 2nd part of the Still Not Asking For It podcast, presented by Rory Banwell.
Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.
The Still Not Asking For It Project was born in July 2014. Rory was pregnant and when her and her partner discovered they were pregnant with a girl, the first thing someone said was 'well, time to buy a gun'; it was then that the shocking nature of embedded rape culture slapped me across the face.</description></item><item><title>Spotlight Series: Still Not Asking For It - Episode 1 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100245/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 13:37:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100245/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our Spotlight Series continues with the Still Not Asking For It podcast, presented by Rory Banwell.
Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.
The Still Not Asking For It Project was born in July 2014. Rory was pregnant and when her and her partner discovered they were pregnant with a girl, the first thing someone said was 'well, time to buy a gun'; it was then that the shocking nature of embedded rape culture slapped me across the face.</description></item><item><title>Spotlight Series: Birds Eye View | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100246/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 02:34:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100246/</guid><description>Podcast Description Introducing Birds Eye View. This is the first episode of the award-winning podcast made by the women inside the Darwin Correctional Centre.
For more info, check out their website here and subscribe wherever you get your podcasts.
Thank you to the producers of Bird's Eye View, Story Projects in the NT.
Support this show http://supporter.acast.com/australiantruecrime.
Become a subscriber to Australian True Crime Plus here: https://plus.acast.com/s/australiantruecrime.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Crime Fiction Friday with Emily Webb - #188 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100247/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100247/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s not Friday but welcome to Emily Webb’s new podcast Crime Fiction Friday! Every week Emily talks to one of the world’s most successful authors about their work and inspiration&amp;nbsp;
Subscribe here.&amp;nbsp;
With thanks to Uncle Jack Charles for the acknowledgement of country.&amp;nbsp;
﻿Show notes for Episode 188:
Your hosts are&amp;nbsp;Meshel Laurie&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;Emily Webb
With thanks to S.R. White
Like us on&amp;nbsp;Facebook&amp;nbsp;​
Follow us on&amp;nbsp;Instagram&amp;nbsp;or&amp;nbsp;Twitter
Support us on&amp;nbsp;Patreon
Visit our&amp;nbsp;Bookshop</description></item><item><title>Nicole Lee went back to court so she could speak about her survival after rape - #187 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100248/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100248/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nicole Lee’s husband raped her virtually every day for years on end and pled guilty to doing so in court. The Judge praised him in his sentencing remarks as a quiet, gentle man. Then the Victorian Government made Nicole fight through the courts again for the right to tell her own story. She and Nina Funnell join us to make it heard.&amp;nbsp;
https://au.gofundme.com/f/stop-silencing-survivors
1800RESPECT if you or someone you know has been effected by sexual assault.</description></item><item><title>Perth’s First Serial Killer - #186 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100249/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100249/</guid><description>Podcast Description Perth was terrorised in the 1960's by an illusive night stalker. He killed men and women, in different ways and ran the police in circles. And that’s just the beginning of this extraordinary story.&amp;nbsp;Film maker Thomas Meadmore has made a 4 part documentary series on Stan and he joins us from Covid lockdown in London to talk about it.
“After The Night” The Stan Original documentary series, streaming from November 29.</description></item><item><title>Catching the Kimberley Killer - #185 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100250/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100250/</guid><description>Podcast Description The remote and unforgiving Kimberley region of Australia's top end is one of the worst places on Earth you'd want to be tracking a crazed killer. Former WA Police Inspector Bob Brown and his team received bravery awards for doing just that. This is their story. ﻿
﻿Show notes for Episode 185:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
With thanks to Bob Brown
Like us on Facebook ​</description></item><item><title>Seven Bones - two violent murders and a fight for justice #184 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100251/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100251/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former Detective Peter Seymour and his team took a crushing not-guilty verdict and turned it into motivation to keep digging.&amp;nbsp;They solved a cold case and uncovered a truly chilling story.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;He co-authored a book on the case called SEVEN BONES: Two Wives, Two Violent Murders, A Fight For Justice
﻿Show notes for Episode 184:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
With thanks to Peter Seymour
Like us on Facebook ​</description></item><item><title>Amazing Grace found in loss to a serial killer - #183 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100252/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100252/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kylie Nicholas is mesmerising. Her younger sister Nicole was chosen at random by serial killer Peter Dupas in 1999. It changed Kylie’s life in the most unexpected ways.
Show notes for Episode 183:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
With thanks to Kylie Nicholas
Like us on Facebook ​
Follow us on Instagram or Twitter
Support us on Patreon
Visit our Bookshop
Listen on Apple Podcasts</description></item><item><title>Re-issue: Peter Dupas: An Australian Serial Killer - #31 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100253/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100253/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former homicide detective Jeff Maher talks to us about the case that finally exposed Australian serial killer Peter Dupas.
Show notes:
Your hosts are&amp;nbsp;Meshel Laurie&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;Emily Webb
With thanks to Jeff Maher
Like us on the&amp;nbsp;Facebook&amp;nbsp;​
Follow us on&amp;nbsp;Instagram&amp;nbsp;or&amp;nbsp;Twitter
Support us on&amp;nbsp;Patreon
Listen to episode 183: Amazing Grace found in loss to a serial killer
If you have any information on the cases covered by this podcast, please contact Crime Stoppers on 1800 333 000.</description></item><item><title>Victoria’s Laws are about to get even worse for victim - #182 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100254/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100254/</guid><description>Podcast Description ﻿Journalist Nina Funnell is exposing the Victorian Governments latest bizarre proposed legislative changes. This time they are trying to wipe the names of victims from history.
Show notes for Episode 182:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
With thanks to Nina Funnell and Chrissie Foster
Support #LetUsSpeak on GoFundMe
Like us on Facebook ​
Follow us on Instagram or Twitter
Support us on Patreon
Visit our Bookshop</description></item><item><title>The Nurse with Camille Bianchi - #181 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100255/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100255/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jim Griffin was a nurse in the children’s ward of Launceston hospital for 18 years until 2019. He was also a prolific paedophile. Journalist Camille Bianchi’s podcast The Nurse examines who knew, and for how long.&amp;nbsp;
You can support the LetUsSpeak campaign at https://au.gofundme.com/f/stop-silencing-survivors
﻿Show notes for Episode 181:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
With thanks to Camille Bianchi
Listen to The Nurse
Like us on Facebook ​</description></item><item><title>Stalking and Murder - #180 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100256/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100256/</guid><description>Podcast Description The inquest into the shocking murders of teenagers Jack and Jennifer Edwards by their father John has revealed his history of family violence and stalking. Journalist and author Megan Norris joins us to talk about her research into the correlation between stalking and murder.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
﻿Show notes for Episode 180:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
With thanks to Megan Norris
Megan's website
Like us on Facebook ​</description></item><item><title>Giving Lawyer X a Voice - #179 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100257/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100257/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do “disgraced” lawyer Nicola Gobbo and “disgraced” former drug squad detective Paul Dale deserve to be given a platform to tell their sides of their stories? Purchase COPS, DRUGS, LAWYER X AND ME by Paul Dale and Vikki Petraitis.
Show notes for Episode 179:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
With thanks to Rachael Brown and Vikki Petraitis
Listen to Trace
Like us on Facebook ​</description></item><item><title>Meet the WAGS - #178 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100258/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100258/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Wives and Girlfriends of some of Australia’s most feared men. Author and journalist Rochelle Jackson tells their stories in her book Partners and Crime, going behind the headlines and hype to reveal what it is really like to live with men who are outside the law, like the infamous Chopper Read, the organised crime boss Bob Trimbole and armed robber Fred Cako.
﻿Show notes for Episode 178:</description></item><item><title>Can TikTok find Kylee-Anne? - #177 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100259/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100259/</guid><description>Podcast Description ﻿Kaz Schaffer is using TikTok to demand answers from the small group of people she believes know what happened to her little sister Kylee who’s been missing since 2004.&amp;nbsp;
Show notes for Episode 177:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
With thanks to Kaz Schaffer
Follow Kaz on TikTok
Help Find Kylee-Ann Schaffer on Facebook
Like us on Facebook ​
Follow us on Instagram or Twitter</description></item><item><title>Could You Just Accept It? - #176 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100260/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100260/</guid><description>Podcast Description Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content and reference to suicide. Listener discretion is advised.
Lyn Cecil believes her son Adam was murdered. At what point would you “just accept” he’d died of suicide and stop fighting?&amp;nbsp;
﻿Show notes for Episode 176:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
With thanks to Lyn Cecil
Like us on Facebook ​
Follow us on Instagram or Twitter</description></item><item><title>Loose Units – Electric Blue - #175 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100261/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100261/</guid><description>Podcast Description Paul Verhoeven’s second book about his father John’s time in NSW police is another fantastic, action-packed and funny read. This time it’s John’s time in the Forensics Unit under Paul’s microscope.&amp;nbsp;
Electric Blue also covers some interesting father-son territory including a very difficult period in both their lives during which Paul was brutally bullied. You can hear more about that in a companion episode of The Nitty Gritty Committee also featuring Paul and John Verhoeven, here.</description></item><item><title>Victorian Rape Survivors Silenced - #174 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100262/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100262/</guid><description>Podcast Description Warning: please be advised this episode contains accounts of sexual assault. Listener discretion is advised.
Journalists Nina Funnel and Sherelle Moody discovered a very big problem with a new piece of legislation passed in Victoria in February 2020. They’ve been helping rape survivors lobby the Victorian Attorney-General Jill Hennessey for several months demanding a fix for the problem without meaningful engagement let alone success.&amp;nbsp;On August 26, Nina published an opinion piece about the legislation on news.</description></item><item><title>Repost: #LetHerSpeak Janelle O’Connor’s sexual assault. WARNING – VIOLENT CONTENT - #159 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100263/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 17:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100263/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is a repost of episode #159, originally published on May 21st 2020.
Janelle O’Connor was the first person in the State of Tasmania to exercise her right to be named as a rape survivor, on the 24th of April 2020. Up until then it was illegal for rape survivors to self-identify.&amp;nbsp;Janelle and NinaFunnel, the founder of the #LetHerSpeak campaign join us to explain the legal changes, and Janelle tells us her story.</description></item><item><title>The Golden Age of Armed Robbery - #172 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100264/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100264/</guid><description>Podcast Description ﻿Bank robbers like Russell ‘Mad Dog’ Cox and Ray Denning were household names in Australia in the 1980s, when they brazenly escaped prison and taunted police for years. Author Mark Dapin joins us to talk about this period in Australian history.
Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.
Show notes for Episode 172:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
With thanks to Mark Dapin</description></item><item><title>Patricia Simmons and her baby brother Robert - #171 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100265/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100265/</guid><description>Podcast Description Patricia Simmons is a child protection worker. Her commitment to helping children find safety is rooted in her own dysfunctional childhood and in her relationship with her baby brother Robert.
﻿Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.
Show notes for Episode 171:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
With thanks to Patricia Simmons
Like us on Facebook ​
Follow us on Instagram or Twitter</description></item><item><title>Simon Fenech is Breaking Good - #170 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100266/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100266/</guid><description>Podcast Description Simon Fenech’s ice addiction transformed him from an athlete, husband and father with a 5 bedroom house and a Harley to a former inmate lining up for food parcels at inner city churches. How did he lose so much and how has he found so much more? He joins us to explain.
Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.
Show notes for Episode 170:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb</description></item><item><title>My Adoption Story is True Crime - #169 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100267/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100267/</guid><description>Podcast Description Liz Colenso discovered as an adult that she was adopted. Her search for her biological mother uncovered a tragic and frightening story.&amp;nbsp;
Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.
Show notes for Episode 169:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
With thanks to Liz Colenso
Like us on Facebook ​
Follow us on Instagram or Twitter
Support us on Patreon
Visit our Bookshop
Listen on Apple Podcasts</description></item><item><title>The Unsolved Murder of Emma Pawelski - #168 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100268/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100268/</guid><description>Podcast Description There are people in Adelaide who know who murdered Emma Pawelski and why. Her mother and her sister are desperate for them to come forward and tell them.&amp;nbsp;
﻿Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.
Show notes for Episode 168:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
With thanks to Sharon McKell
More about Emma's case here
Like us on Facebook ​
Follow us on Instagram or Twitter</description></item><item><title>The First Time He Hit Her - #167 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100269/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100269/</guid><description>Podcast Description Canberra mum Tara Costigan was holding her newborn baby when her ex-partner murdered her in front of her other small children. Although he’d been verbally abusive, it was the first time he hit her.&amp;nbsp;
Heidi Lemon has written a book with Tara’s family and she and Tara’s Aunt Maria join us to talk it. BUY THE FIRST TIME HE HIT HER by Heidi Lemon.
Source audio: 7.30 Report https://www.</description></item><item><title>Gemini Rules Breathing - Astrologer Maggie Kerr | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100270/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 23:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100270/</guid><description>Podcast Description Old School Nitty Gritty Committee is back!
Maggie Kerr is an astrologer of over 30 years’ experience. She says everything that’s happening right now is just down to patterns and it’s all linked to things that’ have happened before.
Today, Maggie’s telling us what patterns are playing out right now and in our immediate future.
Show notes for Episode 721:
Your host is Meshel Laurie
With thanks to guest Maggie Kerr https://www.</description></item><item><title>Undercover Copper Keith Banks - #166 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100271/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100271/</guid><description>Podcast Description Keith Banks was a clean living country boy when he joined QLD Police in the 70s but it took him to some very dark places. He joins us to talk about it.
Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.
Show notes for Episode 166:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
With thanks to Keith Banks
Like us on Facebook ​
Follow us on Instagram or Twitter</description></item><item><title>The Jaidyn Leskie Murder - #165 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100272/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100272/</guid><description>Podcast Description The murder of 14-month-old Jaidyn Leskie is officially unsolved. Journalist and author Michael Gleeson explains the prosecution’s theory as to how he died and the many distractions that prevented his killer seeing justice.
Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.
Show notes for Episode 165:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
With thanks to Michael Gleeson from The Age and Sydney Morning Herald
Listen to Childers</description></item><item><title>The Childers Backpackers Fire - #164 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100273/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100273/</guid><description>Podcast Description Journalist Paul Cochrane joins us to talk about the fire in the Queensland fruit-picking town of Childers that took the lives of 15 people. He hosts the excellent podcast 'Childers The Full Story' and he joins us to tell us about it.&amp;nbsp;
﻿Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.
Show notes for Episode 164:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
With thanks to Paul Cochrane</description></item><item><title>How Lisa Harnum Changed the Conversation - #163 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100274/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100274/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lisa Harnum’s life and death changed the way we think, talk and report about domestic violence in Australia. Former Daily Telegraph Chief Court Amy Dale, reporter and author of THE FALL : How Simon Gittany killed Lisa Harnum joins us to explain.
Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.
Show notes for Episode 163:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
With thanks to Amy Dale</description></item><item><title>The Unsolved Disappearance of Revelle Balmain - #162 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100275/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100275/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stunning young model and dancer Revelle Balmain disappeared in November 1994, just days before realising her dream off moving to Japan to perform. When the police got involved, they discovered her secret life.&amp;nbsp;
Guest John Dale wrote a crime fiction loosly based on Revelle's disappearance called DETECTIVE WORK.
Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.
Show notes for Episode 162:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb</description></item><item><title>Shark Arm - #161 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100276/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100276/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two wealthy Sydney-siders get more than they bargain for when they team up with 2 small-time criminals in this extraordinary depression-era story of two unsolved murders and one nauseous shark.
Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.
Show notes for Episode 161:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
With thanks to Kevin Meagher and Phillip Roope
Like us on Facebook ​
Follow us on Instagram or Twitter</description></item><item><title>A witness finds his courage and a killer is convicted - #160 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100277/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100277/</guid><description>Podcast Description Paul Bellia was just 16, hanging out with his friend Ricky Balcombe in the local shopping mall on a Friday afternoon when an older man walked up to them and stabbed Ricky to death in 1995. Paul spent the following 23 years caught between police asking him to testify against their main suspect and the many intimidating people in his community warning him not to. Some of whom had once been his friends.</description></item><item><title>#LetHerSpeak Janelle O’Connor’s sexual assault. WARNING – VIOLENT CONTENT - #159 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100278/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100278/</guid><description>Podcast Description Janelle O’Connor was the first person in the State of Tasmania to exercise her right to be named as a rape survivor, on the 24th of April 2020. Up until then it was illegal for rape survivors to self-identify.&amp;nbsp;
Janelle and Nina Funnel, the founder of the #LetHerSpeak campaign join us to explain the legal changes, and Janelle tells us her story.&amp;nbsp;
WARNING – This is an extremely disturbing story, please exercise discretion.</description></item><item><title>The Sting – Catching Daniel Morcombe’s Killer - #158 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100279/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100279/</guid><description>Podcast Description Although Queensland police visited Brett Peter Cowan just days after Daniel Morcombe first disappeared in 2003, it took 8 years, an inquest and an incredibly intricate covert operation for them to find a way to convict him of Daniel’s abduction and murder. Journalist Kate Kyriacou covered the case and wrote a book about the covert operation THE STING: The Undercover Operation That Caught Daniel Morcombe's Killer
Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.</description></item><item><title>The Narelle Fraser Conversations - Kira Olney - #157 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100280/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 02:31:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100280/</guid><description>Podcast Description To celebrate our first Australian True Crime online livestream this Saturday Night, starring Narelle Fraser and Ron Iddles, we’re releasing an extra episode this week. It’s another in the series of Narelle Fraser Conversations.
Join us for our very first video live stream event, this Saturday May 16th at 8pm, Narelle Fraser and Ron Iddles, and some other surprises. Purchase your tickets here &amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;https://bit.ly/2L1XK9m
﻿Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.</description></item><item><title>The shocking murder of Bride-to-be Stephanie Scott - #156 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100281/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100281/</guid><description>Podcast Description The rape and murder of country schoolteacher Stephanie Scott just a week before her wedding shocked Australia. Journalist Monique Patterson was the editor of the local paper The Leeton Irrigator at the time, and her reflections are detailed in her book UNITED IN GRIEF.
BUY Monique's book UNITED IN GRIEF
Plus we catch up with Jamie Pultz from “Beenham Valley Road” about his latest podcast, “Who Killed Leanne Holland.</description></item><item><title>The Narelle Fraser Conversations - Patrick Tidmarsh - #155 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100282/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100282/</guid><description>Podcast Description Patrick Tidmarsh is a leading authority on sexual offending, and the investigation of sexual crime. He trains and lectures investigators all over the world on how to improve their response to both offenders and victims.&amp;nbsp;
Narelle Fraser is a former Rape Squad and the Homicide Squad Detective with a focus on victims.
Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.
Show notes for Episode 155:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb</description></item><item><title>The Narelle Fraser Conversations – Retired Victoria Police Assistant Commissioner Sandra Nicholson - #153 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100283/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100283/</guid><description>Podcast Description Retired Victoria Police Assistant Commissioner Sandra Nicholson isn’t the kind of person who seeks attention. Fortunately Narelle knows what an impressive copper lurks beneath the mild-mannered exterior of this quietly spoken lady. She’s even sent other coppers to jail. Sandra Nicholson is a hands-on, supportive leader, but she’s no pushover.
Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.
Show notes for Episode 153:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb</description></item><item><title>Do Policemen Have a Soul? With Gary Raymond - #152 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100284/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100284/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gary Raymond worked some of the highest profile and most challenging cases in NSW policing in living memory, including the brutal abduction and murder of Anita Cobby and the drive-by shooting of 5-year-old Tess Debrincat.&amp;nbsp;He was also deployed to assist Sri Lankan authorities in body recovery after the 2006 Boxing Day Tsunami. His life outside of policing is unlike any we’ve heard described on the podcast before.
Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.</description></item><item><title>The Narelle Fraser Conversations – Michele Williams QC Senior Crown Prosecutor - #151 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100285/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100285/</guid><description>Podcast Description Narelle Fraser dusts off her celebrated interviewing skills for a special series of episodes of Australian True Crime to be featured intermittently throughout the year.&amp;nbsp;In this episode the speaks to legendary Senior Crown Prosecutor Michele Williams QC.
Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.
Show notes for Episode 151:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
With thanks to Narelle Fraser and Michele Williams QC.</description></item><item><title>Welcome To Hell: Yvie Jones | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100286/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 05:15:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100286/</guid><description>Podcast Description We caught up with Yvie Jones from Gogglebox and I’m a Celebrity Get Me Out Of Here for a YouTube Livestream on Friday night. Here are some highlights.
We’ll be doing it again this Friday from 6pm and we’d love you to join us on the Australian True Crime Podcast YouTube channel.&amp;nbsp;
Subscribe to Welcome To Hell on the Nitty Gritty Committee
Support this show http://supporter.acast.com/australiantruecrime.
Become a subscriber to Australian True Crime Plus here: https://plus.</description></item><item><title>Where did Elmer Crawford go? (After murdering his wife and children) - #150 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100287/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100287/</guid><description>Podcast Description Greg Fogarty, author of ALMOST PERFECT: The true story of the Crawford family murders joins us to discuss the story of Elmer Crawford, the "ordinary" family man who hatched an extraordinary plan.
﻿Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.
Show notes for Episode 150:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
With thanks to Greg Fogarty
Like us on Facebook ​
Follow us on Instagram or Twitter</description></item><item><title>Welcome to Hell Trailer | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100288/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100288/</guid><description>Podcast Description Meshel is locked inside with her children and her mother. It's only been a week and it's hell. Her friend comedian Nelly Thomas has a bit of practice but she still loses it sometimes. They have some interesting, unexpected guests lined up, and there's already an episode to sample on Meshel's Nitty Gritty feed. https://podcasts.apple.com/au/podcast/meshel-lauries-nitty-gritty-committee/id980139628#episodeGuid=4c9c8dc6-1d26-4445-9a3b-cc9cbfbebf81
Support this show http://supporter.acast.com/australiantruecrime.
Become a subscriber to Australian True Crime Plus here: https://plus.</description></item><item><title>Tara Schultz and the Price of Survival - #149 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100289/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100289/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tara Schultz is a survivor of many crimes perpetrated against her in childhood. She joins us to share some uncomfortable truths about the difficulties of meeting the ongoing financial costs of her survival.
Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.
Show notes for Episode 149:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
With thanks to Tara Schultz
Follow Tara on Twitter
Like us on Facebook ​</description></item><item><title>Narelle Fraser meets Victor Peirce at the shops - #148 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100290/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100290/</guid><description>Podcast Description Narelle Fraser thought her number was up when she ran into the notorious armed robber Victor Peirce at the shops. She also gives us an update on an unsolved case from her days in the sex crimes squad.
Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.
Show notes for Episode 148:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
With thanks to Narelle Fraser
Get tickets to Narelle's live show on March 28th</description></item><item><title>Journalist Anthony Dowsley on Paul Dale, Lawyer X et al. A Different Perspective - #147 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100291/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100291/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anthony Dowsley’s dogged reporting over several years unmasked lawyer Nicola Gobbo as a police informant and has played a significant role in exposing some of the unorthodox methods employed by Victoria Police in their desperate war against the underworld in the early 2000s.&amp;nbsp;
Entire interview available on Patreon.
Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.
Show notes for Episode 147:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb</description></item><item><title>Paul Dale Pt 2. The Crimes in Question #146 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100292/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 17:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100292/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Disgraced former Drug Squad Detective” Paul Dale was charged with robbery, and then with murder. Some find it hard to believe he’s not in jail or dead, he says he’s an innocent victim of the Lawyer X scandal.&amp;nbsp;You be the judge.
Purchase COPS, DRUGS, LAWYER X AND ME by Paul Dale and Vikki Petraitis.
Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.
Show notes for Episode 146:</description></item><item><title>“Disgraced” Paul Dale. Victim or Villain? - #145 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100293/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100293/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Disgraced former Drug Squad Detective” Paul Dale has seen his reputation so destroyed that his lawyer says he’s virtually beyond defamation.&amp;nbsp;As his biographer Vikki Petraitis puts it, he’s been accused of everything, and yet, he’s never been convicted of anything. Is he the victim of a huge conspiracy, or the luckiest villain in the ongoing saga of the Melbourne Gang war?&amp;nbsp;You be the judge as he joins us to tell his story over two weeks.</description></item><item><title>Missing No More – the Gruesome Truth of the barrel at the barbecues - #144 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100294/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100294/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two “missing” women are found to have suffered similar gruesome fates.&amp;nbsp;Author and journalist Liz Porter returns to tell us the truth about Sylvia Cave and&amp;nbsp;Edwina Boyle.
Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.
Show notes for Episode 144:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
With thanks to Liz Porter
Like us on Facebook ​
Follow us on Instagram or Twitter
Support us on Patreon</description></item><item><title>Defending the Indefensible - #143 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100295/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100295/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tim Marsh defends people we call monsters. He’s Chief Counsel at Victoria Legal Aid, and in the last year alone he’s represented 2 men charged with crimes that rocked the nation. Tim joins us to tell us why he does it, how he copes with it, and about the surprising encounter with a victim’s family member that devastated him.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.</description></item><item><title>105 signs of Recent Injury - #142 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100296/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100296/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jamie Pultz is a former Queensland police officer who’ll soon be launching a podcast investigation into the murder of Leanne Holland.&amp;nbsp;He talks to us about that and about his last podcast project, Beenham Valley Road. We also check up on one of the most memorable guests from Beenham Valley Road.&amp;nbsp;
This episode features the Beenham Valley Road theme song, “Piece is Heaven” by Pete Allen Music. Available on itunes.</description></item><item><title>Special Extra: Clunes Cluedo Episode One | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100297/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100297/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the first episode of Alice Mitchell’s podcast about Nina Nicholson’s unsolved murder, Clunes Cluedo. You’ll find it sometimes overlaps with this week’s episode of ATC, but it’s well worth listening to both because there are some really special details included in this one.&amp;nbsp;
You can subscribe to Clunes Cluedo wherever you get your podcasts.&amp;nbsp;
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
With thanks to Alice Mitchell&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>Justice for Nina - Clunes Unsolved - #141 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100298/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100298/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alice Mitchell is the second cousin of a young woman called Nina Nicholson who was murdered in 1991 on the porch of her home in Clunes, Ballarat (VIC). Nina was a paediatric nurse who was heading out to work when she was attacked. Her murder is still unsolved.
&amp;nbsp;
Alice, who is a private investigator, has become the family sleuth in this case and is letting people know about Nina's case and wants to get a second coronial inquest to look at the murder.</description></item><item><title>Ram Tiwary: The miscarriage of justice you’ve probably never heard of - #140 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100299/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100299/</guid><description>Podcast Description Author Liz Porter, Author of Crime Scene Asia, tells us the unbelievable and disturbing case of Sydney-based Singaporean student Ram Tiwary who spent eight years in a NSW jail for a double&amp;nbsp;murder that he didn't commit.
Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.
Show notes for Episode 140:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
With thanks to Liz Porter&amp;nbsp;
Like us on Facebook ​</description></item><item><title>Arson. - #139 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100300/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100300/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Two things can be true at once,” and arson is part in Australia’s bushfire story.
Dr Troy McEwan is an associate professor in clinical and forensic psychology at Monash university.&amp;nbsp;Her research is focussed on the assessment and treatment of stalking, domestic violence and arson.
&amp;nbsp;
Chloe Hooper, author of excellent books The Arsonist and The Tall Man: Death and Life on Palm Island.
Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.</description></item><item><title>Fiona’s fight to find her husband Bruce’s body - #138 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100301/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100301/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fiona Splitt started an intense advocacy campaign in Queensland to have the "no body, no parole" legislation introduced after the murder of her partner Bruce Schuler in 2012. Bruce was gold fossicking in the remote Palmerville Station area in Cape York, Australia when he was murdered. His body has never been found and a rogue, outback couple Stephen and Dianne Struber were convicted of his murder.
Thanks to Fiona’s immense efforts The “no body, no parole” legislation was introduced.</description></item><item><title>Who Killed Leanne Holland Pt 2 - Graham Stafford Interview #137 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100302/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 16:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100302/</guid><description>Podcast Description Graham Stafford served 15 years for the brutal rape and murder of his girlfriend's 12-year-old sister Leanne. The conviction was overturned in 2009, but Stafford is still locked in a legal battle with the QLD Police Service to have a report into their handling of the case made public.
In the meantime he still faces scepticism and innuendo, including from a controversial episode of Channel 7's recently axed Sunday night program.</description></item><item><title>Who Killed Leanne Holland? Part 1 - #136 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100303/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100303/</guid><description>Podcast Description 12-year-old Leanne Holland was brutally raped and murdered in Ipswich, QLD in 1991. Her sister's boyfriend, Graham Stafford was convicted of the crime, but he maintains his innocence, and the investigation has been found wanting.
Robin Bowles included his story in her book Rough Justice, and she joins us to talk us through the case.
NEXT WEEK, Graham Stafford joins us.
Show notes for Episode 136:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb</description></item><item><title>Shirley Finn, Dirty Girl - #135 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100304/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100304/</guid><description>Podcast Description Perth Brothel owner Shirley Finn's 1975 unsolved murder looms large over the city, with men at the highest levels of government and policing suspected of involvement. Journalist Juliet Wills, author of Dirty Girl: The State Sanctioned Murder of Brothel Madam Shirley Finn, joins us.
Show notes for Episode 135:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
With thanks to Juliet Wills
For more about the campaign to get the palace letters released: https://chuffed.</description></item><item><title>Crime and Sport: Australia's Great Passions - #134 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100305/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100305/</guid><description>Podcast Description From bank robbing football players to drug-dealing football players and stand-over men, (who used to be football players). Ok, they're not all football players. In their new book "Gangland, this Unsporting Life" Susanna Lobez and James Morton have applied their meticulous reporting skills to the intersection of Australian sport and Australian crime. It's very fertile ground.
Purchase Gangland: This Unsporting Life Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.</description></item><item><title>Julie's Big Drug Importation Adventure - #133 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100306/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100306/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Julie was a teenager in 1970s Australia, she and her friends decided to try their hands at drug smuggling. It didn't turn out well, despite the assistance of the Victorian Narcotics Squad.
Show notes for Episode 133:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
With thanks to Julie
Like us on Facebook ​
Follow us on Instagram or Twitter
Support us on Patreon
Listen on Apple Podcasts</description></item><item><title>Jock Palfreeman's Quasi Bulgarian Parole - #132 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100307/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100307/</guid><description>Podcast Description Australian Jock Palfreeman has been in a Bulgarian prison since 28 December 2007 when he was taken into custody for the stabbing murder of Andrei Monov. He says Monov and his friends were attacking two young Roma men, known colloquially as “gypsies”, and he was defending them. The victim’s father says he’s a monster. Australian Story producer and author of the Palfreeman family’s story, Every Parent’s Nightmare, Belinda Hawkins joins us to tell us about the Jock Palfreeman she knows.</description></item><item><title>Re-Issue: Milat Family Insider Special Extra - #131 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100308/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 01:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100308/</guid><description>Podcast Description The “Milat family insider” quoted extensively in Australian media this week is actually our friend Amanda Howard, from the "Monsters Who Murder" podcast. She gives us an update and an insight into her work, as well as a prediction as to whether we can expect a death bed confession.Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily WebbWith thanks to Amanda HowardLike us on Facebook ​Follow us on Instagram or TwitterSupport us on PatreonVisit our BookshopListen on Apple PodcastsListen on Google PodcastsListen on SpotifyIf you have any information on the cases covered by this podcast, please contact Crime Stoppers on 1800 333 000.</description></item><item><title>Re-Issue: The Woman Who Thinks Ivan Milat is Innocent - #130 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100309/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 01:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100309/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amanda Howard, the Serial Killer Whisperer joins us again to talk about the holes she believes are in the case against Ivan Milat. Amanda corresponds with Milat in jail.Show notes:Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily WebbWith thanks to Amanda Howard.Like us on the Facebook ​Follow us on Instagramor TwitterSupport us on PatreonThank you for listening!Support this show http://supporter.acast.com/australiantruecrime. Become a subscriber to Australian True Crime Plus here: https://plus.</description></item><item><title>Dead Man Walking: The Killing of Michael McGurk - #129 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100310/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100310/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael McGurk was murdered with a single gunshot to the head outside his family home in Cremorne in 2009. He described himself as a businessman but others, including politicians and royalty said he was an extortionist, a fraudster and an arsonist. He confided in our guest, legendary journalist Kate McClymont about who he thought might kill him just 10 days before his death.
Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.</description></item><item><title>The Abduction of Joanne Ratcliffe and Kirste Gordon - #128 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100311/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100311/</guid><description>Podcast Description 11-year-old Joanne Ratcliffe was the kind of well-mannered, responsible girl often entrusted to care for younger children. She was no match though for a grown man who seized the opportunity to snatch her and her 4-year-old friend from Adelaide Oval in 1973.Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.Show notes for Episode 128:Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily WebbWith thanks to Suzie RatcliffeLike us on Facebook ​Follow us on Instagram or TwitterSupport us on PatreonVisit our BookshopListen on Apple PodcastsListen on Google PodcastsListen on SpotifyIf you have any information on the cases covered by this podcast, please contact Crime Stoppers on 1800 333 000.</description></item><item><title>Jack and Stacey and Ice in the Latrobe Valley - #127 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100312/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100312/</guid><description>Podcast Description 22-year-old Jack Nankervis was stabbed 70 times by a teenager he didn’t know. His girlfriend Stacey is still trying to put her life back together five years later and understand why it really happened and why no one else seems interested in finding out.Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.Show notes for Episode 127:Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily WebbWith thanks to Stacey Patton.Like us on Facebook ​Follow us on Instagram or TwitterSupport us on PatreonVisit our BookshopListen on Apple PodcastsListen on Google PodcastsListen on SpotifyIf you have any information on the cases covered by this podcast, please contact Crime Stoppers on 1800 333 000.</description></item><item><title>Dianne Brimble: By Her Ex-husband Mark - #126 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100313/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100313/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dianne Brimble died an unnecessary death in the company of strange, cruel men on a cruise she’d saved years for. She’s had no justice, but her ex-husband still fights for her dignity. Read the Inquest into the death of Dianne Brimble - Findings Only.
Purchase Abandoned: The Sad Death of Dianne Brimble Warning: please be advised this episode contains accounts of sexual assault. Listener discretion is advised.
Show notes for Episode 126:</description></item><item><title>Operation Zhivago: A Narelle Fraser Case - #125 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100314/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100314/</guid><description>Podcast Description Narelle is back with a case that’s very close to her heart because it’s connected to her time working with her favourite boss Lorraine Blackwell at Broadmeadows CPS. Lorraine pioneered a victim-focussed approach to the investigation of sexual assault and her influence can still be seen in the Victorian Police force today.
Warning: please be advised this episode contains accounts of sexual assault. Listener discretion is advised.
Show notes for Episode 125:</description></item><item><title>Is Sydney Even Sydney Without The Seedy Cross? - #124 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100315/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100315/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sexy gangster, porn star, part-time models. A letter bomb and a tv home shopping star having sex with another tv home shopping star in a police station before faking his own death and escaping Australia. How has there never been an Underbelly series about this True Crime story from Kings Cross in 1998?As NSW the Premier announces a rollback of the lockout laws, veteran Sydney journalist Mark Morri has finally written a book about this case and these extraordinary people.</description></item><item><title>The Wettenhall Family Murders Rocked the Small Community of Barrabool - #123 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100316/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100316/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Wettenhall Family murders rocked the small community of Barrabool in Victoria. The revelations that came to light in the aftermath however, reflected the sad state of affairs for so many living in regional Australia.
Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.
Show notes for Episode 123:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb
With thanks to Neal Drinnan and Bob Perry.
Like us on Facebook ​</description></item><item><title>Australia's Badlands: The Palmerville Station Murder - #122 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100317/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100317/</guid><description>Podcast Description From Far North Queensland's Cape York comes the terrifying story of the Strubers of Palmerville Station who terrorised gold prospectors for years until they eventually turned to bloody murder. No, this story isn't from the 19th century, this is the story of the murder of Bruce Schuler in 2012.Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.Show notes for Episode 122:Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily WebbWith thanks to Robert Reid.</description></item><item><title>Cardinal Pell's Next Destination, Ararat - #121 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100318/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100318/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr Karen Owen designed the treatment program for sex offenders used by Corrections Victoria. She helps us understand what’s in store for Cardinal George Pell now that he’s leaving the Melbourne Assessment Prison and heading for more long term accommodation.Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.Show notes for Episode 121:Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily WebbWith thanks to Dr Karen Owen, Forensic and Clinical Psychologist and international expert on sex offenders.</description></item><item><title>The Falconio Mystery Continues - #120 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100319/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 17:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100319/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bradley John Murdoch isn't a good man, but did he murder Peter Falconio? That's the question posed by inimitable True Crime author Robin Bowles in her book DEAD CENTRE and she joins us to explain her exhaustive investigations. Most shocking of all, is the lack of evidence of any crime having been committed.
Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.
Show notes for Episode 120:
Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily Webb</description></item><item><title>Greenough Murders: Fighting to Keep a Killer in Jail - #119 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100320/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100320/</guid><description>Podcast Description Karen MacKenzie and her three children were murdered in their Western Australian home in 1993. For her sister Evalyn, the nightmare never ends. She joins us to explain the many ways in which it’s impacted on her life and continues to do so, every day.Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.Show notes for Episode 119:Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily WebbWith thanks to Evalyn Clow.Like us on Facebook ​Follow us on Instagram or TwitterSupport us on PatreonVisit our BookshopListen on Apple PodcastsListen on Google PodcastsListen on SpotifyFor help: Lifeline 13 11 14If you have any information on the cases covered by this podcast, please contact Crime Stoppers on 1800 333 000.</description></item><item><title>Missing But Not Forgotten: A Sister's Story - #118 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100321/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100321/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s National Missing Persons Week in Australia. You can’t look at a missing persons case without at least considering it through the crime filter, even when the last person to see your little brother alive, was your sister. This was the scenario that confronted Jacinta Jackson when her brother Donny disappeared from a camping trip 7 years ago, and she joins us in this episode to talk about it.</description></item><item><title>Remembering Bree - #117 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100322/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100322/</guid><description>Podcast Description The pain of living with loss and injustice. An extraordinarily intimate kitchen table conversation between the family of Bree Jones who died of a drug overdose at the age of 16, at a party in 1995. No one has ever been held responsible for her death despite the best efforts of her family, investigators and the NSW Coroner. Her sister and parents recorded their own episode of Australian True Crime.</description></item><item><title>Murder in Albury - Kim Meredith's Parents and the 5 Minute Window: A Belinda Neil Case - #116 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100323/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100323/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bob and June Meredith were living a simple but idyllic life with their teenage children in Albury in 1996, until a chance encounter with a stranger tore it apart. They join us to tell us about the murder of their daughter Kim. Later in the episode, former homicide detective and lead investigator Belinda Neil joins us to talk about how Kim’s murder investigation changed her life.Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.</description></item><item><title>Death on the Derwent - #115 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100324/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 17:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100324/</guid><description>Podcast Description One man’s mysterious disappearance has become a decade-long tragedy for two Tasmanian women, from different sides of the tracks. Author Robin Bowles has developed a close friendship with one of the women and joins us to talk about her new book on the case.Show notes for Episode 115:Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily WebbWith thanks to Robin BowelsRobin's book "Death on the Derwent" is available in our bookshop https://australiantruecrimepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Journalist Andrew Rule's Scariest Case - #114 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100325/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100325/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's easy to forget it takes a lot of courage to write stories about bad guys week after week. Andrew Rule has irritated some of the baddest in the business and every so often it gets a little bit scary. Andrew joined Meshel and Emily live on stage recently at Melbourne's Chapel off Chapel to talk about a case involving many twists and turns, and one of the scariest times in his reporting career.</description></item><item><title>My Brother the Paedophile Priest - #113 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100326/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 18:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100326/</guid><description>Podcast Description Margaret Harrod and her twin brother Michael both dedicated their lives to God, she as a nun and he as a priest. Their family was the envy of their Catholic community, but there were many secrets inside their home and eventually Margaret found t﻿he courage and the faith to call every one of them out. It continues to be a traumatic journey.
Margaret's book, co written with journalist Sue Smethurst is called "</description></item><item><title>A Kiwi Teen Almost Killed the Queen. Kia Ora cuz! - #112 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100327/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 18:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100327/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1981, a psychopathic New Zealand teenager came very close to assassinating Queen Elizabeth. Embarrassed police not only covered it up but sent him away to Australia, a free man. Why haven't we seen that on the Crown? Former high-ranking New Zealand Detective, now Gold Coast retiree Tom Lewis tried to tell the world and was driven out of his homeland. He and his granddaughter Maria join us to tell the incredible story that's now the subject of a major corruption investigation in New Zealand.</description></item><item><title>The De Gruchy Family Murders - #111 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100328/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 18:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100328/</guid><description>Podcast Description Belinda Neil was settling in on her first day in the homicide squad when she took a phone call that would change the course of her career. An unassuming suburban mother and two of her three teenage children had been brutally murdered. Later that day Belinda and her colleagues would attend the most traumatising crime scene of their careers. One of her colleagues left the police force that day, never to return.</description></item><item><title>Anne Hamilton Byrne and The Family - #110 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100329/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 05:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100329/</guid><description>Podcast Description From humble beginnings in suburban Melbourne to reincarnation as Jesus Christ, a cohort of devoted, well-heeled followers and an enviable real estate portfolio, Anne Hamilton Byrne who died in a nursing home last week really was the quintessential 20th Century cult leader. The only thing more shocking than the abuse she inflicted on dozens of children in her care throughout the 60s, 70s, 80s and 90s, is how various Governmental authorities approved of her guardianship over them in the first place.</description></item><item><title>Lex De Man on Anne Hamilton Byrne's Death - #109 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100330/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100330/</guid><description>Podcast Description When former Detective Lex De Man received a text reading simply, "The Witch is Dead!" he knew exactly what it meant. Since attending a school fire in the small Victorian town of Monbulk in 1987, Lex's life has been consumed with trying to bring about some justice for the people whose childhood's were stolen by Anne.Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.Show notes for Episode 109:Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily WebbWith thanks to Lex De ManListen to previous episode on ‘The Family’, Episode 41 with Chris Johnston https://australiantruecrimepodcast.</description></item><item><title>The David Hookes Matter with Charlie Bezzina - #108 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100331/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 18:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100331/</guid><description>Podcast Description Homicide Detective Charlie Bezzina received a phone call about a man who'd been punched outside a popular St Kilda pub during an altercation with a bouncer. The man was clinging to life, but the prognosis wasn't good. The caller said there was one more detail Charlie needed to know, the victim was International Cricket legend and television commentator David Hookes.Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.Show notes for Episode 108:Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily WebbWith thanks to Charlie BezzinaLike us on Facebook ​Follow us on Instagram or TwitterSupport us on PatreonVisit our BookshopListen on Apple PodcastsListen on Google PodcastsListen on SpotifyIf you have any information on the cases covered by this podcast, please contact Crime Stoppers on 1800 333 000.</description></item><item><title>Frankston Serial Killer Investigation Re Issue - #107 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100332/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 21:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100332/</guid><description>Podcast Description Charlie Bezzina was lead investigator on the Frankston Serial Killer Case in which Carmel and Brian's daughter Natalie was the final victim. In this episode Charlie talks us through the investigation.Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.Show notes for Episode 107:Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily WebbWith thanks to Charlie BezzinaTo support Carmel and Brian please donate to: https://www.gofundme.com/keeptherussellsinfrankstonLike us on Facebook ​Follow us on Instagram or TwitterSupport us on PatreonPurchase The Frankston Murders 25 Years On in our Bookshop Listen on Apple PodcastsListen on Google PodcastsListen on SpotifyIf you have any information on the cases covered by this podcast, please contact Crime Stoppers on 1800 333 000.</description></item><item><title>26 Years After Our Daughter's Murder, We Need Help - #106 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100333/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 17:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100333/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Frankston Serial Killer took their 17-year-old daughter Natalie in 1993, and Carmel and Brian have lived through many more challenges since then. Now they're looking at eviction from their home of 30 years and they're very reluctantly asking for help.Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.Show notes for Episode 106:Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily WebbWith thanks to Carmel and Brian RussellTo support Carmel and Brian please donate to: https://www.</description></item><item><title>ATC Extra. The Family of the Deceased - #105 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100334/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100334/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily is joined by Sandra Charlton, the cousin of Vicki Arnold. Vicki was the woman accused of murdering her best friend Julie-Anne Leahey before killing herself in this week's episode of Australian True Crime. Sandra tells us what it's like to be thrust into the spotlight of a homicide investigation, and to have to clear a beloved relative's name.Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.Show notes for Episode 105:Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily WebbWith thanks to Sandra CharltonLike us on Facebook ​Follow us on Instagram or TwitterSupport us on PatreonVisit our BookshopListen on Apple PodcastsListen on Google PodcastsListen on SpotifyIf you have any information on the cases covered by this podcast, please contact Crime Stoppers on 1800 333 000.</description></item><item><title>A Convenient Murder Suicide: Who Killed Vicki Arnold and Julie-Anne Leahy? - #104 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100335/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 18:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100335/</guid><description>Podcast Description BFFs to the end, Vicki and Julie-Anne died together on a lonely track in Far North QLD in 1991. The police quickly ruled it a murder suicide but the families, the community, the Australian public and relentless local journalist Robert Reid refused to give up on the many inconsistencies in the case, and the brutal death scene. Reid joins us to guide us through the many twists and turns of Vicki and Julie-Anne's case.</description></item><item><title>The Crimes and Times of Uncle Jack Charles - #103 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100336/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100336/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jack Charles, known respectfully and affectionately as Uncle Jack Charles is a survivor who has much to tell about life, starting from the impact of being one of the Stolen Generation; Indigenous children forcibly removed from their families as a result of various government policies. Uncle Jack's life has traversed orphanages, prison, addiction, recovery, art, theatre, activism, advocacy… he is a survivor. We speak with Jack about his incredible life and he delves into deep issues of society, all the while maintaining his indisputable charm.</description></item><item><title>Milat Family Insider Special Extra - #102 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100337/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 11:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100337/</guid><description>Podcast Description The “Milat family insider” quoted extensively in Australian media this week is actually our friend Amanda Howard, from the "Monsters Who Murder" podcast. She gives us an update and an insight into her work, as well as a prediction as to whether we can expect a death bed confession.Warning: please be advised this episode contains graphic content.Show notes for Episode 102:Your hosts are Meshel Laurie and Emily WebbWith thanks to Amanda HowardLike us on Facebook ​Follow us on Instagram or TwitterSupport us on PatreonVisit our BookshopListen on Apple PodcastsListen on Google PodcastsListen on SpotifyIf you have any information on the cases covered by this podcast, please contact Crime Stoppers on 1800 333 000.</description></item><item><title>Karlie and Khandalyce: The Lost Girls with Ava Benny-Morrison - #101 | Australian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9880100338/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9880100338/</guid><description>Podcast Description How did the remains of toddler Khandalyce Pearce-Stevenson end up in a suitcase by the side of a highway in South Australia? How did her mother Karlie’s remains end up over a thousand kilometres away in the notorious Belanglo State Forest. How did detectives solve this heinous crime and reunite them seven years after their brutal deaths? Journalist Ava Benny-Morrison joins us to talk about her book The Lost Girls which fills in the terrible details.</description></item></channel></rss>