<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/heart-starts-pounding-horrors-hauntings-and-mysteries/</link><description>Recent content in Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 02:50:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/heart-starts-pounding-horrors-hauntings-and-mysteries/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>47: "Smee": A Christmas Ghost Story | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 02:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710001/</guid><description>Podcast Description A game of hide and seek takes a paranormal turn. In the spirit of the old Victorian tradition of telling ghost stories around the holidays, I present to you, a modern-day retelling of A.M Burrage's ghost story, "Smee"'
Subscribe on Patreon for bonus content and to become a member of our Rogue Detecting Society. Patrons have access to ad-free listening and bonus content.
Follow on Tik Tok and Instagram for a daily dose of horror.</description></item><item><title>46: The Winecoff Fire: The Deadliest Hotel Disaster in American History | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 02:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710002/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the night of December 7th, 1946, a woman working the night shift at the Winecoff Hotel in Atlanta, Georgia smells smoke. A few floors up, a man is woken by cries for help. Within two hours, almost half of the guests will be dead.
Subscribe on Patreon for bonus content and to become a member of our Rogue Detecting Society. Patrons have access to ad-free listening and bonus content.</description></item><item><title>45: When Looks Kill: Mad Hatters and Other Deadly Trends in Fashion and Beauty | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 02:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710003/</guid><description>Podcast Description A woman loses the ability to move her arms, A man bursts into flames from seemingly nowhere, and one of the most notorious assassinations in history. What they all have in common may surprise you.
Subscribe on Patreon for bonus content and to become a member of our Rogue Detecting Society. Patrons have access to ad-free listening and bonus content.
Follow on Tik Tok and Instagram for a daily dose of horror.</description></item><item><title>44: Thanksgiving Day Terror: The Unsolved Case of The Blount Family | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 19:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710004/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Thanksgiving Day, 1985, Susan Blount awoke to screams coming from her living room. What she would find remains one of the strangest cold cases in Texas today. Subscribe on Patreon for bonus content and to become a member of our Rogue Detecting Society. Patrons have access to ad-free listening and bonus content.
Follow on Tik Tok and Instagram for a daily dose of horror.
We have a monthly newsletter now!</description></item><item><title>43: HSP x Murder With My Husband: Kaelyn and Payton Talk Strange Disappearances | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710005/</guid><description>Podcast Description I'm joined by my friend Payton from Murder With My Husband to bring you two stories of disappearances we could not stop thinking about. In 1928, the world's third richest man, Alfred Lowenstein, vanished mid-flight. On Halloween night, 2002, Chris Jenkins disappeared in Minnesota, leaving many to wonder if there was a 'Smiley Face Killer' operating in the shadows.
Make sure and check out Murder With My Husband for more deep dive true crime with Payton and Garrett: https://linktr.</description></item><item><title>42: Human Sacrifice: Dark Rituals Throughout History | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 02:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Human sacrifice has been a part of many cultures throughout history. But why did they do it? And more importantly, what was it like for the person being sacrificed? In this episode, we dive into ritual sacrifice in places like the Aztec Empire and Cahokia.
Subscribe on Patreon for bonus content and to become a member of our Rogue Detecting Society. Patrons have access to ad-free listening and bonus content.</description></item><item><title>41: Two Marys, Two Murders: A Houston Cold Case | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 01:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710007/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2000, two Houston-area women named Mary Morris were murdered in their cars within a few days of each other. 23 years later, it's still not certain if the two were connected. If you have any information about the deaths of either Mary Henderson Morris or Mary McGinness Morris, you can contact Harris County Sheriff's Homicide Detective, Jeff Thomas (Jeff.Thomas@hctx.net). You can also call Crimestoppers at 1-800-222-TIPS.
Subscribe on Patreon for bonus content and to become a member of our Rogue Detecting Society.</description></item><item><title>40: The Devil's Bible and Other Haunting Tales for Halloween | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 01:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710008/</guid><description>Podcast Description In honor of Halloween, I'm sharing some of the most chilling tales I've heard this year
Subscribe on Patreon for bonus content and to become a member of our Rogue Detecting Society. Patrons have access to ad-free listening and bonus content. Follow on Tik Tok and Instagram for a daily dose of horror.
We have a monthly newsletter now! Be sure to sign up for updates and more. This episode is brought to you by BetterHelp.</description></item><item><title>39: Listener Stories: Ghost Children, Haunted Campgrounds, and More | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 01:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710009/</guid><description>Podcast Description A ghost who steals, ghostly wailing being heard in the night. These are terrifying stories from listeners.
Subscribe on Patreon for bonus content and to become a member of our Rogue Detecting Society. Patrons have access to ad-free listening and bonus content. Follow on Tik Tok and Instagram for a daily dose of horror.
We have a monthly newsletter now! Be sure to sign up for updates and more.</description></item><item><title>38: Cursed Movies: The Wizard Of Oz and The Exorcist | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 01:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can movies really be cursed? Today, we're looking at what's fact and what's fiction when it comes to The Wizard of Oz and The Exorcist being cursed Subscribe on Patreon for bonus content and to become a member of our Rogue Detecting Society. Patrons get a discount on merch. Follow on Tik Tok and Instagram for a daily dose of horror.
We have a monthly newsletter now! Be sure to sign up for updates and more.</description></item><item><title>37: Invisible Intruder: The Chilling Tale of the Denver Spiderman | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 01:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here's a good reminder to check every nook and cranny of your house tonight....
Subscribe on Patreon for bonus content and to become a member of our Rogue Detecting Society. Patrons get a discount on merch. Follow on Tik Tok and Instagram for a daily dose of horror.
We have a monthly newsletter now! Be sure to sign up for updates and more. Heart Starts Pounding is written and produced by Kaelyn Moore.</description></item><item><title>36: Into Thin Air: The Unsolved Disappearance of Joan Risch | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 01:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710012/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happened to Joan Risch the last day she was ever seen?
Limited drop live now. Get yours in time for spooky season. Subscribe on Patreon for bonus content and to become a member of our Rogue Detecting Society. Patrons get a discount on merch. Follow on Tik Tok and Instagram for a daily dose of horror.
We have a monthly newsletter now! Be sure to sign up for updates and more.</description></item><item><title>35: Dark Therapy: Brainwashing and Forced Confinement | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 01:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710013/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happens when the system that says it'll help you instead uses you as part of their sick experiment? We're looking into two stories of people who were promised help, and instead became stuck in a broken system and faced brainwashing, torture, and imprisonment. Subscribe on Patreon for bonus content and to become a member of our Rogue Detecting Society.
Follow on Tik Tok and Instagram for a daily dose of horror.</description></item><item><title>34: Terrifying True Urban Legends | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710014/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 01:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710014/</guid><description>Podcast Description We've all heard terrifying urban legends growing up, but what happens when they're based on real events....
We're diving into some terrifying urban legends that ended up being true.
Subscribe on Patreon for bonus content and to become a member of our Rogue Detecting Society.
Follow on Tik Tok and Instagram for a daily dose of horror.
We have a monthly newsletter now! Be sure to sign up for updates and more.</description></item><item><title>33: Vanished in The Wilderness Pt. 2: The Cult | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 01:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why did Boris Weisfeiler disappear in 1985. And did the cult hiding out deep in the Chilean wilderness have anything to do with it? Today, we're exploring the Colonia Dignidad.
Subscribe on Patreon for bonus content and to become a member of our Rogue Detecting Society.
Follow on Tik Tok and Instagram for a daily dose of horror.
We have a monthly newsletter now! Be sure to sign up for updates and more.</description></item><item><title>32: Vanished in The Wilderness Pt 1: The Professor Disappears | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 01:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710016/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Boris Weisfeiler embarked on a solo vacation to Chile, he never returned. What came next was a deeper and darker rabbit hole than anyone could have ever expected
Subscribe on Patreon for bonus content and to become a member of our Rogue Detecting Society.
Follow on Tik Tok and Instagram for a daily dose of horror.
We have a monthly newsletter now! Be sure to sign up for updates and more.</description></item><item><title>31: Haunted DC: White House Seances, Lincoln’s Ghost, and More | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 01:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710017/</guid><description>Podcast Description We're diving into the two most haunted houses in DC, The White House and The Halcyon House. Who was the ghost that tormented Taft's staff, which first ladies are most often seen haunting the White House grounds, and who was the eccentric owner of one of DC's most haunted houses, The Halcyon House?
Subscribe on Patreon for bonus content and to become a member of our Rogue Detecting Society.</description></item><item><title>30: Nasubi: The Darkest Reality Show You Haven’t Heard Of | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710018/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 01:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710018/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Nasubi was cast for the Japanese reality show Sweepstakes Life in 1998, he didn't know he'd spend the next 15 months in a studio apartment with no food or clothes. All while 17 million people across Japan were watching...
Subscribe on Patreon for bonus content and to become a member of our Rogue Detecting Society.
Follow on Tik Tok and Instagram for a daily dose of horror.</description></item><item><title>29: Morbid Medicine: History’s Deadliest Cures | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710019/</guid><description>Podcast Description From drilling holes in your skull to eating tapeworms for weight loss, we're looking at some of the most morbid medical advice that's been given throughout history
Subscribe on Patreon for bonus content and to become a member of our Rogue Detecting Society.
Follow on Tik Tok and Instagram for a daily dose of horror.
Heart Starts Pounding is written and produced by Kaelyn Moore. Shownotes: https://www.heartstartspounding.com/episodes/morbidmedicine Transcript</description></item><item><title>28: Folklore: Stories of Appalachian Horror | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 01:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Witches in the woods, screams in the middle of the night, the most haunted piece of land in all of Appalachia. Bring a backpack, because we're going deep into the Appalachian wilderness to hear the most terrifying folklore around. Subscribe on Patreon for bonus content and to become a member of our Rogue Detecting Society.
Follow on Tik Tok and Instagram for a daily dose of horror.
Heart Starts Pounding is written and produced by Kaelyn Moore.</description></item><item><title>27: Harvard’s Dirty Secret: Bejeweled Skulls and Grave Robbing | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 01:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710021/</guid><description>Podcast Description The manager of Harvard's Medical school was just indicted for selling human remains to oddities shops, but the history of Harvard's involvement in black market corpse dealings goes back over 250 years. Let's travel through the morgue, past the skeletons found in Harvard's walls, all the way back to the most high profile murder to ever happen at the school.
Subscribe on Patreon for bonus content and to become a member of our Rogue Detecting Society.</description></item><item><title>26: Murder On The Lake: Finland’s Greatest Unsolved Mystery | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 01:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710022/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happened the night of June 4th, 1960, when three teens were murdered at Lake Bodom in Finland? And why has no one ever been charged with the crime?
Subscribe on Patreon for bonus content and to become a member of our Rogue Detecting Society.
Follow on Tik Tok and Instagram for a daily dose of horror.
Heart Starts Pounding is written and produced by Kaelyn Moore. Music from Artlist</description></item><item><title>25: Disney Deaths Pt. 2: The Disney Dark Ages | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 01:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710023/</guid><description>Podcast Description The "Disney Dark Ages" was a period of time from the late 90's to the early 2000's that marked the bloodiest era in the Disney parks' history.
Subscribe on Patreon for bonus content and to become a member of our Rogue Detecting Society.
Follow on Tik Tok and Instagram for a daily dose of horror.
Heart Starts Pounding is written and produced by Kaelyn Moore. Music from Artlist</description></item><item><title>24: Listener Stories: Haunted Disney and More | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710024/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 01:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710024/</guid><description>Podcast Description A haunted ride at Disney, a mysterious man at a car wreck, and a haunted house being rented by college students. Welcome to the Heart Starts Pounding Campfire where we're sharing real-life terrifying stories.
Subscribe on Patreon for bonus content and to become a member of our Rogue Detecting Society.
Follow on Tik Tok and Instagram for a daily dose of horror.
Heart Starts Pounding is written and produced by Kaelyn Moore.</description></item><item><title>23: The Monster With 21 Faces | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710025/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 01:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710025/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1984, an anonymous group in Japan known as The Monster With 21 Faces tormented police, poisoned candy across the country and kidnapped a man. To this day, their identity and purpose remain one of Japan’s greatest unsolved mysteries.
Subscribe on Patreon for bonus content and to become a member of our Rogue Detecting Society.
Follow on Tik Tok and Instagram for a daily dose of horror.
Heart Starts Pounding is written and produced by Kaelyn Moore.</description></item><item><title>22: National Park Horror: True Stories of Terror | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710026/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 00:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dangers inside of National Parks, both strangers and freak accidents. We'll hear about people who got the sense something was watching them, feral people potentially living in the parks, as well as horror stories of people falling into geysers and off of the Grand Canyon
Subscribe on Patreon for bonus content and to become a member of our Rogue Detecting Society.
Follow on Tik Tok and Instagram for a daily dose of horror.</description></item><item><title>21: Bonus: The Dark Psychology of Lizzie Borden (feat. Women &amp; Crime) | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710027/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 01:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Let's take a modern, scientific lens to last week's Lizzie Borden case, and try to understand why someone would commit this crime. Dr. Amy Schlosberg and Dr. Meghan Sacks, professors of Criminology at Fairleigh Dickinson University, join me today to break down the case with what we know today about criminology. Together, they host the Women &amp;amp; Crime podcast.
You could have gotten this episode early by subscribing on Patreon.</description></item><item><title>20: Lizzie Borden: A Fresh Look at a Classic Case | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710028/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 01:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710028/</guid><description>Podcast Description What really happened the morning that Andrew and Abby Borden were murdered with an axe, and why is it still unsolved? Let's dive into the real story, full of the twists and turns that make that day one of the greatest unsolved mysteries in American history.
Subscribe on Patreon for more long form content, including exclusive episodes, and to become a member of our Rogue Detecting Society.
Follow on Tik Tok and Instagram for a daily dose of horror.</description></item><item><title>19: Supernatural Survival: Mysterious Near Death Encounters | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710029/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 00:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710029/</guid><description>Podcast Description From explorer Ernest Shackleton crossing the Antarctic, to famed aviator Charles Lindbergh, many famous stories of survival have included a supernatural being come to be known as The Third Man. Who is this presence that gives guidance and encouragement in extreme survival situations?
Subscribe on Patreon for more long form content, including exclusive episodes, and to become a member of our Rogue Detecting Society.
Follow on Tik Tok and Instagram for a daily dose of horror.</description></item><item><title>18: Disney Deaths: Tragedy in the Happiest Place on Earth | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710030/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 01:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710030/</guid><description>Podcast Description You may have heard that “no one dies at disney” but is that really true? Let’s look into the deaths of Mark Maples, a 15 year old who died on the Matterhorn, Dollie Regina Young who died on the same ride, and Deborah Gail Stone, who was crushed on the America Sings Ride. Subscribe on Patreon for more long form content, including exclusive episodes, and to become a member of our Rogue Detecting Society.</description></item><item><title>17: The Unsolved Mystery of The Lead Masks Case | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710031/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 01:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Did something supernatural occur in Brazil in 1966?
That’s when two men were found deceased on Vintem hill wearing black suits and lead masks, with a note by them that read “4:30 PM be at the determined place.
6:30 PM swallow capsules, after effect protect metals wait for mask signal”
We’re going straight down the rabbit hole in this episode, into the world of the occult, seances, secret societies, and aliens.</description></item><item><title>16: The Greenbrier Ghost: A Haunting Tale of Murder and the Supernatural | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710032/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 02:09:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can a ghost point to the person who murdered them? In 1897, Zona Heaster Shue&amp;rsquo;s mother thought Zona&amp;rsquo;s ghost visited her in the night with vital information, an event that infamously became the only time a ghost&amp;rsquo;s testimony was used in court. Known as the Greenbrier ghost, did Mrs. Shue really see her daughters ghost, or was there something else at play? Subscribe on Patreon for more long form content, including exclusive episodes, and to become a member of our Rogue Detecting Society.</description></item><item><title>15: Special Edition: Is There A Serial Killer In Austin Right Now? | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710033/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Four bodies have been recovered from Lady Bird Lake in Austin, Texas this year, causing many to wonder- is there a serial killer currently operating, and are these drownings at all connected to similar ones five years ago?
Subscribe on Patreon for more long form content, including exclusive episodes, and to become a member of our Rogue Detecting Society.
Follow on Tik Tok and Instagram for a daily dose of horror.</description></item><item><title>14: Ghosts of War: Haunting Encounters in Afghanistan and Iraq | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710034/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ghosts of Russian soldiers, red eyed creatures made from smoke. These are real life horror stories from soldiers in Afghanistan and Iraq in the early 2000's who saw the unexplainable. Have your own story to share, or a request of something you want covered? Reach out on heartstartspounding.com
Follow the podcast on instagram @heartstartspounding,
You can support the podcast on patreon, or with a one time donation to Buy Me A Coffee.</description></item><item><title>13: Listener Stories: Terrifying True Ghost Stories | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710035/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 02:03:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Spine tingling, bone chilling, and downright mysterious hauntings. Listeners share their own heart pounding tales about a headless cowboy, two separate ghost sightings in the military, and a girl who believes she may have gotten a sign from her deceased sister. Have your own story to share? Reach out on heartstartspounding.com
Follow the podcast on instagram @heartstartspounding,
You can support the podcast on patreon, or with a one time donation to Buy Me A Coffee.</description></item><item><title>12: Murder At Road Hill House: The Scandal That Shook Victorian England | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710036/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710036/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Mrs. Kent learned of the grisly murder of her three year old son, she had only one thing to say. “Someone in the house has done it”
What would follow would be the biggest whodunit of the 19th century. The Kent family would have their dirty laundry hung out to dry as London’s top detective investigated them all for the murder of Saville Kent
Heart Starts Pounding is written and produced by Kaelyn Moore.</description></item><item><title>11: Deathbed Confessions: Chilling Secrets Revealed | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710037/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Imagine if the final words you heard from someone were so bone-chilling that they forever altered your perception of them.
These deathbed confessions rocked families, changed the course of police investigations, and showed where the bodies were buried.
Heart Starts Pounding is written and produced by Kaelyn Moore. Follow the podcast on Instagram @heartstartspounding, subscribe on patreon, or support the podcast with a one time donation to Buy Me A Coffee.</description></item><item><title>10: Fatal Dose: Three Tales of Radiation Poisoning | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710038/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 02:48:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710038/</guid><description>Podcast Description A child with a deadly capsule. A rich playboy who lost his jaw and then his life. A fuel plant worker who absorbed more radiation than anyone in history. We're telling three stories about one of the deadliest forms of energy and the people that shouldn't have gone near it. Listener discretion is advised
Enjoying the podcast? Follow @heartstartspounding on instagram. You can support the podcast on Patreon, or make a one time donation by buying Kaelyn a coffee while she researches at Buy Me A Coffee.</description></item><item><title>9: Horrifying Tales from the Troubled Teen Industry | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710039/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710039/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the middle of the night, strangers ripped Zara from her bed and told her she was going to a troubled teen wilderness therapy program. Little did she know, the troubled teen industry would prevent her from going home for over three years.
The Troubled Teen Industry is a multi-billion dollar industry that holds kids prisoner and may do more harm than good in their attempt to rehabilitate teens.</description></item><item><title>8: Natalia Grace: ’Orphan’ Horror Movie Come To Life (feat. Jeff Topolski) | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710040/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Writer Jeff Topolski (Brooklyn Nine-Nine) joins us this week to answer the question: Was Natalia Grace Barnett a murderous woman parading as a child, or a victim of terrible adoptive parents?
In 2010, a 6-year-old girl named Natalia Grace was adopted by Michael and Kristine Barnett. The Barnetts, as well as national headlines, would go on to portray Natalia as a disturbed con artist pretending to be a child.</description></item><item><title>7: Hospital Hauntings feat. Hospice Nurse Julie | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710041/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710041/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is about the supernatural things that happen around the time of someone's death, either leading up to it or right after. We read stories from people who experienced the unexplainable right when their loved one died and hear from two healthcare workers about a supernatural phenomenon that is common when someone is dying. You can follow Hospice Nurse Julie on tiktok @hospicenursejulie
Follow the podcast on instagram @heartstartspounding</description></item><item><title>6: Scary Campground Tales | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710042/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pack a bag, today we're going to a spooky campground. In this episode, we hear two terrifying campground tales.
The first one is The Tale of The Solo Traveler- a tale of a girl who learns something may have been watching her while she camped.
And then we hear a tale from a listener of a time when their husband's intuition while camping may have saved them both.</description></item><item><title>5: The Mysterious Reappearance of Mary Edens | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710043/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710043/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Christmas Eve, 1924, a devastating fire broke out at a schoolhouse in Babbs Switch. 36 people died in total, and every person who was at the schoolhouse that night was accounted for. Except for one person- 3-year-old Mary Edens. Her aunt remembered passing her out of a window to someone, but no one knew what happened to her afterward.
Until 30 years later, when a woman shows up at the Edens home claiming to be Mary.</description></item><item><title>4: The Sodder Children Disappearance | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710044/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710044/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Christmas Eve, 1945, a fire broke out in the Sodder family home destroying the entire house and taking five of the nine children with it. Shortly after the fire, and due to some VERY strange evidence, the father of the family started to believe that maybe the children were actually....kidnapped
In this episode, we'll deep dive into the night of the fire as well as the bizarre events that took place afterward to try and figure out just what happened to those children that fateful night.</description></item><item><title>3: A Naval Base On A Haunted Swamp | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710045/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710045/</guid><description>Podcast Description What if I told you there were a bunch of people in the Navy in Groton, Connecticut who believe their military homes are haunted? And that some of those people believe it's a result of the ancient and mysterious land they live on?
In this episode, we hear from Jack, a behavioral health tech in the Navy who feels something strange coming from the swamp by his house, called Gungywamp.</description></item><item><title>2: Haunted House Tales From Listeners | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710046/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 03:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever wondered if the sound outside your door at night was really a ghost? In this Episode- Kaelyn hears from two listeners with chilling haunted house tales, and Leo gives a little bit of their take on it.
Have a heart pounding story you'd like to share on the podcast? email heartstartspounding@gmail.com. And follow the podcast on instagram @heartstartspounding. This episode will also be available on youtube!</description></item><item><title>1: The Devil in the Nursing Home: America’s First Female Serial Killer | Heart Starts Pounding: Horrors, Hauntings and Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4351710047/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4351710047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amy Archer-Gilligan was one of America's first female serial killers, killing up to 60 of her patients with her "special" lemonade...
Make sure you're following the podcast on instagram @heartstartspounding. Have a heart-pounding story you'd like to share on the pod? Email heartstartspounding@gmail.com
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>