<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Russell Howard’s Wonderbox on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/russell-howards-wonderbox/</link><description>Recent content in Russell Howard’s Wonderbox on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 02:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/russell-howards-wonderbox/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Guz Khan | Russell Howard’s Wonderbox</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4910850001/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4910850001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Man Like Mobeen creator, star and comedian of rare talent - it&amp;rsquo;s Guz Khan. Guz and Russell come together for an electric episode of Wonderbox. It&amp;rsquo;s got everything from putting your noo-nah in a VHS player, childhood quirks like wrapping trees in sellotape, and the episode ends with one of the funniest and most moving stories you&amp;rsquo;ll hear in a long time. After listening to this episode, y&amp;rsquo;all are gonna be like &amp;lsquo;How can I get more Guz Khan in my ears?</description></item><item><title>Iliza Shlesinger | Russell Howard’s Wonderbox</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4910850002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 10:49:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4910850002/</guid><description>Podcast Description US comedy megastar Iliza Sheslinger is in the studio! Russell and Iliza talk about the what happens when an audience member drops their guts during a show, a single fingerless glove and the beautiful stench of a closed bar. Iliza is in the UK right now with her ‘Hard Feelings’ tour. She’s playing the Hammersmith Apollo on the 6th and 8th December, and you can buy those tickets right now from their website here.</description></item><item><title>Rachel Parris | Russell Howard’s Wonderbox</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4910850003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4910850003/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, host of Late Night Mash Rachel Parris sits down with Russell to select her most precious items for the Wonderbox. Russell finds out why the world is a better place because of tiny lederhosen, Tunnock&amp;rsquo;s Teacakes and Rachel recalls her once-in-a-lifetime opportunity to normalise British sex toys. Rachel will be taking a show back out across the UK in 2024 so keep your eyes peeled for that.</description></item><item><title>Jack Whitehall | Russell Howard’s Wonderbox</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4910850004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4910850004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jack Whitehall takes a few minutes away from his brand new baby to chat to Russell about his most precious possessions. Jack tells the most insane story about Jamie Laing seeing his undercarriage, then explains what it&amp;rsquo;s like to party with Man City the day after they&amp;rsquo;ve won the Champion&amp;rsquo;s League. Sensational stuff. Jack&amp;rsquo;s on tour at the moment, and you can get your lovely fingers all over those tickets by going to https://www.</description></item><item><title>John Oliver | Russell Howard’s Wonderbox</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4910850005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4910850005/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s only John flippin&amp;rsquo; Oliver! One of Britain&amp;rsquo;s most-loved exports after cheddar cheese and trains, John Oliver is the host of US late-night show Last Week Tonight as well as being a sensational stand-up comic in his own right. John reveals what it&amp;rsquo;s like to do a gig to one person, why Michael Bolton is a bona fide comedy hero and reveals when, how and why he likes dressing as a cat.</description></item><item><title>Ed Gamble’s Wonderbox | Russell Howard’s Wonderbox</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4910850006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4910850006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ed Gamble is in the house! Ed chooses his most precious items to wang into the Wonderbox, which includes some food-based choices (as you might expect from one who foods as passionately as Ed). Come for the food, then stay for Ed waxing lyrical about his love of Mr Blobby. Ed is touring next year, going hither and thither to some of the most delicious performance venues the UK can offer.</description></item><item><title>Jordan Gray’s Wonderbox | Russell Howard’s Wonderbox</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4910850007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4910850007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stand-up comedian and star of The Voice Jordan Gray joins Russell this week, selecting precious memories to put into the Wonderbox. Jordan explains why a marijuana seed has deep resonance, talks Russell through the agony of a kidney stone and Russell tells a heart-warming story about his brother showing his arse to a whole hot-air balloon full of people. Jordan is on tour at the moment, and you can (and should) get tickets by visiting https://www.</description></item><item><title>Jen Brister’s Wonderbox | Russell Howard’s Wonderbox</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4910850008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4910850008/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s Jen Brister! Russell and Jen work through the perils of sad nipple syndrome, get nostalgic about the delightful stench of Bangkok and pore over the best food to eat if you&amp;rsquo;re planning an evening of sexual gymnastics. Jen is still touring her never-ending tour around the UK, and if you haven&amp;rsquo;t seen the show yet you should. Tickets and dates can be found at jenbrister.co.uk Russell is currently on tour in the US and UK: visit russell-howard.</description></item><item><title>Jimmy Carr’s Wonderbox | Russell Howard’s Wonderbox</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4910850009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4910850009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jimmy Carr joins Russell today to put his most treasured possessions into the Wonderbox. Jimmy explains the importance of a tennis scoreboard, why there’s nothing better than a perfectly made suit and Russell explores the idea of Jimmy having a hype-man at his gigs. Jimmy currently has tour dates in the US and the UK, and you can buy tickets at jimmycarr.com. Russell is currently on tour in the US and UK: visit russell-howard.</description></item><item><title>Munya Chawawa’s Wonderbox | Russell Howard’s Wonderbox</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4910850011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4910850011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s guest is internet comedy star, Munya Chawawa, who chats to Russell about why he loves Streets of Rage, the importance of a slice of pizza and reveals his jaw-dropping hidden ability. Russell is currently on tour in the US and UK: visit russell-howard.co.uk to find out more and book tickets. Munya is also on tour now and you can get tickets for his show at livenation.co.uk Producer: Dan Atkinson Line Producer: Daisy Knight Exec Producer: James Taylor Composer: Fat Lady Music</description></item><item><title>Sam Ryder’s Wonderbox | Russell Howard’s Wonderbox</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4910850010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4910850010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sitting down with Russell today is Britain’s singing sensation Sam Ryder! Sam and Russell discuss Sam’s love of Formula One racing, Sam tries to get a whole branch of Zizzis into the Wonderbox, and he explains why a sheriff’s badge brings back the best memories of all. Russell is currently on tour in the US and UK: visit russell-howard.co.uk to find out more and book tickets. Producer: Dan Atkinson Line Producer: Daisy Knight Exec Producer: James Taylor Composer: Fat Lady Music</description></item><item><title>Trailer | Russell Howard’s Wonderbox</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4910850012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 13:19:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4910850012/</guid><description>Podcast Description A Wonderbox is a place where you keep little reminders of what makes life worth living. Each week Russell will chat to a special guest about what they’d keep in their Wonderbox, recounting the most memorable and funniest moments of their lives.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>