<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Shawn Ryan Show on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/shawn-ryan-show/</link><description>Recent content in Shawn Ryan Show on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/shawn-ryan-show/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>#89 Tim Parlatore - United States v. Donald J. Trump | Part 1 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370136/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tim Parlatore is a former Naval Officer and founder of Parlatore Law Group. He has represented Navy SEAL Eddie Gallagher and President Donald Trump, among other high profile cases. This episode is an inside look at the multiple cases and indictments against the former President. Part one covers the events of January 6th and supposed election interference. Parlatore was on the Trump legal team during the early searches and seizures of Mar-a-lago.</description></item><item><title>#88 Chris Miller - The Future of Warfare | Part 3 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370135/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris Miller is the former Secretary of Defense with a 27 year career in the United States Army. Throughout his career, he oversaw multiple special operations organizations, culminating with his command of the 2nd Battalion, 5th SFG(A). Concluding this three part series, Chris and Shawn discuss the latest developments in the Ukraine / Russia conflict and the implications it has on foreign policy and the United States&amp;rsquo; standing on the world stage.</description></item><item><title>#88 Chris Miller - The Hunt for Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi | Part 2 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370133/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris Miller is the former Secretary of Defense with a 27 year career in the United States Army. Throughout his career, he oversaw multiple special operations organizations, culminating with his command of the 2nd Battalion, 5th SFG(A). In Part Two, Miller recounts the horrific abduction and murder of human rights activist Kayla Mueller by ISIS forces. This atrocity would later result in &amp;ldquo;Operation Kayla Mueller,&amp;rdquo; the mission that targeted and killed ISIS leader Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi.</description></item><item><title>#88 Chris Miller - Former Secretary of Defense on Toppling the Taliban | Part 1 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370134/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris Miller is the former Secretary of Defense with a 27 year career in the United States Army. Throughout his career, he oversaw multiple special operations organizations, culminating with his command of the 2nd Battalion, 5th SFG(A). In Part One of three part series, we cover Miller&amp;rsquo;s background spanning his impressive career. Miller breaks down one of his most important tasks–toppling the Taliban government and supporting the local resistance initiatives.</description></item><item><title>#87 Michael Shellenberger - Elon Musk, Twitter Files and Media Collapse | Part 2 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370132/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael Shellenberger is an award winning Journalist and best selling Author. He is best known for his book &amp;ldquo;San Fransicko,&amp;rdquo; a cautionary tale of how progressives ruin cities. In part two, Michael and Shawn discuss the dissolution of partisan lines in the U.S. political system. Michael outlines the damage disinformation has done to the country&amp;rsquo;s institutions and the erosion of public trust. Shawn and Michael cover the infamous &amp;ldquo;Twitter files&amp;rdquo; and the roles of faith and free will in a modern democracy.</description></item><item><title>#87 Michael Shellenberger - The Demise of California | Part 1 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370131/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael Shellenberger is an award winning Journalist and best selling Author. He is best known for his book &amp;ldquo;San Fransicko,&amp;rdquo; a cautionary tale of how progressives ruin cities. Michael and Shawn jump straight into the current state of California and its failed policies. Michael breaks down how legislation intended to decriminalize homelessness and drug abuse actually enabled the problems rather than solving them. Michael also uncovers the double standards and corruption of the California state government during the pandemic.</description></item><item><title>#86 Laird Hamilton - Near-Death Surf Experiences and Surviving JAWS | Part 2 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370130/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Laird Hamilton is a legendary American big wave surfer, known for riding some of the most dangerous waves ever to break. Laird is also a fitness icon and creator of Laird Superfood. Part two is the story of Hamilton&amp;rsquo;s incredible surfing career. He recounts his struggle to find his footing among an industry set on sponsors and rules and how he ultimately became a trend setter rather than a follower.</description></item><item><title>#86 Laird Hamilton - The Greatest Big Wave Surfer of All Time | Part 1 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370129/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Laird Hamilton is a legendary American big wave surfer, known for riding some of the most dangerous waves ever to break. Laird is also a fitness icon and creator of Laird Superfood. Part one of this two part series is a chronicling of Hamilton&amp;rsquo;s childhood in Hawaii where he met his first love–the ocean. Hamilton recounts what it was like being the odd man out in a culture he would grow to be apart of.</description></item><item><title>#85 Bryce Case Jr. AKA YTCracker - Anonymous Hacker | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370128/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bryce Case Jr., aka YTCracker, is a hacker and musician. Bryce has been called &amp;ldquo;The Original Digital Gangster&amp;rdquo; for his early adoption and manipulation of all things online. Ryan Montgomery, a fan favorite on SRS, calls Bryce his mentor. In this special Holiday release, we cover Bryce&amp;rsquo;s life story starting with his early exploits when the internet was just coming into itself. We discuss his aptitude for clever digital marketing and finding money-making opportunities in every corner of America Online.</description></item><item><title>#84 Nick Bryant - Did Jeffrey Epstein Clone Himself? | Part 2 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370126/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick Bryant is the author of &amp;ldquo;The Franklin Scandal&amp;rdquo; and Activist for Epstein Justice. Bryant is also credited with publishing Jeffrey Epstein&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Little Black Book.&amp;rdquo; Part two is a complete breakdown of Jeffrey Epstein&amp;rsquo;s vile empire and the systems that enabled his rise to a position of power in &amp;ldquo;high society.&amp;rdquo; Bryant details the origins of the &amp;ldquo;Little Black Book&amp;rdquo; and uncovers the names within it. This is the account the mainstream media won&amp;rsquo;t cover.</description></item><item><title>#84 Nick Bryant - Epstein's Secret Black Book | Part 1 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370127/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick Bryant is the author of &amp;ldquo;The Franklin Scandal&amp;rdquo; and Activist for Epstein Justice. Bryant is also credited with publishing Jeffrey Epstein&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Little Black Book.&amp;rdquo; Part one is a deep dive into Bryant&amp;rsquo;s investigation into The Franklin Scandal. This was one of the first child trafficking rings that was highly publicized and alerted the general population to such heinous activities. Bryant explains how the criminal underworld gave way to monsters like Jeffrey Epstein.</description></item><item><title>#83 Victor Marx on How Big Tech &amp; Artificial Intelligence Influence Child Predators | Part 3 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370124/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Victor Marx is a high risk humanitarian, former U.S. Marine, author, filmmaker, and lays claim to the World&amp;rsquo;s fastest gun disarm. In part three, Marx tells us more about his is incredible mission work across the globe. Shawn and Victor discuss faith and the role it plays in a world on the brink. Marx&amp;rsquo;s history and humanitarian work gives him a unique perspective on the challenges facing the United States today.</description></item><item><title>#83 The Methods Victor Marx Used to Overcome His Terrifying Childhood | Part 2 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370123/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Victor Marx is a high risk humanitarian, former U.S. Marine, author, filmmaker, and lays claim to the World&amp;rsquo;s fastest gun disarm. In part two, we get into Marx&amp;rsquo;s humanitarian work with All Things Possible. His missions have taken him all over the world to Iraq, Syria, North Africa and Southeast Asia – mostly in non-permissive and high threat environments. His work focuses on orphans and widows that are victims of war, abuse and crimes against humanity.</description></item><item><title>#83 What Led Victor Marx to Become the World's Fastest Gun Disarmer | Part 1 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370122/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Victor Marx is a high risk humanitarian, former U.S. Marine, author, filmmaker, and lays claim to the World&amp;rsquo;s fastest gun disarm. This is a three part series that covers his life story. In part one, Marx recounts a childhood marked by severe abuse. By the time he graduated from high school, his lifestyle was filled with drugs, fights and theft. Yet, the discipline of the military and his steadfast faith would reset the course of his life.</description></item><item><title>#82 Luis Chaparro - Navy SEAL and Journalist Discuss Combatting Cartels with a Psyop | Part 2 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370121/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Luis Chaparro is a Journalist specializing in narcos, cartels, and immigration. This is his third appearance on SRS where he brings the most up-to-date information on the growing crises south of the border. In part two, Luis outlines a staged and deliberate plan to defeat the cartels–a psyop. Shawn and Luis discuss this strategy in detail, harkening back to Ryan&amp;rsquo;s experiences in the CIA. Chaparro also uncovers a new drug crisis that is overtaking the already disastrous fentanyl epidemic.</description></item><item><title>#82 Luis Chaparro - Journalist with a $60,000 Bounty Breaks into Ovidio Guzmán's House | Part 1 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Luis Chaparro is a Journalist specializing in narcos, cartels, and immigration. This is his third appearance on SRS where he brings the most up-to-date information on the growing crises south of the border. In part one, Chaparro updates us on the aftershock of a small scale war that thrust Mexico into a state of chaos when authorities captured Ovidio Guzman, son of drug lord El Chapo. In retaliation, hundreds of armed cartel members laid siege to multiple cities, occupying multiple areas, establishing blockades, and engaging in shootouts with authorities.</description></item><item><title>#81 Sarah Adams - Barack Obama Visited Beyonce and Jay-Z During the Benghazi Attacks | Part 2 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370002/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is a follow up to our investigation into the Benghazi attacks with Mark Geist. Sarah Adams is a former CIA Targeter with a wealth of experience leading intelligence initiatives during the Global War on Terror. In part two, Adams exposes what was happening Stateside during the Benghazi attacks while U.S. Service Members were fighting for their lives. Shawn and Sarah discuss what measures could have been taken that night to provide support to the CIA Annex team on the ground.</description></item><item><title>#81 Sarah Adams - CIA Targeter Exposes How Hamza bin Laden is Alive | Part 1 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370003/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is a follow up to our investigation into the Benghazi attacks with Mark Geist. Sarah Adams is a former CIA Targeter with a wealth of experience leading intelligence initiatives during the Global War on Terror. In part one of this two part series, Adams gives us an overview of what it&amp;rsquo;s like to run targeting and intelligence operations for the U.S. She also outlines the power structures of different terrorist groups around the world and how they continue to operate today.</description></item><item><title>#80 John Lovell - Navy SEAL and Army Ranger Discuss What's Destroying America | Part 4 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370004/</guid><description>Podcast Description John Lovell is a former Army Ranger turned creator, homesteader and best-selling author. Lovell is the founder of the Warrior Poet Society, a values-based community geared towards training, preparedness, and spirituality. The final part of this series is all about Lovell&amp;rsquo;s wisdom gained from fatherhood. Lovell and Shawn discuss the realties of parenting in a modern world, the value of having values, and how to carve a righteous path in dark times.</description></item><item><title>#80 John Lovell - How a 75th Ranger Built One of the Biggest Tactical Training Networks | Part 3 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370005/</guid><description>Podcast Description John Lovell is a former Army Ranger turned creator, homesteader and best-selling author. Lovell is the founder of the Warrior Poet Society, a values-based community geared towards training, preparedness, and spirituality. Part three of this four part series is all about the closing of Lovell&amp;rsquo;s career as an Army Ranger and his transition into civilian life. Lovell outlines his early days in business and the beginning of his marriage and how to build a strong foundation in a relationship.</description></item><item><title>#80 John Lovell - 75th Rangers’ Deadly Gunfight and Near-Death Ambush | Part 2 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370006/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370006/</guid><description>Podcast Description John Lovell is a former Army Ranger turned creator, homesteader and best-selling author. Lovell is the founder of the Warrior Poet Society, a values-based community geared towards training, preparedness, and spirituality. Part two of this four part series is all about Lovell&amp;rsquo;s career as an Army Ranger in 2nd Ranger Battalion. Lovell served on multiple combat deployments during the Global War On Terror. Lovell vividly recounts the early days of the war, shortly after the 9/11 attacks and a deadly ambush that would be one of the closest calls of his career.</description></item><item><title>#80 John Lovell - Army Spec Ops Dude Recounts the Hardest Portion of Ranger School | Part 1 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370007/</guid><description>Podcast Description John Lovell is a former Army Ranger turned creator, homesteader and best-selling author. Lovell is the founder of the Warrior Poet Society, a values-based community geared towards training, preparedness, and spirituality. Part one of this four part series is all about Lovell&amp;rsquo;s childhood and early life. Lovell is a successful and well known creator, but his origin story has largely remained a mystery until now. We also explore his entry into the 2nd Ranger Battalion and his radical transformation into a believer.</description></item><item><title>#79 Sean Webb - How Average Humans Can Look into the Future Through Consciousness | Part 2 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sean Webb is the author of &amp;ldquo;Mind Hacking Happiness&amp;rdquo; and through his work with the Monroe Institute, Webb has become one of the foremost authorities on remote viewing &amp;amp; consciousness. In part two of this episode, Webb details his time at the Monroe Institute and the programs they offer. Webb provides a full look at the growing body of research taking place at the institute. We also discuss the prospect of having host Shawn Ryan attempt remote viewing at the institute.</description></item><item><title>#79 Sean Webb - CIA Funds Remote Viewing Program | Part 1 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370009/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sean Webb is the author of &amp;ldquo;Mind Hacking Happiness&amp;rdquo; and through his work with the Monroe Institute, Webb has become one of the foremost authorities on remote viewing &amp;amp; consciousness. In this episode, Webb walks us through the history and process of remote viewing. We learn about the CIA&amp;rsquo;s interest in this phenomenon and the back story of one of the most famous remote viewers–Joe McMoneagle. Webb outlines his experience with his first remote viewing.</description></item><item><title>#78 Tim Burchett - Non-human Biologics, UFO Encounters, and Mexico's Alien Bodies | Part 2 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370010/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on SRS, we welcome Tennessee Congressman Tim Burchett to the show. Burchett is one of the few congressmen that is actively pursuing the uncovering of UAP / UFO phenomena, regardless of how much flak it may bring. Burchett put together the first hearing for Congress to seriously evaluate UAP / UFO reports in 50 years. Part two of this episode covers the hearing and breaks down multiple testimonies and encounters.</description></item><item><title>#78 Tim Burchett - Inside UFO/UAP Government Programs | Part 1 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370011/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370011/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on SRS, we welcome Tennessee Congressman Tim Burchett to the show. Burchett is one of the few congressmen that is actively pursuing the uncovering of UAP / UFO phenomena, regardless of how much flak it may bring. Burchett put together the first hearing for Congress to seriously evaluate UAP / UFO reports in 50 years. Part one of this episode explores the origins of the newfound push to explain and investigate these occurrences.</description></item><item><title>#77 Tom Satterly - Delta Force CSM (RET) "All Secure" | Part 3 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370012/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on SRS, we welcome Command SGT Major (R), Tom Satterly to the show. Satterly is a former Delta Force Operator with over twenty years of combat experience. He has participated in operations all across the globe. We&amp;rsquo;re breaking his incredible story into a three part series. Part 3 In this episode, Satterly tells us about the aftermath of Somalia and his career during the Global War on Terror.</description></item><item><title>#77 Tom Satterly - The Battle of Mogadishu "Black Hawk Down" 30th Anniversary | Part 2 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370013/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370013/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on SRS, we welcome Command SGT Major (R), Tom Satterly to the show. Satterly is a former Delta Force Operator with over twenty years of combat experience. He has participated in operations all across the globe. We&amp;rsquo;re breaking his incredible story into a three part series. Part 2 Thirty years ago, on October 3, 1993, U.S. forces planned to seize two of Mohammed Farah Aidid&amp;rsquo;s top lieutenants during a meeting deep in Mogadishu.</description></item><item><title>#77 Tom Satterly - Delta Force Operator | Part 1 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370014/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on SRS, we welcome Command SGT Major (R), Tom Satterly to the show. Satterly is a former Delta Force Operator with over twenty years of combat experience. He has participated in operations all across the globe. We&amp;rsquo;re breaking his incredible story into a three part series. Part 1 We learn about Satterly&amp;rsquo;s upbringing and how he joined the military. Satterly walks us through vivid memories of his recruitment experience.</description></item><item><title>#76 Erik Prince - China vs Taiwan, JFK Assassination, Ad ID Tracking &amp; Social Credit | Part 2 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Part 2 of this episode covers growing conflict on the world stage and secrecy here at home. Shawn &amp;amp; Erik discuss growing tensions between China &amp;amp; Taiwan. How likely is a CCP invasion of the island? What role will the US play in that conflict? Does Taiwan even stand a chance? Have all of these questions answered by Prince, one of the foremost authorities on foreign policy and global security operations.</description></item><item><title>#76 Erik Prince - 6 Enemies of Big Government, Combating Cartels and the Ukraine War | Part 1 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370016/</guid><description>Podcast Description So much has been happening in the world over the last few months–the war in Ukraine, the value drops in the US dollar, a recession and political turmoil. SRS wanted to get insights from someone who can see beyond the veil. That&amp;rsquo;s why we&amp;rsquo;re welcoming back Erik Prince, Founder of Blackwater and American Entrepreneur, Former Navy Seal. Prince explains the shifts in foreign policy and the looming dangers of a no-end war in Ukraine and the growing threat of the CCP.</description></item><item><title>#75 Nick Freitas - Woke Schooling, Identity Crisis, National Divorce and Parenting Advice | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370017/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on SRS we&amp;rsquo;re diving into all things society &amp;amp; culture with Former Green Beret and Virginia State Delegate Nick Freitas. Shawn and Nick discuss the shifting political climate across the country as &amp;ldquo;woke culture&amp;rdquo; creates unintended targets. Freitas lays out the changing value structure of the modern family and how missing fathers are affecting the growth and success of America&amp;rsquo;s youth. Shawn and Nick also touch on the epidemic of mass shootings that have become the new normal for the United States.</description></item><item><title>#74 Mark "Oz" Geist - 13 Hours Survivor Reflects on the Deadly Benghazi Attacks | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today marks the 11th anniversary of the unprecedented attack on a U.S. Consulate and CIA Annex in Benghazi, Libya that claimed the lives of four Americans– J. Christopher Stevens (U.S. Ambassador), Sean Smith (U.S. Foreign Service Information Officer), Glen &amp;ldquo;Bub&amp;rdquo; Doherty (U.S. Navy SEAL / CIA), and Tyrone S. &amp;ldquo;Rone&amp;rdquo; Woods (U.S Navy Seal / CIA). The aftermath of this attack resulted in ten investigations spanning two years that shook the core of American foreign policy and protocol within the State Department.</description></item><item><title>#73 Bedros Keuilian - Discipline, Motivation &amp; Wisdom that Made a Multi-Million Dollar Empire | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370019/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on SRS, Bedros Keuilian tells us all about business. Bedros is a serial entrepreneur and investor in over a dozen industry leading brands and businesses. He’s the founder of Fit Body Boot Camp, three times listed in Inc Magazine as well as Entrepreneur Magazine’s 100 fastest growing franchise brands in the world. Bedros is the author of the Wall Street Journal Best Selling book &amp;ldquo;Man Up – How To Cut The BS and Dominate In Business and In Life.</description></item><item><title>#72 Tony Cowden - CIA Operator Survives Deadly IED Blast that Sent Him to the Morgue | Part 2 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former Green Beret and CIA contractor Tony Cowden is back in part two of this two-part series. Part one dove deep into his upbringing and early career. Now, we&amp;rsquo;re getting into Ground Branch. Ground Branch is known for being the CIA&amp;rsquo;s covert counterpart to Special Operations. Ground Branch has been active in many theaters of war–Afghanistan, Iraq, Libya and Syria, though their actions are rarely covered in the media.</description></item><item><title>#72 Tony Cowden - CIA Operator's Real Life John Wick-Style Gunfight in a Warzone | Part 1 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370021/</guid><description>Podcast Description SRS is honored to bring Tony Cowden&amp;rsquo;s story to the show. Tony is a former Green Beret and CIA contractor with an impeccable career having served in multiple combat deployments. In part one of this two-part series, we cover Tony&amp;rsquo;s upbringing and how his father helped fuel his capacity for resourcefulness and an unmatched work ethic. Tony recounts his experience in the &amp;ldquo;Red Cell&amp;rdquo; Program where he was tracking and surveilling assets on American soil and how he barely made it out of a sticky situation alive on the day of the September 11th, 2001 attacks.</description></item><item><title>#71 Vivek Ramaswamy - EXPOSES Deep State, BlackRock, Big Pharma, Central Bank Digital Currency | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shawn Ryan Show is an open platform. Our goal is to bring truth and share untold stories that the media wouldn&amp;rsquo;t otherwise cover. Part of that goal is to give the American people an opportunity to hear from their leaders and prospective leaders in a long format. We&amp;rsquo;re done with the 15 second sound bytes. That&amp;rsquo;s why 2024 Presidential Candidate Vivek Ramaswamy is on this week. Vivek is the son of immigrants turned American success story and entrepreneur.</description></item><item><title>#70 Brandon Fugal - Owner of the Mysterious Skinwalker Ranch Reveals UAP/UFO Encounters | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brandon Fugal is the owner and proprietor of Skinwalker Ranch. Initially, Brandon&amp;rsquo;s intention was to dispel the rumors and mystique surrounding Skinwalker Ranch. However, a meeting with an Area 51 specialist on the property led to a series of unexplained and peculiar phenomena. This encounter profoundly impacted him and fueled his determination to pursue the truths concealed within the ranch. During this episode, we learn about Brandon&amp;rsquo;s upbringing, explore how he built a prosperous career in commercial real estate, and delve into his acquisition of the infamous Skinwalker Ranch from Aerospace billionaire, Robert Bigelow.</description></item><item><title>#69 Don Graves - World War II Marine Survives Iwo Jima with Flamethrower, Grenades, and Pistol | SRS #69 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370024/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;Yesterday, December 7, 1941 a date which will live in infamy the United States of America was suddenly and deliberately attacked by naval and air forces of the Empire of Japan&amp;hellip;.with confidence in our armed forces with the unbounding determination of our people we will gain the inevitable triumph so help us God.&amp;rdquo; - Franklin D. Roosevelt These were the words that would change the course of history forever.</description></item><item><title>#68 Tyler Vargas-Andrews - Marine's Horrific Account of the Disastrous Afghanistan EVAC | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370025/</guid><description>Podcast Description The United States withdrew the last of its troops from Afghanistan in August of 2021, signaling the end of a nearly 20 year conflict that cost 8 Trillion dollars and the lives of 900,000 people, including over 7,000 U.S. Service Members. The U.S. exit from Afghanistan resulted in the Taliban reestablishing armed control of the country and created a refugee crisis as over 1.5 Million Afghans fled. The withdrawal has been widely considered a disaster and a gross display of incompetent leadership from the President down, echoing similar failures seen at Saigon nearly half a century earlier.</description></item><item><title>#67 Eli Crane - Inside Congress: Political Corruption, Uniparty, Border Crisis &amp; Culture Chaos | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370026/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370026/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on SRS–Eli Crane is back to tell us about his experience so far in Congress. Crane was recently elected in his home state of Arizona and has already seen how rampant corruption is in the U.S. Government. This episode is an uncensored look at how Congress operates behind closed doors. If you&amp;rsquo;ve been wondering &amp;ldquo;What is going on in D.C.?&amp;rdquo; This episode is episode will demystify how it all goes down.</description></item><item><title>#66 Eric Hecker - Antarctica Firefighter for Raytheon Exposes Scary Earthquake Weapon | Part 3 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370027/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last but certainly not least, Eric Hecker closes out our Whistleblower Marathon this week on SRS. Eric is former Navy and contractor for Raytheon, a major U.S. defense contractor. Eric&amp;rsquo;s position as a firefighter and plumber for the South Pole facility gave him unrestricted access to the compound. During his stay, Eric observed highly advanced directed energy weapons and other technologies beyond what we previously thought possible. Eric has also testified to congress under oath and hopes to bring his experience to the public for the good of humanity.</description></item><item><title>#66 DC Long - Army Combat Vet's Mysterious UFO Encounter in Underground Military Base | Part 2 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370028/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Whistleblower Marathon continues with former Army Combat Veteran DC Long. DC and his Father, then government contractors, were tasked with standing up a shoot house at Range 19. Before they knew it, they were ushered underground at gunpoint only to encounter a &amp;ldquo;Monolithic Slab.&amp;rdquo; Long shares his story in great detail, recounting the sights and sounds of this UAP / UFO. Long describes a series of events that unfolded post his encounter that would ultimately separate he and his Father for life.</description></item><item><title>Ron DeSantis - Deadly Force on Drug Cartels, Deconstructing the Weaponized DOJ/FBI, Combating China | Special Edition | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370029/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370029/</guid><description>Podcast Description 15 Minute Discussion with Ron DeSantis The upcoming 2024 Presidential election will be the most decisive vote in modern American history. The American people want to know who these Presidential candidates are and what they stand for. The Shawn Ryan Show is extending an open invitation to any Presidential candidate looking for an open and free platform to express in detail who they are and their visions and plans for America.</description></item><item><title>#66 Michael Herrera - US Marine Encounters UFO Black Ops Human Trafficking Operation | Part 1 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370030/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370030/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;re giving whistleblowers a platform and a voice this week on SRS. Former Marine Michael Herrera tells all in part one of this three part series. Herrera and his team were tasked with responding to a major earthquake and tsunami in Indonesia providing overwatch and logistical support. Little did they know–they would come face to face with a UAP / UFO and be ambushed by an unmarked shadow unit of operators.</description></item><item><title>#65 Dr. Steven Greer - Black Budget, Stargate, Raytheon, Lockheed Skunk Works, UAP/UFO Secrets | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370031/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Steven Greer is back in episode #65 to discuss a wealth of ground-breaking science and discovery. First, he outlines new realizations around zero-point energy and how this supposed newfound technology is as old as time. Greer also covers how this technology has been hidden away from the public for decades by the military industrial complex and corporate interests. Why? Because it could change the balance of power globally.</description></item><item><title>#64 Jim Caviezel - #1 Most Evil and Unforgivable Sin Will Haunt You for Eternity | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370032/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jim Caviezel is an Actor and Producer, known for his work in box office hit films like “The Count of Monte Cristo” and “Deja Vu.” His most influential film, “The Passion of the Christ,” cast him in the lead role as Jesus of Nazareth. Caviezel’s career was seemingly put on hold in Hollywood due to his unapologetic and authentic depiction of Christ and his being outspoken on a subject his new film “The Sound of Freedom” gives audiences a harsh look at: Child trafficking.</description></item><item><title>#63 Shawn Ryan - The Guardian Angel Who Guided Me to Become a Warrior for God | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370033/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370033/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;re taking a step back from our regularly scheduled programming to talk about something we find vital to life: Faith. If you&amp;rsquo;re a fan of the show, you know that Shawn is always seeking truth and questioning the status quo. This type of work is rewarding, but challenging. Between the fog of his past on the battlefield and exposing evil here at home, the light was hard for Shawn to see sometimes.</description></item><item><title>#62 Sean Webb - How Artificial Intelligence will Manipulate the World | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370034/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370034/</guid><description>Podcast Description With the recent departure of one of Google&amp;rsquo;s top engineers Geoffrey Hinton, Artificial Intelligence is the topic on everyone&amp;rsquo;s mind. What is it? Where is it going? How will these advancements affect our everyday lives? Sean Webb is here to cover it all. As the author of &amp;ldquo;Mind Hacking Happiness&amp;rdquo; and through his work with the Monroe Institute, Webb has become one of the foremost authorities on AI &amp;amp; Consciousness.</description></item><item><title>#61 Tyler Grey - Intense Combat / Injury That Ended His Career | Part 2 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370035/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former Delta Force Operator Tyler Grey is back in part two of this two part series. This episode covers the invasion of Fallujah and the horrors of conventional warfare. Grey even discusses his role in supporting the Marines and former SRS guest Cody Alford. Grey takes us back to the night he and his unit went on the hunt for an HVT and how he sustained a life changing injury in Sadr City, Iraq.</description></item><item><title>#61 Tyler Grey - Delta Force Operator's Darkest Hour in War / Overcoming Self Doubt | Part 1 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370036/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode #61 is a masterclass in self discovery and self worth. Tyler Grey is a former Army Ranger Sniper &amp;amp; Delta Force Operator turned Actor and Director. You might know him from the hit CBS series &amp;ldquo;SEAL Team.&amp;rdquo; In part one of this two-part series, Grey recounts his childhood, where he found his love for the military and film. He unpacks his socially awkward history and how his childhood would impact his future endeavors.</description></item><item><title>#60 David Tice - The Power Grid Blackout / America's WORST Enemy Could Attack Any Moment | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370037/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370037/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Tice is a geopolitical strategist and producer / director of the eye opening documentary ‘Grid Down, Power Up.’ David came on to tell us about the unbelievable vulnerabilities of the U.S. power grid. Electricity–it&amp;rsquo;s cheap, fast, and readily available across most of the world. We rely on electricity to survive, yet most of us take it for granted. While we&amp;rsquo;ve gotten comfortable, a disaster has been brewing with every light switch flipped.</description></item><item><title>#59 Dr. Michael Bagnell - Neurologist Unlocks Human Brain and Reveals Tips to Improve Mental Health | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370038/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Michael Bagnell is a Functional Neurologist and Chiropractic Physician who specializes in brain-based healthcare. In this episode, Dr. Bagnell breaks down the intricacies of the &amp;ldquo;default mode network&amp;rdquo; and how the body can be rehabilitated by retraining the brain. Dr. Bagnell explains how memory and trauma inform one another. Shawn &amp;amp; Dr. Bagnell discuss the root of conditions like ADHD, PTSD, and anxiety. He also touches on a surprising new field of research that involves a Dolphin&amp;rsquo;s unique ability to &amp;ldquo;echolocate&amp;rdquo; different issues in humans.</description></item><item><title>#58 Buck Sexton - Twitter Files, Dr. Fauci, Epstein, ChatGPT, Education System, and Title 42 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Buck Sexton is a former CIA analyst and currently an American radio host, author, and conservative co-host of The Clay Travis and Buck Sexton Show. This episode covers a lot ground. We get into Buck&amp;rsquo;s former life as a CIA analyst and how that informs his public works. We discuss the expiration of Title 42 and what that means for the border crisis and asylum seekers. Buck explains how the modern mass media has developed over time and where disinformation collides with the free press.</description></item><item><title>#57 Nick Kefalides - MARSOC Raider / Hitting Rock Bottom and Unlocking Your Full Potential | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370040/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former Marine Raider and Guest #004 returns to the Shawn Ryan Show to discuss a new kind of battle–the one inside. This is a special episode where Shawn &amp;amp; Nick share a personal story with the audience. They cover a mushroom journey they took part in together and how it changed them individually and reframed their friendship. We get to catch up with Nick and his new business continuing to serve veterans and Shawn shares what&amp;rsquo;s next for SRS.</description></item><item><title>#56 Ryan Montgomery - #1 Ethical Hacker Who Hunts Child Predators Catches One Live On Podcast | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370041/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370041/</guid><description>Podcast Description 1 in 5 children in the United States will be sexually exploited online. Every 9 minutes, Child Protective Services finds evidence of child sexual abuse. 93% of victims know the perpetrator. These are horrifying and sobering statistics that drove the Shawn Ryan Show to expose this topic–this is where Ryan Montgomery comes in. Ryan is the #1 &amp;ldquo;ethical hacker&amp;rdquo; in the world and it&amp;rsquo;s a title he&amp;rsquo;s earned by infiltrating websites that host child exploitation and exposing the predators that run rampant there.</description></item><item><title>#55 Prime Hall - MARSOC Raider Survives The Unthinkable / Horrific Combat Experience | Part 2 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370042/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370042/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of this episode, we get heavy into Prime&amp;rsquo;s deployments. We learn about the unique bond US Operators have with their Afghan partners and how those bonds bend and break when the sum of all fears becomes a reality–an insider attack. This attack claimed multiple lives and would influence procedure and policy for the remainder of the war. Prime shares in detail his experience transitioning from intense combat rotations into civilian life and the grueling realities of PTSD.</description></item><item><title>#55 Prime Hall - MARSOC Raider Shares His Darkest Memories / Traumatized to Transformation | Part 1 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370043/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode #55 is an unfiltered look at trauma and the long road to recovery. Prime Hall is a former Marine Raider with 12 years of service and is now a coach and consultant to some of the country&amp;rsquo;s top companies and Olympic athletes. In part one of this two part series, Prime shares the burdens of his childhood that would haunt him well into his Military career. Hall puts the audience in the shoes of a young recruit with a troubled past and a growing rap sheet while also navigating the path to Special Operations.</description></item><item><title>#54 Yeonmi Park - Escaping the Horrors of North Korea &amp; the Kim Dynasty | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370044/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yeonmi Park is an activist and author who fled to the United States after being a victim of sex trafficking. Park recounts her oppressive childhood in North Korea, starved and without electricity. She remembers how the lights of neighboring countries gave her hope for a better life. She spares no detail when explaining what a society under a ruthless dictator, mass killings, and delusional propaganda looks like. Yeonmi takes us through her harrowing journey being smuggled out of North Korea only to meet a new terrifying reality - the Chinese sex trade.</description></item><item><title>#53 David McCormick - Fmr CEO Bridgewater Associates - A Battle Plan for America | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370045/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370045/</guid><description>Podcast Description David McCormick is the former CEO of Bridgewater Associates, a premiere asset management firm and author of Superpower in Peril: A Battle Plan to Renew America. McCormick also served as the Deputy National Security Advisor for International Economic Policy and was a personal representative and negotiator to the G8 under the Bush Administration. McCormick and Shawn discuss the issues at the core of the United States rapid decline in industry, education, innovation, and foreign policy.</description></item><item><title>#52 Andrew Bustamante - CIA Spy / U.S. vs China - The New Cold War | Part 2 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrew Bustamante is back in Part Two of this two-part series to discuss the &amp;ldquo;sleeping dragon,&amp;rdquo; China. Bustamante tells us how a 5,000 year old country like China moves slowly and quietly with little known initiatives like the &amp;ldquo;Belt Way,&amp;rdquo; and how he believes a move to take Taiwan is an imminent threat. We dive deep into the recent Spy Balloon phenomenon over US airspace and growing Chinese influence and capability across the globe through social media and shadow propaganda.</description></item><item><title>#52 Andrew Bustamante - CIA Spy / World War 3, Money Laundering and The Next Superpower | SRS #52 Part 1 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370047/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrew Bustamante is a former Air Force Combat Veteran and CIA Intelligence Officer specializing in covert action and clandestine operations, a.k.a, your everyday Spy. In Part 1 of this two-part series, Bustamante takes us through his recruitment into the Agency and how he met his wife in the field—a true &amp;ldquo;Mr. &amp;amp; Mrs. Smith&amp;rdquo; moment. Bustamante &amp;amp; Shawn get honest with unfiltered opinions on COVID and American foreign policy with China, Russia, and Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>#51 Chris VanSant - Delta Force Operator / Killing Off the "Deck of Cards" &amp; Capturing Saddam Hussein | Part 2 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370048/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Delta Force Operator Chris VanSant is back in Part 2 of this two-part series. This episode dives deep into his role in the invasion of Iraq and the capture of Saddam Hussein. VanSant vividly recalls an engagement with over 300 enemy combatants after a goat herder revealed his team&amp;rsquo;s location. We get a first hand account of the operational tempo it takes to hunt down each player of the infamous &amp;ldquo;Deck of Cards,&amp;rdquo; and what happens when a handful of Delta Operators are outnumbered in the Horn of Africa with only the Navy Destroyer U.</description></item><item><title>#51 Chris VanSant - Delta Force Operator / The Hunt for Saddam Hussein | Part 1 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370049/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris VanSant is a former Delta Force Operator &amp;amp; Army Ranger with 11 combat deployments and 20 years experience. VanSant took part in over 600 combat missions, including the capture of Saddam Hussein. In this episode, we&amp;rsquo;ll cover his upbringing and his time in the Army Rangers &amp;amp; 82nd Airborne and how a DUI as a young recruit changed the course of his career. We get an in-depth look at the grueling OTC / Delta Force training pipeline and find out what its like to go straight from training into an ongoing deployment in Afghanistan, where Chris would meet his team for the first time.</description></item><item><title>#50 Chris / Kristin Beck - Navy SEAL Transitions To Woman Then Back To Man | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370050/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode #50 is one of the most important interviews you&amp;rsquo;ll ever hear. Chris Beck is a retired Navy Seal with 20 years service &amp;amp; 15 deployments under his belt. Even with his Bronze Star with Valor, Chris wasn&amp;rsquo;t only known for his skills behind the trigger, but for his brilliance in technology and engineering. Chris pioneered the mission planning systems for all of SOCOM, revolutionized the future of warfare with the &amp;ldquo;Iron Man&amp;rdquo; Project, and contracted for the Pentagon with a $600 million dollar research and development budget.</description></item><item><title>DECLASSIFIED #47 Dallas Alexander - The World's Farthest Sniper Kill / JTF2 Operator | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370051/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370051/</guid><description>Podcast Description PREVIOUSLY CLASSIFIED - After a cease &amp;amp; desist order, attorneys, and standing our ground for free speech, we are now able to bring you the full production of Episode #47 with Dallas Alexander. You&amp;rsquo;ll get to hear about operations that were declassified in just the last few weeks. Do not miss this one. The Joint Task Force 2 (JTF2) is a highly secretive and elite special operations unit of the Canadian Armed Forces, specializing in counter-terrorism operations, both at home and abroad.</description></item><item><title>#49 Tim Parlatore - The Fight for Free Speech Against a Foreign Government | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370052/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370052/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this special episode, we give you an update on the continued fight for free speech from the attorney working the case—Tim Parlatore. Parlatore explains how the events with our Dallas Alexander episode are unfolding and how the Canadian government is trying, but failing to censor a free American podcast. We&amp;rsquo;ll also explore how woke culture and foreign influence are weakening our institutions, from the military all the way to congress.</description></item><item><title>#48 Dr. Steven Greer - Mystery Behind UFO / UAPs, Alien Phenomenon, and The Secret Government | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370053/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Steven M. Greer, MD, a retired emergency room Physician turned to a life of research of UFO/UAP Phenomenons, is the Founder of The Disclosure Project, The Center for the Study of Extraterrestrial Intelligence (CSETI), The Orion Project, Sirius Technology Advanced Research, LLC and is considered one of the world’s foremost authorities on all things UFO / UAP. In this episode, Dr. Greer lays out exactly how nearly a century of information and discovery of Extraterrestrial life and technology have been hidden from the public and shrouded under a veil of dark money and secrecy.</description></item><item><title>#47 The Canadian Gov does NOT want you to see this. / Special Ops Sniper Refuses COVID Vaccine, Gets Fired | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370054/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370054/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happens when the fabric of a Tier 1 unit is challenged by a global pandemic, mandates &amp;amp; lockdowns? What does standing up for what you believe in look like? Find out in this episode. This episode has been censored at the request of the Canadian Special Operations Forces Command &amp;amp; the National Defence Headquarters by way of a Cease and Desist order.
Shawn Ryan Show Sponsors: https://hvmn.com - USE CODE &amp;ldquo;SHAWN&amp;rdquo; https://mudwtr.</description></item><item><title>#46 Ioan Grillo - Cartel Wars &amp; The Fentanyl Crisis | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370055/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cartels, drugs, money, corruption—author and award winning journalist Ioan Grillo has seen it all in his twenty-plus years&amp;rsquo; of covering Latin America. In this episode, we cover the unprecedented violence that broke out in the city of Culiacán after Mexican authorities recaptured Sinaloa cartel leader Ovidio Guzmán, son of &amp;ldquo;El Chapo.&amp;rdquo; Grillo breaks down the inner workings of Mexico&amp;rsquo;s most notorious cartels, their recruitment strategies and growing turf wars.</description></item><item><title>#45 Bob "Ninja" Poras - Inside CIA's Global Response Staff | Part 2 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370056/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ninja is back in the final installment of this two-part series. This episode spans his entire career working for the CIA, covering the differences between CIA staffers and GRS contractors, and how the enemy evolved their IED based warfare into a new kind of weapon: EFP. Bob gives us a behind the scenes look at the Khost bombing and the triple agent behind it. Learn about an event in Tripoli that saved 150+ lives and lasted a grueling 24 hours - the greatest evacuation you&amp;rsquo;ve never heard about.</description></item><item><title>#45 Bob "Ninja" Poras - CIA / Delta Force Operator | Part 1 | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370057/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bob &amp;ldquo;Ninja&amp;rdquo; Poras has us wondering where he got his call sign. He spent most of his career in the shadows. Some days &amp;ldquo;AWOL&amp;rdquo;, but most of them fighting as the tip of the spear with 1st Special Forces Operational Detachment–Delta (1st SFOD-D), and eventually - working for the CIA as a GRS operator. He covers lessons in leadership and the perfect grenade toss while operating in Panama during &amp;lsquo;Just Cause,&amp;rsquo; his first brush with the same Delta squadron that would later be his own.</description></item><item><title>#44 Solbere - A Scientific Solution to the Carbon Footprint | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370058/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Solbere is an organic liquid treatment that promotes longer, more efficient growth in plants and trees, combatting CO2 emissions, wildfires and drought. On this episode, creators George Baker &amp;amp; Bill Wheatley explain how Solbere can help create a sustainable, healthy atmosphere for the future.
Please leave us a review on Apple &amp;amp; Spotify Podcasts. Vigilance Elite/Shawn Ryan Links: Website | Patreon | TikTok | Instagram Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>#43 Eddie Penney - SEAL Team 6/DEVGRU Operator | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370059/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370059/</guid><description>Podcast Description During his 20 year military career Eddie Penney served as a United States Marine and Navy SEAL with SEAL Team 6. In Eddie&amp;rsquo;s new book Unafraid, a chapter titled &amp;lsquo;Kill Addict&amp;rsquo; he describes desire to take the fight to the enemy and subsequent addiction to the fog of war. Among the many challenges he experienced while serving at DEVGRU the greatest loss occurred while in Gold Squadron: Extortion 17.</description></item><item><title>#42 Rob Luna - Wealth Strategist on the Recession and Inflation | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370060/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rob Luna is confirmation that the American Dream is alive. He went from growing up hungry and battling the tough streets of Los Angeles, to becoming an Ivy League Alumnus and earning MBA degrees in two countries. His 25 years of experience includes consulting with companies such as Amazon, Google, and Facebook, managing money for some of the world’s wealthiest individuals, and building a multimillion-dollar business that was sold to a publicly-traded company.</description></item><item><title>#41 Kyle Morgan - Delta Force Operator | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370061/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kyle Morgan brings us on his journey from his childhood to the world&amp;rsquo;s most elite and secretive special operations unit known as &amp;ldquo;Delta Force&amp;rdquo;. On 20 November 2015, Islamist militants took 170 hostages killing 20 of them in a mass shooting at the Radisson Blu hotel in Bamako, the capital city of Mali. Kyle was one of the sole responders and was awarded the Distinguished Service Cross for his actions that day.</description></item><item><title>#40 Mark Turner - The Russia Ukraine War | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370062/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mark Turner from the Overwatch Foundation returns to give us an intel brief on the Russia Ukraine War and a brief look at the destruction from hurricane Ian. Shawn Ryan Show Sponsors: https://blackbuffalo.com/discount/SRS https://www.bubsnaturals.com (USE CODE SHAWN) https://bullionmax.com/srs https://www.patreon.com/VigilanceElite Vigilance Elite/Shawn Ryan Links: Website - https://www.shawnryanshow.com Patreon - https://www.patreon.com/VigilanceElite TikTok - https://www.tiktok.com/@shawnryanshow Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/shawnryan762 Mark Turner Links: Website - https://www.overwatchfoundationusa.org/ Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>#39 Struggle Jennings | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370063/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shawn Ryan Show Sponsored by Ridge Wallet. Check them out here: https://ridge.com/shawn USE CODE &amp;lsquo;&amp;lsquo;SHAWN&amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; Also sponsored by Bubs Naturals &amp;ldquo;Take the best S*%# of you life&amp;rdquo; https://www.bubsnaturals.com (USE CODE SHAWN) and by MUD/WTR https://www.mudwtr.com/shawn (USE CODE SHAWN) The story of William Harness AKA Struggle Jennings childhood drug dealing gang member to country music rap superstar. Please leave us a review on Apple/Spotify Podcasts: Apple - https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/shawn-ryan-show/id1492492083 Spotify - https://open.</description></item><item><title>#38 Roger Reaves - Pablo Escobar and The Medellín Cartel's #1 Cocaine Smuggler | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370064/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370064/</guid><description>Podcast Description The adventures of Roger Reaves has you sitting on edge as he tells you his vivid memories of Smuggling Drugs into the U.S. He spanned the globe in his numerous aircraft smuggling tons of marijuana and cocaine for Pablo Escobar and the Medellín Cartel and at one point was shot down by Colombian Military Jets. At the height of his career he had a net worth of $60 Million Dollars.</description></item><item><title>#37 Machine Gun Preacher - Sam Childers | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370065/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370065/</guid><description>Podcast Description From 1%er Biker Gang Member to rescuing children from being massacred in Africa. This man has made a positive mark felt by many in this world. Sam Childers AKA The Machine Gun Preacher joins us for an interview on The Shawn Ryan Show. ⬇️ 🚨 Please Donate to Rescue Children 🚨 ⬇️ https://www.machinegunpreacher.org/ Shawn Ryan Show Sponsors: https://blackbuffalo.com/discount/SRS https://www.mudwtr.com/shawn (USE CODE SHAWN) https://www.bubsnaturals.com (USE CODE SHAWN) https://trueclassictees.com/ (USE CODE SRS) Vigilance Elite/Shawn Ryan Links: Website - https://www.</description></item><item><title>#36 Lt. Col. Scott Mann - Operation Pineapple Express | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370066/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Retired Green Beret Lt. Col. Scott Mann and a small team of former special ops personnel orchestrated what is now known as Operation Pineapple Express. Extracting our Afghan Allies from Taliban regime during a time of extreme violence due to the United States withdrawing all forces from Afghanistan. OUR SPONSORS: https://bullionmax.com/srs https://prepwithshawn.com Vigilance Elite/Shawn Ryan Links: Website - https://www.shawnryanshow.com Patreon - https://www.patreon.com/VigilanceElite TikTok - https://www.tiktok.com/@shawnryanshow Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/shawnryan762 🚨↘️ Sign up for the VE Newsletter ↙️🚨 https://www.</description></item><item><title>#35 Dr. John Delony - America's Mental Health Crisis | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370067/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. John Delony is a bestselling author, mental health expert and host of The Dr. John Delony Show. He has two PhDs and over two decades of experience in counseling, crisis response and higher education. Dr. Delony and Shawn dissect what they believe is causing the mental health crisis here in America. OUR SPONSORS: https://bullionmax.com/srs https://www.mudwtr.com/shawn (USE CODE SHAWN) https://www.goodranchers.com/shawn https://www.manscaped.com/ (USE CODE SHAWN) Vigilance Elite/Shawn Ryan Links: Website - https://www.</description></item><item><title>#34 Cody Alford - Marine Raider/MARSOC Sniper Who Became a Nomad | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370068/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cody Alford is a former Marine Raider &amp;amp; Scout Sniper who was on the frontlines of the Battle of Fallujah. After an impressive 15 year career, he chose to walk a totally new path - van life. Shawn Ryan Show Sponsors: 🚨USE CODE SHAWN🚨 https://www.mudwtr.com/shawn (USE CODE SHAWN) https://goodranchers.com/shawn https://www.bubsnaturals.com #VIGILANCEELITE #SHAWNRYANSHOW Vigilance Elite/Shawn Ryan Links: Website - https://www.shawnryanshow.com Patreon - https://www.patreon.com/VigilanceElite TikTok - https://www.tiktok.com/@shawnryanshow Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/shawnryan762 Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>#33 Lily Tang Williams - I Fear the Country I Love is Becoming the Country I Left | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370069/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lily Tang Williams, who escaped communism under Mao&amp;rsquo;s cultural revolution in China came to America with just $100. 🚨Shawn Ryan Show Sponsors 🚨 https://www.mybookie.com (use code SRS) https://goodranchers.com/shawn https://magbreakthrough.com/shawn Vigilance Elite/Shawn Ryan Links: Website - https://www.shawnryanshow.com Patreon - https://www.patreon.com/VigilanceElite TikTok - https://www.tiktok.com/@shawnryanshow Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/shawnryan762 Lily Tang Williams Links: Website - https://www.lilytangwilliams.com/ Twitter - https://twitter.com/Lily4Liberty Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/lily4liberty Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#32 Jason Redman - Navy SEAL Talks Near Death Experience and Seeking Redemption | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370070/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Retired Navy SEAL Lieutenant Jason Redman sits down with Shawn Ryan to discuss his electrifying experiences! He’s lived through it all at the highest level in his Navy SEAL career: From failures as a young leader that resulted in him almost being kicked out of the SEAL teams, to redemption and leading teams in intense combat operations in Iraq, to being shot eight times, including a round to the face, and nearly dying during an enemy ambush, Jason has lived the OVERCOME Mindset he now teaches others.</description></item><item><title>#31 Marc Polymeropoulos - CIA Senior Intelligence Officer | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370071/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marc Polymeropoulos gives great insight of what a career from start to finish at CIA would be like. We discuss how he was recruited, his training at the farm, and his deployments killing bad guys. Marc then discusses his trauma from Havana syndrome. Believed to be caused by microwave weapons. Vigilance Elite/Shawn Ryan Links: Website - https://www.shawnryanshow.com Patreon - https://www.patreon.com/VigilanceElite TikTok - https://www.tiktok.com/@shawnryanshow Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/shawnryan762 Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>#30 Trevor Millar - Psychedelic Provider | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370072/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 19:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shawn recently shared his profound psychedelic experience and how deeply it affected him. So, it was natural that Shawn should sit down with the man who helped him down the rabbit hole - Psychedelic Provider Trevor Millar. This episode dives into Trevor’s story, the opioid epidemic, big pharma, and the alternative treatments to immense inner turmoil that&amp;rsquo;s become so very common in our American life. Please leave us a review!</description></item><item><title>#29 Erik Prince - Inside The Rise and Fall of Blackwater | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370073/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Erik Prince is an American businessman, former U.S. Navy SEAL officer, and the founder of the private military company Blackwater USA. On March 31st, 2004 the lives of 4 BlackWater employees were forever changed along with the smear campaign of the company that followed. Erik Prince reveals the truth inside of his company BlackWater and the current events shaping our world. You&amp;rsquo;ve never heard anything like this! Vigilance Elite/Shawn Ryan Links: Website - https://www.</description></item><item><title>#28 Nick "Machine" Lavery - Active Duty Army Special Forces Amputee | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370074/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick Lavery is an active duty member of The United States Army Special Forces. Nick is not just a warrior on the battlefield, but a warrior for the common American. In this episode we learn of the greatest battles you have never heard of. From small arms gun fights to being ambushed by trusted allies, Nick is an example to any person who has been pushed to the ultimate limit and emerged victorious.</description></item><item><title>#27 Rob O'Neill - The Man Who Killed Bin Laden | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370075/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former SEAL Team Six/Devgru Operator Robert J. O&amp;rsquo;Neill gives a full recap of his career in the SEAL Teams. From start to finish we cover it all. This is a side of Rob you haven&amp;rsquo;t seen before. We get philosophical on topics such as &amp;ldquo;Should we have ever gone to Iraq?&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Would we have been friends with our enemies under different circumstances?&amp;rdquo; And of course&amp;hellip; We get the first hand account of the night Rob killed Bin Laden.</description></item><item><title>#26 Alex Epstein - The Global Energy War | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370076/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370076/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are currently in the middle of a global energy war. Alex Epstein joins us to discuss what the implications of the current Green Initiative will be, how China ties in and stands to benefit in a world where the US now depends on them for energy, and how the benefits of fossil fuels have been completely ignored for years. Alex Epstein is a Fossil Fuel Philosopher, author, and industrial and energy policy commentator.</description></item><item><title>#25 Eli Crane - Navy SEAL Sniper | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370077/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eli Crane joins Shawn Ryan to talk about his time as a Navy SEAL Sniper, starting his multimillion-dollar company &amp;ldquo;Bottle Breacher&amp;rdquo; in his garage, and running for Arizona State Congress. From childhood lessons to failing sniper school, Eli is an example for every American who has ever had to persevere through life&amp;rsquo;s great struggles. View the rest of the interview on Rumble https://rumble.com/v13itqk-shawn-ryan-show-eli-crane-navy-seal-sniper.html Vigilance Elite/Shawn Ryan Links: Website - https://www.</description></item><item><title>#24 Shawn Ryan's Psychedelic Experience | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370078/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370078/</guid><description>Podcast Description I am revealing every little detail of my psychedelic experience, all the intuitions, what I saw, what I felt, what I believe it all meant, and how the journey healed me in the end. I am opening up about my experience for two reasons. The first being because I believe this will help a great number of people, and the second is to raise money for VETS the organization that put me through the treatment so they can continue healing our US Special Operations Veterans.</description></item><item><title>#23 Luis Chaparro - Inside the World's Deadliest Cartel | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370079/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 19:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370079/</guid><description>Podcast Description After being embedded with the Sinaloa Mexican Drug Cartel, Luis Chaparro an investigative reporter brings us some very eye opening insight on what they have been up to. He informs us of a new drug which the cartels are introducing into the United States and Canada that is more addictive and more deadly than fentanyl. He also was able to witness one of the Sinaloa Cartel&amp;rsquo;s Tactical Training camps, describing exactly what they go through.</description></item><item><title>#22 David Rodriguez - Overcome Bullying / Getting Sober | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370080/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former Heavyweight Boxing Champion David Nino Rodriguez joins me on The Shawn Ryan Show to discuss how him being bullied as a child lead him to become a heavyweight boxing champion with an undefeated record of 36-0 with 34 by knockout at his prime. His first round knockout ratio surpassed every heavyweight in history to date and Nino was ranked number 12 in the world by WBA. After being stabbed in the face with a knife he tried to comeback but suffered 2 losses finishing his boxing career with a final record of 39-2.</description></item><item><title>#21 Mark Turner - Inside Ukraine (Recon Marine) | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370081/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former Recon Marine Mark Turner who went to Ukraine on 18 hours notice at the beginning of the Russian invasion of Ukraine joins us on the show. He gives us an inside perspective on what&amp;rsquo;s happening in country as the war continues on. After speaking with high level Ukrainian Politicians they&amp;rsquo;ve asked him to train both Ukrainian military and civilians to go fight the Russians on the front lines of the war.</description></item><item><title>#20 Justin Hughes - Navy SEAL/Modern-Day Da Vinci | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370082/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Justin Hughes the type of American that we can all look up to. His pride for America runs deep, all the way back to grade school. After moving back the the United States from living abroad he could not understand why his fellow Americans would bully him. In the long run it forged him into what he needed inside to become a Navy SEAL. Justin&amp;rsquo;s talks in great detail about his experience fighting the Islamic State on the front lines of Mosul, Iraq.</description></item><item><title>#19 Peter Schweizer - China's Influence Over the United States | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370083/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370083/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week I welcome investigative journalist Peter Schweizer to the Shawn Ryan Show. Peter a six-time New York Times best selling investigator reveals what he has discovered after his latest investigation covering China&amp;rsquo;s Influence over the United States in his new book &amp;ldquo;Red Handed&amp;rdquo;. We cover their influence over multiple area which include Big Tech, Wall Street, US Education, and US Politicians. His book has become the #1 NYT best seller 3 weeks in a row.</description></item><item><title>#18 Robby Starbuck - Congressional Candidate | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370084/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Robby Starbuck, a Congressional Candidate representing Tennessee. We cover several topics in a short amount of time to include Critical Race Theory, what he believes to be the biggest internal and external threats to the United States, why he left California, issues with big tech, Term Limits, George Soros, and who he would like to see on the 2024 Presidential ticket. Robby Starbuck Links: https://starbuck2022.com https://www.instagram.com/robbystarbuck/ https://twitter.com/robbystarbuck Vigilance Elite/Shawn Ryan Links: Website - https://www.</description></item><item><title>#17 Mikal Vega - Navy SEAL / EOD / Call of Duty Director | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370085/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mikal Vega, a man of many accomplishments who has earned a substantial number of different titles. A Navy SEAL, EOD (explosive ordnance disposal), Actor, Director, Producer, Screenwriter, CEO of Vital Warrior, and Master of Self Awareness, just to cover a few. We cover his childhood, his military time both as an EOD Tech, and an Operator at SEAL Team 8, his transition into civilian life, and finally his current career both in Hollywood and Directing for Activision&amp;rsquo;s Call of Duty franchise.</description></item><item><title>#16 Chief Hallgrimson - Guilty of Assault After Rescuing Baby from Murderer | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370086/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chief of Police Greenwood, MO Greg Hallgrimson contacted me over 2 years via email to let me know how much a video I made on social anxiety helped him. After reading his email and googling his name I found out what a hero this man is and invited him on the show. The email is linked below for everyone to read. Chief Hallgrimson saved a 6 month old baby girl from being murdered by her father and then was charged with assault.</description></item><item><title>#15 DJ Shipley SEAL - Team 6 / DEVGRU Operator | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370087/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370087/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode of The Shawn Ryan Show I sit down with former SEAL TEAM 6/DEVGRU Operator DJ Shipley. Shipley has 17 years serving the United States at the highest level as a Navy SEAL Tier 1 operator. Shipley gives us the most descriptive interview I have ever done. His service goes unmatched. Shipley is also the founder of GBRS Group, a tactical training group that only employs Tier 1 Operators and the founder of Tribe Sk8z a company that makes one of a kind skate boards that are works of art, and employs only Gold Star family members (The title, which is reserved for families of military members who have died in the line of duty).</description></item><item><title>#14 Alan Cooper - Marine Recon/Green Beret/CIA Contractor | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370088/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370088/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of the Shawn Ryan Show, Alan Cooper a longtime friend of Shawn&amp;rsquo;s who is a Recon Marine, a Green Beret, and a CIA Contractor sits down with Shawn and discusses some of the highlights of his career. Alan Cooper was a Reconnaissance Marine in Operation Desert Storm who was on the mission that helped end the entire war. Please leave us a review on Apple Podcasts: https://podcasts.</description></item><item><title>#13 Bernie Kerik - September 11th 2001 NYC Police Commissioner | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370089/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370089/</guid><description>Podcast Description 9/11/2021 marks the 20th anniversary of the deadliest attack ever on American soil. September 11th 2001 not only changed our country here in the United States, but the events reshaped the entire world moving forward from that point on in many ways. 2977 people died in the attacks that day, 2606 alone died in The World Trade Center when the towers collapsed, many more firefighters, police officers, and first responders died in what became the greatest rescue mission of all time saving those left to survive in the attacks amongst the rubble.</description></item><item><title>#12 Luis Chaparro - Inside Cartel Drug Operations | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370090/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370090/</guid><description>Podcast Description I sit down with investigative Mexican Cartel / Narcos reporter Luis Chaparro to discuss the DEA&amp;rsquo;s arms deals with the Sinaloa Cartel, and how China is sending chemists to work with drug cartels to produce the most potent fentanyl on the planet to be smuggled into the United States. Please leave us a review on Apple Podcasts: https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/shawn-ryan-show/id1492492083 Follow Luis Chaparro: Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/luiskuryaki Twitter - https://twitter.com/LuisKuryaki Vigilance Elite/Shawn Ryan Links: Website - https://www.</description></item><item><title>The Afghanistan Crisis | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370091/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former Green Beret Tu Lam of Ronin Tactics talks about the Afghanistan Crisis. Vigilance Elite/Shawn Ryan Links: Website - https://www.shawnryanshow.com Patreon - https://www.patreon.com/VigilanceElite TikTok - https://www.tiktok.com/@shawnryanshow Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/shawnryan762 Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#11 The Blackwater Massacre | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370092/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370092/</guid><description>Podcast Description After thirteen years of political persecution and wrongful imprisonment, four U.S. veterans reunited last Christmas with their loyal families after receiving Presidential pardons that some described as “an affront to justice.” In their first joint interview on The Shawn Ryan Show, the four men of Blackwater USA’s Raven 23 Tactical Support Team sit down with Shawn Ryan to discuss the most controversial gunfight of the entire Iraq War, the complete system failure of the U.</description></item><item><title>#10 Marcus Capone - SEAL Team Six Explosive Breacher/Pyschedelic Therapy Advocate | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370093/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marcus Capone founder of VETS Solutions, along with his Wife Amber Capone join us on The Shawn Ryan Show to discuss Marcus&amp;rsquo;s military career as a Tier 1 explosive breacher at DEVGRU also known as SEAL Team 6. Marcus goes in depth as to the effects of explosive breaching and the effects of being combat Warfighter has on the brain. We then cover how single treatment of psychedelic assisted therapy would not only save his life, but bring his family back together after almost losing them due to mild traumatic brain damage.</description></item><item><title>#9 Tu Lam Former - Green Beret / Call of Duty / CEO Rōnin Tactics | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370094/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Retired Green Beret Tu Lam, CEO of Rōnin Tactics and Call of Duty Character has a conversation with Shawn Ryan to discuss how he was smuggled out of Vietnam, his 23 year military career (20 of which as a Green Beret), his dark transition into civilian life living with PTSD from a long career of war fighting in Special Operations, Lam opened up about his childhood, how he overcame Asian racism at a young age, his military career and success in the entertainment industry.</description></item><item><title>US-Mexico Border Crisis 2021 with Ed Calderon | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370095/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370095/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of The Shawn Ryan Show I sit down with Ed Calderon and discuss what is going on down at the US-Mexico border crisis. Ed has first hand knowledge of who is coming across and what might be coming to a city near you. You can find/follow Ed on the links below: Website - https://www.edsmanifesto.com​ Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/edsmanifesto Vigilance Elite/Shawn Ryan Links: Website - https://www.shawnryanshow.com Patreon - https://www.</description></item><item><title>SRS Special Edition with Katie Jean | Andrea Gallagher Wife of accused Navy SEAL War Criminal | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370096/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shawn Ryan&amp;rsquo;s wife, Katie Jean sits down with Eddie Gallagher&amp;rsquo;s wife Andrea, to discuss what life was like for Andrea and her family while her husband was behind bars. Andrea opens up about the NCIS raid that took place at her home on her children, and how she took her husband&amp;rsquo;s freedom into her own hands by creating the #FREEEDDIE campaign which got the attention of President Donald Trump, and the national news.</description></item><item><title>The Debrief with Shawn and Katie | #007 Ed Calderon | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370097/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shawn Ryan and Katie Jean debrief and discuss behind the scenes and the entire experience of Shawn Ryan Show #007 with Ed Calderon. Vigilance Elite/Shawn Ryan Links: Website - https://www.shawnryanshow.com Patreon - https://www.patreon.com/VigilanceElite TikTok - https://www.tiktok.com/@shawnryanshow Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/shawnryan762 Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#8 Eddie Gallagher - Retired Navy SEAL Tried for Murder | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chief Special Operator Eddie Gallagher is without a doubt the most controversial Navy SEALs of modern day history, and quite possibly in the entire history of Naval Special Warfare. Shawn Ryan Show #008 Chief Gallagher explains in depth how teammates under his command at SEAL Team 7 not only accused him of being a war criminal, but relentlessly tried to send him away to life in prison for the alleged murder of an ISIS fighter in Mosul, Iraq.</description></item><item><title>Ed Calderon's first hand accounts with the Portland and Atlanta Riots | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370099/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ed Calderon and Shawn Ryan talk about Ed&amp;rsquo;s first hand account and experience with the Portland and Atlanta riots. Vigilance Elite/Shawn Ryan Links: Website - https://www.shawnryanshow.com Patreon - https://www.patreon.com/VigilanceElite TikTok - https://www.tiktok.com/@shawnryanshow Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/shawnryan762 Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#7 Ed Calderon Drug Cartel / Narcos Expert | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370100/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370100/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The Shawn Ryan Show, former Navy SEAL/CIA Contractor Shawn Ryan sits down with Ed Calderon. For over a decade Ed Calderon worked in the fields of counter narcotics, organized crime investigation, in the northern-border region of Mexico. He is a considered to be one of the top experts in the operations and tactics of the Mexican Drug Cartels and Narcos. Shawn and Ed discuss everything from Ed&amp;rsquo;s personal experiences fighting cartels face to face and the mental and physical scars it has left behind forever, to why China is involving themselves in cartel operations deep in Mexico to how the Cartels are effectively utilizing American street gangs to push more drugs into the United States.</description></item><item><title>The Debrief with Shawn and Katie | #006 Travis Howze | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370101/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shawn Ryan and his wife Katie Jean debrief and discuss behind the scenes and the entire experience of Shawn Ryan Show #006 with Travis Howze. Vigilance Elite/Shawn Ryan Links: Website - https://www.shawnryanshow.com Patreon - https://www.patreon.com/VigilanceElite TikTok - https://www.tiktok.com/@shawnryanshow Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/shawnryan762 Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Storytime - Inside the Navy SEALs Team Room | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370102/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370102/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s been a long time since we&amp;rsquo;ve done a good story time&amp;hellip; Here it is! Shawn Ryan tells Travis Howze a story about a joke played on him in the Team Room when he was a young SEAL on his first platoon. Vigilance Elite/Shawn Ryan Links: Website - https://www.shawnryanshow.com Patreon - https://www.patreon.com/VigilanceElite TikTok - https://www.tiktok.com/@shawnryanshow Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/shawnryan762 Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Navy SEAL Debates Liberal on Defunding The Police | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370103/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shawn Ryan of Vigilance Elite and The Shawn Ryan Show former Navy SEAL and CIA Contractor debates a liberal / democrat on defunding the police. The &amp;ldquo;Defund the Police&amp;rdquo; movement has been, and continues to be one of the most controversial topics of 2020. The great thing about the United States of America is everyone has the right to freedom of speech and the right to their own opinion.</description></item><item><title>#6 Travis Howze - Heroic Firefighter | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370104/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370104/</guid><description>Podcast Description In episode #006 of &amp;ldquo;The Shawn Ryan Show&amp;rdquo; Shawn sits down with Travis Howze. Travis is a Marine Corps Veteran, former Firefighter, former Police Officer, Stand Up Comedian, author of &amp;ldquo;Create Your Own Light&amp;rdquo; and PTSD Awareness Advocate. He was a Charleston firefighter who responded to the deadly Sofa Superstore Charleston 9 fire in 2007 which took the lives of 9 brave men (This was the deadliest firefighter disaster in the US since the September 11 attacks).</description></item><item><title>The Debrief with Shawn and Katie | #005 Mike Ritland | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370105/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shawn Ryan and his wife Katie Jean debrief and discuss behind the scenes and the entire experience of Shawn Ryan Show #005 with Mike Ritland. Vigilance Elite/Shawn Ryan Links: Website - https://www.shawnryanshow.com Patreon - https://www.patreon.com/VigilanceElite TikTok - https://www.tiktok.com/@shawnryanshow Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/shawnryan762 Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hard Truth - No Excuses, Own Your Mistakes | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370106/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vigilance Elite/Shawn Ryan Links: Website - https://www.shawnryanshow.com Patreon - https://www.patreon.com/VigilanceElite TikTok - https://www.tiktok.com/@shawnryanshow Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/shawnryan762 Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hard Truth - Everyday Carry "EDC" Mindset | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370108/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vigilance Elite/Shawn Ryan Links: Website - https://www.shawnryanshow.com Patreon - https://www.patreon.com/VigilanceElite TikTok - https://www.tiktok.com/@shawnryanshow Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/shawnryan762 Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hard Truth - How to Become an Asset | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370109/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vigilance Elite/Shawn Ryan Links: Website - https://www.shawnryanshow.com Patreon - https://www.patreon.com/VigilanceElite TikTok - https://www.tiktok.com/@shawnryanshow Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/shawnryan762 Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hard Truth - How to Integrate In a New Team | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370107/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vigilance Elite/Shawn Ryan Links: Website - https://www.shawnryanshow.com Patreon - https://www.patreon.com/VigilanceElite TikTok - https://www.tiktok.com/@shawnryanshow Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/shawnryan762 Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hard Truth - Keep the Friend Circle Small | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370110/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vigilance Elite/Shawn Ryan Links: Website - https://www.shawnryanshow.com Patreon - https://www.patreon.com/VigilanceElite TikTok - https://www.tiktok.com/@shawnryanshow Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/shawnryan762 Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#5 Mike Ritland - Navy SEAL Warrior K9 Dog Trainer (Part 2) | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370111/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370111/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part 2 of Vigilance Elite&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Shawn Ryan Show&amp;rdquo; #005 with Mike Ritland we discuss some of his methods as a top tier K9 dog trainer working with military, police, and many other government agencies. We go into great detail about the psychology and mindset of the warrior dogs and the toll that a deployment full of combat has on the dogs as they return home from war. Mike opens up about his non-profit &amp;ldquo;The Warrior Dog Foundation&amp;rdquo; which rehabilitates and gives dogs coming back from war a home they can be comfortable in.</description></item><item><title>United We Stand, Divided We Fall | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370112/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Things I will &amp;ldquo;Never Forget&amp;rdquo; about September 11th 2001 and the time period thereafter. Vigilance Elite/Shawn Ryan Links: Website - https://www.shawnryanshow.com Patreon - https://www.patreon.com/VigilanceElite TikTok - https://www.tiktok.com/@shawnryanshow Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/shawnryan762 Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#5 Mike Ritland - Navy SEAL / K9 Dog Trainer (Part 1) | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370113/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370113/</guid><description>Podcast Description In episode #005 of &amp;ldquo;The Shawn Ryan Show&amp;rdquo; (a 2 part series), Shawn sits down with Mike Ritland. Mike is a former Navy SEAL who responded to the USS Cole, participated in one of the largest SEAL Team operations that has ever occurred with SEAL Team 3, and kicked off the initial invasion of Iraq in 2003. He later became one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most recognized protection K9 dog trainers, a New York Times best selling author three times, and amongst many other accomplishments, he founded the &amp;ldquo;Warrior Dog Foundation&amp;rdquo; which is a not for profit organization that rehabilitates and gives attack dogs returning home from war.</description></item><item><title>The Debrief with Shawn and Katie | #004 Nick Kefalides | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370114/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shawn Ryan and his wife Katie Jean debrief and discuss behind the scenes and the entire experience of Shawn Ryan Show #004 with Nick Kefalides. Vigilance Elite/Shawn Ryan Links: Website - https://www.shawnryanshow.com Patreon - https://www.patreon.com/VigilanceElite TikTok - https://www.tiktok.com/@shawnryanshow Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/shawnryan762 Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Vigilance Elite Outtakes | Hilarious Warm Up Round with Nick Kefalides | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370115/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370115/</guid><description>Podcast Description A hilarious warm up session before filming Shawn Ryan Show #004 with Nick Kefalides Vigilance Elite/Shawn Ryan Links: Website - https://www.shawnryanshow.com Patreon - https://www.patreon.com/VigilanceElite TikTok - https://www.tiktok.com/@shawnryanshow Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/shawnryan762 Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#4 Nick Kefalides - Marine Raider / MARSOC Operator | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370116/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370116/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The Shawn Ryan Show, Shawn sits down with former Marine grunt / MARSOC Marine Raider Nick Kefalides. Nick has an incredibly compelling story from his 4 combat tours in both Iraq and Afghanistan. Nick also opens up about his injuries which lead him to medical retirement from the Marine Corps and how he overcame the dreaded transition from a seasoned war fighter to a professional bass fishing guide who now dedicates time educating combat veterans how to successfully transition.</description></item><item><title>The Debrief with Shawn and Katie: #003 Headshot Don | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370117/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shawn and his wife Katie Jean take you behind the scenes of episode #003 in their new debrief series. They talk about what happens off the camera as well as who might be coming next. Vigilance Elite/Shawn Ryan Links: Website - https://www.shawnryanshow.com Patreon - https://www.patreon.com/VigilanceElite TikTok - https://www.tiktok.com/@shawnryanshow Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/shawnryan762 Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#3 Don Bradley - A.K.A. Headshot Don | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370118/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370118/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Shawn Ryan sits down with Don Bradley A.K.A. Head Shot Don who is a former Green Beret and a former CIA Contractor who has over 20 combat deployments with the CIA alone. Don has a severe TBI (Traumatic Brain Injury) and his symptoms can hit unexpectedly so we go right into the meat of this one with absolutely 0 fluff. He is an operator who has seen more combat than most can imagine but consistently displayed the upmost self restraint while under attack and extreme duress which is extremely hard to do.</description></item><item><title>#2 Travis Kennedy - Navy SEAL / BUDS Instructor | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370119/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370119/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Shawn Ryan sits down with Travis Kennedy, a former Navy SEAL, BUD/S instructor, and currently the CEO of KDS (Kennedy Defensive Shooting). We start off discussing the tension and unrest within the United States in regards to the president&amp;rsquo;s response of an attack on US Embassy in Iraq to coordinate a drone strike on the Iranian General Qassem Soleimani. Shawn then gets into the details of Kennedy&amp;rsquo;s broken home childhood, and how he overcame all odds in becoming one the United States&amp;rsquo; elite Navy SEAL Operators.</description></item><item><title>#1 Mike Glover - Green Beret | Shawn Ryan Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8383370120/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8383370120/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Shawn Ryan sits down with Mike Glover, a former Green Beret, CIA Contractor, and currently the CEO of Fieldcraft Survival. Mike talks about his childhood and how it lead him to an impressive career as one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most elite operators. Mike opens up about his experiences training to become a Green Beret, his personal experiences in combat, what lead him to become a CIA Contractor, his struggle to transition into civilian life, and his latest adventures as a business owner and entrepreneur of Fieldcraft Survival.</description></item></channel></rss>