<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Ten Percent Happier with Dan Harris on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/tags/ten-percent-happier-with-dan-harris/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Ten Percent Happier with Dan Harris on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/ten-percent-happier-with-dan-harris/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Ten Percent Happier with Dan Harris - 542: The Enlightened Mind | Part 5 of The Dalai Lama&#39;s Guide to Happiness</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1310100001/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1310100001/</guid>
        <description>Speaker 1
Cows are sacred, so there are cows all over the street just chilling and nobody bothers them. This is the 10% Happier Podcast. I&amp;rsquo;m Dan Harris. And even McDonald&amp;rsquo;s doesn&amp;rsquo;t serve hamburgers here because they don&amp;rsquo;t believe you should eat beef.
Speaker 5
What are you doing
Speaker 1
Dan? Making a little video from my son who will be fascinated by the notion of sacred
Speaker 5</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Ten Percent Happier with Dan Harris - 541 Is Reincarnation Real  Part 4 of The Dalai Lama&#39;s Guide to Happiness</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1310100002/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1310100002/</guid>
        <description>Speaker 1
So this is security where we go check in. This is the 10% Happier Podcast. I&amp;rsquo;m Dan Harris. Pretty soon they&amp;rsquo;ll be bringing in a huge delegation of people who will have what&amp;rsquo;s called
Speaker 3
an audience
Speaker 1
with his holiness. Every morning, except on Sundays, the Dalai Lama holds a public audience at his compound with fans and followers. These audiences are hushed affairs, despite the bustle of the crowd, everybody&amp;rsquo;s patiently working their way through the long line, then they approach the Dalai Lama in small groups and have their pictures taken and</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Ten Percent Happier with Dan Harris - 540: Wise Selfishness | Part 3 of The Dalai Lama&#39;s Guide to Happiness</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1310100003/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1310100003/</guid>
        <description>Speaker 2
He&amp;rsquo;s already laughing. This is the 10% Happier Podcast. I&amp;rsquo;m Dan Harris. Okay, so today is the big day. I&amp;rsquo;ve been in Dharamsala for over a week and it is finally time for my sit down with his holiness, the Dalai Lama. I have flown across the world for this one hour audience, so the stakes feel pretty high. I will admit, I&amp;rsquo;m a little nervous. His holiness can be a bit of a tough nut to crack.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Ten Percent Happier with Dan Harris - 539: The Cake Incident | Part 2 of The Dalai Lama’s Guide to Happiness</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1310100004/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1310100004/</guid>
        <description>Speaker 1
This is the 10% Happier Podcast. I&amp;rsquo;m Dan Harris.
Speaker 2
Hello everybody. Welcome to the second installment of our special week-long series,
Speaker 1
The Dalai Lama&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Happiness.
Speaker 2
I&amp;rsquo;m a very protective producer, Liz, and she won&amp;rsquo;t let me get any closer than this. But they look cute.
Speaker 1
I&amp;rsquo;m in DarmSala, home to His Holiness the Dalai Lama, also
Speaker 2</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Ten Percent Happier with Dan Harris - 538: The Dalai Lama’s Guide to Happiness | Part 1</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1310100005/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1310100005/</guid>
        <description>Speaker 1
This is the 10% Happier Podcast. I&amp;rsquo;m Dan Harris.
Speaker 8
Deep the Isles clear of all carry-on items.
Speaker 1
Hey gang, it&amp;rsquo;s New Years, and we&amp;rsquo;re making a pretty radical departure from our usual format. Thanks,
Speaker 8
thank you for choosing American Airlines. I
Speaker 1
recently flew with a small team to Daram Salah, India, home to his holiness, the Dalai Lama.
Speaker 4</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Ten Percent Happier with Dan Harris - 537: Your Chance for a Do-Over| Bonus Meditation with Oren Jay Sofer</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1310100006/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1310100006/</guid>
        <description>Speaker 1
Before we get started with today&amp;rsquo;s show, I want to tell you about something really awesome that we&amp;rsquo;re doing around here. Back in October, I flew to India to spend a few weeks in Dharamsala. That&amp;rsquo;s a small city nestled at the foot of the Himalayas surrounded by beautiful cedar forests. It&amp;rsquo;s also home to Tenzin Gyatso, who you probably know as the 14th Dalai Lama. He has claimed that the purpose of life is to be happy.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Ten Percent Happier with Dan Harris - 536: How Not to be Owned by Your Cravings | Bonus Meditation with Alexis Santos</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1310100007/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1310100007/</guid>
        <description>Speaker 2
This show is sponsored by BetterHelp. Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be nice if life came with a user manual? Anytime you have a problem, just check the table of contents, go to the right page, follow the instructions and voila problem solved. But we all know that it doesn&amp;rsquo;t work that way. Navigating any of life&amp;rsquo;s challenges can make you feel unsure whether it&amp;rsquo;s a career change, a new relationship, or becoming a parent.</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
