<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Desert Island Discs on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/desert-island-discs/</link><description>Recent content in Desert Island Discs on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 00:18:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/desert-island-discs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pia Sinha, Director Prison Reform Trust | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930301/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 00:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930301/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pia Sinha is the Director of the Prison Reform Trust and a former prison governor. She was awarded the St Martin’s Award for Prison Governance for her role in turning around HMP Liverpool, which was widely described as Britain’s worst jail in 2018, following a highly critical report by HM Inspectorate of Prisons. Pia was born in north India and she and her family came to the UK when she was 14.</description></item><item><title>Peter White, broadcaster | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930001/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 11:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Peter White is an award-winning broadcaster. In 2024 he will celebrate 50 years presenting Radio 4’s In Touch, the programme for blind and visually impaired people. He is also one of the presenters of the network’s consumer series, You and Yours.
Peter was born in 1947 and has been blind since birth. Like his older brother Colin, he has a rare genetic anomaly that meant his optic nerve hadn’t developed properly.</description></item><item><title>Lea Salonga, singer and actor | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930002/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lea Salonga was just 18 when she became an international theatre star, taking a leading role in the world premiere production of the musical Miss Saigon in 1989. Her performance - first in London, then on Broadway - won her Olivier and Tony awards. She has provided the singing voice for two Disney princesses, and has become a strong advocate for better Asian representation on stage and screen. She was born in Manila in the Philippines, where she made her professional stage debut in 1978 at the age of seven in a production of The King and I.</description></item><item><title>Professor Dame Lesley Regan, obstetrician and gynaecologist | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930003/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Professor Dame Lesley Regan is the Government’s first Women’s Health Ambassador for England. She is one of the main drivers behind the upcoming Women’s Health Strategy which aims to tackle the gender health gap and improve services for women.
As a former president of the Royal College of Obstetricians and Gynaecologists – only the second woman to hold that post in its 94-year history – she shone a light on historically taboo subjects from period problems and contraception to the menopause.</description></item><item><title>Patrick Grant, designer and broadcaster | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930004/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 00:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Patrick Grant is a designer, clothing entrepreneur and a judge on the BBC TV programme The Great British Sewing Bee. Patrick was born in Edinburgh in 1972. His interest in clothes and in making things was evident from a very early age, along with a love of sport: his father was a rugby coach and trained Patrick and his friends. Some of his friends went on to represent Scotland and Patrick played for Scotland's under-19 team.</description></item><item><title>Dame Donna Langley, film studio executive | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930005/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dame Donna Langley is chairman and chief content officer for the NBC Universal Studio Group, the first British woman in history to run a major Hollywood film studio. She green lit Christopher Nolan’s latest film Oppenheimer and was one of the earliest and most ardent supporters of the Abba movie Mamma Mia.
She was born in London and brought up on the Isle of Wight. She always knew she was adopted as a baby, which she says made her feel special within her family.</description></item><item><title>Greg Jackson, entrepreneur | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930006/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Greg Jackson is the founder and CEO of Octopus Energy. The company is the UK’s second largest domestic energy provider with over five million customers and is one of Europe’s leading investors in renewables. Greg was born in Germany in 1971 where his father was a surveyor in the army. The family returned to the UK a few years later and, following his parents’ divorce, Greg and his two younger siblings were brought up by his mother in Halifax.</description></item><item><title>Katherine Ryan, comedian | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930007/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 11:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Katherine Ryan is a Canadian comedian and writer. Her edgy and provocative routines have led to sell-out tours, comedy specials on television and her sitcom series The Duchess. Based on her experience at the time, the Duchess tells the story of a successful, happily single mother and Katherine wrote it out of frustration because she believed no one else was telling a story like hers on screen.
Katherine was born in Sarnia in Ontario where she attended a local French-speaking primary school.</description></item><item><title>Lucinda Russell, horse trainer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930008/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lucinda Russell is a Scottish racehorse trainer. Her stables in Kinross have sent out almost 900 winners, including two Grand National champions. She is one of only two Scottish trainers and four women to have celebrated a Grand National win since the event began in 1839, and her yard is the most successful in the history of Scottish jump racing. Lucinda was born in Edinburgh in 1966. Although she didn’t come from a racing background – her father ran the family’s whisky business – she was obsessed with horses from a very young age.</description></item><item><title>Adrian Edmondson, actor, writer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930009/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 23:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adrian Edmondson first shot to national fame in 1982, playing the studded punk Vyvyan in the TV sitcom The Young Ones, set in a seedy student flat. The cast largely came from the developing alternative comedy scene, and included Rik Mayall and Alexei Sayle. Adrian was born in Bradford in 1957. He spent time as a child in Cyprus, Bahrain and Uganda, following his father who worked as a teacher for the armed forces.</description></item><item><title>Shirley Collins, folk singer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930010/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shirley Collins first enjoyed success as one of the leading figures in the British folk revival of the 1960s. She initially performed with her sister, Dolly Collins, and also collaborated with other folk luminaries to create some of the era’s most beloved albums. In the past decade she has made an acclaimed return to the concert stage and the recording studio.
Shirley was born in Sussex in 1935. She can still recall how her grandfather used to sing folk songs to comfort her while they were sheltering during German air raids in the early 1940s.</description></item><item><title>Toto Wolff, Formula 1 executive | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930011/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Toto Wolff is CEO and Team Principal of the Mercedes Formula 1 motor racing team. He has led the team to an unprecedented seven consecutive drivers’ championships – six with Lewis Hamilton - and eight consecutive constructors' championships. He is the most successful manager in Formula 1 history, and arguably one of the most successful managers in any sport. Toto was born Torger Wolff in Vienna. When he was eight his father was diagnosed with a brain tumour and died when Toto was 15.</description></item><item><title>Simon Woolley, crossbench peer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930012/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Simon Woolley, Lord Woolley of Woodford, is principal of Homerton College at Cambridge University. He is the first black man to head an Oxbridge college. He is a co-founder of Operation Black Vote, which campaigns for greater inclusivity in politics, and became a crossbench peer in 2019. Simon spent his early years in an orphanage in Leicester before being fostered and then adopted by a white couple who also adopted his brother Mick.</description></item><item><title>Jill Scott, footballer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930013/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 23:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jill Scott is the second most capped England footballer ever, playing for her country 161 times. Before her retirement last year, she played in ten major international tournaments and was part of the England team who beat Germany to win the 2022 European Championships.
Jill was born and brought up in Sunderland, and excelled in a range of sports from an early age. She won the London mini-marathon when she was 14 but her heart was in football.</description></item><item><title>Peter Doig, artist | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930014/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 23:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Peter Doig is one of Britain’s most successful living artists. His paintings have been exhibited at major galleries around the world, winning wide critical acclaim and selling for tens of millions of pounds at auction, setting sales records. Peter was born in Edinburgh in 1959, but grew up in Trinidad and Canada, where his father had chosen to work. Peter was partly educated at a Scottish boarding school, but didn't enjoy the experience.</description></item><item><title>Stanley Tucci, actor | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930015/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stanley Tucci is an actor, director and writer who is known for his roles in a broad range of feature films including the Devil Wears Prada, Julie and Julia and the Hunger Games. More recently he has whetted the appetites of television viewers with his food and travel series Searching for Italy.
Stanley’s grandparents left Calabria in southern Italy for a new life in America, where his parents were born.</description></item><item><title>Kate Mosse, writer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930016/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 23:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kate Mosse OBE is a British novelist and broadcaster. She is the author of ten novels and short story collections, including The Joubert Family Chronicles and the best-selling Languedoc Trilogy. She has also written four works of non-fiction including her memoir about caring, An Extra Pair of Hands. In 1996 she co-founded the Women’s Prize for Fiction.
Born in Chichester, she studied English at Oxford University and had a very successful career in publishing before writing her first book about pregnancy.</description></item><item><title>Adam Kay, writer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930017/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam Kay is a writer whose memoir This is Going to Hurt; Secret Diaries of a Junior Doctor won the Book of the Year prize at the National Book Awards and has sold over three million copies. It was adapted for television as a BBC series that won four BAFTAs this year, including Adam’s award for best drama writer.
Adam was born in Brighton in 1980 and studied medicine at Imperial College London.</description></item><item><title>Claudia Rankine, poet | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930018/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Claudia Rankine is a poet, essayist and playwright. She is best known for her book Citizen: An American Lyric which combines short stories about everyday injustices experienced by people of colour with poems telling the stories of black men who died during confrontations with the police. The book won several awards in the US and the UK’s Forward Prize for best collection in 2015. Claudia was born in Kingston, Jamaica and at seven followed her parents to New York City where they had emigrated some years before.</description></item><item><title>Jeremy Bowen, journalist | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930019/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeremy Bowen is the BBC’s award-winning international editor. He has been reporting from the world’s conflict zones, including Iraq, Bosnia, the Middle East and Ukraine, for more than 30 years. Jeremy was born in Cardiff in 1960. His father was a journalist for BBC Wales, who covered the Aberfan disaster in 1966, and his mother was a press photographer. In 1984, after university, Jeremy joined the BBC as a news trainee and in 1989 he starting reporting from Afghanistan and El Salvador.</description></item><item><title>Ronnie O'Sullivan, snooker player | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930020/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 23:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ronnie O’Sullivan OBE is currently ranked the number one snooker player in the world, and is widely regarded as one of the finest players in the history of the sport. He has won the Masters a record seven times and he jointly holds the record for winning the World Snooker Championship seven times. Since 1997 he has held the world record for the fastest 147 break, leading to his nickname 'the Rocket'.</description></item><item><title>Professor Sharon Peacock, scientist | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930021/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Professor Sharon Peacock is professor of public health and microbiology at Cambridge University. In March 2020 she set up the COVID-19 Genomics UK (COG-UK) Consortium to map the genetic sequence of the virus as it spread and mutated. Within a year COG-UK was leading the world in identifying mutant COVID strains, and this data was instrumental in helping the development of vaccines and treatments.
Sharon was born in Margate and left school at 16 to work in her local corner shop.</description></item><item><title>Simon Pegg, actor | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Simon Pegg is an actor and screenwriter who became a household name after appearing in two of Hollywood’s most successful film franchises – Mission: Impossible and Star Trek. He also won many fans for co-creating the so-called Three Flavours Cornetto Trilogy of films – Shaun of the Dead, Hot Fuzz and the World’s End.
Simon was born in Gloucester and studied theatre, film and television at the University of Bristol.</description></item><item><title>Professor Peter Hennessy, historian | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930023/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Professor Peter Hennessy is one of the UK’s leading contemporary historians. He has written acclaimed and important books about politics, the civil service, the intelligence agencies and the British constitution on which he is an expert. Peter was born in London in 1947 and read history at St John’s College, Cambridge. He started writing for the Times in the mid-1970s, covering the inner workings of Whitehall whose activities at that time were shrouded in secrecy.</description></item><item><title>Dara Ó Briain, comedian and television presenter | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930024/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 10:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dara Ó Briain has toured the world as a stand-up comedian, and hosted the BBC’s satirical series Mock the Week for 17 years. A science graduate with a love of astronomy, he co-presented the BBC series Stargazing Live with Professor Brian Cox, and is a regular guest on television quizzes and panel shows. Dara grew up in Bray, County Wicklow and attended Irish language schools, playing for the Gaelic football and hurling teams.</description></item><item><title>Liz Carr, actor and activist | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 09:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Liz Carr is most widely known for her role as the forensic examiner Clarissa Mullery in the long-running BBC TV drama Silent Witness. She appeared in more than 70 episodes, from 2013 until 2020. Last year she won the Olivier award for Best Supporting Actress for her performance in the National Theatre production of The Normal Heart. Her role was inspired by Dr Linda Laubenstein, a pioneer in the treatment of AIDS and a wheelchair user: Liz was the first wheelchair user to play the part, almost four decades after the premiere.</description></item><item><title>Amanda Blanc, businesswoman | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930026/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 10:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amanda Blanc is the group CEO of the insurance company Aviva. She is one of a handful of women at the top of FTSE 100 companies and has spoken out against the sexism and misogyny many – including herself - have encountered during their careers. In 2022 she called out disparaging comments made to her by some of the male shareholders at her company’s own AGM. Her published riposte received some 1.</description></item><item><title>Robert Webb, comedian | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930027/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 23:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Robert Webb first reached a wide audience as the co-star of Channel 4’s longest running sitcom, the BAFTA-award winning Peep Show. With his long-standing comedy partner David Mitchell, he also created That Mitchell and Webb Sound for BBC Radio 4, which transferred to TV as That Mitchell and Webb Look, which also won a BAFTA. Robert was born in Lincolnshire and first became hooked on comedy when his impressions of teachers made his school friends laugh.</description></item><item><title>Sonia Boyce, artist | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930028/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 10:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930028/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2022 Sonia Boyce became the first Black British woman to represent Britain at the Venice Biennale exhibition. She also took home the coveted Golden Lion Award for her installation Feeling Her Way, which combined video and collage with improvised performances by five female musicians. Sonia was born in London and grew up near the renowned Whitechapel Art Gallery. As a very young child she would visit the gallery, often alone, relishing the light and space inside the building.</description></item><item><title>Jenny Beavan, costume designer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930029/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 00:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jenny Beavan has won three Oscars for her costumes for the films Room with a View, Mad Max: Fury Road and Cruella, and has received nine further Academy Award nominations. She was born in London, and her parents were both professional musicians who encouraged her to paint, draw and learn a musical instrument. After studying theatre design, she was invited at the age of just 21 to create the sets for a production of Carmen at the Royal Opera House, conducted by Sir Georg Solti.</description></item><item><title>David Sedaris, writer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930030/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 11:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930030/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Sedaris is a writer whose humorous stories and wry takes on everyday encounters have led to 13 bestselling books and many radio programmes including Meet David Sedaris on BBC Radio 4. His work is based on his own life and, although very funny, does not shy away from the bleaker aspects of his experiences. David was born in New York State and grew up in Raleigh in North Carolina.</description></item><item><title>Lesley Manville, actor | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930031/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 00:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lesley Manville made her debut on the West End stage as a teenager in 1972, and since then has taken on a wide range of roles on stage and screen, including an Oscar-nominated performance in the film Phantom Thread. She was born in Brighton and first enjoyed performing as a singer, winning competitions with her sister. When she was 15, she commuted daily to the Italia Conti stage school in London.</description></item><item><title>Professor Corinne Le Quéré, climate scientist | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930032/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 11:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Corinne Le Quéré is the Royal Society Research Professor of Climate Change Science at the University of East Anglia where she studies the way marine ecosystems respond to climate change. She uses computer simulators of the ocean to assess how the carbon cycle functions and her climate models have resulted in significant findings about how warmer temperatures have affected the ocean’s ability to absorb carbon. Corinne was born in Quebec and as a child spent camping holidays in the national parks of Eastern Canada which fostered her interest in the natural world.</description></item><item><title>Michael Pollan, writer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930033/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael Pollan’s award-winning writing about plants, nature and food combines anthropology and philosophy with culture, health and natural history. Time Magazine has named him one of the 100 most influential people in the world and his maxim to ‘Eat food. Not too much. Mostly Plants.’ is a central tenet of the sustainable food movement.
Michael grew up in suburban Long Island, USA, and planted his first garden when he was eight-years-old.</description></item><item><title>Gabby Logan, broadcaster | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930034/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gabby Logan presents a range of popular BBC sports programmes and hosts high-profile sporting events including the Olympics, Premiership football and the World Cup. Gabby was born in Leeds and her father Terry Yorath is a former footballer and manager who played for Leeds United and for the Welsh national team. As a young girl she was a rhythmic gymnast and represented Wales in the Commonwealth Games in 1990.</description></item><item><title>Sir Malcolm Walker, retailer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930035/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 00:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sir Malcolm Walker is the chairman and co-founder of the frozen food supermarket chain Iceland. He was brought up in Grange Moor, West Yorkshire. He was just 14 when his father died, and he helped his mother run a smallholding, driving a tractor and ploughing fields. His business instinct kicked in during his teenage years, when he promoted Saturday night dances by booking bands into local church halls. After receiving rejections from Marks &amp;amp; Spencer and Littlewoods, he became a trainee manager at Woolworths, and recalls that he started at the very bottom, sweeping the floors for many months before gradually winning promotions and moving round the country.</description></item><item><title>Kirsty Young, broadcaster | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930036/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 00:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirsty Young was the award-winning presenter of Desert Island Discs between 2006 and 2018, interviewing 496 castaways. Her TV work includes BAFTA-winning coverage of events marking the centenary of World War One, and memorable live presentation from Windsor of the state funeral of Queen Elizabeth II earlier this year. Kirsty was born in East Kilbride in Scotland. After a chance meeting with a freelance TV cameraman, she became interested in a media career, and worked as a runner and then a researcher for an independent production company, before joining BBC Radio Scotland as a trainee news and continuity announcer, beating 700 other applicants.</description></item><item><title>Steven Spielberg, director | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930037/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Steven Spielberg is the most successful director of his generation and the highest-grossing director of all time: his films have taken more than $10 billion worldwide. From Jaws to E.T. and Jurassic Park to Schindler’s List, his storytelling has captivated audiences around the world. Steven grew up in Phoenix, Arizona, where he started making films as a young boy. In 1958 he made a short Western which won him a Boy Scout merit badge.</description></item><item><title>Cate Blanchett, actor | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930038/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 00:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cate Blanchett is arguably the most celebrated Australian actor ever, winning two Academy Awards, three BAFTAs, three Golden Globes and dozens of other honours around the world. She grew up in Melbourne, and although she enjoyed music and drama at school, she initially had no plans to pursue a career as an actor. She started a degree course in economics and fine art, but dropped out after a year, and later won a place at the National Institute of Dramatic Art in Sydney.</description></item><item><title>Edward Enninful, editor | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930039/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Edward Enninful is the editor-in-chief of British Vogue and the editorial director of Vogue in Europe.
Edward was born in the port city of Takoradi in Ghana in 1972. His father was a major in the Ghanaian army and, following a period of political instability, the family fled the country and settled in London. Edward’s interest in fashion dates back to his childhood in Ghana when he watched his seamstress mother at work making dresses for clients including the President’s wife.</description></item><item><title>Baz Luhrmann, director | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930040/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Baz Luhrmann is an Australian director whose debut film, Strictly Ballroom, became one of Australia’s most successful releases, and also inspired the title of the BBC’s popular Saturday night dance show. He went on to direct Romeo + Juliet, Moulin Rouge!, the Great Gatsby and, more recently, Elvis starring Tom Hanks and Austin Butler. Baz was born Mark Andrew Luhrmann in 1962. His friends nicknamed him Baz after the puppet Basil Brush because of his unruly hair.</description></item><item><title>Barry Hearn, sports promoter | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930041/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Barry Hearn is a promoter who has been at the forefront of some of the biggest snooker, boxing and darts events in the last 40 years. He played a central role in turning snooker into a television phenomenon, and as a boxing promoter he represented Chris Eubank and Nigel Benn. He later turned darts players, including Phil 'The Power' Taylor, into household names.
Barry was born in Dagenham in East London in 1948 and grew up in a council house.</description></item><item><title>Professor Jean Golding, epidemiologist | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930042/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Professor Jean Golding is an epidemiologist who is best known for founding the Children of the Nineties study - more formally known as the Avon Longitudinal Study of Parents and Children. The most detailed project of its kind anywhere in the world, it has followed the lives of children who were born in Avon during 1991 and 1992 and helped scientists make important discoveries about everything from peanut allergy to the effects of long Covid.</description></item><item><title>Richard E Grant, actor | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930043/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 00:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Richard E Grant was born in Swaziland, now Eswatini, one of the smallest countries in Africa, and took his first steps as an actor as a teenager in the local amateur theatre company.
He studied Drama and English at Cape Town University in South Africa, and moved to London in 1982, hoping to find work as an actor, with - in his words - 'nothing more than a couple of suitcases, a boxful of music cassettes and blind ambition.</description></item><item><title>Professor Angela Gallop, forensic scientist | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930044/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Professor Angela Gallop is a forensic scientist who has helped solve some of the most notorious violent crimes in recent British history including the killings of Stephen Lawrence, Damilola Taylor and Rachel Nickell.
After completing a degree in botany and a doctorate on the biochemistry of sea slugs, Angela joined the Home Office’s Forensic Science Service in 1974, and four years later attended her first crime scene, where 18-year-old Helen Rytka was killed by Peter Sutcliffe, the Yorkshire Ripper.</description></item><item><title>Rick Rubin, music producer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930045/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rick Rubin is a multiple Grammy-winning record producer who has worked with a wide range of artists including Adele, the Beastie Boys and the Red Hot Chili Peppers. He also reinvigorated the career of Johnny Cash in the 1990s, with a series of acclaimed stripped-back albums, introducing the legendary Man in Black to a new audience. Rick was born on Long Island in New York in 1963. As a teenager, his first love was punk, but he soon became entranced by New York’s emerging rap scene and started hanging out in hip hop clubs to discover more about what was then considered to be an underground form of music.</description></item><item><title>Maxine Peake, actor | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930046/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Maxine Peake is an actor and writer who first came to public attention in 1998 as Twinkle in the Victoria Wood sitcom Dinnerladies. She went on to play Veronica in Paul Abbott’s series Shameless and later became known for playing real people, including the Hillsborough campaigner Anne Williams, and Sara Rowbotham, the former health worker who exposed the sexual abuse scandal in Rochdale in 2012. Maxine was born in Bolton and after a rocky start at college – she was asked to leave her performing arts course after just two weeks but stuck it out – she won a scholarship to study at RADA.</description></item><item><title>Kevin Sinfield, rugby player | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930047/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 00:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kevin Sinfield OBE is one of the most decorated players in the history of English rugby league. He captained Leeds Rhinos and the England team, and was runner-up in the BBC Sports Personality of the Year poll in 2015. He holds records as the highest points-scorer in Super League history, the third-highest points-scorer in British rugby league history and the record points-scorer for Leeds. After retiring from playing, he switched codes and is currently part of the coaching staff at Leicester Tigers rugby union team.</description></item><item><title>Dr Waheed Arian, doctor | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930048/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr Waheed Arian is a radiologist who set up a charity called Arian Teleheal in 2015. The charity enables volunteer doctors in the west to advise colleagues in conflict zones using smartphone technology. The charity has helped save many lives in countries including Syria, Uganda and Afghanistan where Waheed was born.
In 1988, at the height of the Soviet-Afghan conflict, Waheed and his family fled Kabul for Pakistan where they lived in a refugee camp for the next few years.</description></item><item><title>Jay Blades, presenter and furniture restorer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930049/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jay Blades is a furniture restorer who is best known for presenting the Repair Shop on BBC One. The programme, which attracts many millions of viewers, brings old and damaged family treasures back to life and has been praised for its celebration of craftsmanship and the values of kindness and patience.
Jay grew up in Hackney in East London and was brought up by his mother Barbara. He struggled to read as a young boy which held him back at school and he left at 16.</description></item><item><title>Sue Barker, presenter and tennis player | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930050/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sue Barker is a television presenter and former professional tennis player. She presented the BBC’s Wimbledon coverage for nearly three decades, before stepping down this year, when she received a standing ovation. Sue was born in Devon in 1956, and was educated at the Marist Convent School where she had a reputation for being naughty – until her PE teacher, Mrs Chadwick, diverted her energy into tennis. Aged 11 she was selected for training by the local tennis coach Arthur Roberts, who had already guided players to Grand Slam titles.</description></item><item><title>John Legend, musician | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930051/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 23:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930051/</guid><description>Podcast Description The American singer and songwriter John Legend has won two Emmys, 12 Grammys, an Oscar and a Tony award – making him one of only 16 living artists to have won all four honours. One of his songs, All of Me, written for his wife, the model Chrissy Teigen, has been streamed more than four billion times on digital platforms. He was born John Stephens in Springfield, Ohio into a musical family.</description></item><item><title>Clare Smyth, chef | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930052/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Clare Smyth is a highly acclaimed chef and is the first British woman to win the coveted three Michelin stars for her work. She opened her London restaurant, Core, in 2017, and before that she ran Restaurant Gordon Ramsay, which also held three Michelin stars.
Clare was born in County Antrim, Northern Ireland, and grew up on a farm, where her love of simple ingredients was nurtured. The youngest of three children, she discovered a passion for cooking and decided to make it her career from an early age.</description></item><item><title>Kate Moss, model | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930053/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kate Moss came to fame in the 1990s, and her distinctive look went on to embody the era of Cool Britannia. She has appeared on the cover of hundreds of magazines and starred in campaigns for many of the top fashion houses. She has made cameos on film and television and inspired artists including Lucian Freud, Tracey Emin and Marc Quinn. Kate was born in Croydon in 1974. When she was 14, she was spotted at JFK airport by Sarah Doukas who signed her to her modelling agency.</description></item><item><title>Kate Ewart-Biggs, Deputy Chief Executive, British Council | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930054/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 23:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kate Ewart-Biggs is the deputy chief executive of the British Council, which aims to build connections between the UK and countries worldwide, through education programmes, language learning and cultural activities. Kate was born into a diplomatic family and her early childhood years were spent in France and Belgium. In 1976, when she was eight years old, her father Christopher Ewart-Biggs was appointed British ambassador to Ireland. Two weeks into his new job, he was killed by an IRA landmine.</description></item><item><title>Andrew Ramroop, tailor | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930055/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 23:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrew Ramroop is a Savile Row tailor, whose international client list has included film stars and royalty.
Andrew grew up in a remote village in Trinidad and sewed his first garment at the age of nine, creating a simple pair of trousers from a pillowcase. He left school at 13 and was apprenticed to a local tailor who told him tales about the pinnacle of sartorial excellence, Savile Row – the place where James Bond’s suits were cut.</description></item><item><title>Adele, singer and songwriter | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930056/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adele is a singer and songwriter who has achieved record-breaking sales and global recognition for her four albums which document her life from the age of 19 onwards. Her cache of awards includes 15 Grammys and nine BRITs. She also won a Golden Globe and an Academy Award for the James Bond theme Skyfall which she co-wrote. She was born Adele Laurie Blue Adkins in London in 1988. In 2002 she won a place at the BRIT School for Performing Arts where she studied music and developed her performing and song writing skills.</description></item><item><title>Bono, singer and songwriter | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930057/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bono is a singer, songwriter and the frontman of U2, one of the most recognisable and successful bands in music history. They have sold over 170 million albums, won 22 Grammys – more than any other band – and two Golden Globe Awards. Bono is also known for his work as an activist, especially in Africa where he has played a prominent role in campaigns which tackle poverty and HIV/AIDs.</description></item><item><title>Rita Tushingham, actor | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930058/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rita Tushingham first won international acclaim as a teenager, playing Jo in the film A Taste of Honey. Her performance in this 1961 kitchen sink drama earned her a BAFTA, a Golden Globe and the Best Actress award at the Cannes Film Festival. She starting shooting the film on her 19th birthday. She went on to play roles in the Leather Boys, the Knack… and How to Get it and Doctor Zhivago.</description></item><item><title>Frances O'Grady, General Secretary of the TUC | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930059/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Frances O’Grady is the General Secretary of the Trades Union Congress (TUC), the UK's umbrella group for unions, representing millions of workers. She is the first woman in the 154 year history of the TUC to hold this post, which she took up in 2013. Frances is the youngest of five children, and was brought up in Oxford. Her family has strong links with the trade union movement: her great grandfather and grandfather were founder members of the Irish Transport and General Workers’ Union, and her father was a shop steward at the British Leyland plant in Cowley.</description></item><item><title>Jon Ronson, writer and broadcaster | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930060/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jon Ronson is a writer and broadcaster whose award-winning podcast and Radio 4 series Things Fell Apart investigated the stories behind today’s culture wars. His television programmes and books – from Them: Adventures with Extremists to So You’ve Been Publicly Shamed - explore what he calls “the worlds that are going on underground” and his subjects - from conspiracy theorists to internet trolls - inhabit the fringes of society.</description></item><item><title>David Harewood, actor and presenter | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930061/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930061/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Harewood is a British actor and presenter who found global fame playing the CIA director David Estes in the acclaimed TV drama series Homeland. He was the first black actor to play Othello at the National theatre in 1997 and took the role of Martin Luther King in the Olivier award-winning play The Mountaintop in 2009.
David was born in Birmingham in 1965. After one of his teachers suggested that he should try his luck at acting, he won a place at RADA where he tackled a number of challenging roles including King Lear.</description></item><item><title>Ellie Simmonds, swimmer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930062/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 23:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ellie Simmonds has competed at four Paralympic Games, winning five gold medals and breaking world records on the way. She first came to national attention at the age of 13, when she won two golds at the Beijing 2008 Paralympics, and became the youngest person ever to be awarded an MBE a few months later. Ellie is the youngest of five children and was born with achondroplasia, a form of dwarfism.</description></item><item><title>Bradley Walsh, presenter and actor | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930063/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bradley Walsh is a familiar face to many millions of TV viewers, as the host of quiz shows including The Chase and Blankety-Blank, and as an actor in dramas such as Doctor Who and The Larkins.
Bradley was born in Watford and after leaving school at 16 he was apprenticed to the local Rolls-Royce factory as a jet engineer. A keen footballer, he signed to Brentford FC when he was 19 but his career was cut short by injury after only two seasons with the club.</description></item><item><title>Fiona Hill, foreign affairs specialist | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930064/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fiona Hill is a foreign affairs specialist who advised Presidents George W Bush, Barack Obama and Donald Trump. She came to wider public attention in 2019 when she testified against President Trump during his first impeachment.
Fiona was born in Bishop Auckland, County Durham. Her father was a former coal miner who worked as a hospital porter and her mother was a midwife. After graduating in Russian and History from St Andrews University, she won a scholarship to read Soviet Studies at Harvard.</description></item><item><title>Desert Island Discoveries | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930065/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lauren shares handpicked gems from the Desert Island Discs back-catalogue with Radio 1 presenter Vick Hope, including Bob Mortimer, Maya Angelou, Joe Wicks, Sophia Loren, Tom Hanks, Dame Pat McGrath and Sinéad Burke.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Winnie Byanyima, executive director of Unaids | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930066/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Winnie Byanyima is a human rights advocate and executive director of Unaids, the joint UN Programme which was set up to eradicate Aids as a threat to public health by 2030.
Winnie was born in the village of Ruti, in south west Uganda, where her teacher parents raised her and her siblings to follow their example of doing good things for others. From an early age Winnie adopted the family motto of ‘truth and justice’.</description></item><item><title>Alan Cumming, actor | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930067/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alan Cumming's wide-ranging career on stage includes playing Hamlet, starring opposite Daniel Radcliffe in Samuel Beckett’s Endgame and – perhaps most notably - taking the role of the Emcee in the musical Cabaret in London and New York to great acclaim: his 1998 Broadway performance won seven awards, including a Tony. He’s also appeared in films including GoldenEye and Stanley Kubrick’s Eyes Wide Shut, and in the TV series The Good Wife.</description></item><item><title>Robert Plant, singer and songwriter | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930068/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Robert Plant is a singer and songwriter who was Led Zeppelin’s frontman from the band’s inception in 1968 until it disbanded in 1980. Led Zeppelin sold hundreds of millions of albums and in their heyday acquired a reputation for unbridled rock ‘n’ roll hedonism. Since 1980 Robert has gone on to achieve success as a solo artist and has collaborated with other musicians, notably the bluegrass singer Alison Krauss.</description></item><item><title>Oti Mabuse, dancer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930069/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Oti Mabuse is a dancer, choreographer and TV talent show judge. She has enjoyed great success on the BBC show Strictly Come Dancing and is one of only two professional dancers to win the glitterball trophy twice.
Oti was born in South Africa in 1990, the year that Nelson Mandela was released from prison, and dance was a central part of her life from a very early age: her mother had set up a dance school so that black children could learn ballroom and Latin dancing.</description></item><item><title>Professor Nick Webborn, Chair of the British Paralympic Association | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930070/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Professor Nick Webborn has chaired the British Paralympic Association since 2017. He is a world-leading expert on Paralympic sports medicine and the most widely-published author on the subject. He has attended 11 Paralympic and one Olympic Games. He was born in Swansea in 1956, trained as a doctor in London and joined the RAF as a junior medical officer. In 1981 he was playing in an RAF rugby match when a mistimed opposition tackle left him with a severe spinal injury.</description></item><item><title>Anne Tyler, writer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930071/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anne Tyler is a novelist and short story writer. Her 23 novels include the Accidental Tourist, Dinner at the Homesick Restaurant and the Pulitzer Prize-winning Breathing Lessons. Anne was born in Minneapolis, Minnesota in 1941, the oldest of four children. Her parents were Quakers and the family lived in a succession of Quaker communities in the South until they settled in a Quaker commune in Celo, in the mountains of North Carolina in 1948.</description></item><item><title>Leslie Caron, actress | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930072/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Leslie Caron is an award-winning actress and dancer who starred in some of the most memorable films of Hollywood’s golden age including An American in Paris and Gigi. Leslie was first cast away on Desert Island Discs in 1956 when she was 25, and her return, nearly 66 years later, marks the greatest gap between appearances in the programme's 80-year history. She was born in Paris in 1931 and started ballet lessons at 11 to please her mother, a dancer herself who had performed on Broadway.</description></item><item><title>Professor Sir David Spiegelhalter, statistician | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930073/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Professor Sir David Spiegelhalter specialises in medical statistics. He is the Chair of the Winton Centre for Risk and Evidence Communication at Cambridge University, and one of the most frequently cited experts in his field. During the Covid 19 pandemic, he has made regular appearances as a broadcaster and newspaper commentator, analysing and explaining complex data for a general audience. David was born in Barnstable, the youngest of three children.</description></item><item><title>Lyse Doucet, journalist | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930074/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lyse Doucet is the BBC’s award-winning chief international correspondent, reporting from a range of postings including in Kabul, Islamabad, Tehran and Jerusalem for nearly 40 years. Lyse was born in Bathhurst, New Brunswick, in eastern Canada and after graduating with a master’s degree from the University of Toronto she set her sights on becoming a journalist. She took her first step by signing up with the volunteer agency Canadian Crossroads International which offered her a placement in Ivory Coast, West Africa.</description></item><item><title>John Caudwell, businessman | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930075/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930075/</guid><description>Podcast Description John Caudwell is a businessman and philanthropist who founded the mobile phone company Phones 4U in 1996. It became the UK’s largest independent mobile phone retailer and made him one of Britain’s most successful businessmen. John was born in Birmingham and grew up in Stoke-on-Trent. He came up with his first business venture when he was five – he sold his toys to the other children in his neighbourhood.</description></item><item><title>Deborah Levy, writer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930076/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Deborah Levy is a writer whose novels Swimming Home and Hot Milk were both shortlisted for the Booker Prize. Last year she published the final instalment of her ‘living autobiography’ trilogy of memoirs, and her earlier work includes plays for the RSC as well as short story collections and poetry.
Deborah was born in South Africa in 1959, the eldest child of anti-apartheid activists Norman and Philippa Levy. Her father was arrested when she was five and was imprisoned for four years.</description></item><item><title>Simon Reeve, broadcaster and writer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930077/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Simon Reeve is a broadcaster and writer best known for his TV documentaries which combine travel and adventure with investigations into the challenges faced by the places he visits.
His journeys have taken him across jungles, deserts, mountains and oceans, and to some of the most dangerous and remote regions of the world. He’s dodged bullets on frontlines, dived with seals and sharks, survived malaria, walked through minefields and tracked lions on foot.</description></item><item><title>Richard Osman, writer and broadcaster | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930078/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 17:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Richard Osman is a broadcaster, TV producer and writer who co-presents the quiz show Pointless on BBC One. His first novel, The Thursday Murder Club, was a publishing phenomenon, selling more than a million copies, and the follow-up became one of the fastest-selling titles since records began.
Richard grew up in Haywards Heath in West Sussex and his early passion for television led to him devising quiz shows and programme formats from a young age.</description></item><item><title>Dame Prue Leith, writer and broadcaster | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930079/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dame Prue Leith is a broadcaster, writer, former restaurateur and a judge on the television show the Great British Bake Off. Prue was born in Cape Town, South Africa, during the era of Apartheid. After leaving school she moved to Paris to study at the Sorbonne, but decided that her future lay in food, and took a Cordon Bleu cookery course in London. She set up her own catering business from her bedsit, where space was so tight that she washed lettuces in the bath.</description></item><item><title>Jack Thorne, screenwriter | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930080/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jack Thorne is a writer who has enjoyed great success with his scripts for the stage, cinema and television, winning five BAFTA awards for his TV work. His theatre credits include the international hit play Harry Potter and the Cursed Child, which has won major awards in London and New York. For television, his recent successes include his adaptation of His Dark Materials, from the books by Philip Pullman, and The Virtues, co-written with Shane Meadows, and starring Stephen Graham.</description></item><item><title>Helen Macdonald, writer and naturalist | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930081/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Helen Macdonald is a writer and naturalist who is best known as the author of H is for Hawk which won the 2014 Samuel Johnson Prize and the Costa Book Award, and topped the sales charts. The book chronicles her experiences training a goshawk called Mabel while grieving for her late father. Helen’s father was a staff photographer at the Daily Mirror and her mother was a journalist on local newspapers.</description></item><item><title>Neil Gaiman, writer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930082/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Neil Gaiman is a writer whose list of titles spans many forms from novels, including American Gods, to children’s stories such as Coraline and the comic book the Sandman. Neil grew up in East Grinstead and after finishing school he became a journalist and then wrote short stories and books. One of his early commissions was writing a companion to The Hitchhiker’s Guide to the Galaxy by Douglas Adams.</description></item><item><title>Carl Hester, dressage rider | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930083/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Carl Hester is a dressage rider who has competed in six Olympic Games, winning a team gold at London 2012. Carl grew up on Sark in the Channel Islands, where cars are banned and horses are part of the island’s daily life. He learned to ride on a donkey before progressing to horses. After leaving school, his first job was at an equine therapy centre in Hampshire. A key moment in his early career was an invitation from Dr Wilfried Bechtolsheimer, a leading figure in dressage, to join his yard.</description></item><item><title>Dame Jo da Silva, engineer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930084/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dame Jo da Silva is a structural engineer and disaster relief specialist. Her humanitarian work has taken her from Sri Lanka in the wake of the Tsunami to Pakistan and Haiti to help with their post-earthquake recovery.
Jo was born in Washington DC where her father was a diplomat. As a child she enjoyed making things including buildings for her brother’s train set. After graduating from Cambridge University she joined design and engineering firm Arup where her first assignment involved working with Lord Norman Foster on a design for bus shelters.</description></item><item><title>Joanne Harris, writer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930085/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joanne Harris is a writer who is best known for her novel Chocolat, which was made into an Oscar-nominated feature film starring Juliette Binoche and Johnny Depp.
The daughter of an English father and French mother, Joanne was born in Barnsley and her first few years were spent living above her grandparents’ sweet shop. Her parents were both teachers, and her first language was French. She went on to read modern and medieval languages at Cambridge University and taught French for 15 years, writing fiction in her spare time.</description></item><item><title>Peter Schmeichel, footballer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930086/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Peter Schmeichel is widely regarded as one of the greatest goalkeepers in the modern game. In 1999, he captained Manchester United in one of the most astonishing comebacks in football, as United won the Champions League with two goals in added time, completing a much-coveted Treble, along with the Premiership and the FA Cup. As well as winning numerous trophies during his years at Manchester United, he has played a record 129 times for Denmark, his national team.</description></item><item><title>Michael Sandel, philosopher | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930087/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael Sandel is a political philosopher and professor of government theory at Harvard University in Cambridge, Massachusetts. He has also presented the BBC Radio 4 series The Public Philosopher and The Global Philosopher, in which he examines the thinking behind a current controversy.
His books have tackled the idea of meritocracy and the moral limits of markets, and he has been described as a “philosopher with the global profile of a rock star.</description></item><item><title>Deborah Meaden, businesswoman | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930088/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Deborah Meaden is a businesswoman and entrepreneur. She’s been one of the investment ‘Dragons’ in the BBC TV series since 2006. Destined to be a successful entrepreneur, Deborah Meaden launched her first business straight out of college at nineteen years old, importing artisan Italian glass and ceramic homeware goods to the UK. After running various franchise businesses, she joined her family company, Weststar Holidays and eventually became Managing Director.</description></item><item><title>Dame Sarah Connolly, mezzo-soprano | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930089/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930089/</guid><description>Podcast Description The mezzo-soprano Dame Sarah Connolly has sung at the most prestigious venues around the world, including the Royal Opera House, London and the Metropolitan Opera in New York, as well as Glyndebourne, Vienna and Bayreuth. In 2009 she was a soloist at the Last Night of the BBC Proms, singing Rule Britannia dressed as Admiral Nelson, and she has also made a name for herself taking on male or so-called “trouser roles” in opera, including Handel’s Giulio Cesare (Julius Caesar).</description></item><item><title>Tom Ilube, entrepreneur | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930090/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Ilube is an entrepreneur, known for his successful start-up companies, and a philanthropist. He recently took up the post of chairman of the Rugby Football Union. He was born in 1963 to a Nigerian father and a British mother, and grew up first in London, and then in Uganda, a stay cut short by the rise to power of Idi Amin. He began his teenage years back in the UK, enjoying rugby and ice-skating, before moving with his family to Nigeria, where he also attended university, studying Applied Physics and launching his first business selling flared trousers to fellow students.</description></item><item><title>Tracey Ullman, actor and comedian | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930091/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tracey Ullman was the first woman to be offered her own television sketch show – both in Britain and America – and has starred in film and television dramas alongside Meryl Streep, Cate Blanchett and Hugh Grant. The Emmy-winning Tracey Ullman Show ran for four seasons in the US and provided the launch pad for the Simpsons. Tracey was born in Slough and as a child she would impersonate people and put on shows for the amusement of her mother after the death of her father.</description></item><item><title>Baroness Hale of Richmond, former judge | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930092/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brenda Hale, Baroness Hale of Richmond, is a former judge who served as the first female president of the Supreme Court. In 2019 she announced the court’s judgement that the prorogation of Parliament was ‘unlawful, void and of no effect’. The twinkling spider brooch she wore that day caused a sensation and set social media aflame. She was the first woman and the youngest person to be appointed to the Law Commission and in 2004 became the UK’s first woman law lord.</description></item><item><title>Michael Holding, cricketer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930093/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael Holding is a cricket commentator and former West Indies bowler. He’s widely regarded as one of the greatest fast bowlers in the history of international cricket. In July 2020 when rain stopped play during the television coverage of a Test Match, he gave an unscripted four minute monologue on institutional racism in sport and society in the wake of the death of George Floyd. His spontaneous eloquence won him widespread acclaim, including a Royal Television Society award.</description></item><item><title>Nazir Afzal, lawyer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930094/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nazir Afzal is a solicitor and the former chief crown prosecutor for north-west England. Among his notable cases, he brought the Rochdale sex grooming gangs to trial in 2012.
Nazir’s parents arrived in the UK from Pakistan in 1961 and he was born in Birmingham the following year. After completing his legal training he started his career as a defence lawyer but soon realised that he preferred prosecution to defence, joining the Crown Prosecution Service in 1991.</description></item><item><title>Robert Macfarlane, writer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930095/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 10:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Robert Macfarlane is a writer whose books about the natural world, including The Wild Places and The Old Ways, have won many prizes and taken root in the best-seller charts. He was born into a family of enthusiastic amateur climbers and his early memories include being carried up the Cairngorms on his father's back. This childhood experience led to a lifelong passion, and inspired his first book, Mountains of the Mind, about the complex human fascination with mountains.</description></item><item><title>Dame Jessica Ennis-Hill, athlete | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930096/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dame Jessica Ennis-Hill is an Olympic gold medallist and three-time world champion heptathlete, and is one of the most successful women in British sporting history. She was the face of Team GB during the 2012 London Olympics, and her image adorned billboards and hoardings across the country in the run up to the Games.
Born in Sheffield, Jessica discovered sport as a youngster after attending a local athletics camp during the school holidays.</description></item><item><title>Professor Noel Fitzpatrick, veterinary surgeon | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930097/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 11:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Professor Noel Fitzpatrick is a veterinary surgeon who presents the television series The Supervet. He has pushed the boundaries of treatment available to animals and has developed ground breaking surgery including fitting the world’s first bionic leg on a dog.
Noel was born in Ballyfin in Ireland where his father Sean was a farmer. As a very small boy Noel’s job was to count the sheep at night which he credits as the catalyst for his enduring love of animals.</description></item><item><title>Paul Costelloe, fashion designer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930098/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Paul Costelloe is a fashion designer who recently celebrated his 36th year showing at London Fashion Week, making him the event’s longest-standing designer.
Paul was born in Dublin where his father ran a successful company making raincoats. He studied at the Grafton Academy of Fashion Design and then moved to Paris where he started a fashion course at the Chambre Syndicale de la Couture but felt out of his depth and soon dropped out.</description></item><item><title>Margaret Busby, publisher | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930099/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Margaret Busby is a publisher and editor who was the chair of the Booker Prize jury in 2020.
She has spent a life time in the literary world and was the youngest person and first black woman to set up a publishing house when she was twenty three years old. Together with Clive Allison, she created Allison and Busby based in Soho, London.
Margaret was born in Ghana in the 1940s and spent her childhood at a boarding school in the UK whilst her parents ran a medical practice in rural Ghana.</description></item><item><title>Richard Wilson, actor and director | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930100/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Richard Wilson is an actor and director who became a household name when he played the part of Victor Meldrew in the BBC sitcom One Foot in the Grave. Richard was born in Greenock in Scotland in 1936. As a child he performed in amateur drama productions and harboured a secret desire to become an actor. He left school at 17 and trained as a laboratory technician at Stobhill Hospital in Glasgow.</description></item><item><title>Yo-Yo Ma, musician | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930101/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yo-Yo Ma is a cellist and one of the world's most high-profile classical musicians. He has performed for eight US Presidents, appeared in concert halls across the globe and reached new audiences through film soundtracks and TV shows including The Simpsons and Sesame Street. Yo-Yo Ma was born in Paris in 1955. His Chinese-born parents were both musicians and his father was his first cello teacher. The family moved to the USA when Yo-Yo was seven, and a noted child prodigy, playing for John F Kennedy and Leonard Bernstein.</description></item><item><title>Heather Hallett, former judge and crossbench peer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930102/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Heather Hallett, Baroness Hallett of Rye, is a former judge and a cross-bench peer. Called to the Bar in 1972, Heather practised family, civil and criminal law, eventually specialising in criminal law. In 1989 she became a QC and was the first woman to chair the Bar Council in 1998. She was only the fifth woman to be appointed to the Court of Appeal in 2005 and was appointed vice president of the Court of Appeal Criminal Division in 2013.</description></item><item><title>Amanda Khozi Mukwashi, charity CEO | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930103/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amanda Khozi Mukwashi is the chief executive of Christian Aid, leading development and humanitarian work in Africa, Asia and the Middle East, Latin America and the Caribbean.
Amanda was born in Twickenham and grew up in Zambia and Rome where her stepfather worked in the diplomatic service. She studied international trade and investment law at the University of Zambia in Lusaka and during this time she began to develop her political outlook and commitment to the issue of social justice.</description></item><item><title>Alexei Sayle, comedian | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930104/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alexei Sayle is a comedian and writer, who began his career just over 40 years ago at the small Comedy Store venue in London, which proved a launch-pad for a new generation of comic stars. Alexei was born in Liverpool, where his parents were loyal members of the Communist Party: their politics informed almost every aspect of the family’s life, including holidays by train to eastern European countries that were then part of the Soviet bloc.</description></item><item><title>Brian Greene | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930105/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brian Greene is a theoretical physicist, mathematician and writer, whose area of research is string theory. His books and broadcasts distil the complexities of science for a general audience, leading one critic to say appreciatively “he speaks maths, physics and human.”
Born in New York City, his father taught him the basics of arithmetic when he was a toddler and by the time he was five Brian was multiplying 30-digit numbers by 30-digit numbers - just for the pure joy of working things out by himself.</description></item><item><title>Billie Piper, actor | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930106/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 10:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Billie Piper is an Olivier Award winning actor and former pop star.
She was born in Swindon in September 1982, and her parents nurtured her interests in dance and drama from a young age. After a winning a scholarship to study at the Sylvia Young Theatre School, she moved to London as a young teenager, leaving the family home. By the age of 15, she was a full time pop star.</description></item><item><title>Professor Sir Simon Wessely | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930107/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Professor Sir Simon Wessely is the first ever psychiatrist to be awarded a Regius professorship – an honour bestowed by the Queen. He is professor of psychological medicine at the Institute of Psychiatry, Psychology and Neuroscience at King’s College London, and is also a consultant psychiatrist at King’s College Hospital and the Maudsley Hospital. Born in Sheffield to a father who had come to Britain on the Kindertransport, he started his research career working on unexplained symptoms and syndromes, leading progressive and sometimes controversial work on Chronic Fatigue Syndrome.</description></item><item><title>Maggie O'Farrell, writer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930108/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Maggie O’Farrell has written eight novels, a memoir and a children’s book. In 2020 her novel Hamnet won the Women’s Prize for Fiction, and was also named Waterstones Book of the Year.
Maggie was born in Northern Ireland. Her parents moved around during her childhood, and she grew up in Wales and Scotland. As a young girl, she was very ill and almost died from encephalitis. She says her lifelong love of reading comes from her long stay in hospital followed by an extended convalescence, when she missed a year of school.</description></item><item><title>Dame Louise Casey, crossbench peer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930109/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Baroness Casey of Blackstock is a former civil servant specialising in social welfare, who has worked under five prime ministers. She has taken on some of UK society’s most difficult issues, including homelessness, anti-social behaviour and family breakdown, and has become known for her forthright views.
She grew up in Portsmouth and her first job was working on reception at a branch of the Department of Health and Social Security in the late 1980s.</description></item><item><title>Mark Strong, actor | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930110/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 11:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mark Strong has appeared in more than 60 films, along with numerous TV dramas and plays. His career took off after he won a leading role in the landmark 1996 BBC series Our Friends in the North, and since then his screen work includes dramas such as Syriana, Tinker Tailor Soldier Spy, Zero Dark Thirty and The Imitation Game, as well as the fantasy and comic book worlds of Stardust, Kick Ass and Shazam.</description></item><item><title>Claire Horton, charity worker | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930111/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Claire Horton is the former chief executive of Battersea Dogs and Cats Home, and is currently director general of the Commonwealth War Graves Commission.
She joined Battersea in 2010 during its landmark 150th year, spearheading a campaign which transformed the animal rescue service into a UK top 10 charity brand. During her years in charge, income and volunteer numbers quadrupled; new facilities were developed and the charity successfully campaigned for changes in animal welfare legislation.</description></item><item><title>Sophia Loren | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930112/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sophia Loren is the first performer to win the Best Actress Academy Award for a role in a foreign language film. She won in 1962 for her performance in Vittorio De Sica’s film Two Women in which she played a mother trying to protect her 12-year-old daughter in war-torn Italy. In 1991, she picked up a second Oscar when the Academy presented her with an Honorary Award for her contribution to world cinema.</description></item><item><title>Malala Yousafzai, activist | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930113/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Malala Yousafzai is an activist who was awarded the Nobel Peace Prize when she was 17 - becoming the youngest winner in its history. Today she is known globally for her human rights advocacy and her ongoing campaign to ensure all children have equal access to education.
She was born in the Swat Valley in northern Pakistan where her father Ziauddin was a prominent activist who believed boys and girls should sit side by side in the classroom and co-founded a school which Malala attended.</description></item><item><title>George McGavin, entomologist and broadcaster | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930114/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930114/</guid><description>Podcast Description George McGavin is an entomologist, explorer and broadcaster, who has spread the word about the importance of insects to audiences in their millions. Born in Glasgow, he grew up in Edinburgh where he studied zoology at university. Following a PhD in entomology, he went on to teach and research at the University of Oxford. He gave up his post as the assistant curator of the university’s Museum of Natural History after 25 years to follow his dream of becoming a television presenter.</description></item><item><title>Monica Galetti, chef and restaurateur | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930115/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Monica Galetti is a chef, restaurateur and cook book writer, who is also known as a judge on the television series MasterChef: the Professionals.
Born on the island of Upolu in Western Samoa, she grew up on the family plantation where her earliest food memories are of collecting eggs and mangoes and peeling bananas for special suppers. When she was eight she moved to New Zealand where her mother and stepfather had emigrated a couple of years earlier.</description></item><item><title>Tim Peake, astronaut | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930116/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Major Tim Peake, is an Army Air Corps officer and a European Space Agency astronaut. He was the first British astronaut to carry out a spacewalk. As a child, he became interested in aviation, visiting air shows with his father and learning to fly as a teenager, although space travel was not yet a passion. He joined the school Cadet Corps and found he was in his element. From there he progressed to the Royal Military Academy Sandhurst, and then into the Army Air Corps in 1992.</description></item><item><title>Samantha Power | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930117/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Samantha Power was the USA's youngest ever ambassador to the UN, during President Barack Obama’s second term, and is a writer and academic. She has just been invited to join president-elect Joe Biden's administration. Samantha was born in London but grew up in Ireland. At the age of nine, she moved to the US with her mother and younger brother following the breakdown of her parents’ marriage. Her first ambition was to be a sports broadcaster, but watching live footage of events in Tiananmen Square in 1989 led her to change course and she became a war correspondent instead, reporting on the conflict in Bosnia in the early 1990s.</description></item><item><title>David Olusoga, historian and broadcaster | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930118/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930118/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Olusoga is a historian, writer and broadcaster who has presented a range of programmes including the BBC’s A House Through Time and Civilisations. He is currently professor of public history at Manchester University.
Born in Lagos, the second child to a Nigerian father and a British mother, David was brought up by his mother in Gateshead after his parents’ marriage broke down. As a child he and his siblings experienced sustained racism and he remembers school as a place of violence and cruelty.</description></item><item><title>Colonel Lucy Giles | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930119/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Colonel Lucy Giles is an officer of the British Army’s Royal Logistic Corps and is currently President of the Army Officer Selection Board - the first woman to take on this role. After attending her local comprehensive school in Wincanton, Somerset, she studied Biological Sciences at Exeter University where she joined the University Officers’ Training Corps, despite having no military background herself.
After what she calls a “retrospective year out”, she joined the last female-only company at the Royal Military Academy Sandhurst and was commissioned into the Royal Corps of Transport in 1992, which became the Royal Logistic Corps the following year.</description></item><item><title>Sir Cliff Richard | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930120/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sir Cliff Richard makes a second trip to the island he first visited 60 years ago, when he had just turned 20, but had already topped the UK charts three times. Over the course of his career, Sir Cliff has released over 100 albums and sold well over 250 million records. His chart success in the UK has been eclipsed only by his hero Elvis Presley and one-time rivals, the Beatles.</description></item><item><title>Minette Batters | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930121/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Minette Batters is the first woman to become President of the National Farmers' Union, representing 47,000 members. She was first elected to the post in 2018 for two years, and was re-elected in March 2020. Minette runs a tenanted family farm in Wiltshire. The mixed farming business includes cattle, sheep and arable, as well as the conversion of a 17th century barn into a wedding and events venue. Her father was a tenant farmer, and Minette adored helping him as a youngster, but the idea of taking on the farm herself seemed out of the question: her father strongly advised against it.</description></item><item><title>Professor Sir Jeremy Farrar | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930122/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Professor Sir Jeremy Farrar is Director of the Wellcome Trust, a global charitable foundation which funds scientific research. He is a member of Sage, the scientific group currently advising the government on Covid-19.
He is the youngest of six children and was born in Singapore. His mother was an artist and his father was a teacher, who worked around the world, and the family lived in New Zealand, Cyprus and Libya.</description></item><item><title>Helen Oxenbury | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930123/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Helen Oxenbury is an illustrator of children’s books whose work has featured in many very popular titles for younger readers including the award-winning We’re Going on a Bear Hunt, by Michael Rosen.
Helen has won the Kate Greenaway Medal twice and was awarded a lifetime achievement award by the Book Trust in 2018. She attended the Ipswich School of Art and later the Central School of Art in London where she met fellow illustrator and her future husband, John Burningham.</description></item><item><title>Arsène Wenger, former football manager | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930124/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Arsène Wenger was the manager of Arsenal FC for 22 years, becoming the longest-serving and most successful manager in the club’s history. He was born in Strasbourg in 1949 and grew up as the youngest of three children in the nearby village of Duttlenheim, where his parents ran a bistro. There he listened in to the daily conversations about football, which preoccupied the men of the village.
After playing for his local team and studying for a degree in economics, Arsène made a career as a footballer in France for a decade, before moving into management.</description></item><item><title>Sir Keir Starmer, Leader of the Opposition | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930125/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sir Keir Starmer is the leader of the Labour Party, and the leader of the opposition.
Named after Keir Hardie, a founding father of the Labour party, he was elected leader seven months ago in the wake of Labour’s heavy defeat in the 2019 general election. He stood for, and won, the leadership on a platform of party unity but his resolve has been tested recently by factionalism and infighting.</description></item><item><title>David Mitchell, novelist | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930126/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930126/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Mitchell has published eight novels, two of which – number9dream and Cloud Atlas – have been shortlisted for the Booker Prize. He has also translated two books on autism from Japanese, working with his Japanese wife: their son is on the autistic spectrum. While his work also includes writing for the screen and opera libretti, his main occupation has been, as one critic put it, “quietly pottering away at the frontier of fiction” for more than two decades.</description></item><item><title>Hilary McGrady, Director General of the National Trust | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930127/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hilary McGrady is Director General of the National Trust.
She was born in Lisburn, Northern Ireland, in 1966, where her father was a builder while her mother looked after Hilary and her two older siblings. She spent her childhood roaming the fields near her home, 20 miles outside Belfast. She went to art college after school where she met her husband, Frank. Their relationship initially caused difficulty for her family who were staunch Protestants and unionists, while Frank’s came from a Catholic, nationalist area.</description></item><item><title>Chris Boardman, cyclist | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930128/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris Boardman is an Olympic cyclist, businessman and the Cycling and Walking Commissioner for Greater Manchester. Both his parents were keen competitive amateur cyclists and they backed Chris as he gradually became interested in the sport as a teenager. He left school at 16, and trained as a carpenter to fund his cycling, and his love of making things has never left him. He met his wife Sally when they were teenagers and she supported him when he took time off work to train and compete.</description></item><item><title>Professor Averil Mansfield, retired surgeon | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930129/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Averil Mansfield is a retired vascular surgeon and was the first female Professor of Surgery in the UK when she was appointed in 1993.
She was born in 1937 in Blackpool, where her father worked as a welder on the attractions at the Pleasure Beach. She was an only child and an avid reader when young. After perusing a library book on early advances in surgery, she decided, at the age of eight, that she wanted to become a surgeon.</description></item><item><title>Baroness Floella Benjamin, DBE | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930130/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 09:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Baroness Floella Benjamin DBE is a Trinidadian-British broadcaster, writer and politician. She became a familiar face to millions of viewers through her work on children's television, most notably on Play School, which she first presented in 1976. She was born in Trinidad in 1949, the second of six children. When her parents emigrated to the UK, she and her siblings were initially left behind with foster parents. After 16 months, the family was able to reunite, when the children travelled to England by sea.</description></item><item><title>Samantha Morton, actor | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930131/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Samantha Morton is an actor and director. She has appeared in films directed by Woody Allen and Steven Spielberg, and is also known for her work on independent productions, often with serious themes such as prostitution and bereavement. She has been nominated for two Academy Awards and won many accolades including a BAFTA and a Golden Globe.
Born in Nottingham in 1977, she had a difficult childhood. She was first taken into care as a baby, then spent the next decade between foster parents and her father’s home before being taken into care permanently at the age of 11.</description></item><item><title>Yusuf Cat Stevens, musician | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930132/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2020 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yusuf Cat Stevens is a singer-songwriter who first enjoyed success more than 50 years ago. He was born Steven Demetre Georgiou in July 1948. His Greek Cypriot father and his Swedish mother ran a restaurant in the West End of London, and he helped out there from an early age. He also became interested in music, writing and singing his own songs, partly inspired by the success of The Beatles.</description></item><item><title>Bernardine Evaristo, writer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930133/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bernardine Evaristo won the Booker Prize in 2019 for her novel, Girl, Woman, Other. She is Professor of Creative Writing at Brunel University London.
Bernardine was born in May 1959, the fourth of eight children, to an English mother and a Nigerian father. She grew up in Woolwich in south London, and was educated at Eltham Hill Girls’ Grammar School. She spent her teenage years at the Greenwich Young People’s Theatre and, after deciding that she wanted to be a professional actor at the age of 14, did a Community Theatre Arts course at the Rose Bruford College of Speech and Drama.</description></item><item><title>Your Desert Island Discs | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930134/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Listeners choose the music that has been special to them during the weeks of lockdown. With Jane Moss, Hugh Mullally, Ailish Douglas, Professor Jason Warren, Niti Acharya, Margery Hookings, Simon Spiller, Clare Raybould and Garry Greenland.
DISC ONE: Amazing Grace by Judy Collins DISC TWO: Who Knows Where The Time Goes? by Sandy Denny
DISC THREE: The Whole of The Moon by The Waterboys DISC FOUR: Heimweh op. 57 Nr.</description></item><item><title>Maria Balshaw, Director of Tate | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930135/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Maria Balshaw is the Director of Tate, overseeing four major art galleries: Tate Britain, Tate Liverpool, Tate Modern and Tate St Ives.
Maria was born in 1970 in Birmingham, and grew up in Northampton, where her father, Walter, was a parks officer, and her mother, Colette, was a teacher. She read English and Cultural Studies at the University of Liverpool and fell in love with the newly opened Tate Liverpool at Albert Dock.</description></item><item><title>Steve Backshall, explorer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930136/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Steve Backshall is an explorer, naturalist and broadcaster. His BAFTA-winning programmes bring viewers of every generation closer to nature – from the children's series Deadly 60, featuring close encounters with the most dangerous and venomous creatures on earth, to Blue Planet Live and Springwatch.
His interest in the natural world began at a young age, after his parents decided to swap their terraced house for a smallholding with goats, ducks and geese.</description></item><item><title>Sharon Horgan, writer, actor, producer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930137/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sharon Horgan is a writer, actor and producer best known for co-writing and co-starring in the Channel 4 series Catastrophe with US comedian Rob Delaney.
Sharon was born in 1970 in east London, where her parents Ursula and John were running a pub. They moved to Ireland when Sharon was three and eventually set themselves up as turkey farmers. Sharon went to a convent school, then art college in Dublin, before moving to London in 1990, hoping to become an actor.</description></item><item><title>Annie Nightingale, DJ | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930138/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930138/</guid><description>Podcast Description Annie Nightingale was BBC Radio 1’s first female presenter and is its longest-serving DJ, celebrating her 50th anniversary at the station this year.
Born and brought up in south west London, she fell in love with the romance and mystery of radio through her father’s meticulous tuning of their home set to broadcasts from exotic places like Prague and Hilversum. On leaving school at 17, she spent a year on a journalism course in central London.</description></item><item><title>Jens Stoltenberg, Secretary General of NATO | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930139/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jens Stoltenberg is the Secretary General of NATO and a former Prime Minister of Norway. Although he was born into a political family in Norway, he grew up thinking he would become a statistician, before turning to a career in politics. He served as the Prime Minister of Norway twice. During his second term, Norway experienced one of the darkest days in its recent history, when 77 people were murdered in a bomb attack in Oslo and a mass shooting on a nearby island.</description></item><item><title>Helen Fielding, author | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930140/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Helen Fielding, writer and journalist, is best known for creating Bridget Jones, who first appeared in a newspaper column in the Independent in 1995, in the form of a diary detailing the single 30-something’s exploits in London as she tried to make sense of life and love. The column soon acquired a wider following, and Helen turned Bridget’s story into a best-selling book the following year.
Born in 1958, Helen grew up in Yorkshire with an older sister and two younger brothers.</description></item><item><title>Helen McCrory, actress | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930141/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2020 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Helen McCrory shares the eight tracks, book and luxury she would want to take with her if cast away to a desert island. Helen McCrory OBE is one of the most versatile and critically acclaimed actresses working today. On screen she has played Anna Karenina, Cherie Blair (twice), Harry Potter's Narcissa Malfoy and the Peaky Blinders matriarch Aunt Polly. Her theatre roles range from Yelena in Uncle Vanya to Euripides' Medea.</description></item><item><title>Mark Johnston, racehorse trainer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930142/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Racehorse trainer Mark Johnston is a lynchpin of British flat racing. In August 2018 - when 20-1 shot Poet's Society, ridden by Frankie Dettori, streaked to victory at York - Mark became the most prolific winning trainer in British racing history, saddling 4,194 winners. Based in a 300-acre training yard in Yorkshire, he has never trained fewer than 100 winners each season for the last 26 years including champions such as Attraction, Mister Baileys, Double Trigger and Shamardal.</description></item><item><title>Joe Wicks, fitness trainer and author | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930143/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joe Wicks, professionally known as The Body Coach, is a fitness and nutrition coach. Since the lockdown, he has been running daily free virtual PE lessons for children and adults stuck at home. In March he became a Guinness World Record holder after his second PE with Joe class was watched by 955,158 people around the world, a record number of viewers for a live streamed YouTube workout. Getting children to be more active has been a long-held ambition and in 2019 he went on a tour of fifteen schools around the UK delivering High Intensity Interval Training workouts as part of his mission to get school children working out for 15 minutes a day.</description></item><item><title>Martin Lewis, financial campaigner | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930144/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930144/</guid><description>Podcast Description Martin Lewis is a financial journalist, campaigner and broadcaster. His high-profile campaigns on bank charges, student finance, and mental health and debt have made headlines, and millions of people subscribe to his weekly money tips email. He founded the Money Saving Expert website in 2003 with just £100 and sold it less than a decade later for £87 million, although he calls himself an 'accidental entrepreneur'. He has since supported numerous groups and causes through charitable donations, most recently setting up a Coronavirus Poverty Emergency Fund to help small local charities.</description></item><item><title>Professor Dame Elizabeth Anionwu, former nurse | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930145/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Elizabeth Anionwu is a retired nurse, campaigner and Emeritus Professor of Nursing at the University of West London. A fellow of the Royal College of Nursing, she spent 40 years in the profession and has been named one of the most influential nurses in the history of the NHS. Her career was distinguished by her pioneering work in the understanding of sickle cell disease - bringing better treatment and support to the thousands living with it.</description></item><item><title>Charles Hazlewood, conductor | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930146/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Charles Hazlewood is a conductor and the founder of Paraorchestra, the world's first professional ensemble of disabled musicians. Once described as the Heston Blumenthal of orchestral music, Charles has spent his career challenging Britain’s musical palate, exploding boundaries and expanding our ideas about what an orchestra can be - and do. His repertoire encompasses Beethoven, Bruckner and Barry White, and his critically-acclaimed projects include more than 100 world premieres and the first orchestral headline performance at Glastonbury.</description></item><item><title>Sinead Burke, disability rights activist and teacher | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930147/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sinead Burke is a disability rights activist and teacher. She has combined her love of education and style to campaign for more representation of diversity in the fashion industry. Born in Dublin, Sinead has achondroplasia – a genetic condition which causes restricted growth – and is 3’ 5” tall. She refers to herself as a “little person” and knew she wanted to be a teacher after her first day at school.</description></item><item><title>Simon Armitage, Poet Laureate | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930148/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Simon Armitage was appointed Poet Laureate in 2019. His poems celebrate the everyday and the ordinary with wit and affection. But beyond the wood chip and washing lines he addresses the complexities and the profound feelings that underpin daily life. Born in Huddersfield, Simon Armitage grew up in the village of Marsden in West Yorkshire. Marsden has informed and inspired much of his work and as a boy he would look out of his bedroom window at night to watch the comings and goings of village life.</description></item><item><title>Brian Cox, actor | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930149/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brian Cox CBE is a Scottish actor whose career spans almost 60 years, from his early days sweeping the stage at his local theatre in Dundee to his current Golden Globe-winning role as the media patriarch Logan Roy in the HBO series Succession. He has appeared in more than 100 films, many television series, and has won two Olivier awards for his work on stage. Brian Cox was born in 1946, the youngest of five children, and grew up in a working-class household in Dundee.</description></item><item><title>Dame Helena Morrissey, financier and campaigner | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930150/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dame Helena Morrissey is a former City fund manager and chief executive of a major investment company, who has also campaigned to boost the number of women in the boardroom. Newspapers regularly describe her as 'Superwoman', because alongside her many professional achievements, she's the mother of nine children. Helena Morrissey is the daughter of two teachers, and her drive was evident from an early age. She was - by her own admission - a 'manic Brownie', striving to gain the maximum number of badges, and she also played the piano to a high standard.</description></item><item><title>Daniel Radcliffe, actor | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930151/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Daniel Radcliffe reached a global audience in the title role of the hugely successful Harry Potter films. He has also appeared on Broadway and in the West End, as well as in over a dozen films since the final part of the Harry Potter series was released in 2011. Born in 1989, the only child of Alan and Marcia Radcliffe, Daniel made his acting debut aged 10 in a BBC adaptation of David Copperfield.</description></item><item><title>Chris Riddell, illustrator, author and political cartoonist | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930152/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris Riddell is an illustrator, author of children’s books and a political cartoonist. From 2015 to 2017, he was the Children’s Laureate, and he has won three Greenaway Medals for his work – more than any other illustrator.
He was born in 1962 in Cape Town, South Africa, where his parents were both anti-apartheid activists. They moved to the UK when Chris was a year old. He grew up first in rural England, and later in south London where his father, a vicar, became chaplain of Brixton Prison.</description></item><item><title>Dorothy Byrne, journalist | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930153/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930153/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dorothy Byrne is the head of News and Current Affairs at Channel 4, and has worked in journalism for more than four decades. In 2018 she received the Outstanding Contribution Award at Royal Television Society Journalism Awards, and her recent commissions include the Channel 4 News investigation into Cambridge Analytica, the Michael Jackson expose Leaving Neverland and the BAFTA-winning documentary For Sama, about one family’s life under siege in Aleppo, which also won an Oscar nomination.</description></item><item><title>Melanie C | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930154/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Melanie Chisholm - known as Melanie C - is a singer and songwriter who found global fame as one fifth of the Spice Girls, the most commercially successful female group ever. Melanie was one of 400 other hopefuls who answered an advertisement to form a new girl band in 1994 - little knowing how her life would be turned upside down by fame and worldwide success. She was given the nickname Sporty Spice and presented what she calls a "</description></item><item><title>Ian Wright, former footballer and broadcaster | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930155/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ian Wright is a former professional footballer and now a football pundit on TV and radio. He began his career at Crystal Palace before moving to Arsenal where he became their highest goal scorer of all time, a record only surpassed eight years later by Thierry Henry.
Born to a Jamaican couple in south-east London, Ian grew up with his mother and step-father. His biological father had left the family when Ian was under two years old.</description></item><item><title>Zoe Ball, broadcaster | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930156/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Zoe Ball is a radio and television presenter. She became the first woman to present the BBC Radio 1 Breakfast Show in 1997, and then the first woman to present the Radio 2 Breakfast Show in 2019. Zoe grew up in Buckinghamshire with her father – TV presenter Johnny Ball – and her stepmother. After working behind the scenes in TV as a runner and researcher, she first moved into the spotlight hosting children's programmes, including the very successful BBC Saturday morning show Live &amp;amp; Kicking, with Jamie Theakston.</description></item><item><title>Sonita Alleyne, Master of Jesus College, Cambridge | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930157/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930157/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sonita Alleyne is the Master of Jesus College, Cambridge, the first woman to hold the post and - more significantly - the first black master of any Oxbridge college. In her previous career in the media, she was the co-founder and former CEO of the production company Somethin’ Else. Born in Barbados, she came to England aged three and grew up in East London, the youngest of three children.</description></item><item><title>Anne Enright, writer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930158/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930158/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anne Enright won the Booker Prize for her fourth novel, The Gathering, in 2007, and was appointed the inaugural Laureate for Irish Fiction in 2015. She has written seven novels, two collections of short stories and a book of essays about motherhood and her work has been widely translated. Born in Dublin in 1962, Anne is the youngest of five children. She was a voracious reader from an early age, finishing every children's book at her local library.</description></item><item><title>Dame Sue Campbell, Director Women's Football at the FA | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930159/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dame Sue Campbell is the Director of Women’s Football at the Football Association. The women’s game has become increasingly popular recently and last year the England team - the Lionesses - made it to the World Cup semi-finals.
Born in 1948, just outside Nottingham, Sue was sporty from an early age, even changing schools to allow her to play football. She became a PE teacher in Manchester and realised how transformative sport could be, increasing self-esteem, motivation and self-belief.</description></item><item><title>Michael Lewis, writer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930160/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930160/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael Lewis is a best-selling non-fiction writer and journalist. He initially worked for an investment bank, and his experiences of Wall Street excess in the 1980s informed his acclaimed first book, Liar’s Poker. Three of his later books – Moneyball, The Blind Side and The Big Short – have been adapted into Hollywood feature films. He was born in New Orleans in 1960, where his father was fond of quoting the family motto: 'Do as little as possible, and that unwillingly, for it is better to receive a light reprimand than perform an arduous task.</description></item><item><title>Rupert Everett, actor | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930161/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 12:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930161/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rupert Everett is an actor, writer and director whose breakthrough came in 1981 when he was cast as a gay schoolboy in Another Country, Julian Mitchell's play and subsequent film. Rupert later starred in Dance with a Stranger before making a splash in Hollywood playing Julia Roberts's gay confidante in My Best Friend's Wedding. But his movie career took a dive after The Next Best Thing - in which he played the gay father of Madonna's baby - flopped.</description></item><item><title>Stephen Merchant, writer, comedian and actor | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930162/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930162/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stephen Merchant first came to fame with the TV sitcom The Office, which he co-wrote and co-directed with Ricky Gervais. He continued to work with Gervais on the series Extras, Life is Short and An Idiot Abroad. His comedy hero as a young man was John Cleese and as a fellow tall West Country boy, he felt he would try his hand at a comedy career. As a teenager, he worked at Radio Bristol, was a wedding DJ and enjoyed drama at school.</description></item><item><title>Heidi Thomas, screenwriter | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930163/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Heidi Thomas is a screenwriter and playwright best known for Call the Midwife. The BBC TV series, which began in 2012, was originally a six part adaptation of a trilogy of memoirs by Jennifer Worth, recalling her experiences as a midwife in the East End of London. It was an immediate hit, with 10 million viewers a week, becoming one of BBC One’s most popular dramas and a fixture in the Christmas schedules.</description></item><item><title>Professor Russell Foster, professor of circadian neuroscience | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930164/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930164/</guid><description>Podcast Description Professor Russell Foster is head of the Sleep and Circadian Neuroscience Institute at the University of Oxford, professor of circadian neuroscience and the director of the Nuffield Laboratory of Ophthalmology. An expert in sleep, he describes it as 'the single most important health behaviour we have'. Born in 1959, as a child he loved his toy microscope and digging up fossils. Despite being labelled “entirely non-academic” by his headmaster and attending remedial classes for some years, he achieved three science A levels which won him a place at the University of Bristol.</description></item><item><title>Asif Kapadia, film director | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930165/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Asif Kapadia is an Academy Award-winning film director, renowned for his documentaries about the musician Amy Winehouse, the Brazilian motor racing star Ayrton Senna, and the Argentinian footballer, Diego Maradona.
Born in 1972, Asif is the youngest of five children. His parents emigrated from Gujarat in the mid-1960s. His father’s ambition to seek his fortune took the family to the US for a short time in the late 70s, but by 1980 they had returned to London.</description></item><item><title>Isabella Tree, writer and conservationist | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930166/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930166/</guid><description>Podcast Description Isabella Tree is a conservationist and writer of the award-winning book Wilding: the Return of Nature to a British Farm, which tells the story of rewilding a 3,500 acre farm estate in Sussex, which she oversaw with her husband Charlie. The adopted daughter of Michael Tree and Lady Anne Cavendish, Isabella grew up in Mereworth Castle in Kent, and then in Shute House, a vicarage in Dorset. Following her expulsion from two secondary schools, she attended Millfield School as a sixth former, where mutual friends introduced her to her future husband.</description></item><item><title>Stephen Graham, actor | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930167/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stephen Graham is an actor, whose credits include key roles in films including This is England and The Irishman, and in TV dramas such as Boardwalk Empire and Line of Duty. Stephen was born in Kirkby just outside Liverpool in 1973. He discovered acting at school, where a starring role in a production of Treasure Island at the age of 10 was a turning point: local actor Andrew Schofield was in the audience and suggested that Stephen should join the Everyman Youth Theatre in Liverpool.</description></item><item><title>Lauren Laverne picks some of her favourite episodes | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930168/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 17:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hear stories &amp;amp; track choices from castaways including Len Goodman, Maya Angelou and Stephen Hawking.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kimberley Motley, lawyer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930169/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 11:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kimberley Motley is an American attorney and the first foreign lawyer to practise in Afghanistan.
Born in 1975 to an African-American father and a North Korean mother, she grew up in a poor neighbourhood in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, where hers was the only mixed-race family - and the only family with two parents. Education was very important to her parents, who sent their four children to private schools and also paid for extra tutoring.</description></item><item><title>Russell T Davies, screenwriter | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930170/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Russell T Davies is one of the U.K.’s most successful television writers. He spent his teenage years learning his dramatic craft with the West Glamorgan Youth Theatre, and his career in television began in the children’s department at the BBC.
His first solo hit TV series was the ground-breaking, sexually frank drama Queer as Folk, first broadcast on Channel 4 in 1999.
A lifelong Doctor Who fan, he relaunched the series in 2005 for a new generation of viewers.</description></item><item><title>Wendell Pierce, actor | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930171/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930171/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wendell Pierce is an American actor best known for his role as Bunk Moreland in the television series The Wire. Since the series ended in 2008, he has made around 40 film and television appearances, including Treme, Selma and the legal drama Suits, in which he played Robert Zane, the father of Rachel Zane, played by Meghan Markle. His theatre credits range from The Cherry Orchard to Death of a Salesman.</description></item><item><title>Dame Glenys Stacey, former Chief Inspector of Probation | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930172/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dame Glenys Stacey has spent 40 years in public service, including high profile work as a regulator in key areas of national life. She has just stepped down after her five year term as Her Majesty’s Chief Inspector of Probation during which she criticised the decision to privatise the Probation service calling it “irredeemably flawed”. Glenys was born in Walsall Wood in the West Midlands, where her father was a painter and decorator for the council and her mother worked full time in Union Locks.</description></item><item><title>Baroness Arminka Helić | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930173/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930173/</guid><description>Podcast Description Baroness Arminka Helić is credited with persuading William Hague, the former foreign secretary, and the actor and director Angelina Jolie to launch the Preventing Sexual Violence in Conflict Initiative (PSVI) to campaign against rape as a weapon of war.
Born in Bosnia-Herzegovina, Arminka fled her home country as violence escalated in the former Yugoslavia and her family appeared on a Serbian death list. Following the intervention of Lady Miloska Nott, wife of the former secretary of state for defence Sir John Nott, she arrived in London as a refugee in October 1992.</description></item><item><title>Lin-Manuel Miranda, composer &amp; lyricist | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930174/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930174/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lin-Manuel Miranda is best known as the composer, lyricist and original star of the multi-award-winning Broadway musical, Hamilton. It won the 2016 Pulitzer Prize in Drama, 11 Tony Awards and Grammy for Best Musical Theatre Album. The London production won seven Olivier Awards in 2018. Lin-Manuel was brought up in New York by his Puerto Rican parents, and his creativity and sensitivity to music began when he was a child: he performed in Gilbert and Sullivan’s Pirates of Penzance as a teenager and created films using his father’s camcorder.</description></item><item><title>Sabrina Cohen-Hatton, firefighter | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930175/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930175/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr Sabrina Cohen-Hatton is the Chief Fire Officer for West Sussex Fire and Rescue Service. She is one of the most senior women in the Fire and Rescue Service in the UK. After spending some time living on the streets as a teenager, her work as a firefighter began at the age of 18, after she had applied to 31 different fire services. During her career, her interest in psychology and fascination with how people make choices in stressful situations led to her studying for a degree, followed by a PhD.</description></item><item><title>Thom Yorke, musician | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930176/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930176/</guid><description>Podcast Description Thom Yorke has been the front man of Radiohead, one of Britain’s most successful British bands, for 34 years. They have sold over 30 million albums worldwide, and have won three Grammys and four Ivor Novello awards. Their debut studio album, Pablo Honey, was released in 1993, with their debut single, Creep, becoming a big international success. Thom decided on his career at the age of seven, when he lay on the floor between large speakers at a friend’s house and listened to Queen’s Bohemian Rhapsody.</description></item><item><title>Jo Fairley, businesswoman | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930177/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930177/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jo Fairley is a businesswoman and writer. She co-founded the Green &amp;amp; Black’s chocolate company with Craig Sams, her husband, and has launched several other successful ventures since then.
Jo did not enjoy school, left at 16 with six O-levels and learned shorthand and typing at a secretarial college. She got a job with a magazine publisher and worked her way up through the features department to become the UK’s youngest magazine editor at the age of 23.</description></item><item><title>Sir Tim Waterstone, businessman | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930178/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930178/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sir Tim Waterstone is the founder of the bookshop chain that bears his name. Born in May 1939, he was the youngest of three children. His father, who worked for a tea company all his life, served in the Royal Army Service Corps during the war, and so was absent when Tim was very young. Their relationship was difficult throughout his childhood. Tim was educated at boarding schools from the age of six, when his parents went to India for two and a half years.</description></item><item><title>Dame Sally Davies, chief medical officer, England | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930179/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dame Sally Davies is the outgoing Chief Medical Officer for England. She will take up her next post as Master of Trinity College, Cambridge, later this year. She was born in Birmingham in 1949 to academic parents - her father was an Anglican priest and theologian, her mother a scientist. She studied medicine at Manchester University and after two 'brutalising' years spent learning the job on the wards, she welcomed the opportunity to move to Madrid as a diplomat’s wife.</description></item><item><title>John Cooper Clarke, poet | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930180/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930180/</guid><description>Podcast Description John Cooper Clarke first achieved fame with his poetry during the punk rock era of the late 1970s. Born in Salford in 1949 to Hilda and George, he suffered from tuberculosis as a child and was sent to recuperate with a relative in Wales. He failed his 11 plus exam and was educated at a secondary modern school which he hated. However the one “rose in a garden of weeds” was his English teacher, Mr Malone, who instilled a love of poetry in John and his classmates.</description></item><item><title>Marcus Wareing, chef | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930181/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marcus Wareing is a prize-winning chef, restaurateur, TV presenter and cookery book writer, who gained his first Michelin star at the age of just 26. He grew up in Southport, and by the age of 11 was helping out in his family’s fruit and vegetable business, which dominated his father’s life. Marcus assumed he would join the business, but his father told him to take a catering course instead, as the family firm had no future.</description></item><item><title>Sue Biggs, DG Royal Horticultural Society | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930182/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930182/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sue Biggs is the Director General of the Royal Horticultural Society. She’s been at the helm of the RHS since 2010 and during that time, its membership has grown to more than half a million people. The RHS is also renowned for its spectacular flower shows and garden festivals around the country, including Chelsea, Hampton Court, Chatsworth House and Tatton Park. Sue has had a lifelong love of gardening since her mum gave her a packet of seeds on her seventh birthday.</description></item><item><title>Jared Diamond, academic and author | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930183/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930183/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jared Diamond is Professor of Geography at the University of California, Los Angeles, although his interests and expertise range far wider, from physiology to ornithology, history to ecology and from anthropology to evolutionary biology. His 1997 book, Guns, Germs and Steel, asked why Eurasian civilizations prospered and conquered others. It won a Pulitzer Prize and has sold more than a million copies around the world. He was born in Boston in 1937 to a physician father and a mother who was a teacher and a concert pianist.</description></item><item><title>Emily Eavis | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930184/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930184/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily Eavis is co-organiser of the Glastonbury Festival. Together with her husband and her father, she masterminds the booking of bands and oversees the setting up of what is the largest greenfield festival in the world. The site itself becomes the size of Oxford town centre once it’s built and rigged, and when tickets for 2019 went on sale, they sold out within 36 minutes.
Born in 1979, she was a small child when her parents, Jean and Michael, were inspired to make the Glastonbury Festival an annual event, although she wasn’t keen on the yearly invasion of the family farm.</description></item><item><title>Nitin Sawhney, musician, producer, composer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930185/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930185/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nitin Sawhney is a composer, musician and producer working in the worlds of music, film, video games, dance and theatre. He has released 10 studio albums, scored over 50 films and television programmes, and is known for his collaborations, with musicians and artists including Paul McCartney, Akram Khan, John Hurt and Andy Serkis. He was born in 1964 to parents who had emigrated from North India the previous year to work in the UK.</description></item><item><title>Professor Monica McWilliams, social scientist | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930186/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930186/</guid><description>Podcast Description Professor Monica McWilliams is an academic, peace campaigner and former politician. In 1996, she was the co-founder of the Northern Ireland Women’s Coalition political party and was elected to a seat at the Multi-Party Peace Negotiations, which led to the Belfast (Good Friday) Peace Agreement in 1998. She served as a member of the Northern Ireland Legislative Assembly from 1998-2003 and was the Chief Commissioner of the Northern Ireland Human Rights Commission from 2005-2011.</description></item><item><title>Lubaina Himid, artist | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930187/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930187/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lubaina Himid is a Turner Prize-winning artist, curator and Professor of Contemporary Art at the University of Central Lancashire. Lubaina was born in Zanzibar in 1954. Her mother was from Britain and her father was originally from the Comoros Islands. He died from malaria when Lubaina was just a few months old, and so she and her mother returned to England. She studied Theatre Design at the Wimbledon College of Art and began organising exhibitions of works by fellow black women artists in the early 1980s as part of the Black Art Movement.</description></item><item><title>Derren Brown, illusionist | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930188/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930188/</guid><description>Podcast Description Derren Brown, illusionist and mentalist, chooses the eight tracks, book and luxury he want to take with him if cast away to a desert island. BOOK CHOICE: Collected works of Carl Jung
LUXURY: Leica Camera CASTAWAY'S FAVOURITE: Goldberg Variations
Presenter: Lauren Laverne
Producer: Sarah Taylor
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Pat McGrath, makeup artist | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930189/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930189/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pat McGrath is a renowned make-up artist. She works with the world’s top designers, photographers, editors and models, creating images for the pages of the world’s most glamorous magazines. She and her team also work at the most high-profile catwalk shows in Milan, London, New York and Paris. She born and brought up in Northampton by her mother, who had a passion for fashion and make-up, which she passed onto Pat.</description></item><item><title>Louis Theroux | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930190/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930190/</guid><description>Podcast Description Louis Theroux is a television documentary maker. He has received two BAFTAs and a Royal Television Society Award for his work which includes the series Louis Theroux’s Weird Weekends and When Louis Met…
Born in 1970, and brought up in south London, he is the son of the American writer Paul Theroux and the BBC World Service radio producer Anne Castle. He was privately educated at Westminster School and read History at Oxford, graduating with a first.</description></item><item><title>Martin Freeman, actor | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930191/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930191/</guid><description>Podcast Description Martin Freeman is a multi-award winning actor, best known for his roles as the lovable Tim in BBC Two’s The Office and as Dr Watson to Benedict Cumberbatch’s Sherlock Holmes. He also played Bilbo Baggins in Peter Jackson’s Hobbit trilogy, Lester Nygaard in the US drama series Fargo and Everett K Ross in the film Black Panther.
Born in Hampshire in 1971, he grew up in Teddington in south-west London.</description></item><item><title>Jacqueline de Rojas, President of techUK | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930192/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930192/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lauren Laverne’s castaway this week is Jacqueline de Rojas, the President of techUK, the body that represents 900 companies in the technology sector. She is Chair of the Board of Digital Leaders, co-Chair of the Institute of Coding and sits on the government’s Digital Economy Council. She was born Jacqueline Yu in Kent to a Chinese father and British mother, and moved to Swindon when her mother left the marriage.</description></item><item><title>Marlon James, writer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930193/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930193/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marlon James is a writer who won the Man Booker Prize in 2015 for A Brief History of Seven Killings, a novel which centres on an attempt to assassinate Bob Marley. Marlon was the first Jamaican to win the Prize. He was born in Kingston in 1970 and grew up in suburbia. His mother worked as a detective, and his father was lawyer, leading to a family joke that his mum locked criminals up and his dad got them out.</description></item><item><title>Dame Esther Rantzen, broadcaster and campaigner | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930194/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930194/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dame Esther Rantzen is best known as the presenter of the long-running TV series That’s Life, which began on BBC One in 1973. She was both presenter and producer of the programme, which was hugely successful, regularly reaching 20 million viewers. It featured consumer affairs, vox pops and light-hearted pieces about talking dogs and peculiarly shaped vegetables, along with serious investigations, including reports on the safety of children’s playgrounds and on child abuse.</description></item><item><title>Trevor Sorbie, hairdresser | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930195/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930195/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trevor Sorbie is known as an innovative hairdresser and is the founder of the charity, MyNewHair. Born into a family of hairdressers – both his father and grandfather were barbers – he spent the first decade of his life in Scotland before the family relocated to Essex. His first ambition was to become an artist, but when he left school aged 15 with no qualifications after being bullied, his father suggested that he could help out at his barbershop.</description></item><item><title>Margaret MacMillan, historian | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930196/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930196/</guid><description>Podcast Description Professor Margaret MacMillan is a Canadian historian, author and broadcaster. In 2018 she delivered the Reith Lectures on BBC Radio 4, in which she examined the tangled history of war and society. She was born in Toronto in 1943, and her interest in history was kindled by the stories her parents told about when they were young and by the historical adventure novels she read as a child. After a long academic career in Canada, she found herself in the international spotlight in her late 50s.</description></item><item><title>Ann Cleeves, writer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930197/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930197/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ann Cleeves is a crime writer best known for two series of novels, both of which have been adapted for television. Vera, for ITV, features her detective Vera Stanhope, and Shetland, for the BBC, focuses on DI Jimmy Perez, who works for the Shetland police. Born in 1954, Ann grew up in Herefordshire and Devon. After secondary school she spent a year providing childcare for a family in London before reading English at the University of Sussex.</description></item><item><title>Cressida Dick, Commissioner of the Metropolitan Police | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930198/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930198/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cressida Dick is Commissioner of the Metropolitan Police.
She was born in 1960, the youngest child of two university professors. Her parents divorced when she was still at primary school and she and her older siblings grew up in Oxford. Their father died when Cressida was just 11. She read Agriculture and Forest Sciences at Oxford University before spending a year in accountancy. She joined the Metropolitan Police in 1983 where her first beat was on the streets of Soho.</description></item><item><title>Bob Mortimer, comedian | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930199/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930199/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bob Mortimer is a comedian best known for his work with his comedy partner Vic Reeves.
For 30 years, he and Vic have appeared in numerous TV series together, including Vic Reeves’ Big Night Out, Shooting Stars and The Smell of Reeves and Mortimer. Bob first saw Vic performing in a south London pub: Vic was wearing a Bryan Ferry mask while trying to tap dance with wooden planks strapped to his feet.</description></item><item><title>Wendy Cope, poet | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930200/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930200/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wendy Cope is one of England’s most popular and widely-read contemporary poets. Wendy was born in Erith, Kent. Her father was 29 years older than her mother and she was sent to boarding school at the age of seven. Although English was her favourite subject at school, in a bid to defy her English teacher’s expectations, she read history at Oxford. Following graduation she became a primary school teacher.</description></item><item><title>James Rebanks, shepherd and writer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930201/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930201/</guid><description>Podcast Description James Rebanks is a shepherd and the best-selling author of The Shepherd’s Life. Born in Cumbria in 1974, he grew up venerating his grandfather, who taught him what he needed to know in order to take over the family farm from his father one day. He found school an irksome distraction, and left aged 15 with two GCSEs. It wasn’t until his early 20s, after he’d developed an interest in reading and had met his future wife Helen, that he decided to return to study at a local college in the evenings.</description></item><item><title>Ruth Jones, actor and writer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930202/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930202/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ruth Jones is an actor and writer. She co-created and starred in the award-winning TV comedy series Gavin and Stacey, and also wrote and took the title role in the comedy drama Stella, which ran for six series. She grew up in Porthcawl, in South Wales, where the local secondary school nurtured her love of performance. She took to the stage in numerous school musicals, along with fellow pupil Rob Brydon.</description></item><item><title>Jeremy Deller, artist | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930203/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930203/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Turner Prize-winning artist Jeremy Deller is perhaps best known for We’re Here Because We’re Here, a moving and powerful memorial to the Battle of the Somme, and The Battle of Orgreave – a re-enactment of the confrontation between police and pickets at the height of the miners’ strike.
Deller doesn’t paint, draw or sculpt and his work encompasses film, photography and installations. At school his creative endeavours were not always appreciated, and at 13 he was asked to leave the art class.</description></item><item><title>Alan Carr, comedian | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930204/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930204/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alan Carr, comedian and chat show host, is known for his love of silliness, dressing up and camp daftness. His stand-up shows have filled arenas, and on TV he co-hosted the Friday Night Project and then his own show - Chatty Man. Alan was born into a footballing family – his dad, Graham, was a professional player and then a manager. Alan first tried his hand at comedy while reading Theatre Studies at Middlesex University.</description></item><item><title>Hella Pick, journalist | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930205/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 15:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930205/</guid><description>Podcast Description As one of the Guardian’s first female foreign correspondents, Hella Pick reported on events that shaped the world in the second half of the 20th century, from Martin Luther King's civil rights activism to Watergate, the Gdansk shipyard strikes to the collapse of the Soviet Union. Born in Vienna in 1929, she was raised by her mother who, in March 1939, put her on a Kindertransport train to Britain to escape the Nazis.</description></item><item><title>Mariana Mazzucato, economist | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930206/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930206/</guid><description>Podcast Description Professor Mariana Mazzucato is an economist, who focuses on value and innovation. Born in Italy, Mariana moved to America as a child, when her father accepted a post at Princeton University. She has lived in the UK for the last 20 years and is currently Professor in the Economics of Innovation and Public Value and the Director of the Institute for Innovation and Public Purpose at University College London.</description></item><item><title>Gary Barlow, singer-songwriter | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930207/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930207/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gary Barlow, musician and Take That lead singer, has written more than a dozen chart-topping songs, and has received six Ivor Novello awards including the award for Outstanding Contribution to British Music. Born in Cheshire in 1971, his interest in music was sparked at an early age by a child’s keyboard. At the age of 10, he saw Depeche Mode on Top of the Pops, prompting the desire to take to the stage himself.</description></item><item><title>Tom Kerridge, chef | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930208/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930208/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Kerridge is a chef, restaurateur and TV presenter. Tom made his name with his Buckinghamshire pub The Hand and Flowers, which he opened with his wife in 2005. It is the only British pub with two Michelin stars.
Tom grew up near Gloucester. After his parents divorced when he was 11, his mother took two jobs to support the family, and Tom was often left to cook for himself and his younger brother.</description></item><item><title>Kate Atkinson, novelist | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930209/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930209/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kate Atkinson won the Whitbread Book of the Year Award for her 1995 debut novel Behind the Scenes at the Museum, and has won the Costa Novel Award twice, for Life After Life in 2013 and for A God in Ruins two years later.
Born in York in 1951, she was the only child of a couple who ran a medical and surgical supplies shop. She began to write after she had failed her doctorate at Dundee University and had given birth to two daughters.</description></item><item><title>Tracey Thorn, musican and writer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930210/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930210/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tracey Thorn, musician and writer, is best known as one half of the duo Everything but the Girl. Brought up in Brookmans Park, Hertfordshire, she bought her first guitar, a black Les Paul copy, when she was 16 and her first band was called the Stern Bobs. Shortly after, she formed her own all-female band, Marine Girls, before moving to Hull University to study English. On her first night there, she met her future husband, Ben Watt, and they went on to form Everything But the Girl.</description></item><item><title>Vanley Burke, photographer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930211/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930211/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vanley Burke is a Jamaican-born photographer often described as the Godfather of Black British Photography. His body of work is regarded as the greatest photographic record of African Caribbean people in post-war Britain. He is motivated by a desire to document culture and history. Vanley was born in 1951 in St Thomas, Jamaica. When he was four, his mother emigrated to Britain to train as a nurse, leaving him in his grandparents’ care.</description></item><item><title>Jacqueline Gold | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930212/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930212/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jacqueline Gold is the CEO of the retail brands Ann Summers and Knickerbox. She joined the business at the age of 19 for work experience, and faced resistance because her father, David Gold, was the owner. By the time she was 21, she had persuaded the largely sceptical all-male board to invest in her radical idea: to re-invent the Ann Summers brand by selling lingerie and sex toys at women-only parties held in their homes.</description></item><item><title>Venki Ramakrishnan | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930213/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930213/</guid><description>Podcast Description Venki Ramakrishnan is a Nobel Prize-winning molecular biologist. He is most renowned for his research into the atomic structure of the ribosome - a complex molecule in the cell which translates DNA into chains of amino acids that build proteins, the essence of life. This work eventually secured Venki a Nobel Prize in 2009, which he shared with Ada Yonath and Thomas Steitz. Venki was born in Tamil Nadu, in the south of India.</description></item><item><title>Nile Rodgers | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930214/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930214/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nile Rodgers is a Grammy-winning composer, musician, and producer. With his own band, Chic, he's been enticing people on to the dance floor since the mid-1970s with hits like Le Freak and Good Times. With over 200 production credits to his name, he has worked on many highly successful albums from Sister Sledge’s We Are Family to David Bowie’s Let’s Dance and Madonna’s Like a Virgin.
Born in New York City in 1952 to a teenage mother, he spent his early life immersed in his parents’ bohemian, beatnik, and drug-dominated lifestyle.</description></item><item><title>Thea Musgrave | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930215/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930215/</guid><description>Podcast Description Composer Thea Musgrave celebrated her 90th birthday this year, an event marked by celebrations and concerts around the world, including the BBC Proms and the Edinburgh International Festival. She has published more than 150 compositions, including major orchestral works and numerous operas, and continues to write every day. Thea was born in Edinburgh in May 1928, and still has sharp memories of hearing news of the Dunkirk evacuation in 1940.</description></item><item><title>Tom Daley | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930216/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930216/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Daley started diving aged seven and by the age of 14 was representing Great Britain at the 2008 Olympics in Beijing. He has won six British Championships, three European Championships and won the World Championships in 2009 and 2017.
Born in Plymouth in 1994, he’s the oldest son of Rob and Debbie Daley. He has two younger brothers. His success at a very young age led to widespread media attention, but as he became famous, he was bullied and had to change schools at the age of 15.</description></item><item><title>Henry Marsh | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930217/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930217/</guid><description>Podcast Description Henry Marsh is a neurosurgeon, who pioneered a technique of operating on the brain while the patient is under local anaesthetic. The procedure is now standard practice. He is also an acclaimed writer. He was born in 1950 in Oxford, where his father was an academic. His mother came to England as a political refugee from Nazi Germany in the late 1930s. Henry did not initially pursue a career in medicine: after dropping out of university, he found work as a hospital porter, and only then decided to train as a doctor.</description></item><item><title>Danielle de Niese | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930218/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930218/</guid><description>Podcast Description Danielle de Niese is a soprano who has taken starring roles with leading opera companies around the world. She was born in Melbourne, Australia, to Sri Lankan parents, and at the age of eight she won a national TV talent show, singing a pop medley. When she was ten, her parents moved the family to Los Angeles, so that she could pursue her dream of becoming an opera singer.</description></item><item><title>Pam Ayres | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930219/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930219/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pam Ayres is a poet and broadcaster.
Pam was born in the Vale of the White Horse and retains her characteristic Berkshire burr. She is the youngest of six children, and grew up in the company of her four brothers and a sister in a small council house. Although she was interested in writing from an early age, she failed her 11-plus exam and left school at 15 to join the Civil Service and later the Women's Royal Air Force, where she found opportunities to appear in amateur dramatics.</description></item><item><title>Marianne Elliott | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930220/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930220/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marianne Elliott is the first woman to win two Tony awards for theatre direction: the first for War Horse and the second for The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night Time. Both transferred to Broadway from the National Theatre, London, and have gone on to travel the world. Marianne's parents, grandparents and great-grandparents all worked in the theatre. Her father, Michael Elliott, was a founding director of the Royal Exchange theatre in Manchester and her mother, Rosalind Knight, now in her 80s, has enjoyed a lifetime on the stage and is still working.</description></item><item><title>Baroness Newlove | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930221/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930221/</guid><description>Podcast Description Baroness Newlove is the Victims' Commissioner for England and Wales. She became a campaigner after her husband, Garry Newlove, was murdered by several youths in 2007. Born in Salford in 1961 she grew up in a working class family. Having left school at sixteen she became a copy typist at a magistrate's court and later a committal court assistant. She met Garry when she was 20 and they married and had two daughters.</description></item><item><title>Billie Jean King | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930222/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930222/</guid><description>Podcast Description Billie Jean King won 39 Grand Slams and a total of 20 Wimbledon titles and is regarded as one of the greatest tennis players of all time. Born in California in 1943, she was the eldest daughter of Bill and Betty Moffitt. She discovered tennis at the age of ten: at 15 she won in her age bracket at the Southern California championships, and in 1961, she won the women’s doubles at Wimbledon with Karen Hantze, the youngest pair to achieve such a victory.</description></item><item><title>Philip Treacy | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930223/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930223/</guid><description>Podcast Description Philip Treacy is one of the most prolific and acclaimed hat designers working in the UK. His work was very much in evidence at this year's Royal Wedding and at Royal Ascot. Meghan Markle wore one of his designs for her first official public engagement as the Duchess of Sussex. Other notable clients include Madonna, Tina Turner, Grace Jones, who has showcased his creations on and off stage, and Lady Gaga, for whom he made a black telephone hat.</description></item><item><title>Guy Singh-Watson | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930224/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930224/</guid><description>Podcast Description Guy Singh-Watson is an organic farmer and founder of Riverford, a major British supplier of organic vegetables through a box delivery scheme. Born in 1960 and the youngest of five children, his parents became tenant farmers in Devon in 1951. He describes himself as "a proper little farm boy", and spent his free time outside, clambering up trees, catching rabbits, rearing his own pig and helping on the farm.</description></item><item><title>Martina Cole | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930225/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930225/</guid><description>Podcast Description Martina Cole is a British crime writer, known to her fans as the Queen of Crime. Martina has written 24 novels, 15 of which have topped the original fiction sales charts - more than any other author. She has sold more than 16 million books around the world, and her work has been translated into 29 languages. She also works in prisons, leading reading schemes and writing workshops for prisoners.</description></item><item><title>John Motson | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930226/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930226/</guid><description>Podcast Description John Walker Motson, OBE, also known as Motty, has been commentating on football since 1971. He covered more than 2000 games on television and radio, including all the major football championships, 29 FA Cup finals (with an additional five replays), 10 World Cups, 10 European Championships and 200 England games. At the age of 72 he's just retired.
Known not only for his footballing knowledge and his voice, he is often recognised by his knee-length sheepskin coat.</description></item><item><title>Professor Carlos Frenk | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930227/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930227/</guid><description>Podcast Description Professor Carlos Frenk is a cosmologist and one of the originators of the Cold Dark Matter theory for the formation of galaxies and the structure of the universe. He has worked at Durham University since 1985, where he was appointed the inaugural Ogden Professor of Fundamental Physics in 2001 and has been Director of the Institute for Computational Cosmology since 2002. Born in Mexico in 1951, he is the son of a German Jewish immigrant father and a Mexican mother with Spanish roots.</description></item><item><title>Gillian Reynolds | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930228/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930228/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gillian Reynolds spent 42 years as the radio critic of the Daily Telegraph before she was headhunted by the Sunday Times at the age of 82. Born into a working class family in Liverpool, her mother ran a market stall and her father was a seaman, but also a gambler. Her mother was determined to ensure that Gillian had a good education, and she was the first in her family to go to a grammar school.</description></item><item><title>David Baddiel | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930229/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930229/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Baddiel is a comedian and writer. Known both for his solo work and for his comedic collaborations with, among others, Rob Newman and Frank Skinner, he has also written a screenplay, a musical and several books. Born in 1964 to Jewish parents, the second of three boys, he was brought up in Dollis Hill, London. His father was a scientist from Swansea and his mother was a refugee, whose family had to flee from Nazi Germany.</description></item><item><title>Dr Sue Black | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930230/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930230/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Sue Black is a computer scientist, academic and social entrepreneur. She was instrumental in saving Bletchley Park, the home of vital codebreaking during the second world war. Currently an honorary professor at UCL, she founded BCS Women for women in science and the social enterprise Tech Mums, which teaches parents about computing. She is also on an advisory board for the government's digital services.
Born in Fareham, Hampshire, she was 12 when her mother died of a brain haemorrhage.</description></item><item><title>Sir Peter Lampl | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930231/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930231/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sir Peter Lampl is a philanthropist who has given over £50 million and worked for 20 years to combat educational inequality. In 1997 he founded the Sutton Trust with the aim of improving social mobility. The Trust has funded over 200 research studies, and it initiates and supports a wide range of programmes, covering everything from early years education to access to the professions. The son of a Viennese émigré, Peter Lampl grew up in modest circumstances in Yorkshire until the age of 11, when his family relocated to Surrey.</description></item><item><title>Abi Morgan | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930232/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930232/</guid><description>Podcast Description Abi Morgan is a screenwriter and playwright best known for TV dramas The Hour, River and The Split and the films Shame, Suffragette and The Iron Lady. She won two Emmy Awards for The Hour, as well as two BAFTAs for Best Single Drama for White Girl and Sex Traffic, and Meryl Streep won an Academy Award for her portrayal of Margaret Thatcher in The Iron Lady. Born into a theatrical family - her father was a theatre director, her mother is an actress - she only began to write during her university days at Exeter.</description></item><item><title>Anne-Marie Duff | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930233/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930233/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anne-Marie Duff is a stage and screen actor.
Born in 1970 to Irish parents, she grew up in a working class household in west London. A shy child and a voracious reader, she took acting classes from the age of 11, but failed to get into drama school on her first attempt. Her second application to the Drama Centre in London was successful and she's barely been out of work since.</description></item><item><title>David Byrne | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930234/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930234/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Byrne was a founding member of the band Talking Heads. Born in Dumbarton, Scotland, he emigrated first to Canada and then to the USA before the age of ten. He started playing in bands at school and, when art school didn't work out for him, he founded Talking Heads with a couple of friends. They played their first gig, opening for the Ramones, at the legendary New York club CBGB's, in June 1975.</description></item><item><title>John Gray | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930235/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930235/</guid><description>Podcast Description John Gray is a philosopher. His academic career included professorships at Oxford University and the London School of Economics, and visiting professorships at Harvard and Yale in the USA. He retired from academia in 2008, and has dedicated himself to writing full time since then. He is the lead book reviewer of the New Statesman and a regular contributor to the Guardian.
Born in 1948 in South Shields, his father was a Tyneside dock worker, his mother a homemaker.</description></item><item><title>Matt Smith | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930236/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930236/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matt Smith is best known as the eleventh Timelord in the BBC One series, Doctor Who. At 26, he became the youngest actor to take the part. His future looked set to be in football: he played at youth level for Northampton Town, Nottingham Forest and Leicester City until a serious back condition ended his highly promising career prematurely. His drama teacher encouraged him to take up acting and he joined the National Youth Theatre and studied drama at the University of East Anglia.</description></item><item><title>Dame Minouche Shafik | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930237/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930237/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dame Minouche Shafik is the director of the London School of Economics and a former Deputy Governor of the Bank of England.
She was born in Egypt but her family had to flee the country when she was four years old, because her parents lost everything during President Nasser's nationalisation programme. Her father, a scientist, found work in America, and Minouche and her sister attended numerous schools there, before she went back to Egypt at the age of 16.</description></item><item><title>Christopher Nolan | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930238/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930238/</guid><description>Podcast Description Christopher Nolan is best known for reviving the Batman film franchise and for directing the blockbusters Inception and Dunkirk. His films have taken nearly $5 billion at the box office. Born in London in 1970 to an English father and an American mother, he discovered film-making at the age of seven. In what he describes as "a leap of faith", his father lent him his Super 8 camera - and he's not stopped making films since.</description></item><item><title>Chi-chi Nwanoku | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930239/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930239/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chi-chi Nwanoku is a double bass player and founder of Europe's first professional majority black and minority ethnic orchestra, Chineke!.
Chi-chi is the eldest of five children, born to a Nigerian father and an Irish mother. Early on, she discovered two competing passions: playing the piano and 100 metre sprinting. She was aiming to qualify for the 1976 Olympics when she suffered a knee injury which cut short her life as an athlete.</description></item><item><title>Jack Whitehall | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930240/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930240/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jack Whitehall, stand-up comedian, actor, sit-com writer and producer is Kirsty Young's castaway.
He co-wrote and starred in the sitcoms Fresh Meat and Bad Education. He and his father launched their chat-show Backchat in 2013 and recently made a TV series together travelling around Cambodia, Vietnam and Thailand. Jack played Paul Pennyfeather in a TV adaptation of Evelyn Waugh's Decline and Fall in 2016 and has forthcoming roles in Good Omens and a film about Marc Bolan and David Bowie.</description></item><item><title>Garry Kasparov | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930241/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930241/</guid><description>Podcast Description Garry Kasparov is a Russian chess grandmaster, who became the youngest ever world champion at the age of 22. He is also a writer and a political activist. He grew up in the Soviet Union, the only child of engineer parents. He learned chess by watching his parents play as they worked out chess problems in the newspaper. As a five year old he was fascinated by the mysterious little pieces and the board with its 64 squares.</description></item><item><title>Christina Lamb | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930242/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 13:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930242/</guid><description>Podcast Description Christina Lamb is chief foreign correspondent for the Sunday Times and travels the world reporting from war zones and hot spots, speaking not just to key protagonists but also seeking out and detailing the daily impact of conflict on civilians.
An only child, and brought up in Carshalton Beeches, she was a voracious reader and dreamed of being an explorer. Although she was rebellious at school, and at one point was asked to leave, she won a place at Oxford and went on to edit the university newspaper.</description></item><item><title>Angela Hartnett | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930243/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930243/</guid><description>Podcast Description Angela Hartnett is a chef, TV presenter and cookery writer. She holds a Michelin star and runs her own restaurants. Angela was born in 1968 to an Italian mother and Irish father, and her culinary career has been influenced by her Italian background and her grandmother's cooking. After studying for a history degree, Angela began work in the catering industry before joining Gordon Ramsay at his restaurant Aubergine. In 2002 she took over at the Connaught, London, as the first woman chef to run its restaurant.</description></item><item><title>Charlie Brooker | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930244/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930244/</guid><description>Podcast Description Charlie Brooker is a satirist, broadcaster and writer. He created the Emmy-award winning series, Black Mirror, and presents Screenwipe and Newswipe which won Best Comedy Entertainment Show award at the British Comedy Awards in 2011. Born in 1971, his career has been influenced both by his early love of technology - he was a keen computer gamer - and by his passion for the anarchic, surreal and experimental comedy of Monty Python and The Young Ones.</description></item><item><title>75 Years of Desert Island Discs | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930245/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930245/</guid><description>Podcast Description 75 Years of Desert Island Discs - Kirsty Young ends the programme's anniversary year with some gems from the archive, including the creator of the format, Roy Plomley, actress Bebe Daniels, broadcaster Richard Dimbleby, trumpeter Louis Armstrong, politician Dame Barbara Castle and cellist Jacqueline du Pre. Kirsty also chooses some of her favourite moments with Dame Judi Dench, Sir David Attenborough, comedian Sarah Millican, the surgeon David Nott and rugby referee Nigel Owens.</description></item><item><title>Bruno Tonioli | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930246/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930246/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bruno Tonioli, dancer, choreographer and a judge on BBC One's Strictly Come Dancing, is Kirsty's guest. He was brought up in Ferrara, Northern Italy, and was the only child of hard-working parents who hoped he would be an accountant. Bruno wanted to pursue a creative career and joined a raunchy cabaret dance troupe when he was a teenager, and performed across Europe. He went on to train in other areas of dance and choreography and spent the 1980s working on pop videos with The Rolling Stones, Elton John, Bananarama, Boy George, George Michael, Duran Duran and many more.</description></item><item><title>Christine McVie | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930247/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930247/</guid><description>Podcast Description Christine McVie enjoyed huge success with Fleetwood Mac, penning many of their signature songs including You Make Loving Fun, Oh Daddy, Little Lies, Everywhere and Songbird. The band has sold more than 100 million records and the album Rumours remains one of the most popular discs of all time, with sales of more than 40 million copies. The album was recorded during 1976 whilst the band members were going through relationship break-ups and the stories of excess and drug taking during the 1970s and 1980s are well documented.</description></item><item><title>Kelsey Grammer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930248/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930248/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kelsey Grammer is best known for his two-decade-long portrayal of psychiatrist Dr Frasier Crane which began on the NBC sitcom Cheers. He continued the role in the hugely successful spin-off series Frasier which ran for 11 years. When the series ended in 2004, it had won a total of 35 Emmys. Born in the Virgin Islands, he was brought up by his mother and maternal grandparents in Florida, after his parents divorced.</description></item><item><title>Tim Martin | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930249/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930249/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tim Martin is the chairman and founder of the pub company JD Wetherspoon. He opened his first pub, Martin's Free House, in 1979 in North London. Now the chain employs 37,000 people, in 891 pubs of which 54 are hotels. Travelling from his home in Devon, Tim visits at least ten of them a week taking detailed 'call notes' on the staff, the beer, the quality of the food and even the cutlery.</description></item><item><title>Naomi Klein | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930250/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930250/</guid><description>Podcast Description The writer and activist Naomi Klein reached an international audience with her first book, the best-selling No Logo, a rallying cry against the power of corporate brands and the replacement of traditional manufacturing jobs with sweatshop labour. Since then, she's turned her intellectual ire on to even bigger terrain - the political and economic systems underpinning capitalism and climate change. The way to save the planet, she says, requires a radical rethink which will address what she calls the "</description></item><item><title>Micky Flanagan | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930251/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930251/</guid><description>Podcast Description Micky Flanagan found mainstream success as a comedian in 2007 with his autobiographical 'What Chance Change?' show at the Edinburgh fringe, where he was nominated as best newcomer. Raised in the East End of London, he left school at 15 with no qualifications and followed his dad into work as a fish porter at Billingsgate fish market. When he quit that job, he spent a summer working in a kitchen in New York, and then returned to London to spend much of the 1980s working in the furniture trade.</description></item><item><title>Anna Pavord | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930252/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930252/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anna Pavord, writer &amp;amp; gardener, is interviewed by Kirsty Young for Desert Island Discs
Producer: Cathy Drysdale.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Professor Phil Scraton | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930253/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930253/</guid><description>Podcast Description Professor Phil Scraton is Professor Emeritus at the School of Law at Queen's University Belfast. A criminologist and author, he's director of the Childhood, Transition and Social Justice Initiative and was lead researcher of the Hillsborough Independent Panel. Born into a working class family in Wallasey in the Wirral in 1949, he attended a seminary at the age of 12. Deciding the religious life was not for him he worked as a bus conductor before attending Liverpool University where he read Sociology.</description></item><item><title>Kay Mellor | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930254/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930254/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kay Mellor, OBE, is an English screenwriter and director best known for TV drama series including Band of Gold, Playing the Field, Fat Friends and The Syndicate. She has won a Bafta award, along with numerous nominations, and she received a Royal Television Society Fellowship in 2016. She has also worked as an actress, and has written for the stage. Kay was born in Leeds and has lived there all her life.</description></item><item><title>Edna Adan Ismail | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930255/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930255/</guid><description>Podcast Description Edna Adan Ismail is a midwife and campaigner. As a 12 year old growing up in British Somaliland, her dream was to build her own hospital. It took her some 50 years and all her savings to realise her ambition, and the state of the art hospital she built is a testament to her passion and dogged determination. Nursing and midwifery have been her life since she won a scholarship to study in the UK in the mid-1950s, when she cycled to appointments in her black raincoat to deliver babies all around London.</description></item><item><title>Jane Gardam | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930256/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930256/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane Gardam is best known for her trilogy of novels about an ex-colonial QC nicknamed Old Filth. A writer for both adults and children, she has won two Whitbread awards, the Katherine Mansfield Award and has been shortlisted for the Booker and the Orange Prize for Fiction.
Born in 1928, she grew up in North Yorkshire where her father was a schoolmaster at a small independent boys' school. Her mother wrote sermons and was an inveterate letter-writer.</description></item><item><title>Sir James MacMillan | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930257/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930257/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sir James MacMillan is a Scottish composer and conductor. He's one of Britain's most successful living classical composers, with his percussion concerto, Veni Veni Emmanuel, receiving more than 600 performances since its premiere in 1992. He draws inspiration from both the spiritual and the secular: many of his works draw on his Roman Catholic faith, while his passion for Celtic football club provided the initial spark for a piano concerto.</description></item><item><title>Siddhartha Mukherjee | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930258/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930258/</guid><description>Podcast Description Siddhartha Mukherjee is a cancer specialist. His biography of the disease, The Emperor of All Maladies, won the Pulitzer Prize in 2010. A haematologist and oncologist by training, his research focuses on cancer therapy and gene functions related to blood cells. His latest book, The Gene, goes in search of normality, identity, variation and heredity. Born in India in 1970 he grew up with his extended family in Delhi.</description></item><item><title>Professor Dame Jane Francis | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930259/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930259/</guid><description>Podcast Description Professor Dame Jane Francis is the Director of the British Antarctic Survey. She is no stranger to surviving in extreme conditions, because for much of her career her research has taken her to the Polar Regions. Travelling with her fossil hammer, her principal interests are in palaeoclimatology and palaeobotany. She specialises in the study of fossil plants, and how they shape our understanding of climates in the distant past, when Antarctica was much warmer.</description></item><item><title>Paul Greengrass | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930260/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930260/</guid><description>Podcast Description Paul Greengrass has directed three Jason Bourne films, starring Matt Damon, Captain Phillips with Tom Hanks in the title role, and the 9/11 film United 93, which earned him an Academy Award nomination. He won a Bafta for the film The Murder of Stephen Lawrence, and he wrote and directed the acclaimed Bloody Sunday. His father was a merchant seaman and his mother a teacher and he grew up in Gravesend in Kent.</description></item><item><title>Dr Kevin Fong | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930261/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930261/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirsty Young's castaway is Dr. Kevin Fong. He is a consultant anaesthetist at University College Hospital London, and an expert on space medicine. He is a senior lecturer in Physiology at UCL and the co-director of the Centre for Aviation, Space and Extreme Environment Medicine.
Born to parents who had come to the UK from Mauritius, he grew up in London. His parents put great emphasis on education - which they had both missed out on in their youth.</description></item><item><title>Sheryl Sandberg | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930262/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930262/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sheryl Sandberg, Chief Operating Officer of Facebook, is Kirsty Young's castaway. She worked for Google at the beginning of the tech boom before joining Facebook in 2008. Raised in Miami Beach, Florida, she studied economics at Harvard. She became chief of staff for Larry Summers, Treasury Secretary under Bill Clinton, before moving to Silicon Valley.
Sheryl published her first book called Lean In: Women, Work, and the Will to Lead in 2013 which tried to answer the question why so few women reach the top echelons of their professions.</description></item><item><title>Jayne-Anne Gadhia | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930263/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930263/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirsty Young's castaway is Jayne-Anne Gadhia, Chief Executive of Virgin Money. She is currently the government's Women in Finance Champion. She worked for Fred Goodwin at RBS just prior to the financial crisis before returning to Virgin Money in 2007. A mother of one, she endured many miscarriages and has written about her experience of post-natal depression following her daughter's birth.
An only child, she was brought up first in the Midlands, then in East Anglia.</description></item><item><title>John McEnroe | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930264/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930264/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirsty Young's castaway is the tennis player and commentator, John McEnroe. He won three singles and five doubles Wimbledon titles, four singles and four doubles at the US Open and was ranked number one in the world for four consecutive years in the 1980s. John McEnroe grew up in New York and didn't pick up a tennis racquet until the age of eight, but his talent was quickly spotted and he began to compete in junior tournaments.</description></item><item><title>Sue Perkins | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930265/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930265/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirsty Young's castaway is the comedian and TV presenter Sue Perkins. She and her friend Mel Giedroyc first appeared as a comedy duo at the Edinburgh Fringe over 20 years ago and together they presented the first seven series of The Great British Bake Off. Born at the end of the 1960s, Sue grew up in Croydon, the eldest of three siblings. By her own description a "shy and awkward"</description></item><item><title>Professor Carlo Rovelli | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930266/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2017 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930266/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirsty Young's castaway is the theoretical physicist, Professor Carlo Rovelli. His book 'Seven Brief Lessons on Physics' became one of the fastest-selling science titles of all time, catapulting him from the world of academia into the global spotlight. Committed to bridging the gap between science and art and making complex scientific issues comprehensible for the lay person, he is currently Professor of Physics at Aix-Marseille University. Born in Verona, and an only child, he was encouraged to learn, to be independent and dreamed of travelling through space.</description></item><item><title>Stella McCartney | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930267/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930267/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirsty Young's castaway this week is the fashion designer Stella McCartney.
Born the middle child of Paul and Linda McCartney, Stella's early years were a paradox: she would either spend her days riding ponies, sharing one of two bedrooms with her sisters in a farmhouse, and generally mucking around in the countryside - or touring the world with her parents' band Wings and spending time in the company of stars such as David Bowie and Iggy Pop.</description></item><item><title>Jed Mercurio | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930268/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2017 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930268/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirsty Young's castaway is Jed Mercurio. Creator of Line of Duty, and an award-winning TV writer, producer, director and novelist, he is one of the few British script-writers to work as an American-style show-runner. A former hospital doctor and RAF officer, he has been ranked among UK television's leading writers by TV industry magazine Broadcast. His Italian parents moved to the UK after the Second World War and he was brought up in Cannock in the Midlands.</description></item><item><title>Rick Wakeman | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930269/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930269/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rick Wakeman, musician and composer, is interviewed by Kirsty Young for Desert Island Discs
Producer: Paula McGinley.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sonia Friedman | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930270/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930270/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirsty Young's castaway is the theatre producer, Sonia Friedman. Acclaimed as the most influential producer in British theatre today, she has produced over 160 new shows. They include Funny Girl with Sheridan Smith, Jerusalem starring Mark Rylance, Benedict Cumberbatch's Hamlet, the record-breaking Book of Mormon and the musicals Legally Blonde, and Dreamgirls. Her productions both here and on Broadway have won numerous awards, including a record-breaking 14 Olivier Awards in 2014, and nine this year for Harry Potter and the Cursed Child.</description></item><item><title>Elif Shafak | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930271/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2017 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930271/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirsty Young's castaway this week is the Turkish writer Elif Shafak. Elif Shafak has published ten novels and several volumes of non-fiction and her work is translated into 47 languages. She is the most widely read female novelist in Turkey today.
Born in 1971, she was raised by a single working mother and also, for the first ten years of her life, by her grandmother in Ankara. Her mother's job as a diplomat led to a move to Madrid when Elif was ten years old - and so began a peripatetic life which has taken her to places as diverse as Jordan and Germany, the United States and finally to London where she has lived for the past seven years.</description></item><item><title>Demis Hassabis | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930272/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2017 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930272/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirsty Young's castaway is Dr Demis Hassabis. An artificial intelligence researcher and co-founder and CEO of DeepMind, he is also a neuroscientist, a computer games designer, an entrepreneur, and in his youth, a world-class chess player.
Born in 1976, he was introduced to chess aged four and, by the age of twelve, was the world's second-highest ranked player for his age. With his winnings, he bought himself a PC and taught himself to code.</description></item><item><title>Liz Lochhead | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930273/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2017 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930273/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirsty Young's castaway this week is the writer and poet Liz Lochhead. She was the Makar, the Scottish national poet, between 2011 and 2016.
Liz was born in Motherwell, not far from Glasgow, in 1947. She was always drawing at school and so decided to study at the Glasgow School of Art, where she didn't enjoy the drawing, but did start writing. After winning a poetry competition, she started performing her poems at readings in Scotland.</description></item><item><title>Ed Sheeran | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930274/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2017 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930274/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirsty Young's castaway this week is Ed Sheeran. His songs have brought him two Grammys, four Brit awards and global success. Shortly after the release of his latest album, Divide, tracks from it occupied nine of the top 10 places in the UK singles chart.
Born into a creative family, Ed had piano and cello lessons as a youngster and briefly sang in a local church choir. At the age of 11, seeing Eric Clapton play Layla on TV at the Queen's Golden Jubilee concert inspired him to take up the guitar.</description></item><item><title>Arundhati Roy | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930275/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2017 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930275/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirsty Young's castaway is the writer, Arundhati Roy. She won the Booker Prize for her first novel, The God Of Small Things, which has been translated into 40 languages and became the best-selling book ever by a non-expatriate Indian. After a gap of 20 years, her second novel will be published in June.
Brought up in Kerala, her Syrian Christian mother left her marriage when her children were young and set up a small school where Arundhati and her brother were educated.</description></item><item><title>Amanda Levete | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930276/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930276/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirsty Young's castaway this week is the architect Amanda Levete. She won the Stirling prize in 1998 for the Media Centre at Lord's Cricket Ground which she designed with then husband, the late Jan Kaplicky. Later this year the Victoria and Albert Museum in London will open her extension, featuring a new entrance, courtyard and gallery. Brought up in Richmond, the oldest of three children, she showed her independent spirit early on, and left school at 16.</description></item><item><title>Marian Keyes | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930277/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930277/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirsty Young's castaway is the writer Marian Keyes. Her twelve novels to date have sold 35 million copies and are published in 33 languages. Some of her novels have been adapted for the screen. She has also published three volumes of journalism.
Marian was born the eldest of five children in Ireland in 1963. While she was academically successful at school, she says she wasn't taught to think for herself, which left her ill prepared for university where she studied law.</description></item><item><title>Jimmy Carr | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930278/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930278/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirsty Young's castaway is the comedian and television presenter Jimmy Carr. He is the son of Irish immigrant parents and grew up in Berkshire. Despite being dyslexic, he got good enough A levels to study at Cambridge University. After graduating with a degree in Political Science, and working for a major multinational company in London, Jimmy had what he calls an 'early midlife crisis', during which he lost his Catholic faith and was generally unhappy.</description></item><item><title>Dame Katherine Grainger | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930279/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930279/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirsty Young's castaway is the Olympian and rower, Dame Katherine Grainger. A six-time rowing World Champion across a variety of classes, her silver medal at Rio in 2016 made her the most successful female British Olympic athlete ever, having won medals in five consecutive games.
Born in Glasgow in 1975, her parents were teachers. At school she earned a black belt in karate, and it wasn't until she went to Edinburgh University that her passion for rowing was truly ignited.</description></item><item><title>Sir Antony Beevor | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930280/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930280/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirsty Young's castaway is military historian, Sir Antony Beevor. His books about some of the key battles of the Second World War are best-sellers and have been credited with reinvigorating the whole genre. There was little indication of this future success while he was boarder at Winchester public school where he failed to pass either his History or his English A levels. During the five years he spent in the army, including two years at Sandhurst for officer training, he studied history under the great military historian, John Keegan.</description></item><item><title>Clive James | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930281/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930281/</guid><description>Podcast Description Roy Plomley's castaway is broadcaster and writer Clive James.
Favourite track: Baby Love by Diana Ross and The Supremes
Book: Book about how to build a plane out of palm fronds and coconut fibre by Willy Messerschmitt
Luxury: Space invaders
Transcript</description></item><item><title>June Brown | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930282/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930282/</guid><description>Podcast Description June Brown is best known today for her role as the long-suffering chain-smoking Dot Cotton (now Dot Branning) in the BBC TV soap EastEnders. She arrived on a three month contract in 1985 and is still in the show. She was nominated for a BAFTA in 2008.
She celebrates her 90th birthday in February 2017 and has no intention of retiring as acting "keeps her alive". June was born in Suffolk and brought up in a music-loving family.</description></item><item><title>Nigel Owens | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930283/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930283/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirsty Young's castaway this week is the rugby union referee Nigel Owens.
His steely authority and quick wit on the field have won him worldwide praise - he's widely regarded as one of the best referees in the business for the impact he makes on the flow and coherence of a game. In 2015 he became the second Welsh official since 1991 to referee a World Cup Final - in a memorable match between New Zealand and Australia.</description></item><item><title>David Beckham | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930284/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930284/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Beckham is Kirsty Young's guest as Desert Island Discs celebrates its 75th Anniversary. As a professional footballer he's the only Englishman to win the league titles in England, Spain, the US and France. He spent the bulk of his career as a midfielder for Manchester United, winning the Treble - Premiership, FA Cup and Champions League - in 1999, before moving to Real Madrid in 2003. He headed to the US to play for LA Galaxy in 2007, and ended his career at Paris Saint-Germain in 2013, retiring in May that year.</description></item><item><title>Desert Island Discs at 75 | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930285/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930285/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirsty Young celebrates 75 years of Desert Island Discs with some of the wonderful voices in the archive and chooses some of her favourite interviews from her 10 years as presenter. From Dustin Hoffman to Maya Angelou, Stephen Hawking to Victoria Wood, we have glimpses into the castaways' lives and times. Coronation Street stalwart, Betty Driver explains why she chose a song she hates to take with her to the island, Dawn French recalls the infamous 'puddle' scene in the Vicar of Dibley and legendary broadcaster Richard Dimbleby describes his very early days in broadcasting.</description></item><item><title>Caitlin Moran | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930286/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930286/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirsty Young's castaway this week is the writer Caitlin Moran.
A columnist for The Times newspaper for 25 years, she's published five books and co-wrote the Channel 4 sitcom Raised by Wolves. The eldest of eight children, and raised on benefits on a council estate in Wolverhampton, she was taken out of school by her parents aged eleven and educated herself at the library and by watching television, reading all the classics and learning from popular culture.</description></item><item><title>Wayne McGregor | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930287/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930287/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirsty Young's castaway is the choreographer Wayne McGregor. Despite his background in contemporary dance, he has been resident choreographer at the Royal Ballet - the first from outside the company - for the past ten years. He has brought to Covent Garden a fascination with technology, a passion for collaborative efforts with visual artists and musicians, and he is renowned for drawing inspiration particularly from the field of science.</description></item><item><title>Pinky Lilani | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930288/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930288/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pinky Lilani, who was awarded a CBE in 2015 for services to women in business, is the founder of the annual Asian Women of Achievement Awards and the Women of the Future Awards. She also runs her own company, which uses Indian food as a means of team-building, and has published two cook books.
Pinky was born in Calcutta, now Kolkata, where her parents were affluent and very sociable.</description></item><item><title>Sir Kenneth Grange | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930289/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930289/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sir Kenneth Grange is a designer. He's been designing elements of our everyday lives for the past six decades. Born in London in 1929, he went to Willesden art school aged fourteen and four years later he left and embarked on a remarkable career. He is still working today at 87 years old. "Why would I stop? I mean, if a bloke can play the piano, you don't stop him playing it, do you?</description></item><item><title>Gareth Malone | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930290/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2016 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930290/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gareth Malone is a choirmaster who has coaxed and cajoled people from nervous adults to reluctant teenagers to open their mouths and sing for the pure joy of it - in front of television cameras. Gareth's first two TV series, which charted his attempts to build successful choirs in schools with little or no tradition of singing together, both won major awards, and gripped and inspired viewers. He has since also worked widely on TV with adult groups from a wide range of backgrounds, and his Military Wives Choir even hit the top of the charts at Christmas.</description></item><item><title>Bruce Springsteen | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930291/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930291/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirsty Young's castaway this week is Bruce Springsteen.
His career has brought him 20 Grammys, two Golden Globes, an Academy Award and his albums sell in their millions around the world. He grew up in New Jersey where the Catholic church played a central role in his early life. The family teetered on the brink of poverty, and his first guitar was rented, rather than bought. He spent his apprentice years as a musician and singer with local bands before landing a record deal in 1972.</description></item><item><title>Sir Philip Craven | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930292/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 11:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930292/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sir Philip Craven is the President of the International Paralympic Committee and a former wheelchair basketball athlete.
Craven represented Great Britain in wheelchair basketball at five editions of the Paralympic Games, from 1972 to 1988. He also competed in track and field athletics and swimming at the 1972 Games.
He won gold at the wheelchair basketball World Championships in 1973, and bronze in 1975, as well as two gold medals (1971, 1974) and a silver (1993) at the European Championships.</description></item><item><title>Davina McCall | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930293/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930293/</guid><description>Podcast Description Davina McCall is an English television presenter. She began her career on MTV before moving to Channel 4 with the cult hit Streetmate.
She was the presenter of Big Brother during its run on Channel 4 between 2000 and 2010 and enjoyed it so much that she planned her family around the transmission schedule. All three of her children were born in September.
Davina hosts a variety of prime time and popular programmes including ITV's Long Lost Family which seeks to reunite family members.</description></item><item><title>Emma Bridgewater | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930294/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930294/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emma Bridgewater is a British ceramic designer and businesswoman. She set up her pottery business in 1985 in Stoke-on-Trent, when many other manufacturers in the city were either closing down or going overseas. Her pottery is instantly recognizable, decorated with polka dots, stars, hearts or elegant lettering using 19th century sponge-printing techniques.
It is an unlikely career for someone who studied English at University. Together with her husband, illustrator Matthew Rice, Emma Bridgewater has played a part in keeping the pottery tradition alive in Stoke-on-Trent.</description></item><item><title>Nicola Adams | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930295/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2016 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930295/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirsty Young's castaway is Nicola Adams. She made history when she won the first ever Olympic gold medal in women's boxing at London 2012, retaining it in Rio 2016. She is the first woman fighter to hold European, World, Commonwealth and Olympic titles. Having watched classic Muhammad Ali and Sugar Ray Leonard fights on TV as she was growing up, she entered the ring for the first time at a working men's club when she was only 13.</description></item><item><title>Yotam Ottolenghi | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930296/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930296/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirsty Young's castaway is the cookery writer and restaurateur Yotam Ottolenghi. His food mixes the flavours of the Middle East and the Mediterranean and has been credited with changing the way many eat and cook, fuelling the surge in popularity of cooking ingredients including wakame seaweed, orange blossom, pomegranate seeds and za'atar. Born to a German mother and an Italian father in Jerusalem, he grew up enjoying a wide range of culinary influences and he loved food from an early age.</description></item><item><title>Ali Smith | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930297/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930297/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ali Smith is a Scottish writer. Born in Inverness in 1962, the youngest of five children by seven years, she says, "I grew up completely alone but with all the comforts of knowing I had a cushioning family structure around me - and yet I could free myself from it."
After reading English at Aberdeen and nearly completing a PhD at Cambridge, she started down an academic path, winning a lectureship at Strathclyde University in Glasgow, but she soon decided that academia wasn't for her.</description></item><item><title>Michael Bublé | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930298/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 13:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930298/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirsty Young's castaway is the singer, Michael Bublé. Born in Burnaby, British Columbia, as a young boy he spent hours listening to his grandfather's record collection which featured the stars of the Great American songbook - Frank Sinatra, Dean Martin and Ella Fitzgerald. At sixteen he was singing at venues often in exchange for the free plumbing services his grandad offered to get him on stage. But it took ten years of plugging away at restaurants, clubs, and corporate gigs before he met David Foster, a music producer at Warner Brothers.</description></item><item><title>Jackie Kay | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930299/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2016 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930299/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirsty Young's castaway is the poet and writer Jackie Kay. Born in Edinburgh in 1961 to a Scottish mother and a Nigerian father, she was adopted as a baby by a white Scottish couple, Helen and John Kay, and grew up in Bishopbriggs, Glasgow. Her father worked for the Communist Party and her mother was the Scottish secretary for CND. She began to write seriously at the age of 17 when recovering from a moped accident, and while reading English at the University of Stirling she became a feminist and politically active in the arena of gay and lesbian rights and racial equality.</description></item><item><title>Dr Robert Langer | Desert Island Discs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9685930300/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2016 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9685930300/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirsty Young's castaway is the scientist Dr Robert Langer. Institute Professor at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology, he is the most cited engineer in history, and was awarded the prestigious US medals of both Science and of Technology and Innovation. A pioneer of many new technologies including controlled release drug delivery systems and nanotechnology, Langer is also regarded as the founder of tissue engineering in regenerative medicine where synthetic structures are used to provide the scaffolding on which new skin, muscle, bone and potentially entire organs can be grown.</description></item></channel></rss>