<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>StrictlyVC Download on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/strictlyvc-download/</link><description>Recent content in StrictlyVC Download on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/strictlyvc-download/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>StrictlyVC Download - OpenAI CEO Sam Altman on ChatGPT and Our Future with AI</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1320100001/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1320100001/</guid><description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Connie Loizis, and this is Alex Gove, and this is Strictly VC Download.
Hey everybody, hope you&amp;rsquo;ve had a good week. We are just beginning to dry out here in Marin
after weeks and weeks of rain. Speaking of misery, perhaps the biggest story this week is all of the
layoffs that have been taking place. On Wednesday, Microsoft sacked 10,000 employees, roughly 5% of
its workforce. And today, Google&amp;rsquo;s parent company, Alphabet, announced that it is laying off 12,000</description></item><item><title>StrictlyVC Download - Sequoia’s Alfred Lin on FTX, Crypto, and Investing for the Long Haul</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1320100002/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1320100002/</guid><description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Connie Loizis, and this is Alex Gove, and this is Strictly VC Download.
Hi, happy Friday, dear readers and listeners. Hope you&amp;rsquo;re well and enjoying the start to the
new year. We are finishing up the week over here. We&amp;rsquo;re really excited and enervated after our first
Strictly VC Insider Evening of the year last night in San Francisco. We had a great time,
we saw a lot of readers, and we thoroughly enjoyed the different discussions that were happening.</description></item><item><title>StrictlyVC Download - VCs Pushing Startups May Face Investor Demands Themselves</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1320100003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1320100003/</guid><description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Connie Loizis. And this is Alex Gove. And this is Strictly VC Download.
Hello, listeners. Happy New Year. Can you believe it&amp;rsquo;s 2023? We hardly can,
but it&amp;rsquo;s so exciting. I have to say this has been a very long week. I know I say that a lot,
but this week has been really, really, really long for some reason. I&amp;rsquo;m sure the weather has
not helped. If you live in California, or you own a television or computer, you probably know that</description></item><item><title>StrictlyVC Download - VC Bradley Tusk Thinks Twitter Will Cost Elon Musk Much More Than He Paid for It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1320100004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1320100004/</guid><description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Connie Loizos. And this is Alex Gove. And this is Strictly VC Download.
Hi, everyone. Happy holidays. As is always the case, we&amp;rsquo;ve waited too late in the day to put
this podcast together. So we&amp;rsquo;re just going to skip straight to two quick conversations that
we had this week, and we hope you will enjoy. One of the chats is with serial entrepreneur
and investor Fabrice Grinda, whose firm is currently the most active venture firm in the</description></item><item><title>StrictlyVC Download - Economist, VC, and MIT fellow Paul Kedrosky on the Dangers of OpenAI</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1320100005/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1320100005/</guid><description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Connie Loizos, and this is Alex Gove, and this is Strictly VC Download.
Hi, happy Friday, everyone. I was at a friend&amp;rsquo;s house for lunch earlier with a bunch of very,
very joyous Argentinians after Lionel Messi and company survived one of the wildest games of the
World Cup in a penalty shootout that I hope some of you caught. It was really amazing and exciting
to watch. But now, of course, it is getting late.</description></item></channel></rss>