<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/no-priors-artificial-intelligence-machine-learning-technology-startups/</link><description>Recent content in No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/no-priors-artificial-intelligence-machine-learning-technology-startups/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How AI can help small businesses | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830049/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830049/</guid><description>Podcast Description AI tools are helping small business owners manage their businesses, so they can stay focused on the aspects of their business they love to do. This week on No Priors, Sarah and Elad are joined by Alyssa Henry, an executive at some of the most impactful companies from Microsoft to Amazon. Most recently she was the CEO of Square. She led Square’s team as they were very early adopters of a consumer-facing product that used GPT-2 and have continued to incorporate AI into their offerings.</description></item><item><title>AI is the new enterprise UI with Clara Shih, CEO Salesforce AI | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830048/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830048/</guid><description>Podcast Description AI is the new UI for enterprise customers, according to Clara Shih, the CEO of Salesforce AI. Salesforce released Einstein, now called Einstein GPT, in 2016, making it an early example of how beneficial AI can be when embedded in enterprise software. This week on No Priors, Sarah and Elad talked with Clara about what the evolution of AI in enterprise looks like, how Salesforce is adoption AI across the organization, and the onboarding process for companies looking to integrate AI into their workflow, plus the challenges of pricing for AI services.</description></item><item><title>Open AI leadership shuffle, new diffusion models, and starting the cult of Q* | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830047/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830047/</guid><description>Podcast Description OpenAI’s leadership has taken us all on a rollercoaster so it’s great timing for another host-only episode. This week Sarah and Elad get into what has been going on at OpenAI and what the turbulent leadership changes tell us about the importance of good intent and good incentives when building these influential companies. They also talk about innovative products coming out of Pika Labs, why people are moving away from diffusion models to MLMs, and how, in AI investing, the ASP is the opportunity.</description></item><item><title>AI Agents That Reason and Code with Imbue Co-Founders Kanjun Qiu and Josh Albrecht | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830043/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 12:39:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830043/</guid><description>Podcast Description The future of tech is 25-person companies powered by AI agents that help us accomplish our larger goals. Imbue is working on building AI agents that reason, code and generally make our lives easier. Sarah Guo and Elad Gil sit down with co-founders Kanjun Qiu (CEO) and Josh Albrecht (CTO) to discuss how they define reasoning, the spectrum of specialized and generalized agents, and the path to improved agent performance.</description></item><item><title>Mistral 7B and the Open Source Revolution With Arthur Mensch, CEO Mistral AI | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830041/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Open Source fuels the engine of innovation, according to Arthur Mensch, CEO and co-founder of Mistral AI. Mistral is a French AI company which recently made a splash with releasing Mistral 7B, the most powerful language model for its size to date, and outperforming much larger models. Sarah Guo and Elad Gil sit down with Arthur to discuss why open source could win the AI wars, their $100M+ seed financing, the true nature of scaling laws, why he started his company in France, and what Mistral is building next.</description></item><item><title>What is Digital Life? with OpenAI Co-Founder &amp; Chief Scientist Ilya Sutskever | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 12:03:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each iteration of ChatGPT has demonstrated remarkable step function capabilities. But what’s next? Ilya Sutskever, Co-Founder &amp;amp; Chief Scientist at OpenAI, joins Sarah Guo and Elad Gil to discuss the origins of OpenAI as a capped profit company, early emergent behaviors of GPT models, the token scarcity issue, next frontiers of AI research, his argument for working on AI safety now, and the premise of Superalignment. Plus, how do we define digital life?</description></item><item><title>AI Threats &amp; Opportunities in Cyber Security With Material Security Co-Founder Ryan Noon | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 09:53:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cyber Security is going to change significantly in the era of AI, according to Ryan Noon, cofounder of Material Security, a security company that makes cloud-based Google and Microsoft email a safe place for sensitive data. Elad Gil and Ryan talk about how Material Security started to use LLMs, potential security threats from AI hacks, and the role of the government in securing the Internet. Ryan also shares his advice for founders.</description></item><item><title>What Google Cloud Can Teach Enterprises Developing &amp; Rolling Out AI Tools, With Kawal Gandhi | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 18:54:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830003/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the Lead for Generative AI in the Office of the CTO for Google Cloud, Kawal Gandhi has a unique vantage point on enterprise AI rollout. Sarah Guo and Elad Gil sit down with Gandhi this week to discuss his insights on how enterprises can effectively invest in AI development, the importance of TPUs, and Google’s internal AI applications. Plus, when will email get more intelligent? Kawal Gandhi has worked at Google for nearly a decade in search and ad roles before focusing on the development and marketing of AI tools.</description></item><item><title>From App to Suite to Platform, with HubSpot's Co-Founder Brian Halligan | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Startups aren&amp;rsquo;t the only companies racing to build the new world of AI. This week, Sarah Guo talks with Brian Halligan, the co-founder, longtime CEO and now executive chairperson of HubSpot, the fastest growing CRM. He talks about category creation, coining the term ‘inbound marketing,’ lessons in scaling from an app to a suite to a platform, staying innovative at scale, and how they&amp;rsquo;re navigating the AI disruption. Brian also describes the life-threatening moment he decided to step back from the CEO role.</description></item><item><title>Model Quality, Fine Tuning &amp; Meta Sponsoring Open Source Ecosystem | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 01:17:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830005/</guid><description>Podcast Description What Does it Take to Improve by 10x or 100x? This week is another host-only episode. Sarah and Elad talk about the path to better model quality, the potential for fine tuning to different use cases, retrieval systems (RAG), feedback systems (RLHF, RLAIF) and Meta’s sponsorship of the open source model ecosystem. Plus Sarah and Elad ask if we’re finally at the beginning of a new set of consumer applications and social networks.</description></item><item><title>If DNA is Code, Can AI Help Write It? Scaling Cell Programming and Synthetic Biology, with Ginkgo Bioworks Co-founder and CEO Jason Kelly | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ginkgo Bioworks is using DNA as code to digitize the cell programming revolution. Ginkgo is using AI and synthetic biology to keep the next pandemic at bay, and accelerate our production capabilities for medicine, food, and agriculture. Ginkgo’s co-founder and CEO Jason Kelly joins hosts Sarah Guo and Elad Gil to discuss bioengineering protein as a foundational model, specialized data learning from an evolutionary perspective, what we need to prepare for a future pandemic, and more.</description></item><item><title>How Replit’s AI Tools are Changing Software Development with Co-founder and CEO Amjad Masad | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 11:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Replit’s develop-to-deploy platform and new AI tool, Ghostwriter, are breaking down the barriers to entry for beginner programmers. Replit’s CEO, co-founder, and head engineer Amjad Masad joins hosts Sarah Guo and Elad Gil to discuss how AI can change software engineering, the infrastructure we still need, open source foundation models, and what to expect from AI agents.
Before co-founding Replit, Amjad Masad worked at Facebook as a software engineer, where he worked on infrastructure tooling.</description></item><item><title>The Intersection of AI and Blockchain, with Transformers author and NEAR founder Illia Polosukhin | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830008/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 11:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830008/</guid><description>Podcast Description More than 25 million users are using NEAR-powered applications. Co-founder of NEAR protocol and Transformers author Illia Polosukhin joins hosts Sarah Guo and Elad Gil to discuss the intersections of crypto and AI technology, what we should expect from AI agents, decentralized data labeling, why AI’s alignment problem is really a human problem, and more. Show Links: Illia Polosukhin - Co-founder of NEAR | LinkedIn NEAR
Sign up for new podcasts every week.</description></item><item><title>The World’s Largest AI Processor with Cerebras CEO Andrew Feldman | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830009/</guid><description>Podcast Description The GPU supply crunch is causing desperation amongst AI teams large and small. Cerebras Systems has an answer, and it’s a chip the size of a dinner plate. Andrew Feldman, CEO and Co-founder of Cerebras and previously SeaMicro, joins Sarah Guo and Elad Gil this week on No Priors. They discuss why there might be an alternative to Nvidia, localized models and predictions for the accelerator market.
Show Links: Andrew Feldman - Cerebras CEO &amp;amp; Co-founder | LinkedIn Cerebras</description></item><item><title>AI Superpowers for Frontend Developers, with Vercel Founder/CEO Guillermo Rauch | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Everything digital is increasingly intermediated through web user experiences, and now AI development can be frontend-first, too. Just ask Guillermo Rauch, the founder and CEO of Vercel, the company behind Next.js. In this episode of No Priors, hosts Sarah Guo and Elad Gil speak to Guillermo about their AI SDK and AI templates, and why Vercel is focused on making it easy for every frontend engineer to build with AI.</description></item><item><title>AI-Powered Biological Software with Jakob Uszkoreit, CEO of Inceptive | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 14:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830011/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;Biological Software&amp;rdquo; is the future of medicine. Jakob Uszkoreit, CEO and Co-founder of Inceptive, joins Sarah Guo and Elad Gil this week on No Priors, to discuss how deep learning is expanding the horizons of RNA and mRNA therapeutics. Jakob co-authored the revolutionary paper Attention is All You Need while at Google, and led early Google Translate and Google Assistant teams. Now at Inceptive, he&amp;rsquo;s applying these same architectures and ideas to biological design, optimizing vaccine production, and magnitude-more efficient drug discovery.</description></item><item><title>The AI Tutor For Every Child and the Next Frontier of Education, From Khan Academy’s Creator Sal Khan | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830012/</guid><description>Podcast Description The future of education is right at your children’s fingertips. Sal Khan, CEO and Founder of Khan Academy, joins Sarah Guo and Elad Gil this week on No Priors. For over a decade, Sal Khan has been trying to reform education, beginning with tutoring his cousins in math. He&amp;rsquo;s the father of the YouTube &amp;ldquo;chalk talk&amp;rdquo; format, and has now served tens of millions of students through Khan Academy.</description></item><item><title>Listener Q&amp;A: 2024 Tech Market Predictions, Long Term Implications of Today’s GPU Crunch, and Will AI Agents Bring Us Happiness? | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830013/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast, Sarah Guo and Elad Gil answer listener questions on the state of technology and artificial intelligence. Sarah and Elad also talk about the 2024 tech market, what type of companies may reach their highest valuation ever and the (former) unicorns that may go bust. Plus, how do Sarah and Elad define happiness? Hint: it’s a use case for a specialized AI agent. Sign up for new podcasts every week.</description></item><item><title>Eradicating Machine Learning Pain Points with Weights &amp; Biases CEO Lukas Biewald | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830014/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830014/</guid><description>Podcast Description How are ML developer tools helping to advance our capabilities? Lukas Biewald, CEO of Weights &amp;amp; Biases, joins Sarah Guo and Elad Gil this week on No Priors. Lukas explores the impact of ML in various industries like gaming, AgTech, and fintech through his insightful perspective. He discusses the impact of LLMs, puts them in context of the evolution of ML engineering over the past decade and a half, and tells the backstory of Weights &amp;amp; Biases&amp;rsquo; success.</description></item><item><title>How Palantir’s AI Bet is Revolutionizing Defense and Beyond, with CTO Shyam Sankar | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can frontiers as high-stakes as next-generation, AI-enabled defense depend on something as mundane as data integration? Can &amp;ldquo;large language models&amp;rdquo; work in such mission critical applications? In this episode of No Priors, hosts Sarah Guo and Elad Gil are joined by Shyam Sankar, the Chief Technical Officer of Palantir Technologies and inventor of their famous Forward Deployed Engineering force.
Early employee and longtime leader Shyam explains the evolution of technology at Palantir, from ontology and data integration to process visualization and now AI.</description></item><item><title>The Timeline for Realistic 4-D: Devi Parikh from Meta on Research Hurdles for Generative AI in Video and Multimodality | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Video dominates modern media consumption, but video creation is still expensive and difficult. AI-generated and edited video is a holy grail of democratized creative expression. This week on No Priors, Sarah Guo and Elad Gil sit down with Devi Parikh. She is a Research Director in Generative AI at Meta and an Associate Professor in the School of Interactive Computing at Georgia Tech. Her work focuses on multimodality and AI for images, audio and video.</description></item><item><title>Bringing AI to the Data Cloud, with Snowflake's CEO Frank Slootman | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Frank Slootman, CEO of Snowflake Computing, joins Sarah Guo and Elad Gil this week on No Priors. Before scaling Snowflake to its blockbuster IPO and beyond, Frank was also the CEO from early to scale for landmark enterprise companies ServiceNow and Data Domain. Frank grew up in the Netherlands and is also the author of three books: Amp It Up, Rise of the Data Cloud, and Tape Sucks. In this episode, our hosts talk with Frank about the opportunity for generative AI in the enterprise, why Snowflake isn&amp;rsquo;t really a data warehousing company, their acquisitions of Neeva and Streamlit, apps within Snowflake, and how AI relates to traditional analytics and BI.</description></item><item><title>What's for Dinner? AI-Driven Commerce with Instacart CEO Fidji Simo | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830018/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fidji Simo, the CEO of Instacart and co-founder of Metrodora Institute, a medical center and research institute for neuroimmune axis disorders, shares her personal journey from growing up in France, to leading the Facebook app, to becoming a wartime CEO. Fidji talks about the future of Instacart, their AI strategy, how the current era of AI is different from prior ML waves, and the impact of LLMs in commerce, robotics and healthcare.</description></item><item><title>What happens to Observability If Code is AI-Generated? The Potential for AI in DevOps, with Datadog Co-founder/CEO Olivier Pomel | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Olivier Pomel, co-founder and CEO of Datadog, the leading observability company, discusses the company’s founding story, early product sequencing, platform strategy, and acquisitions. Olivier also shares his thoughts on their more recent expansion into security, and why he’s bullish on the potential for AI in DevOps. ** No Priors is taking a summer break! The podcast will be back with new episodes in three weeks. Join us on July 20th for a conversation with Devi Parikh, Research Director in Generative AI at Meta.</description></item><item><title>Listener Q&amp;A: AI Misconceptions, The Reality of Regulation, Infinite Context, Incumbent AI Execution and Startup Ideas | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830020/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on No Priors, Sarah and Elad do another hangout to answer listener questions. Topics include debunking common misconceptions about AI and its implications on the world, the analogy to nuclear power and nuclear safety, the impact of larger context windows, developer productivity, incumbent announcements of AI products, and some requests for (fat) startups. No Priors is now on YouTube! Subscribe to the channel on YouTube and like this episode.</description></item><item><title>AI &amp; Defense Technology with Anduril CEO Brian Schimpf | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today on No Priors, we discuss defense technology, AI, drones, and autonomous vehicles (think giant submarine drones!) with Brian Schimpf, the co-founder and CEO of Anduril, a next-generation defense technology company. From his early days of coding at age 12 to working on self-driving cars, and finally founding Anduril, Brian&amp;rsquo;s incredible journey led him to create innovative solutions for pressing defense problems. This episode covers the impact of AI, intelligent software, and other technologies to defense.</description></item><item><title>Going Full Send on AI, and the (Positive) Impact of AI on Jobs, with Kevin Scott, CTO of Microsoft | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830022/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Sarah and Elad speak with Microsoft CTO Kevin Scott about his unlikely journey from rural Virginia to becoming the driving force behind Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s AI strategy. Sarah and Elad discuss the partnership that Kevin helped forge between Microsoft and OpenAI and explore the vision both companies have for the future of AI. They also discuss yesterday’s announcement of “copilots” across the Microsoft product suite, Microsoft’s GPU computing budget, the potential impact of open source AI models in the tech industry, the future of AI in relation to jobs, why Kevin is bullish on creative and physical work, and predictions for progress in AI this year.</description></item><item><title>The AI Will See You Now: Exploring Biomedical AI and Google’s Med-PaLM2 With Karan Singhal | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830023/</guid><description>Podcast Description What if AI could revolutionize healthcare with advanced language learning models? Sarah and Elad welcome Karan Singhal, Staff Software Engineer at Google Research, who specializes in medical AI and the development of MedPaLM2. On this episode, Karan emphasizes the importance of safety in medical AI applications and how language models like MedPaLM2 have the potential to augment scientific workflows and transform the standard of care. Other topics include the best workflows for AI integration, the potential impact of AI on drug discoveries, how AI can serve as a physician&amp;rsquo;s assistant, and how privacy-preserving machine learning and federated learning can protect patient data, while pushing the boundaries of medical innovation.</description></item><item><title>Will Everyone Have a Personal AI? With Mustafa Suleyman, Founder of DeepMind and Inflection | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830024/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mustafa Suleyman, co-founder of DeepMind and now co-founder and CEO of Inflection AI, joins Sarah and Elad to discuss how his interests in counseling, conflict resolution, and intelligence led him to start an AI lab that pioneered deep reinforcement learning, lead applied AI and policy efforts at Google, and more recently found Inflection and launch Pi. Mustafa offers insights on the changing structure of the web, the pressure Google faces in the age of AI personalization, predictions for model architectures, how to measure emotional intelligence in AIs, and the thinking behind Pi: the AI companion that knows you, is aligned to your interests, and provides companionship.</description></item><item><title>Personalizing AI Models with Kelvin Guu, Senior Staff Research Scientist, Google Brain | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830025/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830025/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do you personalize AI models? A popular school of thought in AI is to just dump all the data you need into pre-training or fine tuning. But that may be less efficient and less controllable than alternatives — using AI models as a reasoning engine against external data sources. Kelvin Guu, Senior Staff Research Scientist at Google, joins Sarah and Elad this week to talk about retrieval, memory, training data attribution and model orchestration.</description></item><item><title>Listener Q&amp;A: AI Investment Hype, Foundation Models, Regulation, Opportunity Areas, and More | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830026/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830026/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on No Priors, Sarah and Elad answer listener questions about tech and AI. Topics covered include the evolution of open-source models, Elon AI, regulating AI, areas of opportunity, and AI hype in the investing environment. Sarah and Elad also delve into the impact of AI on drug development and healthcare, and the balance between regulation and innovation. Sign up for new podcasts every week. Email feedback to show@no-priors.</description></item><item><title>The Computing Platform Underlying AI, with Jensen Huang, Founder &amp; CEO of NVIDIA | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830027/</guid><description>Podcast Description So much of the AI conversation today revolves around models and new applications. But this AI revolution would not be possible without one thing – GPUs, Nvidia GPUs. The Nvidia A100 is the workhorse of today’s AI ecosystem. This week on No Priors, Sarah Guo and Elad Gil sit down with Jensen Huang, the founder and CEO of NVIDIA, at their Santa Clara headquarters. Jensen co-founded the company in 1993 with a goal to create chips that accelerated graphics.</description></item><item><title>Your AI Friends Have Awoken, With Noam Shazeer | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830028/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Noam Shazeer played a key role in developing key foundations of modern AI - including co-inventing Transformers at Google, as well as pioneering AI chat pre-chatGPT. These are the foundations supporting today’s AI revolution. On this episode of No Priors, Noam discusses his work as an AI researcher, engineer, inventor, and now CEO. Noam Shazeer is currently the CEO and Co-founder of Character AI, a service that allows users to design and interact with their own personal bots that take on the personalities of well-known individuals or archetypes.</description></item><item><title>The Future is Small Models, with Matei Zaharia, CTO of Databricks | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830029/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830029/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you have 30 dollars, a few hours, and one server, then you are ready to create a ChatGPT-like model that can do what’s known as instruction-following. Databricks’ latest launch, Dolly, foreshadows a potential move in the industry toward smaller and more accessible but extremely capable AIs. Plus, Dolly is open source, requires less computing power, and fewer data parameters than its counterparts. Matei Zaharia, Cofounder &amp;amp; Chief Technologist at Databricks, joins Sarah and Elad to talk about how big data sets actually need to be, why manual annotation is becoming less necessary to train some models, and how he went from a Berkeley PhD student with a little project called Spark to the founder of a company that is now critical data infrastructure that’s increasingly moving into AI.</description></item><item><title>What’s Beyond GitHub Copilot? With Copilot's Chief Architect and founder of Minion.AI Alex Graveley | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830030/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Everyone talks about the future impact of AI, but there’s already an AI product that has revolutionized a profession. Alex Graveley was the principal engineer and Chief Architect behind Github Copilot, a sort of pair-programmer that auto-completes your code as you type. It has rapidly become a product that developers won’t live without, and the most leaned-upon analogy for every new AI startup – Copilot for Finance, Sales, Marketing, Support, Writing, Decision-Making.</description></item><item><title>How do we go from search engines to answer engines? With Perplexity AI’s Aravind Srinivas and Denis Yarats | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830031/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830031/</guid><description>Podcast Description With advances in machine learning, the way we search for information online will never be the same. This week on the No Priors podcast, we dive into a startup that aims to be the most trustworthy place to search for information online. Perplexity.ai is a search engine that provides answers to questions in a conversational way and hints at what the future of search might look like. Aravind Srinivas is a Co-founder and CEO of Perplexity.</description></item><item><title>What is the future of search? With Neeva’s Sridhar Ramaswamy | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830032/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830032/</guid><description>Podcast Description For the first time in decades web search might be at risk for disruption. Bing is allied with OpenAI to integrate LLMs. Google has committed to launching new products. New startups are emerging. Sridhar Ramaswamy co-founded the challenger AI-powered, private search platform Neeva in 2019. He is a former 16-year Google veteran who most recently led the internet’s most profitable business as SVP in charge of Google Ads, Commerce and Privacy.</description></item><item><title>What is the role of academia in modern AI research? With Stanford Professor Dr. Percy Liang | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830033/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830033/</guid><description>Podcast Description When AI research is evolving at warp speed and takes significant capital and compute power, what is the role of academia? Dr. Percy Liang – Stanford computer science professor and director of the Stanford Center for Research on Foundation Models talks about training costs, distributed infrastructure, model evaluation, alignment, and societal impact. Sarah Guo and Elad Gil join Percy at his office to discuss the evolution of research in NLP, why AI developers should aim for superhuman levels of performance, the goals of the Center for Research on Foundation Models, and Together, a decentralized cloud for artificial intelligence.</description></item><item><title>How AI can make drug discovery fail less, with Daphne Koller from Insitro | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830034/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Life-saving therapeutics continue to grow more costly to discover. At the same time, recent advances in using machine learning for the life sciences and medicine are extraordinary. Are we on the verge of a paradigm shift in biotech? This week on the podcast, a pioneer in AI, Daphne Koller, joins Sarah Guo and Elad Gil on the podcast to help us explore that question. Daphne is the CEO and founder of Insitro — a company that applies machine learning to pharma discovery and development, specifically by leveraging “induced pluripotent stem cells.</description></item><item><title>Why the Future of Machine Learning is Open Source with Huggingface’s Clem Delangue | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830035/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830035/</guid><description>Podcast Description After starting as a talking emoji companion, Hugging Face is now an organizing force for the open source AI research ecosystem. Its models are used by companies such as Apple, Salesforce and Microsoft, and it&amp;rsquo;s working to become the GitHub for ML. This week on the podcast, Sarah Guo and Elad Gil talk to Clem Delangue, co-founder and CEO of Hugging Face. Clem shares how they shifted away from their original product, why every employee at Hugging Face is responsible for community-building, the modalities he&amp;rsquo;s most interested in, and what role open source has in the AI race.</description></item><item><title>Founder Stories: What’s behind the largest commercial autonomous system on earth? With Zipline’s Keller Rinaudo Cliffton | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830036/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830036/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a special bonus episode from our Founder Stories series, where entrepreneurs share the story of their startup journey. A delivery with Zipline is the closest thing we have to teleportation. It sounds like science fiction, but Zipline delivers life saving medical supplies such as blood and vaccines to hospitals, doctors and people in need around the world with the world&amp;rsquo;s largest autonomous drone network. This week on the podcast, Sarah Guo talks to Keller Rinaudo Cliffton, the co-founder and CEO of Zipline, about building a full-stack business that involves software, hardware and operations, how a culture of ruthless engineering practicality enabled them to do unlikely things, the state of autopilot in aircraft, their AI acoustic detect-and-avoid system, and why founders should build for users beyond the &amp;ldquo;golden billion.</description></item><item><title>How can we make sure that everyone has access to AI? Can small models outperform large models? With Stability AI’s Emad Mostaque | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830037/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830037/</guid><description>Podcast Description AI-generated images have been everywhere over the past year, but one company has fueled an explosive developer ecosystem around large image models: Stability AI. Stability builds open AI tools with a mission to improve humanity. Stability AI is most known for Stable Diffusion, the AI model where a user puts in a natural language prompt and the AI generates images. But they&amp;rsquo;re also engaged in progressing models in natural language, voice, video, and biology.</description></item><item><title>What does AI-powered content creation look like? with Runway ML’s Cristobal Valenzuela | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830038/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830038/</guid><description>Podcast Description For a long time, AI-generated images and video felt like a fun toy. Cool, but not something that would bring value to professional content creators. But now we are at the exciting moment where machine learning tools have the power to unlock more creative ideas. This week on the podcast, Sarah Guo and Elad Gil talk to Cristobal Valenzuela, a technologist, artist and software developer. He’s also the CEO and co-founder of Runway, a web-based tool that allows creatives to use machine learning to generate and edit video.</description></item><item><title>The bot Cicero can collaborate, scheme and build trust with humans. What does this mean for the next frontier of AI? With Noam Brown, Research Scientist at Meta | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830046/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830046/</guid><description>Podcast Description AGI can beat top players in chess, poker, and, now, Diplomacy. In November 2022, a bot named Cicero demonstrated mastery in this game, which requires natural language negotiation and cooperation with humans. In short, Cicero can lie, scheme, build trust, pass as human, and ally with humans. So what does that mean for the future of AGI? This week’s guest is research scientist Noam Brown. He co-created Cicero on the Meta Fundamental AI Research Team, and is considered one of the smartest engineers and researchers working in AI today.</description></item><item><title>The bot Cicero can collaborate, scheme and build trust with humans. What does this mean for the next frontier of AI? With Noam Brown, Research Scientist at Meta | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830039/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830039/</guid><description>Podcast Description AGI can beat top players in chess, poker, and, now, Diplomacy. In November 2022, a bot named Cicero demonstrated mastery in this game, which requires natural language negotiation and cooperation with humans. In short, Cicero can lie, scheme, build trust, pass as human, and ally with humans. So what does that mean for the future of AGI? This week’s guest is research scientist Noam Brown. He co-created Cicero on the Meta Fundamental AI Research Team, and is considered one of the smartest engineers and researchers working in AI today.</description></item><item><title>This is “No Priors” | No Priors: Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Technology | Startups</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3162830040/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3162830040/</guid><description>Podcast Description AI is transforming our future, but what does that really mean? In ten years, will humans be forced to please our AGI overlords or will we have unlocked unlimited capacity for human potential? That&amp;rsquo;s why Sarah Guo and Elad Gil started this new podcast, named No Priors. In each episode, Sarah and Elad talk with the leading engineers, researchers and founders in AI, across the stack. We&amp;rsquo;ll talk about the technical state of the art, how that impacts business, and get them to predict what&amp;rsquo;s next.</description></item></channel></rss>