<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/duncan-garner-editor-in-chief/</link><description>Recent content in Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 01:01:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/duncan-garner-editor-in-chief/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Slam Dunc #157 - We need to get better at celebrating success in New Zealand | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590101/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 01:01:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590101/</guid><description>Podcast Description My old school, Westlake Boys High, have won rugby’s World Schools Festival in Thailand. I'm so pleased for them but in New Zealand we can sometimes be reluctant to celebrate our successes publicly, be it sporting, business or otherwise.
Does the 'Tall Poppy' syndrome still exist in Kiwi culture? Should we be shouting louder about our successes?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>You asked and we delivered; Mumsy is back | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590102/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:48:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mumsy gets nearly as much fan mail as we do, so it only seemed right to get her back in the studio one last time this year.
How has her year been, what might her 2024 look like, and can I get her to sing a Xmas carol (spoiler alert - yes I can...)
Oh, and Mumsy has her first fan experience. Who and where was it?!
See omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #156 - Nicola Willis, Grant Robertson and 'the numbers' - where is the Auditor General? | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590103/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:35:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nicola Willis is doing what every incoming government does and that is to trash the reputation of the previous government. She is basically saying they openly misled Kiwis to make themselves look like better economic managers than they were. We have a Public Finance Act, and an Auditor General. Can someone please get to the bottom of this...
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Demanding better: The fight for disability rights and accountability | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590104/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:17:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Casey is a mother whose fortitude is tried and tested to it's limits as she fights for the rights of her two-year-old son, Wolf. Born prematurely and diagnosed with cerebral palsy, Wolf's journey is a complex labyrinth of disability care options and services. Casey's passion echoes through the episode as she shares her skirmishes with ACC over coverage and her trying dispute with their disability service provider.
There's a profound power in claiming accountability.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #155 - Fair pay or fair enough? | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590001/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:14:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590001/</guid><description>Podcast Description One of the last things the last government did was to bring in fair pay agreements.
One of the first things the new government has done is to repeal those fair pay agreements.
So, who has got it right when it comes to fair pay?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>'The Week That Was' with Nickson Clark and Leah Panapa | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590002/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:05:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590002/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the penultimate 'Week That Was' panel for the year I'm joined by The Edge afternoon host, and greenskeeper, Nickson Clark, and radio royalty Leah Panapa. Plenty to get stuck into this week:
All the things the government are repealing.
What is going on with the Cook Strait ferries?
Should we be allowed to drive on our beaches?
And is leaving passive aggressive notes for stranger ever a good idea.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #154 - What to do with the Cook Strait ferries? | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:51:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590003/</guid><description>Podcast Description The new government has said 'no thanks' to KiwiRail’s request for an extra $1.47 billion for infrastructure needed for Cook Strait’s new mega-ferries.
There's no doubt the costs around the project have blown out, but where does this leave the vital inter-island crossing, and what does the government now do about it?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A chat with the next generation: The world according to my 13yo son and his mates | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:45:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590004/</guid><description>Podcast Description When I was their age, my biggest concerns were probably what toy I wanted for my birthday or how much more time I could spare to play outside before sunset. But, in today's episode, my young guests, Buster, Lukka, and Jarelle , show us that being 12 or 13 isn't all fun and games. As we chat about everything from school reports and math grades to the implications of climate change and lowering the voting age to 16, I'm often left in awe of their profound insights.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #153 - Prime Minister Winston Peters... | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 01:29:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590005/</guid><description>Podcast Description At 79 a lot of men are spending their pension, getting a funeral plan sorted, wearing the same cords for the third straight day and playing indoor fake lawn bowls whilst waiting for meals on wheels to show up.
Not Winnie - he's just knocked out a 24hr stint as Acting Prime Minister. So, how did he do?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Feeding New Zealand: The story behind the 'Meat The Need' telethon | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 01:26:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ready to feel inspired and make a difference? Join me for a heartening conversation with Wayne Langford, the driving force behind the life-changing 'Meat the Need' telethon. The aim? To provide a whopping 1.2 million meat and milk meals for 110 food banks across New Zealand. Wayne, a humble farmer with a massive heart, takes us through the conception of this incredible charity event as it enters it's second year.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #152 - The two Luxons vs the mobilising Maori | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590007/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:27:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590007/</guid><description>Podcast Description It seems to me there are two distinctly different Christopher Luxons - Private Chris and Public Chris.
Either way, one of the Luxons needs to guide his coalition pals Winston and David away from a potential race war cliff.
Maori are increasingly unhappy, and rightly so. And they are not going to go quietly.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mastering stress-free productivity with Nat Milne | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:18:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Step into the shoes of Nat Milne, a successful businesswoman who has cracked the code to stress-free productivity. This episode is your golden ticket to understanding how to create a healthy work-life balance, as Nat shares her journey and the transformative impact the Beminded program has had on her life. Hear about her struggles and successes in juggling a thriving business and family life, and get an insider's view on how managing stress became her gateway to success.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #151 - Xmas may not be so merry this year | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590009/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 00:58:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590009/</guid><description>Podcast Description We've been saying this a fair bit recently but this has been a tough year for many of us. And unfortunately next year may not see much improvement.
So how can we keep our spirits up and our stress levels down over the holiday season?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Innovations and stigmas in addiction support | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 00:49:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join us for an eye-opening conversation with River Paton from Pivot by Explore, a holistic alcohol, drug, and wellbeing service. We explore Pivot's unique approach to helping individuals grappling with substance use, addressing the difference between heavy drinking and addiction, and how self-referrals can initiate the journey towards recovery. River's insights underscore the importance of trained professionals and wellbeing coaches with lived experience, whose authenticity helps build stronger connections with their clients.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #150 - Today I am a proud, but concerned, Dad | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590011/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 01:05:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today I am full of fatherly pride. But I am also concerned we are in danger of being divided along 'iwi versus Kiwi' lines.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>'The Week That Was' with Mark Sainsbury and Wilhelmina Shrimpton | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590012/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:44:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590012/</guid><description>Podcast Description I'm joined by a couple of broadcasting legends for this weeks panel. Men's health campaigner Mark Sainsbury and founder &amp;amp; director at Wils &amp;amp; Co Media Wilhelmina Shrimpton sit down with me to discuss:
Mark Mitchell's police agenda.
The govt's tax cuts.
Pookeno.
And selecting overseas All Blacks.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #149 - A cyberattack warning for us all to heed | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590013/</guid><description>Podcast Description This could happen to any of us.
Kiwi covers band 'The Pink Floyd Experience' recently lost everything to hackers. Their business, social media pages, their identities and their ability to make money.
So how did it end? It’s a warning to us all.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The impact of identity theft: A rock bands saga | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590014/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590014/</guid><description>Podcast Description We have all heard about hackers stealing identities, but have you ever wondered how it impacts individuals and businesses on a professional and personal level?
In this episode I bring you an intimate conversation with Darren Whittaker, the lead man of 'The Pink Floyd Experience' tribute band, who knows all too well the havoc that cyber-criminals can wreak. He walks us through the harrowing experience of losing control of their social media accounts, thereby stalling their operations and even holding up an upcoming tour.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #148 - I'm no longer the alpha male | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:12:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590015/</guid><description>Podcast Description There comes a time in a fathers life when he just has to admit that his son now has the wood on him. I have been putting off owning up to it, but for me, that time is now...
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Changing lives: The "I Have a Dream" story | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:07:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ever been punched in the gut by a societal issue? That's how it feels tackling the lack of wrap-around services for underprivileged children in our communities.
As we showcase the amazing work of the "I Have a Dream" charity in this episode, we're reminded of just how vital these services are. This charity pairs kids with navigators to guide them through school and into adulthood – a truly inspirational approach.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #147 - Nice try Christoper Luxon... | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:21:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590017/</guid><description>Podcast Description The government is softening us up for changes in their so-called 'mini budget'. But what did I hear in Christopher Luxon's announcement yesterday?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Understanding New Zealand's gang culture with Jarrod Gilbert | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590018/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:12:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Discover a world that lies under the radar yet influences society in profound ways. Renowned gang researcher, Jarrod Gilbert, takes us on a journey into the heart of New Zealand's gangs.
Gilbert, having lived amidst these communities for six years, brings unique insider perspectives. He dissects the nuances of gang culture, and the ethical dilemmas he faced during his time with the gangs. We look at the complexities of gang-community dynamics, the potential fallout from new firearms laws, and the realities of gang-related issues often overlooked by policy makers.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #146 - Repealing the smoking laws: the saga continues.. | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 00:41:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Still the story rages on, and the more the Government explains the dumping of our smoke free laws to pay for tax cuts, the more they sound like they're losing the argument.
Rather than being laudable, this policy is laughable. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Championing children's rights with Chief Children's Commissioner Dr Claire Achmad | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 00:30:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590020/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode I sit down with the newly appointed Chief Children's Commissioner Dr Claire Achmad, for an important conversation on children's rights in New Zealand.
Dr Achmad shares her thoughts on the necessity for advocacy for these rights, spotlighting the often-dismissed matters in governmental decision-making processes that directly impact our younger generation. From child poverty, accessibility to healthcare and education, to the silent epidemic of family violence, Dr Achmad provides an in-depth analysis of real-life challenges that children in New Zealand face.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #145 - Surviving the staff Xmas Party.. | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590021/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:37:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tis the season for socialising with work colleagues. Here is your old mate EIC's advice to survive, and thrive, at the staff Xmas party...
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>'The Week That Was' with Simon Pound and Mel Homer | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:25:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590022/</guid><description>Podcast Description My guests this week are partner at Previously Unavailable, co founder of Ingrid Starnes and host of ‘Business is Boring’ podcast Simon Pound, and broadcaster and Celebrity Treasure Island survivor Mel Homer. Lots to sink our teeth into this week...
The government's 'First 100 Days' plans.
Is there a gender double-standard around being drunk in public?
Should government departments be phasing out te reo Maori?
And why oh why don't we use investment funds to fund infrastructure projects in this country?</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #144 - Why I feel sorry for Tory Whanau | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 01:32:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wellington mayor Tory Whanau has come out and admitted she has a problem with alcohol.
Why people feel the need to film public figures living their supposedly private lives is another story, but this is not the first instance of publicly elected officials and alcohol not mixing well.
However, I have a sense we could be seeing some double-standards at play here...
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Peter Montgomery: Sailing, broadcasting, and heartbreaking loss | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590024/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 01:14:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join me for an intimate journey with one of my all-time favourite broadcasters, the legendary PJ Montgomery.
Peter sheds light on the personal and professional aspects of his life, from finding himself in the commentary booth through to the recent loss of his beloved wife Claudia.
He also talks frankly about the profound transformation he's witnessed in the broadcasting arena. Ever wondered how the digital age has reshaped the world of broadcasting?</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #143 - The new government's disgraceful u-turn on smoking | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 00:51:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590025/</guid><description>Podcast Description I find it extraordinary that in 2023 I'm even saying something like this but has this new government traded peoples lives in order to fund tax cuts for the wealthy?
I am of course talking about the decision to scrap New Zealand's world-leading 'generation ban' on smoking.
Some health experts are saying this repealing could cost up to 5,000 lives per year. It is morally bankrupt, and I am utterly stunned.</description></item><item><title>Sam Stubbs: Revolutionising New Zealand's approach to housing and investment | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 00:43:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Simplicity founder Sam Stubbs is wanting to change the way New Zealander's look at housing, and investing in infrastructure in general. In this episode he joins me to for a look into the current housing crisis and what he, and others, could and should be doing about it. He also discusses the role New Zealand's pension funds should play in long-term investments in infrastructure projects, comparing their impact on economic growth with successful models like Singapore and Denmark.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #142 - Accepting and embracing our differences | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590027/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 00:58:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gay or straight, black or white, big or small - human beings are all different.
I have no time for people or organisations who marginalise or discriminate against those who they perceive to be different to them.
Who are we to be judging how other people choose to live their lives? Why not focus our efforts on getting along a little better?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Empathy, acceptance, and advocacy: Robert Rakete &amp; Jeanette Thomas on parenting transgender children | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590028/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 00:49:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ever wondered what it's like to raise a transgender child? As well as being cohosts on The Breeze radio station, Robert Rakete and Jeanette Thomas are both parents to transgender children.
These two offer a candid peek into their lives, sharing intimate experiences and the battles they’ve fought for acceptance. They speak frankly about their struggles, their triumphs, and the unique journey of parenting a transgender child.
Despite prejudices and fears still plaguing the transgender community, Robert &amp;amp; Jeanette share heartening tales of acceptance.</description></item><item><title>Kamahl Santamaria on his mental health | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590029/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 02:45:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Warning: The following content includes discussions about suicidal thoughts that may cause emotional distress.
In this Editor-in-Chief discussion, Kamahl Santamaria discusses the severe impact on his mental health following allegations of inappropriate behavior at TVNZ.
Need to talk? Free call or text 1737 any time for support from a trained counsellor.
Lifeline – 0800 543 354 (0800 LIFELINE) or free text 4357 (HELP).
Youthline – 0800 376 633, free text 234 or email talk@youthline.</description></item><item><title>An exclusive interview with controversial journalist Kamahl Santamaria | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590030/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 01:24:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590030/</guid><description>Podcast Description In his first public interview in 18 months controversial journalist Kamahl Santamaria sits down with the Editor in Chief to tell his side of the story.
Santamaria was sensationally removed from TVNZ's 'Breakfast' show last year after only 32 days as host. The press release said it was due to a 'family emergency' but it since transpired that there were allegations of inappropriate behaviour toward female staff members. This wasn't the first time these sorts of allegations had been made against Santamaria.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #140 - Christopher from marketing gets to work | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590031/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 00:24:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mr Outcomes has finally wrangled his coalition partners into a hopefully cohesive government.
But now the real work starts, and the country waits with baited breath..
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>'The Week That Was' with Simon Bridges and Carmen Vicelich | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590032/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 00:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590032/</guid><description>Podcast Description She was a lively old 'Week That Was' panel today! I was joined by Chief Executive of the Auckland Chamber of Commerce Simon Bridges and Founder and CEO of Valocity and Data Insight Carmen Vicelich to discuss:
The coalition negotiations.
Congestion charges.
Why the 'City of Sails' can't seem to host any sailing events.
And the dire state of our marine environments.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #139 - Deputy PM; David vs Goliath | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590033/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 01:23:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590033/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the coalition negotiations finally seem to be drawing to a close, the most significant sticking point seems to be who will be Deputy Prime Minister.
Seymour once said it's not about the jobs. It's always about the jobs..
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Pio Terei on cultural crossroads, parenthood and more | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590034/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 01:16:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join us on this candid journey with Pio Terei, a revered comedian, actor, and two-decade veteran at The Parenting Place. With a twinkle in his eye and a wealth of experience, Pio speaks about living between the Māori and Pākehā worlds, painting a vivid picture of New Zealand's societal evolution. We traverse topics that dig deep into the heart of our daily lives, unravelling the beauty of simplicity, the dangers of excessive device usage, and the misunderstood concept of wealth.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #138 - The rape and pillaging of our fishing stocks | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590035/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 00:15:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590035/</guid><description>Podcast Description It feels like we have been discussing and debating this for years and yet here we are in 2023 and we still have a problem with destructive and unsustainable fishing practices in New Zealand.
We are one of the last countries in the South Pacific to still bottom trawl. It's impact can be devastating. What can be done, and who will do it?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>The overfishing crisis: New Zealand's marine dilemma | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590036/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 00:10:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590036/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode we navigate New Zealand's troubled fishing waters with Sam Woolford from LegaSea. Sam gives us a harrowing look at the devastating impact of commercial bottom trawling on marine life, the alarming loss of species and benthic environment destruction contributing to this crisis. In particular we take a hard look at the issue of overfishing and the use of destructive fishing techniques in the Hauraki Gulf Marine Park.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #137 - MFAT and te reo Maori.. | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590037/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 00:27:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590037/</guid><description>Podcast Description MFAT is a ministry usually too scared to make any decision unless it’s made for them.
So why does it appear they are looking at removing te reo Maori from some of it's official useage?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Breaking free from the Brethren: Craig Hoyle's incredible story | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590038/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 00:18:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590038/</guid><description>Podcast Description We're pulling back the curtain on the exclusive religious sect known as the Exclusive Brethren with our guest, Craig Hoyle, author of the new bestselling book "Excommunicated".
Raised in the unyielding grip of the Brethren, Craig exposes the generational trauma and unravels the intricacies of his deeply personal journey of self-discovery and acceptance within a rigid religious community. He shares the pangs of guilt surrounding his sexuality, the futile attempts at 'curing' him through prayer and exorcism, and his futile relocation to Australia.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #136 - Coalitions and media moanings | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590039/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:22:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590039/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the coalition negotiations continue I wonder whether some in the media are paying too much attention to the length of time it is taking.
Does the general public really care as much as the media think? I am not so sure..
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Exploring the cosmos with Rocket Lab Founder, Peter Beck | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590040/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:11:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ever wondered how a tool and die maker apprentice from New Zealand ended up launching rockets into space and competing with the likes of Jeff Bezos and Elon Musk?
Strap in for a thrilling journey with Peter Beck, the founder of Rocket Lab, who's daring to dream big and rewrite the rules of the space industry. With 22 rocket launches planned for next year and the Neutron, a larger rocket designed for lifting heavier satellites into low Earth orbit, Rocket Lab is heading for the stars.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #135 - Why I'm getting better at sleeping | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590041/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 23:49:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590041/</guid><description>Podcast Description I'm an 'active relaxer'. I struggle to sit still for too long. I like doing stuff.
This has traditionally meant that I've not been great at getting a restful nights sleep as I often find myself lying awake with an overactive brain.
However, I've recently found something that seems to be helping with the sleeping blues..
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>'The Week That Was' with Graeme Hill and Petra Bagust | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590042/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 23:47:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590042/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week I'm joined by not only two great New Zealander's but two of our best broadcasters. Graeme Hill, who has branched out into avocados, and Petra Bagust, host of the 'Grey Area's' podcast, are in studio with the EIC to discuss:
The missing coalition government.
Protecting our kids from violent pornography.
Thrifting.
And the highs and lows of travelling alone.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunk #134 - Bank profits in New Zealand | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590043/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 01:01:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you bank locally? Or are you, like the vast majority of Kiwis, with one of the big four Australian-owned banks?
It's reporting season for bank profits and yet again the numbers are eye-watering. So why don't more of us bank local to try and keep more of our money in the country?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Boxing rings and boardrooms: The Dean Lonergan story | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590044/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 00:57:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join us for an inspiring chat with Dean Lonergan, the hard-working Kiwi league player and entrepreneur who has tasted both success and failure in equal measure.
Lonergan shares his journey from rugby league international to the multi-million dollar promotions business. He is one of the industry's good guys and his candid anecdotes and insights from his life and career will inspire and motivate anyone with a passion for sports or entrepreneurship.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #133 - What coalition government? | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590045/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 00:47:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590045/</guid><description>Podcast Description I'm filing a missing report with the police today. One coalition government - have you seen it?
For some so supposedly driven by outcomes, Christopher Luxon seems to have stumbled at the very first hurdle..
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Online thrifting: Conscious consumerism with Wendy Quach | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590046/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 00:43:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Remember the sheer joy of discovering a hidden gem in a thrift store? Our guest today, Wendy Quach, founder of '&amp;amp; Again', has transformed that experience into a unique online platform. Wendy has ingeniously married her passion for thrifting and her tech background into a streamlined process, making it effortlessly simple to sell secondhand clothes online. From a modest beginning in her parents’ bedroom, she has grown her venture into an expansive 280-square-metre warehouse.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #132 What our kids are seeing online: the disturbing reality | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590047/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:54:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590047/</guid><description>Podcast Description So many of our under 12yo's have access to devices that can quickly and easily get them online. Once there they are at the mercy of the 'wild west' that is the internet.
So what are they being exposed to, how is it getting in front of them, and who's responsibility should it be to police and educate?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Protecting our children: A call to arms against online exploitation | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590048/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:46:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590048/</guid><description>Podcast Description The online world is a wild west, where our children are exposed to unspeakable acts of depravity. From real rape scenes to animal bestiality, the online content accessible to our youngsters is a ticking time bomb. We’re going to strip this issue bare, question why protective measures are not in place, and call out the lack of governmental action. We’re pushing for effective blocks, barriers, and firewalls to shield our children from this horror show.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #131 - Against Paul Henry's advice, I meet a listener... | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590049/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 01:20:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Legendary broadcaster Paul Henry once offered me some sage advice around meeting your fans/listeners. Don't do it, they're bound to be crazy.
With those 'wise words' ringing in my ears, I headed off to a remote island with a couple of fans of the podcast...
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Travelling alone in your 70's: Mumsy's tale.. | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590050/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 01:08:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Due to illness, Mumsy found herself minus her travelling partner on the eve of a big trip to Europe. In your 70's this can be a worrying situation, but I suggested that she go on the trip by herself as who knows when she may next get the opportunity.
So how did it all pan out, what tips and advice does Mumsy have, would she recommend it to other retirees and what song did she belt out on a karaoke night?</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #130 - My advice to Nice Guy Chippy | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590051/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:07:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Labour are quietly melting down while the eyes of the nation are for the most part on the other team.
The big loser in all this? Nice Guy Chippy..
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>'The Week That Was' with Rawdon Christie and Marie Dyhrberg | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590052/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:01:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590052/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the 'Week That Was' today I'm joined by a GC and a KC - former breakfast tv host turned real estate guru Rawdon Christie, and criminal defence lawyer Marie Dyhrberg:
Are more us struggling with debt than ever before?
Speaking of struggling, if you had to get a side hustle, what would it be?
What is wrong with our nursing industry?
And 'Bird of the Century' goes global!</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #129 - And still a little country waits... | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590053/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 01:03:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Christopher. David. Winston.
One hopes they are furiously beavering away behind the scenes to form a government as quickly as possible. But one is not so sure..
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Habitat for Humanity: 30 years of housing those in need | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590054/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:55:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, I sit down with Alan Thorp from Habitat for Humanity New Zealand, a man who has spent over half his life committed to providing affordable housing for families in need. Alan brings to the table a wealth of knowledge and experience on tackling housing challenges.
Our conversation takes us deep into the intricacies of the New Zealand housing market, where we shine a light on the harsh realities of extended motel living and the financial implications of upgrading state housing.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #128 - Media is doing it tough and you could be next | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590055/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 01:19:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Media companies are often some of the first to feel the pinch when times are tough and other businesses pull back on 'discretionary spending' such as advertising.
The fallout from high inflation is starting to bite. Really bite. So what does this mean for you and I?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bird of the Century and the conservation challenges in New Zealand | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590056/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 01:02:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590056/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this compelling conversation, I am joined by Nicola Toki from Forest and Bird. While Forest &amp;amp; Bird turns 100 this year, the 'Bird of the Year' competition has been running since 2005 and has become a wonderful way to celebrate and learn about nature. This years special 'Bird of the Century' competition has become a global phenomenon, thanks to television star John Oliver's recent involvement.
In the podcast Nicola talks about the remarkable work of Forest and Bird and the sobering reality of conservation challenges in New Zealand, with 82% of all our current native birds on the threatened species list.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #127 - The alarming truth about nursing in NZ | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590057/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 00:39:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590057/</guid><description>Podcast Description On todays podcast episode Amanda (not her real name) spoke openly and honestly about why she quit nursing after loving it for 20 years.
If alarm bells weren't already ringing throughout New Zealand's nursing industry, they most definitely should be.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Unmasking healthcare woes: From veteran nurse to courageous whistleblower | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590058/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 00:35:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590058/</guid><description>Podcast Description I was taken aback when I first heard the nerve-racking stories of Amanda, a 20-year veteran in nursing who courageously decided to walk away from her profession. It's tough to imagine the anguish that Amanda had to endure while facing unsafe practices, assault, and abuse during her tenure in New Zealand hospitals. Our discussion is a revealing portrait of the grim realities of healthcare facilities in these tumultuous times.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #126 - So Winston is once again kingmaker.. | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590059/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 00:26:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Christopher Luxon now finds himself with a tricky balancing act on his hands. On one side you have the wiley old kingmaker Winston Peters, while on the other side is ACT leader David Seymour who, despite getting more of the vote, may now have to play third fiddle...
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Understanding debt: A fresh perspective on collection and management | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590060/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 00:15:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Drawing from his own experiences of growing up in a single parent household struggling with debt, Mark Francis, the executive general manager of DebtManagers, has reimagined debt collection in a way that provides a breath of fresh air. He brings a refreshing perspective to the harsh reality of debt, prioritizing empathy and understanding in an industry often clouded by fear and pressure. Having been at the receiving end of the debt collection process, Mark has made it his mission to redefine the industry by treating customers as people, not just debtors.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #125 - It's quiet out there; too quiet... | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590061/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 00:22:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Politicians. Remember them? They've gone from being everywhere (except on DGEIC if you're Christopher Luxon) to being as hard to spot as a kiwi during daylight hours.
So what is going on behind the closed doors...
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>'The Week That Was' with Paula Bennett and Hamish McKay | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590062/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 00:12:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's 'Week That Was' panel is straight out of the top drawer. Former deputy PM turned commercial real estate whiz Paula Bennett, and fellow real estate agent and legendary sportscaster Hamish McKay get stuck into:
What has happened in politics since the election? Is anybody home?
What has happened to rugby since the RWC final?
The Ruthless Empire case and the 'right to silence'
And what to seek out, and avoid, when bargain shopping
See omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #124 - The right to silence in child abuse cases | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590063/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 01:05:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590063/</guid><description>Podcast Description The tragic case of Ruthless-Empire has once again highlighted something in our legal system that I believe urgently needs looking at.
No right to silence.
No plea bargain.
No discounts on sentence.
No background story.
No sympathy from judges.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Inside politics: A candid conversation with former Labour minister Stuart Nash | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590064/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 01:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pull up a chair as we journey through the labyrinth of political life with former Labour Party Minister Stuart Nash, who imparts fascinating insider tales from his time in Parliament.
Together, we dissect the relentless demands of a ministerial role, delve into complex decision-making during the pandemic era, and appraise key political figures including Jacinda Ardern and Grant Robinson. This candid conversation provides a rare glimpse into the machinations of Parliament, from advocating for constituents and navigating government red tape, to the heated issue of gun reforms.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #123 - Hallowe'en | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590065/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 01:27:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hallowe'en is Americanised rubbish. Not our thing. Annoying. I don't get it and I don't get why it has become so popular here.
Well, that was until yesterday...
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Actress and Pasifika trailblazer Teuila Blakely | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590066/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 01:19:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teuila Blakely will be familiar to many Kiwis thanks to her roles on tv and film productions such as Shortland Street and Sione's Wedding. As such, she has found herself leading the way for Pasifika women in the tv/film industry
She was also involved in a high-profile sex-tape incident with former NZ Warriors player Konrad Hurrell but refused to let that define her. In this episode Teuila talks about her upbringing and the 'overt racism' her family had to overcome, the recent passing of her mother, and what we could learn from our pacific neighbours.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #122 - Are we good losers when it comes to the All Blacks? | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590067/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 00:25:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are we better losers than we used to be when it comes to the All Blacks? Are the bad old days of calling for players heads after a big loss behind us?
I hope so and I hope the New Zealand public give the players the warmest of welcomes when they arrive home after what was ultimately a pretty successful World Cup.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Inside NZ's fuel industry with former Z Energy CEO Mike Bennetts | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590068/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 00:11:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join me for a riveting conversation with Mike Bennetts, the former CEO of Z Energy. Mike shares the trials and tribulations he faced as he tried to transition the company to biofuels. Despite his efforts, the venture was unsuccessful, leading the company to reset its vision, values, strategy, and community connections.
Mike discusses the challenges they faced, the significant investment in revamping convenience stores, how the Shell brand became a limitation for their green aspirations, and shares his insights and considerable experience with fuel pricing and New Zealand's fuel security.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #121 - World Rugby should apologise | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590069/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 02:23:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590069/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 2023 Rugby World Cup final highlighted what any people have been increasingly worried about of late. And that is our traditional national game is broken.
World Rugby need to stand up, take responsibility and fix the bloody thing.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sir Michael Hill - jeweller | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590070/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 02:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590070/</guid><description>Podcast Description For this episode I had the absolute pleasure of talking with New Zealand business royalty Sir Michael Hill.
In an extended chat Michael talks about his upbringing, problems with bullying and family, learning his trade and building a multi-national business empire, those adverts, and passing on his secrets to success to younger New Zealanders.
This is an enthralling conversation with a surprisingly humble man who has been there and done that when it comes to turning a small business into a household name.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #120 - Name suppression | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590071/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 01:12:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590071/</guid><description>Podcast Description A potentially precedent-setting case is currently playing out in our Supreme Court. It involves a young sex offender who is asking for permanent name suppression. Should he get it?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>'The Week That Was' with David Moffett and Christine Rankin | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590072/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 01:08:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590072/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the 'Week That Was' panel this week we have former head of New Zealand Rugby David Moffett, and one of my fav's who is now a leading business advisor at The Engine, Christine Rankin. I get their thoughts on:
The election result and how the leaders fared.
The Rugby World Cup and some naughty All Blacks.
The state of our tourism industry, and where to holiday in UnZud.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #119 - The worrying state of New Zealand's tourism industry | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590073/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 00:59:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pre-Covid, tourism was New Zealand's number one earner. Now it is number three, having shed billions of annual dollars.
While countries such as Australia are upping their tourism marketing spend in order to try and reinvigorate their tourism industry, New Zealand has been cutting back its promotional spending. Is this the right approach? And who should be leading our international tourism charge?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A unique perspective on New Zealand's tourism future with Gavin Oliver | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590074/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 00:51:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590074/</guid><description>Podcast Description My guest today is Gavin Oliver, the founding director of EcoZip Adventures. Gavin's journey from UK visitor to successful business owner brings a unique perspective to the conversation about the trials and triumphs of New Zealand's tourism sector.
We dig into the current state of the industry, and ask if the absence of tourism dialogue in recent political campaigns is a missed opportunity. How should New Zealand revamp its tourism strategies?</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #118 - The Labour Party's fight for survival | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590075/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 01:20:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590075/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a shall we say 'underwhelming' election result, is the Labour Party actually now fighting for its survival?
It sounds drastic to say that but I believe they could be in danger of becoming a minor party, or even slowly dying out altogether..
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The future is hybrid: The implications and challenges of working remotely | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590076/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 01:06:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Prepare to have your assumptions about hybrid work shattered. Promising to reveal the inner workings of this new normal, my guest Gillian Brookes, a renowned expert on hybrid working, weighs in on the impact it has on our lives and how we are acclimating to this shift.
Research that shows how getting it right at home can potentially increase productivity by around 3-4%. What are the potential cost savings for businesses by having a remote workforce?</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #117 - Do we need a treaty referendum? | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590077/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 00:30:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590077/</guid><description>Podcast Description ACT Party leader David Seymour has reiterated a referendum on the principles of the Treaty of Waitangi would be a condition for forming a government in coalition with National.
Surely this is the last thing New Zealand needs at the moment?!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Navigating neurodiversity with Phillis Meti: A champion's perspective | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590078/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 00:11:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get ready to be enthralled as I am joined by Phillis Meti, a four-time golfing world champion in the long drive format.
Phillis is currently in Atlanta preparing for her fifth world championship but takes time out to talk with DGEIC about her 17 years at the top, her passion for helping others, and the neurodiversity battles she has had to overcome on the way. She was introduced to golf by her father, and incredibly she won her first world championship at just 19 years old at her very first attempt.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #116 - We have a new government.. | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590079/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 01:36:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Call it a 'blue-nami' or a 'blue rinse' - whatever it was, the country has spoken.
New Zealand now finds itself with a first-term Prime Minister who may or may not need to cosy up to Winston Peters, who once again finds himself back in parliament.
And what will become of Chippy and Toni/Tony?
Here's my take..
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>From stroke to symphony: Andrew Stopps inspiring journey | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590080/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 01:29:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590080/</guid><description>Podcast Description You've heard it often, "A stroke could happen to anyone," and for Andrew Stopps, a dedicated music teacher and consultant, the reality of this statement hit hard one morning. Andrew takes us through his startling journey, from an uneventful morning, struggling to find a cupboard handle, to the alarming realisation that he was suffering from a stroke.
Andrew's recovery journey is nothing short of inspiring as he harnesses the power of his passion for music and the arts to find resilience in the face of adversity.</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #115 - What has happened to kindness? | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590081/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 00:14:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590081/</guid><description>Podcast Description During the Covid lockdown years Prime Minister Jacinda Ardern rammed home the 'be kind to each other' message. But did we listen, and are we listening still? I'm not so sure..
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>'The Week That Was' with Mikey Havoc and Shelly Davies | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590082/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 00:09:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590082/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the eve of an election who better to have in studio with me than UnZud broadcasting royalty Mr Mikey Havoc, and plain language guru Shelly Davies. Lots to talk about this week..
The Election. The awful humanitarian situation around the Gaza Strip.
How do we still have people living in bushes for years in New Zealand?
And would you be pissed off if your holiday was cut short to save someone's life?</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #114 - Who is Christopher Luxon? | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590083/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 01:24:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590083/</guid><description>Podcast Description With election day rapidly approaching I shine the DGEIC spotlight on National's first-term leader. What do we really know about Christopher Luxon, and will be be able to keep Winston and Seymour in check?
And what will become of poor old Chippy should Labour go on to lose the election?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Pre-election panel with Matthew Hooten and Josie Pagani | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590084/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 01:08:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today I wrangled two of New Zealand's foremost political analysts into the studio to give the upcoming election a good going over. Who is on the up, who is slipping, what might happen on election day, what might happen in the days and weeks after?
And, of course, bloody Winston Peters...
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Slam Dunc #113 - The passing of Dr Tom Mulholland | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590085/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 01:26:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590085/</guid><description>Podcast Description From now on we're going to post my 'Slam Dunc' up as it's own stand-alone piece each day.
Today's one is both personal and extremely sad. Dr Tom Mulholland has passed away. It has affected me deeply, and serves as the starkest of reminders..
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>New Zealand's cybersecurity crime wave | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590086/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 00:48:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we explore the fascinating and slightly terrifying world of cybersecurity in New Zealand with expert Alastair Miller from Aura Information Security. Alastair takes us through the stark reality of growing cyberattacks, from state actors targeting big corporations to teenagers manipulating computer games for ransomware, no one is safe. We have been guilty in the past of thinking that 'it won't happen to me', but the reality is cybercriminals show no discrimination when it comes to IP addresses.</description></item><item><title>Pharmac: Rachel Smalley on advocacy and transparency in New Zealand's health sector | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590087/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:44:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590087/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happens when a renowned journalist confronts a seemingly untouchable pharmaceutical authority? Rachel Smalley dared to do just that.
Emails from Pharmac staff personally attacking Smalley, obtained under the Privacy Act, appear to reveal an alarming lack of focus, empathy and priority in the leadership group. I think heads need to roll. Immediately.
Pharmac was established with the noble intention of regulating New Zealand's pharmaceutical industry in the mid-90s.</description></item><item><title>Professor Paul Spoonley on New Zealand's immigration and population growth challenges | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590088/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 00:35:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join me on an important exploration of New Zealand's current societal challenges with the brilliant Paul Spoonley, a sociologist and population studies expert at Massey University.
We look into the complexities of the largest population growth in New Zealand's history, brought about by high levels of immigration, and the opportunities and challenges that this presents. From housing speculation to political protests, Paul offers a profound understanding of how this surge impacts services, infrastructure, and the national sentiment.</description></item><item><title>'The Week That Was' with Nickson Clark and Nuwi Samarakone | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590089/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 00:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Another top-shelf 'Week That Was' panel this week with greenskeeper and The Edge afternoon host Nickson Clark, and business commentator &amp;amp; powerhouse entrepreneur Nuwi Samarakone. We got stuck into:
Is Christopher Luxon running scared? And what has happened to ACT lately?
Air NZ, Sanitarium and the supermarkets - are we getting fair deals?
Starting from the bottom to try and make a success of your life - the Suzanne Paul story.</description></item><item><title>From hardship to household name: Suzanne Paul's remarkable life | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590090/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:58:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590090/</guid><description>Podcast Description She began selling vibrating massage pillows in a Henderson mall. Now, nearly 35 years later, there would hardly be a person in New Zealand or Australia who hasn't heard Suzanne Paul's distinctive accent promoting the latest must-have gizmo. But Suzanne’s story is not just about sales and infomercials. Her rollercoaster personal life is just as compelling.
In this episode she talks about fighting her way out of poverty, her multiple marriages, the life lessons learned, and her incredible resilience in the face of adversity and hardship.</description></item><item><title>Fighting for your rights: Consumer NZ's Jon Duffy | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590091/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 00:48:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we delve into the world of consumer affairs with Consumer NZ's head honcho Jon Duffy.
For decades Consumer NZ has been fighting for our consumer rights by shining spotlights on those who need to be shown up and holding those to account who try and pull a fast one on the unsuspecting public.
In this enlightening conversation we address a wide array of consumer-focused topics including airlines, banks and of course supermarkets.</description></item><item><title>A candid conversation about men's health with former All Black Josh Kronfeld | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590092/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 01:15:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Being a dad, a physio, and a former All Black, Josh Kronfeld has a lot to share when it comes to men's health and the strategies for a balanced life. This episode is an enlightening journey into the world of men's health, specifically focusing on the three Ps: Prostate, Pelvis, and Penis. Josh shares his experiences, offers unique insights, and breaks down the impact of stress on these critical areas.</description></item><item><title>Prime Minister Chris Hipkins | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590093/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 01:01:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Your Editor-in-Chief and Producer Dave-O put in a bit of Saturday afternoon overtime in order to get some quality one-on-one time with one of the busiest people in the country at the moment, Prime Minister Chris Hipkins.
In what turned out to be one of the PM's last engagements before testing positive for COVID-19, Hipkins speaks refreshingly openly and honestly. Has he finally brought his A-game to the campaign?</description></item><item><title>'The Week That Was' with Sir Bob Harvey and Dame Denise L'Estrange-Corbet | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590094/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 00:39:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590094/</guid><description>Podcast Description For 'The Week That was' this week I'm joined by a Sir and a Dame - the equally delightful Bob Harvey and Denise L'Estrange-Corbet. And what a rollicking good time we had chatting about:
The second political leaders debate, Winston, and Auckland Central.
Covid vaccines.
Side hustles and starting again late in life.
And the All Blacks...
Chapters:
3:16 - Slam Dunc
6:47 - The Week That Was</description></item><item><title>From Taskmaster to Tina from Turners: Comedian Bubbah on her newfound fame | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590095/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 00:44:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590095/</guid><description>Podcast Description She will be familiar to most Kiwi's as the smiling, car-loving Tina from Turners. Or perhaps from the last season of Taskmaster NZ, where amongst other things she got a tattoo of the other contestants on her arm.
Her real name is Sieni Leo'o Olo, though her stage name (she is a comedian) is Bubbah, and she is an absolute delight to talk to. Refreshingly genuine, if not a bit.</description></item><item><title>Complex and controversial: Dr Aseem Malhotra on COVID vaccines | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590096/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 00:37:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode may well be DGEIC's most controversial one yet.
I am joined by visiting British cardiologist and public health campaigner Dr. Aseem Malhotra. From advocate to critic, Dr. Malhotra shares his thoughts and experiences around the COVID vaccines.
I won't say too much here but instead I'll leave you to listen to the conversation and form your own opinions.
Chapters:
4:35 - Slam Dunc
7:35 - Dr Aseem Malhotra</description></item><item><title>From Te Awamutu to the world: Author Heather Morris' inspiring success story | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590097/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 00:19:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Heather Morris is a bestselling author and an inspiring 70-year-old Kiwi grandmother from Te Awamutu who just happens to have sold 16 million copies of her books.
In this episode Heather shares the incredible tale of her writing journey. She takes us behind the scenes, revealing how her first book 'The Tattooist of Auschwitz' was a beautiful accident that stemmed from a conversation with 87-year-old holocaust survivor, Lale Sokolov.</description></item><item><title>Green Party co-leader James Shaw | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590098/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 00:13:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Picture a cleaner, greener New Zealand. What could be the hurdles and who takes the responsibility?
Today on the People's Podcast I'm joined by Green Party co-leader James Shaw to look at New Zealand's political landscape, the Green Party's positioning, and the nation's emissions profile. It's a discussion loaded with hot topics - carbon emissions, electric cars, New Zealand's housing crisis, multi-generational poverty, immigration, capital gains tax, and the climate crisis at large.</description></item><item><title>'The Week That Was' with Mark Richardson and Mel Homer | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590099/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 02:07:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590099/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this special 100th episode of the poddy I am joined by a couple of dear friends and broadcasting champions - Mark Richardson and Mel Homer. We kick around:
The first political leaders debate.
Mental Health Awareness Week.
The current state of the New Zealand hospitality industry.
And the current state of the New Zealand media industry.
It's a bloody good listen if I do say so myself..</description></item><item><title>Culinary Conversations: The journey, challenges, and future of New Zealand's food scene with Josh &amp; Helen Emett | Duncan Garner - Editor-In-Chief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8414590100/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 02:51:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8414590100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ever wonder what it takes to succeed in the restaurant industry? Join me for an exciting conversation with culinary world powerhouse couple, Josh and Helen Emett.
The couple are just about to open their third restaurant and they lay bare the pressures they face, how they keep their motivation burning, and their perspective on the evolution of New Zealand's restaurant scene. We look at signature dishes (and onion rings), and delve into the difficulties around diversity in the industry, the challenges of opening another restaurant in the current climate, and how New Zealand's food scene stacks up globally.</description></item></channel></rss>