<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/i-catch-killers-with-gary-jubelin/</link><description>Recent content in I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 17:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/i-catch-killers-with-gary-jubelin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>‘Someone could stab you’: Garth Wood Pt. 2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250308/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250308/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a professional boxer, Garth Woods faced his share of tough fights, but nothing prepared him for life behind bars. While he expected to face a bunch of hardened crims, instead he found people facing mental health and addiction battles. Garth opens up about the hardest moments of his prison sentence and the lessons he has learned that he still carries with him today. Get episodes of I Catch Killers a week early and ad-free, as well as bonus content, by subscribing to Crime X+ today.</description></item><item><title>'The punch that sent me to prison': Garth Wood Pt.1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250309/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250309/</guid><description>Podcast Description The interview Gary wished he didn't have to do. Former professional boxer and rugby league winger, Garth Wood returns to I Catch Killers having recently been released from prison for assault. In this raw and honest conversation, Garth explains what happened, his regrets about the incident, and what it’s like being caught up in the justice system. Get episodes of I Catch Killers a week early and ad-free, as well as bonus content, by subscribing to Crime X+ today.</description></item><item><title>Surviving one of the world's toughest prisons: Sean Turnell Pt.2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250001/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250001/</guid><description>Podcast Description The first time Sean Turnell saw a gun in real life, was when an AK47 was being pointed at his head. For the next few years, the economics professor spent his days locked in a horrifying 150-year-old prison alongside drug traffickers. The bars were rusty, the walls were stained with blood, there were huge scorpions, rats, and spiders, and the food often poisoned the prisoners. This is his extraordinary story of survival.</description></item><item><title>Wrongly jailed for 650 days: Sean Turnell Pt.1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250002/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sean Turnell spent 650 days in one of Southeast Asia’s most notorious prisons for a crime he didn’t commit. His ankles and wrists were shackled, and he was tortured and forced to live on a concrete floor in a box with no windows. Until that moment, he’d never been on the wrong side of the law. He’d never even received a parking ticket. But his whole world changed when he was accused of being an MI6 spy.</description></item><item><title>‘The Aussie who revolutionised the drug trade’: Conor Woodman Pt.2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250003/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conor Woodman, meth, methamphetamine, drug lab, meth lab, South East Asia, Myanmar
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Undercover in a jungle meth lab: Conor Woodman Pt.1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250004/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conor Woodman was captured, blindfolded and driven through the jungle with a bag over his head. The investigative journalist was being taken to a meth lab in South East Asia. He was in a brutal place where tigers are cooked for dinner, child prostitution is rife on the streets and rebels kill people and eat their hearts to send a message. I CATCH KILLERS' LIVE PODCAST RECORDING Join Gary Jubelin for a live recording of his hit podcast I Catch Killers.</description></item><item><title>Remembering the children: The Bowraville murders Pt. 2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250005/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Evelyn’s laughter, Clinton’s fast feet and Colleen’s friendly spirit live on in Bowraville when hundreds of students celebrate their legacy at an annual sports carnival. It’s been 33 years since the murders, but the pain is still as raw as it was in 1990-91. Join Gary as he reunites with the families, chats to locals and even speaks to the New South Wales police officers for the first time since he finished his career as a homicide detective.</description></item><item><title>Back to the scene of the killings: The Bowraville murders Pt.1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250006/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Three murdered children, one country town and a serial killer who still walks the streets. The Bowraville murders are one of Australia’s most notorious unsolved serial murder cases. The victims were 16-year-old Colleen Walker Craig, Evelyn Greenup, 4, and Clinton Speedy-Duroux, 16. Gary Jubelin first went to Bowraville in 1997 to investigate these horrific crimes. Today he’s going back to Bowraville to retrace the steps of the missing children.</description></item><item><title>Remembering Lynette: Hedley Thomas Pt.2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250007/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lynette Dawson, now remembered as Lynette Simms, went missing from her home in 1982. But it would take another 40 years for her husband Chris Dawson to be convicted of her murder. Investigative journalist Hedley Thomas shares his own personal connection to Lyn’s story.
I CATCH KILLERS' LIVE PODCAST RECORDING Join Gary Jubelin for a live recording of his hit podcast I Catch Killers. Spend the evening with Gary and his guests from both sides of the world of crime and punishment as well as the exclusive opportunity to take part in a live Q&amp;amp;A.</description></item><item><title>Catching a killer: Hedley Thomas Pt.1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250008/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250008/</guid><description>Podcast Description A school teacher, a missing wife and abuse of a school girl. The Teacher’s Pet was the podcast that captivated the world. The award-winning journalist behind it, Hedley Thomas, joins Gary once more to discuss the ins and outs of the investigation into Lynette Dawson’s disappearance - ultimately landing murderer Chris Dawson behind bars.
I CATCH KILLERS' LIVE PODCAST RECORDING Join Gary Jubelin for a live recording of his hit podcast I Catch Killers.</description></item><item><title>‘Anything better than death is a bonus’: Derrick McManus Pt.2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250009/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Derrick McManus wasn’t meant to survive. He was shot in his stomach, arms and legs when a police ambush took a terrifying turn. The shooter, armed with a Chinese military weapon, was firing thousands of shots in all directions. McManus was lying on the ground, bleeding for three hours. He was just 30 seconds away from death.
I CATCH KILLERS' LIVE PODCAST RECORDING Join Gary Jubelin for a live recording of his hit podcast I Catch Killers.</description></item><item><title>Ambushed and shot 14 times: Derrick McManus Pt.1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250010/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Derrick McManus trained with the SAS. As an elite member of the STAR (Special Tasks and Rescue) Group, he ran VIP security to the Queen, high risk witness protection and underwater recovery. But what started as another ordinary day ended with McManus being shot 14 times in 15 seconds. What unfolded became one of Australia’s longest police sieges.
I CATCH KILLERS' LIVE PODCAST RECORDING Join Gary Jubelin for a live recording of his hit podcast I Catch Killers.</description></item><item><title>BONUS: Gary Jubelin sits down with the True Crime Cheat Sheet podcast | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250011/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 06:58:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gary joins Nina Young, co-host of True Crime Cheat Sheet, to talk about what really goes down in the police interview room from the heartbreaking to the hilarious. It's a fascinating inside look into a world most of us will never see.
Want to hear more? Listen to True Crime Cheat Sheet today! https://podcasts.apple.com/au/podcast/true-crime-cheat-sheet/id1485347114 See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Prison time and the ultimate challenge: Ant Middleton Pt.2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250012/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250012/</guid><description>Podcast Description When the judge’s hammer went down, sentencing Ant Middleton to 14 months behind bars for assaulting a cop, he smiled. Not to be smug, but because he was stepping into the unknown. He needed to be the best prisoner he could be. The elite soldier is always chasing a challenge. But it was one of his biggest missions that almost killed him - and it wasn’t in a war zone.</description></item><item><title>‘What it’s like to take a life…’: Ant Middleton Pt. 1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250013/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ant Middleton has faced death more times than he can count. One night during dinner, he got a call. Within minutes, Middleton packed up his lasagna and was off on a secret mission. He didn’t know how long he’d be away, he didn’t know where and he couldn’t tell his wife. The former soldier spent years with the special forces as a point man and sniper. He sits down with Gary Jubelin to answer the question he hates most: what is it like to kill?</description></item><item><title>Justice for Leisl: Jerildene Cane Pt.2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250014/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250014/</guid><description>Podcast Description At 23, Leisl Smith had her whole life in front of her. But her ex boyfriend, James Scott Church, had other ideas. Six years after she went missing, he was charged with her murder. After a gruelling 13-week trial, there are still no answers. Why? Because Church took his own life a day before the verdict was due to be made public - locking the judge’s verdict away forever.</description></item><item><title>Missing or murdered: Jerildene Cane Pt.1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250015/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Leisl Smith, 23, was last seen in 2012. Her car was found abandoned months later. In 2018, Smith’s ex boyfriend James Scott Church was charged with her suspected murder. But what unfolded on the last day of the trial was completely unprecedented. It was a twist nobody expected. Jerildene Cane joins Gary in hopes she can find justice for her little sister.
I CATCH KILLERS' LIVE PODCAST RECORDING Join Gary Jubelin for a live recording of his hit podcast I Catch Killers.</description></item><item><title>Prison and forgiveness: Andrew Geldert Pt.2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250016/</guid><description>Podcast Description A duffle bag stuffed with cash, guns and ecstasy. It was all Andrew Geldert needed to taste freedom after leaving the army. The former sniper became heavily entrenched in the underworld, seeking the next big thrill. But an undercover cop infiltrated his crew. He was arrested after he dropped his son off at daycare. Sentenced to years behind bars, Andrew saw prison as a way to be set free.</description></item><item><title>From the army to the underworld: Andrew Geldert Pt.1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250017/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrew Geldert almost died when he was shot twice at close range in a bikie room brawl. As a boy, he watched his mum’s boyfriend hang himself from a gumtree in his backyard. He cut the body down with a blunt kitchen knife. At 19, he was a sniper in the army. He’s been a professional boxer, a nominee member of a bikie club, a drug dealer and maximum security prisoner.</description></item><item><title>The Tyrannosaurus Waltz: Trent Dalton Pt.2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Growing up, there was a monster in Trent Dalton’s life. Tackling a limb each of the man abusing their mother, the four Dalton boys restrained him until police arrived. Domestic violence, crime, loss, grief, loved ones going to prison - these experiences filled Trent’s boyhood. Until he broke free from the invisible wall that had been locking him into a future of crime.
Discover Trent Dalton’s latest book, Lola In The Mirror.</description></item><item><title>Notorious crims and Pearl Jam: Trent Dalton Pt.1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 14:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mysterious hidden rooms, secret red telephones, drug dealers and infamous prison escapes. Trent Dalton’s childhood was far from normal. Raised in a murky world surrounded by felons, the Dalton boys could have easily taken the path of crime. Instead, the award-winning author found love - and a Rolling Stone magazine.
Discover Trent Dalton’s latest book, Lola In The Mirror.
Get episodes of I Catch Killers a week early and ad-free, as well as bonus content, by subscribing to Crime X+ today.</description></item><item><title>Rogue animal recaptured: Ron Isherwood Pt. 2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250020/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ron Isherwood escaped prison by swimming through shark infested water. He was a heroin addict who went from gangster criminal to drug dealer. He soon turned his heavily inked back on the life he was born into. For years he was clean. He stayed out of trouble, out of prison. Until the afternoon he went down for importing 12 kilograms of cocaine into Australia.
Get episodes of I Catch Killers a week early and ad-free, as well as bonus content, by subscribing to Crime X+ today.</description></item><item><title>Drugs, gangs and growing up the hard way: Ron Isherwood Pt.1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250021/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ron Isherwood was sent to prison for four attempted murders. He was 17. Growing up, his room was filled with rifles - all given to him by serious gangsters, kangaroo skins, gun belts with bullets, swords, machetes. His father was an “evil” man who once shot at Ron because he slammed the car door, and rewarded him for helping with robberies. Despite a deadly childhood filled with crime, drugs and underworld crims, Ron managed to find his way out the other side.</description></item><item><title>Bodies falling from the sky: ABF Commissioner Michael Outram Pt.2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250022/</guid><description>Podcast Description A plane shot down over Ukraine by deadly Russian missiles. Hundreds of bodies strewn across a field. It was a moment that left Australian Border Force Commissioner Michael Outram without sleep for months. This is how it all unfolded.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cracking the cocaine code: ABF Commissioner Michael Outram Pt.1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 14:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Crime syndicates are smuggling cocaine completely undetected through secret undercover doors scattered across the country. But narcotics aren’t the only things infiltrating the nation. Australian Border Force Commissioner Michael Outram joins Gary to share how the world’s biggest criminals are dropping drugs across the border. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tale of two sides: Dying Rose Pt.2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250024/</guid><description>Podcast Description A young woman was found dead in a garage. Another woman’s death sends her mother overseas. Every case is a tale of two sides - the families and the police. The reporters behind the latest true crime podcast investigation, Dying Rose, share the stories that would have otherwise been lost. Listen to Dying Rose today.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Six deaths, one national shame: Dying Rose Pt.1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250025/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250025/</guid><description>Podcast Description A young mother was found hanging in a tree. A daughter was found dead, mauled by dogs in a backyard.Those are just two of the chilling cases uncovered by a team of reporters, who have lifted the lid on some of Australia’s darkest secrets. Gary Jubelin sits down with the reporters behind Dying Rose, a true crime podcast investigation.
Listen to Dying Rose today.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Badass female warrior: Dr Felicity Gerry KC Pt.2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr Felicity Gerry KC dropped out of school to ride horses. But it didn’t stop her becoming a top barrister, representing people accused of some of the most horrific crimes. Moving to Australia over a decade ago, she saw first hand the horrors of Don Dale - including the appalling treatment of one of her clients, who was starved in prison to “take the bite out of him”.</description></item><item><title>Defending the fish brain terrorist: Dr Felicity Gerry KC Pt.1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250027/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr Felicity Gerry KC fights for people caught up in messy situations - murders, terrorism and war crimes. She represented a terrorist accused of the bomb plot in Federation Square on Christmas Day. She even helped save Mary Jane Veloso from death row just 30 minutes before the young mother was due to face the firing squad. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Finding strength at rock bottom: Andrew Truong Pt.2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former drug dealer Andrew Truong spent years meeting addicts in secretive locations to sell them their next hit of heroin. But the law soon caught up to him. Thrown into jail with cockroaches and rusty showers, Truong felt like his life was about to end. Ultimately, his new life was just beginning.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Heroin and highs before the low: Andrew Truong Pt.1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250029/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Drugs, fast cars, cash and beautiful women. That’s all convicted drug dealer Andrew Truong wanted in life. He went from selling party pills at raves to dealing heroin in dingy streets. He was earning more money selling drugs than he was working three day jobs. For two years, Truong’s life revolved around selling drugs and eating Hungry Jacks. Until it all came crashing down.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>‘I’m also a survivor’: Grace Tame Pt. 2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250030/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Grace Tame was 15 when she was first sexually abused by her teacher. She was a school girl. He was an ex soldier. But the true fighter in this story is Grace. Overcoming the darkest moments of her life, the fearless activist is reclaiming her power while also supporting victims of sexual abuse. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The loneliness of the long-distance runner: Grace Tame Pt. 1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250031/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250031/</guid><description>Podcast Description You might know Grace Tame as an activist for survivors of sexual assault, but there’s so much more to the 2021 Australian of the Year. As a teenager, Grace moved to the US by herself and struck up a friendship with John Cleese. Grace joins Gary Jubelin to chat about everything - including why she ran for 72 kilometres straight, how she uses humour to punch up and what really happened during that moment she met former prime minister Scott Morrison.</description></item><item><title>Battling bikies: Craig Semple Pt.2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250032/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Armed with beer glasses and metal knuckle dusters, the Finks bikie club violently crashed a police Christmas party. Former detective Craig Semple got caught on the wrong end of one bulked-up bikie who king-hit him, knocking him to the ground. For years after, he spent nights lying awake fantasising about vengeance. This is his revenge story.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The cop who fell to Earth: Craig Semple Pt.1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250033/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250033/</guid><description>Podcast Description In just two years, former detective Craig Semple dealt with 12 murders and a budding serial killer. There were jail murders, drug murders and domestic violence murders. He even spent Christmas morning at a murder scene, after spending the night setting up a swing set for his young kids. But ultimately, locking up the bad guys took its toll. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Baddest | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250034/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 05:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Meet one of the baddest figures of Sydney’s underworld. He committed his first crime at 12 years old. He was acquitted of several armed robberies involving millions of dollars, fast cars and balaclavas, and he was charged with attempted murder. His identity has been hidden - until today.
Read more about this fascinating story at thebaddest.com.au.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>‘Street-smart with a psychopath profile’: Shirley Singh Pt. 2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250035/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Sica horrifically killed three of Shirley Singh’s children. They were found dead in a spa bath. The water was overflowing. There was blood on the walls. Years before he committed the horrendous triple murder, Max Sica was described by a prison psychologist as having the hallmarks of a psychopath. This is how a quiet family home became the scene of one of the most gruesome crimes Australia’s ever seen.</description></item><item><title>‘My three children were murdered’: Shirley Singh Pt.1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250036/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shirley Singh’s three youngest children were brutally murdered in the family home. Max Sica killed his girlfriend Neelma, 24, and her two siblings, Kunal, 18, and Sidhi, 12. He attacked them with a garden fork, dumped their bodies in the spa bath and flooded them with scalding hot water. Just a decade earlier, Sica had been sentenced to nine years behind bars for 83 offences. The fearless mum joins Gary to share her chilling story, keeping the memory of her three kids alive.</description></item><item><title>Seizing the superannuation of child abusers: Andrew Carpenter Pt.2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250037/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250037/</guid><description>Podcast Description While many paedophiles face a few years behind bars, their victims are given a life long sentence of suffering. Fighting lawyer Andrew Carpenter has one mission - to make Australia the most dangerous place for child sex offenders, and it starts with seizing super. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The man most hated by child sex offenders: Andrew Carpenter Pt.1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250038/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrew Carpenter is a lawyer and a mixed martial arts ring announcer. He’s also known as the most hated man in Australia by child sex offenders - and it’s his badge of honour. As a voice for survivors of child sexual abuse, Carpenter has spent years locking up the lowest of the low criminals.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The detective and the killer: Jack Roney Pt.2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jack Roney had a secret. Between searching for missing children and attending heartbreaking murder-suicides as a detective, he was looking for something more. During his commute to work, Jack secretly spent months fiercely bleeding words onto the page. Soon after, he left his career as a cop in favour of life as a crime writer.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Stranger than fiction: Jack Roney Pt.1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250040/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jack Roney joined the police fresh out of high school. He attended fatal car crashes, got in fights with bikies, was sent to the scene of tragic murder-suicides and interviewed children whose parents were shot and killed in their own home. Needing to escape the heavy toll of child protection, Jack Roney found a way to process the hard truth of what he was seeing by becoming a crime fiction writer</description></item><item><title>Catching the Jet Set Bandit: Ed Kinbacher Pt.2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250041/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former detective senior sergeant Ed Kinbacher has seen a lot of crime in the past 40 years. He locked up notorious con man Danny Shakespeare. He observed the horror left behind by a mother who killed eight children days before Christmas. But one case that still bugs him is that of the mysterious Jet Set Bandit. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to solve a murder with pigs and acid: Ed Kinbacher Pt.1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250042/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ex top cop Ed Kinbacher has a reputation for unorthodox investigations. He’s conducted his own backyard experiments to catch killers, he’s taken unusual measures to track down persons of interest, and he’s been first on the scene as an active shooter fired at a Queensland hospital. Following in the footsteps of his grandfather and father, policing very much runs through the recently retired detective senior sergeant’s blood.
See omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>"Are you going to really help my husband?" Craig Foster Pt.2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Craig Foster sacrificed his entire life for a man he’d never met. Foster spent months flying around the world between FIFA, the UN and European embassies fighting for footballer Hakeem al-Araibi, who was wrongfully detained on his honeymoon. Prepared to lose whatever it took, including his house, Foster assured al-Araibi’s wife that her husband wasn’t going to die in prison. What unfolded was an incredible race against the clock.</description></item><item><title>Pride, playing for your country and exposing injustice: Craig Foster Pt. 1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250044/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Craig Foster is a former Socceroo captain, TV presenter, law student - he’s even won the odd Logie Award. But at his core, he’s just a guy from rural Australia, hoping to make an impact on the world. When he heard Hakeem al-Araibi had been wrongfully detained in a Thai prison, Foster reacted the only way he could. He quit his job, packed up his life and went overseas to save a man he’d never met.</description></item><item><title>Breaking the badness: Tony Hoang and Russell Manser Pt. 2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250045/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tony Hoang was a teenage drug dealer hanging out with violent gangs and feeding a raging heroin habit. Not far away, Russell Manser had robbed his first bank at 22 - the first in a string of several violent burglaries. This is how they escaped the deadly world of crime.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Breaking the badness: Jeffrey Morgan and Nader Hamdan Pt. 1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250046/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nader Hamdan was just 16 when he punched a cop in the jaw and grabbed his gun. On the other side of New South Wales in Redfern’s notorious streets, Jeffrey Morgan was running riots with police and robbing banks. Both men were heading to an early grave or life behind bars. Instead, they turned their troubled lives around. This is their redemption story. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Giving up was not an option: Damien Thomlinson Pt.2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250047/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250047/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of Gary's chat with Damien they talk about his incredible survival and how his positive attitude and drive helped push him forward and achieve what many thought was going to be impossible. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Without warning: A Commando's incredible survival Pt.1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250048/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Private Damien Thomlinson is a former member of the elite 2nd Commando Regiment of the Australian Army who was terribly injured after a bomb explosion in Afghanistan. His inspiring journey back from the dead stands as proof that no challenge is too great and that the ANZAC spirit is truly alive and well.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>William Tyrrell update | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250049/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250049/</guid><description>Podcast Description There's been a lot of headlines about the William Tyrrell investigation recently. This is what Gary Jubelin has to say.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Someone somewhere knows something Meni Caroutas Pt.2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250050/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Imagine if your loved one suddenly vanished. Just disappeared into thin air with no trace left behind. Every year in Australia, 38,000 missing persons reports are made. While many are found, thousands are left with no answers. Former cop-turned-reporter Meni Caroutas, host of The Missing Australia podcast, talks to Gary about some of the most chilling unsolved investigations.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>From Kings Cross cop to the hunt for missing persons Meni Caroutas Pt.1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250051/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250051/</guid><description>Podcast Description King's Cross in the '80s for a young cop was like Mardi Gras, the circus and New Year's Eve all rolled into one. Whatever you wanted, you could get it. For former detective Meni Caroutas, working the glitter strip was his dream job - until everything suddenly came crashing down. Meni joins Gary to chat about the moment his career ended, and how it led him to his lifelong mission of finding missing persons.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: I Catch Killers audiobook preview | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250052/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 03:33:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here's a special treat - the first few chapters of Gary's book I Catch Killers from Audible. Serial killings, child abductions, organised crime hits and domestic murders. This is the memoir of a homicide detective.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>On the trail of terrorists: Lindsay Hall and Amanda Glover Pt 2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250053/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250053/</guid><description>Podcast Description A Bunnings employee and a nail gun. That was the key to foiling a potentially very deadly Christmas terrorist attack in Victoria. AFP's Lindsay Hall and Amanda Glover walk Gary through some of their biggest stings.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Face to face with the Federal Police: Lindsay Hall and Amanda Glover Pt 1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250054/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250054/</guid><description>Podcast Description As acting members of the Australian Federal Police, Amanda Glover and Lindsay Hall have spent more than 40 years investigating police fraud, drug crimes and preventing terrorist attacks. The duo sit down with Gary to chat about the tricks they use to catch crims, and Glover reveals how she busted a suspicious family daycare syndicate that falsely claimed $13 million of taxpayer money.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>‘I’ve gone too far on this one’: Paul Fenech Pt. 2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250055/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adults-only funny man Paul Fenech has written a Bogan Bible, holds a record for the most amount of swearing on TV, and he’s thong-slapped his fans right around Australia. Working his way up from cleaner to comedian, he’s walked a fine line between humour and causing offence. But Pauly tells Gary the one time he took it too far. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Comedy and cancel culture: Paul Fenech Pt. 1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250056/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Paul Fenech is the Logie-winning Maltese-Australian comedian who created smash hits Pizza, Housos and Bogan Hunter. But he says woke sensibilities have changed so much that his career would be impossible today - and he’s waiting for the day he gets cancelled.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Breaking rocks and the problem with prison: Matt Law Pt. 2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250057/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today. Having spent 18 years behind bars, ex-bikie Matt Law knows the problems of prison better than anyone. He’s lived much of his adult life maximum security, he’s been addicted to opiates, but now he’s found a new sense of calm. Working as a peer mentor, Matt is helping ex-prisoners find their feet upon release. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bikie life and 18 years behind bars: Matt Law Pt. 1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250058/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today. Matt Law has spent half his life in jail. When he was a kid, he escaped a difficult home life and became a ward of the state. As he got older he searched for a tribe and found it - in an outlaw bikie gang. Matt takes us into the dark world of bikie life, revealing the strict club rules and what it takes to be nominated.</description></item><item><title>How to solve a murder: Charlie Bezzina Pt.2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250059/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today. Fingerprints identify the victim as 26-year-old Kelly Hodge, but a killer is still on the loose. Homicide detective Charlie Bezzina talks us through each of the five suspects, only to end up with dead ends, until months later they receive a call. This is what led them to her murderer. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to solve a murder: Charlie Bezzina Pt.1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250060/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today. A naked body was found wrapped in a blanket on the side of the road. Legendary homicide detective Charlie Bezzina takes us through every step of the investigation as the cops experienced it, in real-time, revealing the vital clue that led them to the killer.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Drug dealer turned stand-up comic: Andrew Hamilton Pt.2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250061/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today. What do you get when you combine a mushroom dealer and a prison sentence? In Andrew Hamilton's case, the answer is comedy gold. In part two Andrew takes Gary through his time behind bars and the prison food reviews that helped launch his stand-up comedy career. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A mushroom kingpin goes to jail: Andrew Hamilton Pt.1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250062/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today. Andrew Hamilton was a PR young-gun with a bright future, he also owned a high-profile pizza shop in Potts Point. From the outside everything looked great. But underneath it all Andrew had a secret life as one of Sydney's biggest magic mushroom dealers, and his gambling and drug addictions were running rampant. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Introducing: The Missing | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250063/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 06:26:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
Enjoy a sneak peak into the new series, The Missing Australia. Episode one is here for your listening pleasure. Former cop-turned-reporter Meni Caroutas investigates some of Australia's roughly 2,600 unsolved missing persons cases. If you enjoy this episode, you can listen early and ad-free to The Missing Australia podcast now on Crime X+.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dark obsession: Nicole Madigan Pt. 2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250064/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today. Nicole Madigan felt like she couldn't escape her stalker Karissa as she continued to bombard her with endless harassment. Finally, she was pushed too far. In part two Nicole talks to Gary about the long process to get justice and protect herself and her family. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Pursued by a stalker: Nicole Madigan Pt. 1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250065/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today. Nicole Madigan is an accomplished and confident journalist, but her life was totally turned upside down by the actions of a stalker. In part one, she tells Gary how a chance encounter with a stranger led to a campaign of abuse and harassment that would last for years. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The cost of a life in Kings Cross: Neil Cummins Pt. 2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250066/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
He walked beside John Ibrahim for a decade, and now Neil Cummins tells us why he had to walk away. He also shares what it was like to pick up the pieces of his life and rebuild into something stronger. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Walking beside John Ibrahim: Neil Cummins Pt. 1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250067/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
Neil Cummins has dealt with bikie brawls, street fights and the general chaos that was life on the streets of King's Cross. Neil worked his way from nightclub doorman to personal bodyguard to John Ibrahim, the king of the cross himself, today he takes us into the seedy underbelly of that time. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The hunt for Mr Cruel: Chris O'Connor Pt. 2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250068/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
Chris O'Connor was the lead investigator on Task Force ‘Spectrum’ which was responsible for investigating the abduction and sexual assault of several schoolgirls in Victoria and sadly the murder of one of those girls. This case is wildly known as the Mr Cruel Investigation. Today Chris gives us a rare inside look into the decades-long investigation.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The worst of the worst: Chris O'Connor Pt. 1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250069/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
Chris O'Connor is a former Detective Senior Sergeant specialising in Sex Crime Investigation and during his 36-year career in the Victorian Police, he was widely regarded as one of the most experienced detectives in this field.
In part one, Gary and Chris talk about what it was like investigating some of the worst predators in the country, from child abusers to a man who was purposefully infecting people with HIV.</description></item><item><title>Dead man's switch: Duncan Burns Pt. 2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250070/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
The road to recovery is seldom a straightforward and easy path. Duncan Burns cheated death and walked away from his club, but it took some more hard lessons to put him on his current mission as a youth worker looking to keep young offenders out of detention centres and change the way we look at crime. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Shot in a gang war: Duncan Burns Pt. 1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250071/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
Duncan Burns was a lost young man searching for a tribe when he first met a bikie gang member who introduced him to a lifestyle of fast rides, fast living and plenty of drugs. Unfortunately for Duncan, this world isn't one you can survive in long and in 2005 he was shot in a gang war and left dying in the gutter. See omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>'Honesty is easy': Nader 'Lionheart' Hamdan Pt 2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250072/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
Looking at Nader Hamdan's early life, a betting man might expect him to end up in and out of jail - or even dead. But Nader defied the odds through grit, determination and his unrelenting passion for becoming a champion boxer. In part two of his chat with Gary, Nader talks about what gave him the drive to change and what he wants to tell young men who are struggling to stay on the right side of the law.</description></item><item><title>'The Devil had him': Nader 'Lionheart' Hamdan Pt 1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250073/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
Nader 'Lionheart' Hamdan is a legend of the boxing world, in 2003 he was ranked number two in the world in the middleweight division, just behind Oscar De La Hoya. But Nader's rise to the top wasn't easy, he was troubled and violent in his youth, in part one he talks about his years in a juvenile detention centre after an incident with a policeman's gun.</description></item><item><title>Remembering Courtney: Leesa and Ron Topic Pt. 2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250074/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
Leesa and Ron Topic felt like they were in a living nightmare, they had endless questions about how their average ordinary daughter could end up shot dead by police. It took an inquest for them to find answers. In part two, the couple shares what Courtney's legacy is and why they will never stop fighting for change.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>'Judge, jury and executioner': Leesa and Ron Topic Pt.1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250075/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
‘Make sure you hang out the washing’ - This was the last communication Leesa Topic had with her daughter Courtney. It was written on a note she left in the kitchen of their West Hoxton Park home.
Within hours of hanging out the family’s washing, Courtney Topic aged just 22, who had never been in trouble was shot dead by police.
Today, we are talking to Leesa and Ron Topic, the parents of Courtney.</description></item><item><title>Rock bottom and recovery: Tom Carroll Pt. 2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250076/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
Tom Carroll was at the top of his game, he had it all: world championships, a loving family, fame and fortune - but he also had a dark secret, Tom was an addict. In part two of his chat with Gary, he talks about his experiences with crystal meth and cocaine, and the rock bottom moment that led him to recovery and enlightenment. See omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>Big waves, big risks: Tom Carroll Pt. 1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250077/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
Tom Carroll has caught his share of killer... waves. A two-time world champion surfer, Tom has had huge highs and crashing lows. In part one of his chat with Gary, Tom talks about what drew him to surfing, his career and how he became involved in drugs.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Speaking with a survivor: Twelve Tribes Pt. 2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250078/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
Matt Klein says that he was drawn to the kindness and community spirit of the Twelve Tribes, but eventually, the bizarre and sometimes cruel rules governing the group led to him fleeing with his children. His wife remains in the group and has cut off contact with Matt and the family. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Gary interviewed by Matty Johns | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250079/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
The tables were turned when Matty Johns sat down with Gary to ask him about everything from his early career to his post-policing life. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Inside a secretive Australian sect: Twelve Tribes Pt. 1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250080/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
The inside workings of the Twelve Tribes religious group here in Australia and around the world are shrouded in mystery. We're joined by Journalist Tim Elliott who is pulling back the curtain and exposing some dark truths.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tracking terrorists: David Leach Pt 2. | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250081/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
In part two of Gary's chat with recently retired Scotland Yard Detective David Leach, the pair talk about David's work in some very high-profile counter-terrorism investigations and his work on a decade-old unsolved murder.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Face to face with a serial killer: David Leach Pt 1. | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250082/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
Not everyone can say they stared down a serial killer, but recently retired Scotland Yard Murder Squad and Counter Terrorism Detective David Leach has done just that. In part one of his chat with Gary, David talks about the investigation that led to the arrest of Levi Bellfield, a serial killer that had been terrorising London until his arrest in 2004.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Presumption of innocence?: Ben and Amy Smith Pt 2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250083/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
In part two of Ben and Amy Smith's conversation with Gary, the pair describe the strain of being accused of sexual assault, the experience of going through court and what it felt like to hear the jury finally deliver their verdict. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A man accused: Ben and Amy Smith Pt 1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250084/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
Ben and Amy Smith saw their world turned upside down when Ben was arrested and charged with multiple sexual assaults. The former policeman maintained his innocence and Amy stood by him, gathering the evidence that would eventually clear his name.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Regrets and redemption: John Elias Pt 2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250085/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
John Elias knows he's no angel. A shooting, match-fixing, drug and firearm offences - are just some of the crimes he was linked to or convicted of. But John is sharing his story because he thinks there is a lesson to be taken from it, and he hopes young people hear it. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The original rugby league bad boy: John Elias Pt 1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250086/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
John Elias' rap sheet goes far beyond on-field indiscretions. As a 16-year-old he was serving time in Long Bay Prison with some of the hardest prisoners in the state. After prison, he carved out a career for himself as a high-profile professional rugby league player, but like a moth to a bright light, he was drawn to the adrenaline of the criminal world.</description></item><item><title>Seeing the Northern Territory intervention from the inside | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250087/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
In 2007, the Federal Government launched the Northern Territory Emergency Response, also known as the Intervention. It included restrictions on alcohol, changes to welfare payments, acquisitions of parcels of lands, education, employment and health initiatives, restrictions on pornography and other measures. When Mary Keaney saw the confronting images on the news, she uprooted her life to travel there and work for the Aboriginal Legal Aid Service.</description></item><item><title>A wild child that went from protester to barrister | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250088/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
Mary Keaney grew up a rebel with a strong social conscience, she spent her youth protesting, fighting for the environment and other important causes. Then, in her 20s, she read Nelson Mandela's autobiography and learnt that if you want to fight the system, you first need to understand it. That simple message sent her on a path to becoming a lawyer. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>The people on the back of the bus | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250089/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
In part two of Gary's chat with former Assistant Commissioner Ken Mckay, the pair discuss what it really takes to crack down on gang violence and how the media both helps and hinders the efforts. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Busting bikies and battling bludgers | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250090/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
Ken 'Slasher' Mckay spent 35 years in the police, rising the the rank of Assistant Commissioner. He's an old school cop who locked up plenty of bikies and underworld figures in his time. In part 1, he and Gary talk about some of his cases and he shares his opinion on the current state of policing. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Walking away from the mob | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250091/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
Michael Franzese is one of the only men who turned his back on the Mafia and walked away with his life. In part 2 of his chat with Gary, they talk about his time in prison and how he came to turn his life around and leave his life of crime. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>One-on-one with a former Mafia boss | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250092/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
Michael Franzese is the former Capo of the infamous Colombo crime family in New York. In part one, he tells Gary how he became a 'made man', what life was like in the mob and his relationship with the Australian Mafia. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>On the trail of a two million dollar heist | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250093/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
Graeme Simpfendorfer tells Gary about the 2.4 million dollar Armaguard heist pulled off by the infamous 'Road Gang' and how a long-term investigation, Operation Octopus led to a breakthrough. Graeme also shares what it was like working the Black Saturday bushfires, and reveals the job that almost broke him.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The cases that made Hunted's lead investigator | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250094/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
Graeme Simpfendorfer first decided he wanted to become a cop when the bank he was working at was held up. Since then, he's worked in all areas of policing, from the armed hold-up squad to the Sexual Offences Child Abuse Investigation Team (SOCIT). Graeme is now the lead investigator on the hit show Hunted. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Life of Brian | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250095/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
Dean King thought rehab was just an easy way to escape his life in prison, he couldn't have predicted the enormous life-changing transformation he would find there. In part two Dean, tells Gary how he has kept his positive outlook throughout his struggles and always looked on the bright side of life. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Teen killer to millionaire | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250096/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
Dean King was facing the unthinkable at just 15 years old, charged with murder after a robbery gone wrong and facing a stint in an adult prison. In part one we go through Dean's downward spiral into heroin use and violence behind bars. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Infiltrating the Mafia | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250097/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
How Colin McLaren and a team of elite cops pulled off the largest undercover sting in Australian history when they posed as money laundering art dealers to infiltrate the mafia in New South Wales.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bullets rained down | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250098/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
Former detective Colin McLaren’s jaw-dropping career saw him dealing with mass shootings, hunting the Mr Cruel serial rapist and infiltrating the mafia. In part one, he shares the inside stories of these life-changing cases.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>They always leave a trace | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250099/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
Greg Kelly joins us again to talk more about his work, this time in the field of arson investigation. Greg outlines the telltale signs of arson and his involvement investigating the tragic Quakers Hill nursing home fire. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Inside the world of the crime scene examiner | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250100/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
Detectives are often credited with solving tough crimes, but it's often the work that's done behind the scenes that dictates if a crime is solved, this is the work of the forensic investigator. We're joined today by Greg Kelly, a forensic investigator who will take us into the world of the crime scene examiner.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The sometimes less than glamorous life of a call girl | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250101/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
In part two of her chat with Gary, Amanda Goff shares some more of her experiences as Samantha X and reveals why she retired from escort work and what the future has in store. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Amanda Goff became Samantha X | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250102/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
Gary has stared down murderers, but Amanda Goff still managed to make him nervous. In part one, Amanda and Gary discuss why she decided to trade in her 'picket fence' life to become a sex worker. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How a thug found inner peace | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250103/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
Luke Kennedy's wild ride through life almost came to an end in a disastrous trip to Thailand that left him in hospital. But it was this trip that would plant the seeds that would lead him to redemption.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sex, drugs and a Buddhist monk | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250104/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
Luke Kennedy's life was ruled by his ego, like many lost young men he was a wrecking ball of pain, brawling, getting stabbed and generally up to no good, until a catastrophic chain of events led him to enlightenment. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Facing the death penalty | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250105/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rob Langdon was in a foreign country, away from his family and friends, facing the death penalty for murder. In part two of his chat with Gary, Rob talks about his strategies for survival in the unforgiving prison in Afghanistan and how he came to be released. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Seven years in an Afghan prison | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250106/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
Rob Langdon describes himself as an honest man, not necessarily a good man. He was a former soldier working as a private contractor in Afghanistan when he was involved in an incident that resulted in a man's death and saw him facing the death penalty. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Pride, pain and finding your tribe | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250107/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
In part two of Rudy's chat with Gary, he talks about how he fell in love with a man out of the blue in his 20s and realised that he was gay. Rudy also talks about travelling back to New Zealand to find his cultural roots and how he finally found his place in the world with comedy. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>A lifetime of trauma and laughter | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250108/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
Comedian Rudy-Lee Taurua was born into a world where people talked with their fists and drugs and alcohol abuse was the norm. It felt inevitable that he would go down the same path. In part one of his chat with Gary, he talks about his decade-long addiction and how he overcame it.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>An act of state sponsored terrorism | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250109/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
In part two of Philip Marshall, he talks more about the fascinating investigation into the sinking of the Rainbow Warrior and the breakthroughs that lead them to answers and an arrest.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The sinking of the Rainbow Warrior | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250110/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Philip Marshall found himself on the case of a lifetime as he and a team of New Zealand cops were brought in to investigate the sinking of the Rainbow Warrior, a Green Peace vessel that was involved in protesting nuclear testing. The case took Phillip and his team on a wild ride with many twists and turns.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>40-year wait for justice | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250111/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
Russell Oxford joins Gary once again and the pair talk through the final path to justice for Roxlyn Bowie's family and how it feels for him to see John Bowie convicted after decades of work. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dear John... | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250112/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to Crime X+ today.
Russell Oxford returns for a record-breaking fifth episode of I Catch Killers. Russell shares the story of Roxlyn Bowie, a 31-year-old woman from Walgett in NSW . Russell covers her mysterious disappearance and her family's 40-year wait for answers and justice that finally came earlier this year.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The media's role in keeping investigations honest | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250113/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250113/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of Hedley's chat with Gary, they talk about his investigations into the murder of Lynette Dawson and Shandee Blackburn. The pair discuss the media's role in uncovering mistakes and corruption that can otherwise hinder the course of justice.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hedley Thomas - a journalistic outsider | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250114/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hedley Thomas is a multi-award-winning journalist whose work has exposed corruption and miscarriages of justice. He has helped solve serious crimes that might otherwise have remained unsolved. You won't want to miss this fascinating insight into Hedley's work.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The aftermath of a shooting | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250115/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250115/</guid><description>Podcast Description The night Daryl Green was shot, his dad received the most horrifying call a parent can get, his son was lying in hospital, shot in the face and shoulder. Daryl's recovery and subsequent return to policing showed his incredible strength and resilience. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Shot twice | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250116/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Daryl Green is a former Queensland cop who found himself shot twice in an ambush while responding to a routine call, his partner was shot too, Daryl shares his experience of that harrowing night and how he immediately went into fight mode. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The man who vanished into thin air | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250117/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Caroline and Kylie are back to talk more about the disappearance of Paddy Moriarty, the mischievous Larrimah local who vanished without a trace along with his dog, Kellie. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Getting lost in Larrimah | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250118/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gary is joined by Kylie Stevenson and Caroline Graham, two journalists, podcasters and authors who found themselves drawn into a very unusual murder mystery in a tiny outback town. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Terrorist attacks and Mexican drug cartels | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250119/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250119/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of Nathan Edward's chat with Gary, they talk about what it was like to be on the ground documenting the September 11 attacks and aftermath and the time he found himself visiting an ice factory in Sinaloa.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Capturing a coup and meeting a murderer | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250120/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nathan Edwards is a former newspaper photographer who has covered some of Australia's, and the world's, biggest crimes. In part one Nathan tells Gary about the time he had a conversation with a murderer before he was arrested, his time covering a murder mystery on Norfolk islands and his experience seeing the aftermath of the Bali bombings.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The fight to keep our kids safe | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250121/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250121/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of Kristi McVee's chat with Gary, she talks about PTSD, leaving the police and her new mission to keep kids safe.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The toughest job in policing | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250122/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kristi McVee is a former detective and specialist child interviewer, she spent years investigating child sexual abuse and prosecuting pedophiles. In this chat, she gets real about the scope of the problem and the challenges you face as a cop chasing down pedophiles. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Solving the murder of Lainie Coldwell | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250123/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lainie Coldwell was found at dead the base of a large gum tree with severe head injuries that later killed her. At first glance, it looked like an accident, but Gerry Thornton trusted his gut and his single-minded pursuit of the truth, even when he wasn't supported by his own organisation, lead to a murder conviction for her husband. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A cop that refused to give up | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250124/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250124/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we're joined by Gerry Thornton, a former Queensland cop who worked for 32 years covering high-profile investigations such as the murder of Lainie Coldwell. In part one, Gerry talks about his career and his habit of chasing up clues that other people tended to ignore. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>'I came from the darkness into the light' | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250125/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tony's life hit rock bottom as his friends died around him, he had no one to turn to, no one he could trust, and then a twist of fate took him to his salvation.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Heroin, horror and heartache in Cabramatta | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250126/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tony Hoang turned to the streets to escape the violence and anger of his home life. He fell in with gang members and found himself making thousands of dollars a month running heroin through Cabramatta when he was just 15 years old. He was living the high life, but things soon came crashing down. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The risks and dangers of the job | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250127/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Corrective Services Officer Paul Coyne has experienced some dicey situations at work, and he isn't ashamed to say he's been scared. The key is to rely on your training and know you have the experience to deal with confronting situations and still function.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The silent role in the justice system | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250128/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Prison officers do some of the most important work in the justice system, but the general public doesn't often hear much about them, today Corrective Services Officer Paul Coyne joins us to tell us about his work and to dispel some common myths.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Fighting the good fight | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250129/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Victim's advocate Howard Brown has never shied away from a fight. In part two of his chat with Gary, he talks about the laws and procedures he has helped to change and how he handles the heavy emotional impact of his important work. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The man who has given everything to helping victims | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250130/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Howard Brown is a victim's advocate who dedicated his life to supporting and assisting victims of crime. In part one of his chat with Gary, Howard talks about the tragedy that gave him his life mission and some of the ways he has been able to change the system for the better. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>August in Kabul | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250131/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Photographer Andrew Quilty made the tough decision to return to Afghanistan during the Taliban takeover in Kabul to document the changes to the place he called home for years. He shares his story in his fascinating book, August in Kabul and today he tells us all about life inside a city in crisis.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>When your job is documenting danger... | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250132/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Multi-Walkley award-winning photojournalist Andrew Quilty has made a career out of running toward danger when everyone else is running away. He has shot some infamous scenes in Australia including the Cronulla riots and has spent years in Afghanistan documenting conflicts and most recently the Taliban takeover.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kicking down doors and finding peace in the kitchen | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250133/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250133/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of Gary's chat with former police officer Matt Moss, they talk about Matt's time in tactical policing, his path to becoming a detective and his time on My Kitchen Rules. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rage, riots, raids and recovery | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250134/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matt Moss is the world's most positive man, when Gary first met him he was in hospital after being shot and still had a smile on his face. In part one, he and Gary talk about the Bathurst riots, when Matt got shot during a raid and his recovery. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Graham Henry and Gary at the BAD Sydney Crime Writers Festival | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250135/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former notorious gangster and stand-over man Graham Henry and Gary sit in front of a live audience to discuss his book ‘Last Man Standing’.If you enjoyed the previous 4 part podcast, you will find this live interview with no safety net fascinating. It’s a real insight into the world of a hardcore gangster.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Grace Tobin and Gary Jubelin at the BAD Sydney Crime Writers Festival | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250136/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250136/</guid><description>Podcast Description The tables are turned when Gary is interviewed by good friend and ABC journalist Grace Tobin and members of the audience as they ask questions about his career and the release of his new book ‘Badness’ . See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Busting a bomb maker | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250137/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250137/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of Shane's chat with Gary, the pair discuss more of Shane's fascinating career including his work assessing threats both internationally and domestic and the time he busted a bomb maker.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The terrorist hunter | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250138/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250138/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shane Healey is a former soldier, private contractor and Army Intelligence Officer with expertise in counter-terrorism. In his chats with Gary, Shane talks about his time in the Army and how he used his intelligence skills to predict the actions of terrorists and stop them in their tracks. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What does it mean to be a man? | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250139/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Harry Garside is one of the country's best boxers, there's no doubting he's a tough guy. But he wants to challenge the idea that men and boys have to act a certain way to be considered 'manly'.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A fighter who is challenging conventions | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250140/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Harry Garside is an Olympic bronze medallist boxer and an all-around nice guy. In part one of his chat with Gary, he talks about his humble beginnings and the strength and dedication it took to get to the top of his game.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What if we changed the way we thought about prison? | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250141/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250141/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of Liz Sears' chat with Gary, the pair discuss her work in prison and how programs like the prison cafe, which gives prisoners purpose and a sense of worth are improving outcomes and why creating a sense of community in jails can benefit the greater community in the long run. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>An officer gives us a peek behind the prison walls | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250142/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Liz Sears is a Corrective Services Officer Senior Assistant Superintendent at maximum security prison. In part one of her chat with Gary, she talks about what life is really like day to day behind bars. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Coming to Australia | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250143/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250143/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of Gary's chat with Deng Adut, he talks about escaping his home country and arriving in Australia as a refugee. Deng overcame adversity to become a lawyer, a refugee advocate and NSW Australian of the Year.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The horrors of being a child soldier | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250144/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250144/</guid><description>Podcast Description Deng Adut was taken away as a 6-year-old to fight for the Sudan People's Liberation Army. In part one he tells Gary about the traumas of his childhood and the moments that gave him hope. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How do you fight the system? | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250145/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 05:11:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250145/</guid><description>Podcast Description When you want answers, but the answers that come don't make sense, how do you empower yourself in a system that is stacked against you? in part two, Anna and Sue talk about their dealings with the police and the coroners as they try and find out what happened to their loved ones.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two families looking for justice | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250146/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anna Davey and Sue Cole are two women connected by two unrelated tragedies. Both of them lost family members in suspicious circumstances and have spent years looking for answers. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>When the party's over | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250147/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250147/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two, Gary and Rick talk about what it was like to hit rock bottom and what gave Rick the motivation to get through rehab and become clean and sober after years of heroin addiction. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Living like a rockstar | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250148/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rick Grossman was living every young musician's dreams, he was a bass player for the rock bands Divinyls and Hoodoo Gurus. But his new life came with some dangerous temptations that took him down a dark path. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Going into prison as a bikie and walking out a changed man | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250149/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250149/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of his chat with Gary, former Bandidos member Johnny 'Two Guns' Walker talks about what life was like in prison and what it was like when he got out and started over. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Becoming an outlaw | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250150/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 19:39:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Johnny “2 Guns” Walker is a former Bandidos Sergeant-at-Arms. He tells Gary what led him to become a bikie and talks about the slippery slope of crime.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Unmasking the real Richard Dorrough | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250151/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Richard Dorrough, a former member of the Navy, took his own life in 2014. He left behind a shocking note, claiming to have murdered three people. But there was a problem, no one knew who the victims were. Dan Box and his team explored the mystery in the new podcast, Bloodguilt. In part two of his chat with Gary, Dan takes us through the case. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>A letter, a confession and a mystery to crack | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250152/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan Box is one of Australia's most respected crime journalists. He's also an author and a podcaster. He is the co-author of Gary's memoir, I Catch Killers'. Have a listen to these two old mates having a chat about Dan's work and the murder mystery he's spent years solving. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>When drug busts go wrong | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250153/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250153/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of Gary's chat with former Drug Squad Detective Paul Willingham, we learn what happens when drug busts go wrong and labs explode. We also learn about the unique hazards associated with dismantling a lab.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The frontlines on the war on drugs | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250154/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former Drug squad Detective Inspector Paul Willingham has seen first-hand the destruction drugs can cause and the sophisticated operations that keep a steady supply flowing to the streets. In Part one of his chat with Gary, Paul takes us into the world of drug labs and busts.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A guilt that will never leave and two years in prison | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250155/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lisa Mottram isn't sharing her story for forgiveness, or to try and fix her image. She knows that her crime is something she will have to live with for the rest of her life. But she wants others to understand just how quickly your life can go downhill if you drink and drive.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A split second decision that destroyed lives | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250156/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lisa Mottram isn't a career criminal, she'd never been arrested or even had much interaction with the cops before 2018, when one terrible decision lead to her destroying lives, including her own. Lisa is here to share her story so no one else follows her down the same path.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Police don't show weakness | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250157/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250157/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Shaun O'Gorman got into a violent altercation with a suspect, he knew he'd reached a tipping point. He had to get help before he destroyed himself. If you or someone you know need support, make sure you contact Lifeline on 131114
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The unbreakable cop with invisible demons | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250158/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250158/</guid><description>Podcast Description A warning up front that this episode contains mentions of suicide, if you need support contact Lifeline: 131114. At his lowest moment, Shaun O'Gorman spent three nights with a loaded glock pistol by his side in bed trying to think of reasons not to end his life. On the outside, he was a tough, thick-skinned cop, but on the inside, the job was getting to him.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Choosing kindness in a cruel world | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250159/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250159/</guid><description>Podcast Description After losing two sons, you wouldn't blame Ralph and Kathy Kelly if they chose to hide away from the world and become angry and withdrawn. Instead, they are on a mission to make the world a kinder place. Learn more at https://www.staykind.org/
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ralph and Kathy Kelly's unimaginable loss | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250160/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250160/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ralph and Kathy Kelly never imagined they'd one day be campaigning for change against street violence and spending their nights out on the street helping young people get home safely. They were just an average Aussie family until their son Thomas was taken from them suddenly one night in an act of senseless violence. Tragedy struck the family again four years later when their other son, Stuart, died by suicide.</description></item><item><title>An arrest 10 years in the making | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250161/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250161/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ken Gamble is not the man you want chasing you when you're on the run. In part two of his chat with Gary he talks about the hunt for conman Peter Foster. He also discusses his involvement in investigating the disappearance of Theo Hayez.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A private investigator and an international child retrieval | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250162/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250162/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ken Gamble is the kind of man who never gives up on a case, doggedly chasing down leads wherever they take him, even if that means getting on a plane and travelling to a different country. In part one, Ken talks about how he got his start as a private investigator and shares how he helped to retrieve a child that had been taken from her mother.
See omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>How many times can you die before you choose life? | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250163/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Danny Shannon couldn't go on with the life he was living, collapsing in the street from overdoses, ruining his relationships and destroying his body. It was time to make some big changes, in this episode he shares how he did it, and how he's helping others overcome.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Heroin, a pile of cash, and a prison break without a plan | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250164/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250164/</guid><description>Podcast Description Danny Shannon is one lucky man, he's survived more drug overdoses and rehab attempts than most addicts combined. In this episode, Danny shares how he turned to a life of drugs before seeing the light in recovery and recounts the time he escaped Silverwater prison without much of a plan.&amp;nbsp;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How do you solve a murder with a chicken salad roll? | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250165/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Retired officer John Goobanko is back for part two and he's got a cracker of a story about how he solved a murder using a chicken salad roll, as well as many more wild cop yarns.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>41 years cleaning up the Gold Coast | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250166/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250166/</guid><description>Podcast Description Very recently retired police officer John Goobanko joins us today. John's impressive career spans 41 years policing the Gold Coast in Queensland. John has been involved in some incredible jobs, everything from extortion to murders and kidnappings.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The aftermath of the Bali bombing | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250167/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250167/</guid><description>Podcast Description AFP officer Mick Travers was watching the news when he was that there had been a terrorist attack in Bali, soon after his phone rang and he found himself deployed to one of the most challenging crime scenes he's ever encountered.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Seeing death on a scale few people will ever witness | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250168/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mick Travers is a retired AFP Superintendent who amongst other things responded to the Bali Bombing, Thredbo Disaster and Asian Tsunami. Mick has seen a lot in his long career and he shares some of the lessons he's learnt along the way.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Abuse didn't stand in the way of Sharon's dreams | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250169/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sharon Morgan felt like a fraud, by day she was attending domestic violence calls as a police officer and providing the victims with support and advice, but each night she'd return home to her own abusive partner. Sharon finally said enough was enough and left her partner, since then she's had an inspiring and powerful career story.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>She was helping victims every day, but she was a victim herself | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250170/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250170/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is a special milestone for I Catch Killers. Gary sat down with his first current serving officer, Sergeant Sharon Morgan. In part one of their chat Sharon talks about her beginning in the cops and the long road she walked to get there.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Leaving the police and losing your identity | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250171/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250171/</guid><description>Podcast Description in part two of Gary's chat with former detective David Mcgowan the pair discuss the culture shock that comes with leaving the police after a long career and how you can rebuild your life and find a new identity.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The cops left in no man's land | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250172/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250172/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Mcgowan is a former Victorian Police Major Crime Detective and now Chief Executive Officer of the Police Veterans Victoria. In part one of his chat with Gary he talks about his career and what lead him to want to help police veterans.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Leaving the club and starting over | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250173/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250173/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Brent decided to start a new life, it didn't come easily, but he was determined to use the lessons he had learnt on his own painful journey to help others.&amp;nbsp;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cops and bikies don't mix | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250174/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250174/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brent Simpson and Gary knew about each other back when they were on opposite sides of the law. Now, they sit down man to man to talk about Brent's life as a bike Sergeant-at-arms and the lessons he's learnt since leaving and turning his life around.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Standing up for Bowraville | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250175/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250175/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part 2 of Gary's chat with David Shoebridge the two reminisce about their shared experiences in Bowraville and their fight to help the community find justice.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Toughness comes in many forms | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250176/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250176/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Shoebridge is standing as the lead Senate candidate for the Greens in the 2022 federal election. He's also a man who has exhibited an admirable mental toughness and stood up for what he believes with empathy and compassion.&amp;nbsp;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What happens when you get out of Jail? | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250177/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 22:03:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250177/</guid><description>Podcast Description In&amp;nbsp; part two of Gary's chat with Dr Mindi Sotiri the pair discuss the difficulties of life after prison and what happens when we don't have the right support in place.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jailing is failing | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250178/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250178/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr Mindi Sotiri is the Executive Director at the Justice Reform Initiative, she and Gary sat down to talk about why the current justice system isn't quite working as well as it should.&amp;nbsp;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A new path starts in prison | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250179/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeffrey Morgan reached a turning point in prison when he realised he could no longer continue living the way he had been. The journey he took from that day to become a successful businessman and TV presenter is truly inspiring.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Becoming a bank robber | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250180/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeffrey Morgan grew up in Redfern and from his start in petty crime, he soon found himself moving into more serious offences like bank robbery and other armed holdups. Jeffrey's story is thankfully one of redemption and the power of positive thinking and motivation.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Solving the mystery of Anne Frank | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250181/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brendan Rook was a member of the elite group of investigators who scoured through clues, witness accounts and documents to try and finally solve the mystery of who betrayed Anne Frank and her family and gave them up to the Nazis.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Aussie cop tracking down war criminals | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250182/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250182/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brendan Rook has lived many lives, he's been a Queensland homicide detective, a war crimes investigator for the International Criminal Court and he's recently been a part of the team who investigated the mystery of who betrayed Anne Frank and her family.&amp;nbsp;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Bada Bing police raids and a year behind bars | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250183/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250183/</guid><description>Podcast Description When the police raided the Bada Bing nightclub and Dreamgirls club in Kings Cross, Alyson knew it was all over. Before long the police were at her door and she was arrested. Alyson served 14 months in a women's prison and the lessons she learnt during that time have helped her to get her life straight. She now works with a mentoring program helping other women adapt to a life after prison.</description></item><item><title>From country girl to Kings Cross drug dealer | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250184/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250184/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alyson Colquitt left her home in rural NSW to travel and experience life. She found herself working as a stripper in Kings Cross, using drugs and eventually selling them on the side. It was the beginning of a journey that would leave her behind bars.
&amp;nbsp;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Graham Henry: Unravelled | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250185/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250185/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part 4 of Gary's chat with Graham Henry the pair discuss the end of the green light era and the moment he stabbed a police prosecutor...
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Graham Henry: Plots and betrayals | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250186/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250186/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part 3 of Gary's conversation with Graham Henry the pair talk about the time he plotted to Kill Neddy and that time Neddy plotted to kill him...&amp;nbsp;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>When Graham met Neddy | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250187/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250187/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of Gary's chat with notorious underworld figure Graham Henry he talks about what led to his life of crime and how he met his criminal partner, Neddy Smith.
You can find Graham's book here
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Graham Henry - A treacherous life | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250188/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250188/</guid><description>Podcast Description Graham Henry is one of Sydney&amp;rsquo;s most well-known gangsters. He operated with his mate Arthur (Neddy) Smith with violence and intimidation at a time when they were given a green light to commit crimes by corrupt police such as Roger Rogerson.&amp;nbsp; Graham is the last man standing and is going to give us an insight into a world of crime people rarely speak about.&amp;nbsp;
You can find Graham's book here</description></item><item><title>The contender | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250189/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250189/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of Gary's chat with Garth Wood the pair talk about his time on The Contender television show, his incredible fight against Anthony Mundine and how men need to be more comfortable speaking up when they need support.&amp;nbsp;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A fighter at the crossroads | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250190/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250190/</guid><description>Podcast Description Garth Wood grew up in the rough streets of inner-city Sydney. His life could have taken many paths.&amp;nbsp; He played in the NRL for Souths and Balmain just like his father and brother.&amp;nbsp; He found himself cut from the NRL and broke up with his partner. He had no qualifications, was unemployed and turned to alcohol and started hanging out with the wrong crowd...&amp;nbsp;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Sacrificing everything to catch a killer | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250191/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250191/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of Peter Seymour's story, we hear about the lengths he and his team went to secure a conviction and how it felt to watch a not guilty verdict play out in court. Peter also talks about how a long career caught up with him and left him broken.&amp;nbsp;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Seven bones, two wives and a bizarre murder mystery | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250192/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250192/</guid><description>Podcast Description Peter Seymour joined the New South Wales Police Force in 1980 as an eighteen-year-old and spent 24 years in Police.
We will talk about his career and one of the more bizarre murder investigations in Australia&amp;rsquo;s history. Two wives die in suspicious circumstances: co-incidence or, as husband Thomas Keir describes it, &amp;lsquo;bad luck&amp;rsquo;?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Leaving the Legion and walking across Australia | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250193/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250193/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of Gary's chat with David Mason they talk about his life after leaving the French Foreign Legion, including his epic journey across Australia accompanied by just a few camels.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Running away to join the French Foreign Legion | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250194/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250194/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever daydreamed about dropping everything and starting a new life? David Mason didn't just think about it, he did it. He gave up a comfy life in Australia to join the French Foreign Legion and the adventures were well worth it.&amp;nbsp;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Healing the rift between cops and the Indigenous community | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250195/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250195/</guid><description>Podcast Description For decades, there was no love lost between the Redfern Indigenous community and the police. Communication was poor and crime rates were high. Then Shane Phillips and a group of other Aboriginal leaders decided to try something new, and the results were incredible.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Becoming a warrior | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250196/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250196/</guid><description>Podcast Description Born and raised in Redfern, Shane Phillips is an outstanding community leader, respected by Indigenous and non-Indigenous people alike for his integrity, hard work and determination to get things done. In 1999 Shane went on a boat trip that changed his life and lead him to a new way to help heal his community.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>When trials by media go wrong | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250197/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250197/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of Gary's chat with defence lawyer John Korn, the pair debate about whether police should give details to the media. And John talks about why he didn't appreciate the Prime Minister's recent apology.&amp;nbsp;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A cop and a defence lawyer are natural enemies | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250198/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250198/</guid><description>Podcast Description John Korn has over 40 years of experience working in Criminal Law. He and Gary have known each other for quite a while, but most of their interactions have been on opposite sides of a courtroom. Now they sit down to talk about how police and lawyers interact as well as some of John's cases.&amp;nbsp;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The memories you wish you could forget | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250199/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250199/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of Gary's chat with former crime scene officer Bob Gibbs, they talk more about some of the cases he worked on as he was called into to record the results of worst of human nature murders and mutilations. Bob also shares the impact the job had on him and how he's doing today.&amp;nbsp;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>On the scene of the Port Arthur massacre | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250200/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250200/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bob Gibbs has seen some horrific things as a crime scene officer, but nothing prepared him for the carnage that occurred in Port Arthur when 35 people were murdered.He shares his memories of that day.&amp;nbsp;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Brutalised as a ward of the state, Wilma has fought back | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250201/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250201/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Part two of Gary's chat with Wilma Robb, she talks about life after abuse and how she learned to use her voice to help other survivors.&amp;nbsp;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>'I was just a kid' | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250202/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250202/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wilma Robb's story is about brutality and degradation. She was made a ward of the state because she had no one to look after her. As a 13-year old girl in the care of the state, she had her face smashed into a sink and was told to clean up the mess as blood poured out of her mouth.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Wilma is an outspoken advocate for the girls subjected to the brutal regime at Parramatta Girls School and Hay Institute for girls.</description></item><item><title>An addict is reborn as a genuine Aussie hero | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250203/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250203/</guid><description>Podcast Description Simon Fenech pulled himself out of addiction and the criminal world in which he was deeply entrenched and he created a new life for himself. Not only that, but he gives back through the program that helped him, fruit2work, which employs people who have been in prison to give them a second chance.&amp;nbsp;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>From champion kickboxer to ice addict | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250204/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250204/</guid><description>Podcast Description What would make a champion kickboxer and loving husband and father turn to ice? Simon Fenech, a successful sportsman and committed family man, tried crystal meth for the first time after a traumatic work accident. He was instantly hooked. Soon, he was dealing to support a $1000-a-day addiction.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Giving up was not an option | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250205/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250205/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of Gary's chat with Damien they talk about his incredible survival and how his positive attitude and drive helped push him forward and achieve what many thought was going to be impossible.&amp;nbsp;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Without warning: A Commando's incredible survival | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250206/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250206/</guid><description>Podcast Description Private Damien Thomlinson is a former member of the elite 2nd Commando Regiment of the Australian Army who was terribly injured after a bomb explosion in Afghanistan. His inspiring journey back from the dead stands as proof that no challenge is too great and that the ANZAC spirit is truly alive and well.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A glimpse inside crime within the prison system | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250207/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250207/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of Gary's chat with Dave Christie, they talk about his work with corrective services and we get a rare look at how crime continues even behind bars.&amp;nbsp;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Closing the net on fraudster and scam artists | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250208/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250208/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dave Christie was a NSW cop for 37 years. He spent most of his time as a detective and a large portion was in the Fraud Squad as well as four years heading up the Corrective Services Investigation Unit for the NSW Police. We take a deep dive into his policing career and get a greater understanding of the impact of fraud and you might even get a few tips on how to prevent yourself from becoming a victim.</description></item><item><title>Helicopters and hacksaws | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250209/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250209/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of Gary's chat with Mark Dapin they talk more about famous prison breaks including the story of Russell Cox and John Killick.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Australia's most shocking prison breaks | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250210/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250210/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Gary is joined by respected journalist and author Mark Dapin to talk about the stories behind some of Australia's most infamous prison breaks and the crooks behind them.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Spanian's path to redemption | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250211/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250211/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of Gary's chat with viral sensation Spanian he talks about the moment he knew he had to turn his life around and his rise to fame online.&amp;nbsp;
Publication Details:&amp;nbsp;The Unfiltered Hood Life&amp;nbsp;by&amp;nbsp;Spanian&amp;nbsp;(with Christopher Kevin Au) Hachette Australia $34.99
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Spanian's unfiltered hood life | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250212/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250212/</guid><description>Podcast Description Viral hip-hop star Spanian spent much of his life in a vicious vortex of crime, violence, incarceration and drug addiction. In part one of his discussion with Gary he talks about his childhood and how his experiences shaped him.
Publication Details:&amp;nbsp;The Unfiltered Hood Life&amp;nbsp;by&amp;nbsp;Spanian&amp;nbsp;(with Christopher Kevin Au) Hachette Australia $34.99
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>From knockabout to actor to author | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250213/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250213/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of Gary's chat with Bryan Brown they talk about his book, Sweet Jimmy, and why Australian's are so fascinated with true crime.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bryan Brown is a convincing criminal | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250214/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250214/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gary is used to sitting down with cops and crims on I Catch Killers, but in this episode, he's doing something a bit different. Gary sat down with Aussie actor and now author, Bryan Brown to talk about how he got started in his career and why he's such a believable on-screen bad guy.&amp;nbsp;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Seeing the path you don't want to take | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250215/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250215/</guid><description>Podcast Description Richie 'Vas' Vaculik grew up in a culture where crime and jail time were almost a right of passage. After a few brushes with the law himself, Richie decided it was time to make some changes.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Life as a Bra Boy with Richie Vaculik | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250216/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250216/</guid><description>Podcast Description Richie 'Vas' Vaculik grew up in Maroubra, Maroubra Beach was his playground and the Bra Boys were like family. He was their Minister for Good Times and a central character in the Bra Boys' story as they became famous and infamous in equal measure.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Raging against the justice system | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250217/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250217/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of Gary's chat with Ken Marslew he shares his experience moving through the justice system and discovering just how broken it is. Ken knew things had to change and so he decided he was the man for the job,
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Living every parent's worst nightmare | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250218/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250218/</guid><description>Podcast Description Every parent's nightmare is finding out something horrible has happened to their child. That nightmare became a tragic reality for Ken Marslew back in 1994 when the police arrived to tell him his son had been murdered. Since that day Ken has been on a remarkable journey and helped hundreds of people along the way.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Living with the Mafia | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250219/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250219/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of Gary's chat with Joe Pistone, he goes in-depth about his famous undercover operation and talks about the rules you just don't break when you're dealing with the mob.&amp;nbsp;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Joe Pistone: The Real Donnie Brasco | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250220/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250220/</guid><description>Podcast Description For six years, Joe infiltrated the New York Mafia. His undercover name was Donnie Brasco. The Hollywood Movie, Donnie Brasco starring Jonny Depp was based on Joe&amp;rsquo;s life story. He talks about his time undercover hanging out with the likes of Sonny Black and Lefty Ruggiero.&amp;nbsp;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A gun to the head | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250221/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250221/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of Gary's conversation with former police officer Keith Banks, he talks about the dark side of policing, including losing a good mate in the line of duty and the impact it had on his life.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Never lose the fear | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250222/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250222/</guid><description>Podcast Description We welcome back Keith Banks for another great chat. Keith talks about his time in tactical policing as well as his work in witness protection. He also explains why it's important for cops to stay scared.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Revealing the real Roger Rogerson | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250223/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250223/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Gary's final chat with former homicide detective Russell Oxford he takes us through the in-depth investigation into the murder of Jamie Gao and the path that took them to arrest Former detectives Roger Rogerson and Glen McNamara.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>International manhunts and witness protection | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250224/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250224/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part 3 of Gary's conversation with former homicide Detective Russell Oxford he talks about some more of his high profile investigations including his work on the Clairmont serial killer investigation and his time in Beirut.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>William Tyrrell update | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250225/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250225/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a big week of news, Gary sits down with journalist Claire Harvey to give his official response to some of the allegations and questions surrounding the investigation he led for four years.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Catching the Butcher of Wollongong | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250226/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250226/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of Gary's chat with retired detective Russell Oxford, he walks us through a series of murders in Sydney and Wollongong and how he and his team tracked down the killer- Mark Valer, then known as Mark van Krevel, a man dubbed 'the Butcher of Wollongong'.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Solving the murder of Janine Balding | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250227/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250227/</guid><description>Podcast Description One of the true greats of policing in Australia, Detective Chief Inspector Russell Oxford sat down with Gary just one week into retirement to talk about some of his biggest cases, including the murder of Janine Balding and another case that led to him arresting a fellow cop.&amp;nbsp;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A survivor's fight for justice | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250228/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 21:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250228/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of Gary's chat with Russell he talks about his time in prison and how he became driven to get involved in the Royal Commission into Institutional Responses to Child Sexual&amp;nbsp;Abuse.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Voice of a survivor | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250229/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250229/</guid><description>Podcast Description Russell Manser&amp;nbsp;has an extensive criminal history. He robbed banks, escaped from custody, was a heroin addict and spent 23 years in gaol.
What wasn&amp;rsquo;t known about Russell is that he was the victim of institutionalised sexual abuse. He's a&amp;nbsp;tough guy who has the courage to talk about his experiences and encourage others to come forward.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The execution that started a reign of gangland terror | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250230/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250230/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of Gary's chat with former homicide detective Charlie Bezzina. In this episode Charlie talks about the killing of Melbourne gangland figure Alphonse Gangitano and the spate of murders that followed.&amp;nbsp;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hunting an Australian serial killer | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250231/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250231/</guid><description>Podcast Description Charlie Bezzina was one of Victoria's top Homicide detectives. In his 17 years in the Homicide Squad, he investigated more than 300 suspicious deaths, including 150 murders - among them the crimes of serial killer Paul Denyer, better known as the Frankson Serial Killer.&amp;nbsp;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Turning struggles and pain into success | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250232/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250232/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of Gary's chat with the incredible Lovemore Ndou, he tells us how he channelled the dark experiences of his past into his success in the future and how he's worked for equality and change.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lovemore Ndou: An incredible Life | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250233/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250233/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lovemore Ndou has lived many lives, from a young child in South Africa struggling with loss and violence in apartheid to a champion boxer and now a lawyer and an author. He has an amazing inspirational story to tell.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How do cops heal after the unthinkable? | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250234/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250234/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the second part of our chat with former police officer Helen McMurtrie, we're also joined by Alana Singleton. Alana is also a former cop and now helps first responders like Helen recover from PTSD and other mental health issues post-retirement through the Emerge and See program.&amp;nbsp;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Shot in the neck - how a country cop survived | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250235/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250235/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Helen McMurtie talks us through her life as a female uniform cop in the city and the country. She also discusses when she got shot in the neck and thought she was going to die attending a violent domestic. This 2018 crime was the last crime scene Gary attended before his retirement.
&amp;nbsp;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The prison break that stopped the nation | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250236/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250236/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1999 John Killick and his then-girlfriend Lucy Dudko pulled off the most daring prison break in Australian history when Lucy hijacked a helicopter and landed it in Silverwater prison before she and John flew to freedom. John tells us everything that went down before the big event and why he doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to be known as the helicopter man. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bank robberies and jailbreaks: John Killick's life of crime | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250237/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250237/</guid><description>Podcast Description John has spent more than 30 years in some of the toughest jails in the country. He&amp;rsquo;s got an extensive criminal history and is known for committing multiple bank robberies, as well as multiple prison breaks. But he&amp;rsquo;s turned his life around now and he shares some insights into what put him back on the right path.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Behind the glamour of spies | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250238/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250238/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of Gary&amp;rsquo;s chat with Jack, he reveals that being a spy isn&amp;rsquo;t like it looks in the movies. Jack also shares the hardest moments and unexpected struggles that come with the job.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A meeting with a spy | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250239/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250239/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jack Beaumont has lived a million lives, he&amp;rsquo;a former spy for the French Foreign Secret Service, fighter pilot and now an author. In part one of the chat, Jack shares how he went from the skies to deep undercover hunting bad guys. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Racing's most colourful sages and scallywags | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250240/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250240/</guid><description>Podcast Description To celebrate the launch of his new book Chance, Gary catches up with True Crime Australia podcaster and crime journalist Andrew Rule, who has turned his mind to some of racing&amp;rsquo;s most colourful sages and scallywags.
More information about the book at: https://www.panmacmillan.com.au/9781760987718/
Search for Andrew Rule&amp;rsquo;s podcast by typing &amp;lsquo;Life and Crimes&amp;rsquo; into the search wherever you get your podcasts. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>From NSW cop, to hash trafficker, to supermax | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250241/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250241/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former NSW cop Charlie Staunton left Australia after an appearance at the Wood Royal Commission into police corruption, his life would take a dramatic turn when he fell in with an international drug operation and was jailed in Canada for importing 25 tonnes of hash.
To listen to I Catch Killers first, ad free, read journalism about the podcast and watch galleries and videos, go to icatchkillers.com.au to see our range of subscription offers.</description></item><item><title>72 scotch bottles that changed a cop's life | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250242/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250242/</guid><description>Podcast Description Charlie Staunton always thought of himself as a good cop but was compromising his values from the first week he joined the NSW Police Force. It all fell apart when he stumbled across six dozen cases of scotch whiskey. To listen to I Catch Killers first, ad free, read journalism about the podcast and watch galleries and videos, go to icatchkillers.com.au to see our range of subscription offers. See omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>Solving an Underworld Murder | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250243/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250243/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a luxury car salesman&amp;rsquo;s vehicle was found close to a notorious suicide spot it looked as if he may have taken his own life, but it didn&amp;rsquo;t take long for suspicions to grow.
To listen to I Catch Killers first, ad free, read journalism about the podcast and watch galleries and videos, go to icatchkillers.com.au to see our range of subscription offers. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Cases That Haunt Me | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250244/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250244/</guid><description>Podcast Description Crown prosecutor Margaret Cunneen recalls the headline cases that helped establish her reputation, the controversies she became embroiled in and why she jumped to the other side of the bar table.
To listen to I Catch Killers first, ad free, read journalism about the podcast and watch galleries and videos, go to icatchkillers.com.au to see our range of subscription offers. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Prosecutor | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250245/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250245/</guid><description>Podcast Description For over four decades Margaret Cunneen helped put away some of Australia&amp;rsquo;s worst as a crown prosecutor and, as her profile grew, so did the media attention
To listen to I Catch Killers first, ad free, read journalism about the podcast and watch galleries and videos, go to icatchkillers.com.au to see our range of subscription offers. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Fight never ends for Bowraville families | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250246/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250246/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bowraville murders - Part 2. Three decades after three Indigenous children were murdered, their families remain as focused as ever on trying to get justice for their loved ones in the case that also changed the life of Gary.
To listen to I Catch Killers first, ad free, read journalism about the podcast and watch galleries and videos, go to icatchkillers.com.au to see our range of subscription offers. See omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>Three murders, no justice | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250247/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250247/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bowraville murders - Part 1. The families of three Indigenous children who were all murdered in the NSW regional town of Bowraville open up on the toll of losing their loved ones and the inept police investigation that followed.
To listen to I Catch Killers first, ad free, read journalism about the podcast and watch galleries and videos, go to icatchkillers.com.au to see our range of subscription offers.See omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>The Mindhunter | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250248/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250248/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr Sarah Yule broke new ground when she became the first forensic psychologist appointed to an operational role in an Australian police force. In this episode she and Gary discuss her career path and the amazing innovations she made her in field.
To listen to I Catch Killers first, ad free, read journalism about the podcast and watch galleries and videos, go to icatchkillers.com.au to see our range of subscription offers.</description></item><item><title>Dissecting a Crime Scene | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250249/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250249/</guid><description>Podcast Description Forensic psychologist Dr Sarah Yule reveals her approach to operational policing and what a forensic psychologist does to help track down crooks. If you&amp;rsquo;re a fan of Mindhunter, or the way the mind of a criminal operates, this episode of ICK is for you.
To listen to I Catch Killers first, ad free, read journalism about the podcast and watch galleries and videos, go to icatchkillers.com.au to see our range of subscription offers.</description></item><item><title>Fighting for Justice | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250250/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250250/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a young boxer Khalid Baker was about to represent Australia at the Commonwealth Games but instead spent 13 years in prison as a convicted murderer. He maintains his innocence and tells Gary that he won&amp;rsquo;t rest until he clears his name and wins a world boxing title. To listen to I Catch Killers first, ad free, read journalism about the podcast and watch galleries and videos, go to icatchkillers.</description></item><item><title>Finding Peace Behind Bars | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250251/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250251/</guid><description>Podcast Description Khalid Baker was young and angry when sentenced to 17 years in jail for a murder conviction that many experts have cast doubt on and he claims to have never committed. While he spent his 20s behind bars he reveals how he made it through and focused on his goal to win a world boxing title. To listen to I Catch Killers first, ad free, read journalism about the podcast and watch galleries and videos, go to icatchkillers.</description></item><item><title>Fighting Back Then Going Back | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250252/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250252/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bernie Matthews emerged from prison at the turn of the century to become a journalist who broke major stories. That’s why for so many, including himself, it was such a tragedy when he once again found himself behind bars. “It was collateral damage to my life&amp;hellip;I think it’s in my DNA” he tells Gary in the final of the four-part special.
To listen to I Catch Killers first, ad free, read journalism about the podcast and watch galleries and videos, go to icatchkillers.</description></item><item><title>Katingal: A New Kind of Hell | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250253/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250253/</guid><description>Podcast Description Part 3 of four. Katingal was Australia’s first SuperMax prison and an experiment in sensory deprivation. Bernie Matthews was the longest serving prisoner in what has been described as an ‘electronic zoo’. At one stage he tried to burn it down before it was shut for good due to the inhumane conditions.
To listen to I Catch Killers first, ad free, read journalism about the podcast and watch galleries and videos, go to icatchkillers.</description></item><item><title>The Brutality of Grafton Jail | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250254/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250254/</guid><description>Podcast Description Part 2 of a four part special. When Bernie Matthews arrived at Grafton Jail as an intractable prisoner in the 1970s he received a smack in the mouth and a bowl of maggot-infested porridge. Bashings from prison guards became a bloodsport and left physical and psychological scars on whoever spent time in Grafton’s cells.
To listen to I Catch Killers first, ad free, read journalism about the podcast and watch galleries and videos, go to icatchkillers.</description></item><item><title>The Cop and The Crook | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250255/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250255/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bernie Matthews was a notorious armed robber when Gary Jubelin was in the armed hold-up squad. If they had faced off in their chosen trades guns would have been drawn. Bernie would become an award-winning journalist and opens up to Gary about his life as a stick-up merchant and prison escapee. Part 1 of a four part special with Bernie.
To listen to I Catch Killers first, ad free, read journalism about the podcast and watch galleries and videos, go to icatchkillers.</description></item><item><title>Stabbed, near death, one cop's oath to never be a victim again | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250256/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250256/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part 2, Jason Semple had been stabbed and left to die in a gutter but, not only did he survive, he became one of Australia&amp;rsquo;s hardest cops. He explains to Gary how he summoned the willpower and strength to live a life inspired by Peter Forsyth, his colleague that died on that tragic night in Sydney. To listen to I Catch Killers first, ad free, read journalism about the podcast and watch galleries and videos, go to icatchkillers.</description></item><item><title>The Sydney Police Stabbing That Shocked a Nation | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250257/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250257/</guid><description>Podcast Description Constable Jason Semple had just begun his career in the Police Force when he and his new friend and colleague Peter Forsyth were stabbed while off-duty on an inner-city street in Sydney. Peter tragically died but Jason overcame his life-threatening injuries and, as he tells Gary, life would never be the same again.
To listen to I Catch Killers first, ad free, read journalism about the podcast and watch galleries and videos, go to icatchkillers.</description></item><item><title>Season 3 Preview | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250258/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 10:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250258/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 3 of I Catch Killers will be available first, ad free, with exclusive video content and award winning investigative journalism with a subscription to icatchkillers.com.au.
In this episode producer Claire Harvey sits down with Gary to talk about the guests and topics of discussion in Season 3. Here are the guests Gary has lined up, and the titles of each episode:
Jason Semple: ‘Victim to Protector’
Bernie Matthews: ‘The Cop and the Crook’</description></item><item><title>What is Justice? | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250259/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250259/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 3 of I Catch Killers will publish in early April. Before then we&amp;rsquo;ve got some bonus episodes for you.
In part 2 with solicitor and former police prosecutor Tony Trichter we deep dive into the legal system. With a discussion about ‘What is justice?’ We cover off some well-known cases such as the Cardinal George Pell matter. Gary and Tony also talk about the powers of a citizen’s arrest and have a conversation about what is self-defence.</description></item><item><title>Knowledge is Power | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250260/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250260/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 3 of I Catch Killers will publish in early April. Before then we&amp;rsquo;ve got some bonus episodes for you.
Solicitor Tony Trichter spent 35 years in the NSW Police Force, working mainly as a police prosecutor. He recently retired as the Commander of the Police Prosecutions Branch and is now working as an Adjunct Industry Professor. In part 1 of this 2-part bonus episode Tony is going to talk to us about his experience as a prosecutor in the criminal courts, breaking down the often-confusing court process.</description></item><item><title>Pure Evil - A Serial Killer's Story | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250261/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250261/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 3 of I Catch Killers will publish in early April. Before then we&amp;rsquo;ve got some bonus episodes for you.
In Part 2 with Duncan McNab, we are taken on a journey of murder and torture where Wilder goes on a murderous rampage across the United States before being gunned down in a shoot out with police. At the time of his death Wilder was responsible for murdering 9 women.</description></item><item><title>Monster in Plain Sight | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250262/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 04:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250262/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 3 of I Catch Killers will publish in early April. Before then we&amp;rsquo;ve got some bonus episodes for you.
This is the story of Christopher Wilder an Australian born serial killer, as told through the eyes of investigative journalist Duncan McNab who meticulously researched the life and crimes of Wilder for his book ’The Snapshot Killer.’ In part 1 of this 2 part bonus interview, we learn of Wilder’s crimes and deviant behaviour whilst growing up in Australia, before becoming the FBI’s most wanted for multiple murders of women in the United States.</description></item><item><title>2020 Sydney Crime Writers Festival | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250263/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250263/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 3 of I Catch Killers is coming soon. Before season 3 we&amp;rsquo;ve got another bonus episode for you, here is Gary&amp;rsquo;s onstage appearance at the Sydney Crime Writers festival, the interviewer is Michael Duffy.
For more information on the Sydney Crime Writers festival go to: https://www.badsydney.com/See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ray Watson - Retired Victorian Armed Hold Up Squad Detective | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250264/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250264/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 3 of I Catch Killers is coming soon. In this bonus episode Gary talks to retired Victorian armed hold up squad Detective Ray Watson, Ray talks about his career from 1973 to the year 2000 and how he may have been one of the harder cops for his superiors to supervise.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Instructions Sold Separately - Part 2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250265/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250265/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is part 2 of Gary&amp;rsquo;s appearance on a podcast called Instructions Sold Separately which is produced by the team at Swiss 8. In this bonus episode you&amp;rsquo;ll hear him talk frankly about his dismissal from the cops, and also the skills he uses to de-escalate situations. Search for Swiss 8 Instructions Sold Separately to find out more about this podcast.
Swiss 8 is a health promotion charity, founded by Australian Combat Veterans.</description></item><item><title>Instructions Sold Separately - Part 1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250266/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 22:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250266/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 3 of I Catch Killers is coming soon. Before then we have some bonus episodes for you. This is part 1 of Gary&amp;rsquo;s appearance on a podcast called Instructions Sold Separately which is produced by the team at Swiss 8. We&amp;rsquo;ll publish part 2 of the chat next week. Search for Swiss 8 Instructions Sold Separately to find out more about this podcast.
Swiss 8 is a health promotion charity, founded by Australian Combat Veterans.</description></item><item><title>Mass-Murderers, Gangsters and Bikies | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250267/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250267/</guid><description>Podcast Description One of the country&amp;rsquo;s most in-demand criminal psychologists, Dr Tim Watson-Munro&amp;rsquo;s clients have included some infamous criminals from Hoddle St Massacre gunman Julian Knight to gangster Alphonse Gangitano, bikie Mick Hawi and corporate crook Alan Bond. New episodes of season 2 will be released exclusively on icatchkillers.com.au a week earlier than anywhere else. Subscribers to icatchkillers.com.au get exclusive access, as well as access to articles, videos of Gary&amp;rsquo;s interviews and interactive content.</description></item><item><title>Australia's Most Vicious Jail | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250268/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250268/</guid><description>Podcast Description Beginning his career as a criminal psychologist at Parramatta Jail in the late 70s, Dr Tim Watson-Munro was exposed to life&amp;rsquo;s dark underbelly and he had to learn fast how to navigate this new world.
New episodes of season 2 will be released exclusively on icatchkillers.com.au a week earlier than anywhere else. Subscribers to icatchkillers.com.au get exclusive access, as well as access to articles, videos of Gary&amp;rsquo;s interviews and interactive content.</description></item><item><title>Bringing Matthew Home | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250269/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250269/</guid><description>Podcast Description After 10 heartbreaking years a breakthrough in the search for Matthew came in 2017 when the man who disposed of his body, Michael Atkins, was forced to reveal its location. New episodes of season 2 will be released exclusively on icatchkillers.com.au a week earlier than anywhere else. Subscribers to icatchkillers.com.au get exclusive access, as well as access to articles, videos of Gary&amp;rsquo;s interviews and interactive content.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Every Parent's Nightmare | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250270/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250270/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Mark and Faye Leveson&amp;rsquo;s son Matthew went missing in 2007, feared dead, their world changed in an instant, never to be the same again.
New episodes of season 2 will be released exclusively on icatchkillers.com.au a week earlier than anywhere else. Subscribers to icatchkillers.com.au get exclusive access, as well as access to articles, videos of Gary&amp;rsquo;s interviews and interactive content.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Passion for Justice | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250271/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250271/</guid><description>Podcast Description Renowned Criminologist Xanthe Mallett has researched some of Australia&amp;rsquo;s most notorious cases and says the justice system has failed in many of them.
New episodes of season 2 will be released exclusively on icatchkillers.com.au a week earlier than anywhere else. Subscribers to icatchkillers.com.au get exclusive access, as well as access to articles, videos of Gary&amp;rsquo;s interviews and interactive content.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Psychopaths and DNA Technology | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250272/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250272/</guid><description>Podcast Description Xanthe Mallett is an internationally renowned criminologist and anthropologist. She not only knows how to read a crime scene but why the crime has happened.
New episodes of season 2 will be released exclusively on icatchkillers.com.au a week earlier than anywhere else. Subscribers to icatchkillers.com.au get exclusive access, as well as access to articles, videos of Gary&amp;rsquo;s interviews and interactive content.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Breaking the Bikies | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250273/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2020 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250273/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the head of Strike Force Raptor Deb Wallace has left a lasting legacy on the streets of Sydney by bringing down scores of Outlaw Motorcycle Gangs. This is how she did it. New episodes of season 2 will be released exclusively on icatchkillers.com.au a week earlier than anywhere else. Subscribers to icatchkillers.com.au get exclusive access, as well as access to articles, videos of Gary&amp;rsquo;s interviews and interactive content.</description></item><item><title>Feminine and Ferocious | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250274/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250274/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the early part of her career Deb Wallace played a key role into the Anita Cobby murder investigation before she developed her unique policing method on the streets of Cabramatta where she took on the dangerous 5T gang.
New episodes of season 2 will be released exclusively on icatchkillers.com.au a week earlier than anywhere else. Subscribers to icatchkillers.com.au get exclusive access, as well as access to articles, videos of Gary&amp;rsquo;s interviews and interactive content.</description></item><item><title>A Dog Attack And What Makes A Good Detective | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250275/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2020 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250275/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hunting down bikies and crims was Wayne Hayes&amp;rsquo;s life. He reveals the secrets to his detective work and recalls the day he was attacked by a police dog. New episodes of season 2 will be released exclusively on icatchkillers.com.au a week earlier than anywhere else. Subscribers to icatchkillers.com.au get exclusive access, as well as access to articles, videos of Gary&amp;rsquo;s interviews and interactive content.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Deaths That Haunt Us | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250276/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250276/</guid><description>Podcast Description There are certain deaths in Australia that capture the public&amp;rsquo;s attention and it has been Wayne Hayes&amp;rsquo;s job to investigate what really happened. From the murder of a young constable to the death of a solider in Iraq, he recalls those cases that have left a lasting impact on him and the nation. New episodes of season 2 will be released exclusively on icatchkillers.com.au a week earlier than anywhere else.</description></item><item><title>When Panic Takes Over A Cop’s Life | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250277/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250277/</guid><description>Podcast Description Karen Davis had seen it all during a decorated 20-year career but seemingly out of nowhere, the gravity of life as a police officer descended and she was diagnosed with PTSD. She came through the other side to become a celebrated fiction crime writer. New episodes of season 2 will be released exclusively on icatchkillers.com.au a week earlier than anywhere else. Subscribers to icatchkillers.com.au get exclusive access, as well as access to articles, videos of Gary&amp;rsquo;s interviews and interactive content.</description></item><item><title>A Young Constable’s Brutal Initiation | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250278/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250278/</guid><description>Podcast Description For a woman, walking into the NSW police force in the 1980s was a daunting experience. Not only did you have to contend with grisly homicides and horror smashes but being hit on by sleazy old cops was also a common occurrence.
New episodes of season 2 will be released exclusively on icatchkillers.com.au a week earlier than anywhere else. Subscribers to icatchkillers.com.au get exclusive access, as well as access to articles, videos of Gary&amp;rsquo;s interviews and interactive content.</description></item><item><title>Living Well Is The Best Revenge | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250279/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250279/</guid><description>Podcast Description Taking down a Christchurch mass murderer - and how an Arabic-speaking Aussie rose above police racism to become the world&amp;rsquo;s most sought after investigator. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss the final part in our series with former NSW Police deputy commissioner Nic&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Taking On The World | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250280/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250280/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dodging mortars in Iraq, hunting monsters in Syria and unearthing an IRA double-crosser. In Part 2, Nick Kaldas tells Gary Jubelin about the bad guys he has helped to take down around the world.
New episodes of season 2 will be released exclusively o&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Enemy Within | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250281/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 03:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250281/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the first of an emotional three-part series, Nick Kaldas, the former deputy commissioner of the NSW Police Force, reveals to Gary Jubelin how he became No.1 the target of an Internal Affairs witch-hunt and the toll it took on him and his family.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>I Knew I Hit Him Straight Away | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250282/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250282/</guid><description>Podcast Description Part 2 of the interview with Brett Pennell, in this highly charged and emotional episode Brett talks in detail about the moment, as a police sniper, he had to make the ultimate decision when his colleagues came under fire.
New episodes of season 2 wi&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Sniper’s Dilemma | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250283/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250283/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shooting dead a civilian to protect his mates is the day Brett Pennell can never forget, and he relives a lifetime of high-risk work as a tactical officer and sniper, telling Gary Jubelin about his lingering feelings of betrayal, anger and guilt.
New&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>BONUS EPISODE: Life &amp; Crimes with Andrew Rule - Catching killers. Part 2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250284/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 07:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250284/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gary&amp;rsquo;s appearance on the podcast Life &amp;amp; Crimes with Andrew Rule. I Catch Killers Season 2 is coming on the weekend of October 3/4. To get new episodes before anyone else, and for bonus content such as articles, galleries and videos search icat&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>BONUS EPISODE: I Catch Killers Book Launch Interview Part 2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250285/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 08:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250285/</guid><description>Podcast Description I Catch Killers producer Claire Harvey interviews Gary about the writing of his book, including some questions from the live streaming audience around Gary&amp;rsquo;s thoughts on becoming a private detective, what personality type he looks for in his homic&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>BONUS EPISODE: I Catch Killers Book Launch Interview Part 1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250286/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 02:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250286/</guid><description>Podcast Description From a recent live stream interview, I Catch Killers producer Claire Harvey interviews Gary about the writing of his book, including some questions from the live streaming audience on William Tyrell, the Bowraville case and which cases still keep Gary &amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>BONUS EPISODE "I'm not a dog. I'm a f**king snitch." | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250287/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250287/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Cop and the Snitch: In this explosive bonus episode a criminal informant who risked his life to help homicide detective Gary Jubelin catch killers for 22 years speaks for the first time For more information, articles and galleries visit &amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>BONUS EPISODE "If I'm that bad, send me to jail" | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250288/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250288/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gary Jubelin&amp;rsquo;s most searing interview ever, introducing his explosive new book. Pre-order now at booktopia.com.au
For more information, articles and galleries visit truecrimeaustralia.com.au
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"The distraction grenades gave us sufficient time to go in and put them down" Former Undercover Cop Keith Banks - Part 2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250289/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250289/</guid><description>Podcast Description Part 2 on Keith Banks&amp;rsquo; journey through the Queensland Police Force&amp;hellip;gone is the scruffy hair and smoking joints undercover, Keith takes us through the time he came across a 14 year old shot up on heroin which changed his outlook on being an under&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"I had issues that I now know to be PTSD" Former Undercover Cop Keith Banks - Part 1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250290/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250290/</guid><description>Podcast Description Keith Banks was a scared little boy from the Queensland bush who emerged from his violent childhood with a dream: to protect the vulnerable. He shares an explosive account of drugs, corruption and life in the shadows as an undercover cop who found hims&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Life In Black and Blue. The Story Of An Aboriginal Police Officer Jarin Baigent - Part 2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250291/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 05:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250291/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Part 2 Jarin Baigent offers her perspective as a cop and also as an Aboriginal woman, on the Black Lives Matter movement. She also talks about the high concentration of Aboriginal inmates in our jails and the ongoing challenges the Police have in co&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Life In Black and Blue. The Story Of An Aboriginal Police Officer Jarin Baigent - Part 1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250292/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250292/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jarin Baigent grew up on The Block in Redfern and knew as a little girl, when her family was the victim of multiple break-and-enters, that she wanted to be a cop. She tells the unvarnished story of policing her own community and the frustrations - and &amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"We realised......you are the murderer" Retired Detective Sergeant Mark Zjedlar - Part 2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250293/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250293/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Part 2 Mark Zjedlar talks about his time in the child abuse squad and the impact working in that team can have, he opens up on the suicide of colleagues and his time working vietnamese gangs
CONTENT WARNING: This episode of I Catch Killers contain&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"all of sudden this kid emerges, holding a gun" Retired Detective Sergeant Mark Zjedlar - Part 1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250294/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250294/</guid><description>Podcast Description An armed offender, soaked in petrol and holding a lighter, was one of the first members of the public Mark Zjedlar encountered as a raw young cop - the start of a career that took him to the mean streets of Sydney’s drug gangland and the disturbing wor&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"I'm a f**king man, put me in jail with the f**king men" Ex-Bikie Cunno - Part 2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250295/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250295/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part 2 of Cunno&amp;rsquo;s chat he talks very openly of his experiences in jail, from his first stint as a 17 year old knowing he could take her of himself, to the fascinating dynamics between &amp;ldquo;the crooks, the good c**ts and the junkies.&amp;rdquo; Cunn&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"I was 15 years old walking around with a sawn-off shotgun" Ex-Bikie 'Cunno' - Part 1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250296/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250296/</guid><description>Podcast Description Life as bikie lured ‘Cunno’ from an early age, and in this stunning interview he takes us into a world of criminals, fugitives, dealers and killers. He’s served hard time for manslaughter and numerous other violent crimes, narrowly survived wild prison&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Out in the back yard rolled out in plastic was an adult female" Retired Senior Sergeant and Crime Scene Officer Steve Horn - Part 2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250297/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250297/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part 2 of the interview with Steve Horn he reveals where he looks for microscopic droplets that can catch a killer, the reason you’ll never catch him digging straight down when looking for a body, and why a good detective is always exceedingly polit&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"the village was not that far down the road, the children were taken up there in horse and cart" Retired Senior Sergeant and Crime Scene Officer Steve Horn - Part 1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250298/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250298/</guid><description>Podcast Description Steve Horn is a living legend, regarded as the longest serving crime scene officer in the western world, with 44 years under his belt. In this episode he talks about investigating WW2 war criminals working with the KGB, his time identifying so&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"I open the latch suitcase, and there's a body of a woman" Retired Detective Superintendent Ian Lynch - Part 2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250299/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250299/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Part 2 Ian Lynch describes in detail the perplexing case of a woman found in a suitcase, the time when an informant gave evidence about a murder that he had actually committed to throw the cops off the scent&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.and got found out, investigating th&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"why is the fridge all tied up? Oh that's because there's a man in there" Retired Detective Superintendent Ian Lynch - Part 1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250300/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250300/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Crossbow Butcher was as scary as he sounds, and it was Detective Superintendent Ian Lynch’s job to bring this sadistic killer to justice for a spree of murders. Ian also talks about his first big arrest of a notorious drug dealer, a horrific murder&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"He was the escapee, he was the armed robber" Retired Homicide Detective Ian 'Speed' Kennedy - Part 2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250301/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250301/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part 2 of the chat with Retired Homicide Detective Ian &amp;lsquo;Speed&amp;rsquo; Kennedy he talks in detail about the culprits of the rape and murder of Anita Cobby including how her parents earned the respect of everyone for the way they conducted themselv&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"yes, that's my bootmark on his face" Retired Homicide Detective Ian 'Speed' Kennedy - Part 1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250302/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250302/</guid><description>Podcast Description The gang-rape and murder of beauty queen Anita Cobby as she walked home from the train station after a busy day as a nurse will never leave Ian ‘Speed’ Kennedy, the cop who solved the case and saw her murderers locked up for life. He reveals how his si&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"My heart was breaking, we found out that Katrina Dawson had died from one of our bullets" Retired Detective Chief Inspector Angelo Memmolo - Part 2 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250303/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250303/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Part 2 with Angelo Memmolo, he discusses his time fighting the middle eastern crime gangs including the notorious Bassam Hamzy, and the running of the Lindt Cafe siege investigation, the toughest thing he has ever had to do - and that’s say&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"A policeman in front of me copped a brick straight to the head and went down" Retired Detective Chief Inspector Angelo Memmolo - Part 1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250304/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250304/</guid><description>Podcast Description Angelo Memmolo is a legend. In Part 1 he talks about the terrifying day as a Redfern constable he had to fight back a rioting crowd raining down bricks and rocks to rescue two cops, a gunfight in a shopping mall carpark with an armed-robbery g&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>BONUS EPISODE "I preferred the simplicity of the baton, the gun and then fists if you needed them" | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250305/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250305/</guid><description>Podcast Description We turn the tables in this episode, with I Catch Killer&amp;rsquo;s showrunner Claire Harvey sitting down to interview Gary Jubelin. Talking through his career path as an apprentice electrician, his time in uniform, to the armed hold up sq&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"I didn't want the bastard to beat me" Retired Detective Superintendent Dennis O' Toole - Part 1 | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250306/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250306/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Granny Killer was a middle-aged pie salesman by day and a ruthless serial killer by night, stalking the helpless old ladies of Sydney’s elite lower north shore. His rampage ended only when Detective Superintendent Dennis ‘Miles’ O’Toole burst in up&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"I've seen people die every way possible, but not this" Retired Detective Sergeant Jason Evers | I Catch Killers with Gary Jubelin</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1754250307/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1754250307/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lying on the floor with a loaded shotgun pressed into the back of his head, Detective Sergeant Jason Evers was supposed to be off-duty when he managed to talk his way out of an armed hold-up - and the experience taught him more about homicide than he e&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>