<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Defenders on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-defenders/</link><description>Recent content in The Defenders on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 19:45:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-defenders/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>BONUS: Kate Cox Denied an Abortion in Texas | The Defenders</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3677940009/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 19:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3677940009/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Kate Cox received a devastating diagnosis in the 20th week of a much-wanted pregnancy, she turned to her doctor for help. Instead of receiving the care she needed, she was met with cruelty at the hands of the Texas courts. In this mini episode, we chat with Slate’s Dahlia Lithwick about what this story means for the rest of the country.
Resources:
Dahlia’s recent article about Kate Cox: https://slate.</description></item><item><title>Gossip Saves Lives | The Defenders</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3677940008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3677940008/</guid><description>Podcast Description We travel to the Rio Grande Valley in Texas, where abortion bans intersect with immigration policy. And our team crosses the border into Mexico to buy something you can’t get in Texas: abortion pills. Learn more about Frontera Fund at https://fronterafundrgv.org/. Learn more about the National Latina Institute for Reproductive Health at https://www.latinainstitute.org/. To learn more about all the organizations featured in The Defenders, visit: https://lemonadamedia.com/the-defenders-resource-page/
Share your thoughts on The Defenders!</description></item><item><title>Grief But Not Regret | The Defenders</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3677940007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3677940007/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do you make a complicated reproductive choice when you’re racing against the clock? We follow two women in Georgia as they figure out how to end their pregnancies in a state with a 6-week ban. And then we talk to Sister Song’s Monica Simpson about how the Reproductive Justice movement is expansive enough to hold space for people with conflicted feelings about their abortions. Learn more about SisterSong at https://www.</description></item><item><title>My Jesus Flipped Tables | The Defenders</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3677940006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3677940006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Reproductive rights and religion may not feel like they go hand in hand. But in Atlanta, Black faith leaders are challenging that by talking about abortion…in church.
Learn more about Faith in Public Life at https://www.faithinpubliclife.org/
Learn more about Religious Coalition for Reproductive Choice at https://rcrc.org/
Follow Tiffanie Mackey at https://www.tiffanielanelle.com/
To learn more about all the organizations featured in this series, visit: https://lemonadamedia.com/the-defenders-resource-page/
Gloria Riviera and Samantha Bee are our hosts.</description></item><item><title>Abortion is a Winning Issue | The Defenders</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3677940005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3677940005/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s a trend happening across America. In blue AND red states, people are voting to protect abortion rights, with Ohio just the latest example. It turns out abortion is winning elections. This week, Sam sits down with author and writer Rebecca Traister to dissect why a record number of voters are showing up in droves to protect reproductive freedom. Follow Rebecca Traister: https://rebeccatraister.com/
Learn more about All Above All: https://allaboveall.</description></item><item><title>Joy is Resistance | The Defenders</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3677940004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3677940004/</guid><description>Podcast Description What does gender affirming care have to do with abortion? It’s all about bodily autonomy. And the forces that brought down Roe are going after Trans rights next. We stay in Tennessee this week as we break down the anti-trans, anti-abortion playbook and meet a group of young people who are navigating their state’s attacks on LGBTQ rights. Learn more about OUTMemphis at https://www.outmemphis.org/.
Gloria Riviera and Samantha Bee are our hosts.</description></item><item><title>They Haven’t Seen The Last of Us | The Defenders</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3677940001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 08:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3677940001/</guid><description>Podcast Description What does it mean to be an abortion activist in a state where abortion is completely banned? We travel to Tennessee alongside two activists who are risking everything to expand access to care. Learn more about Abortion Care Tennessee at https://www.abortioncaretn.org/about-us.
Follow Tia Freeman on Instagram @slipp3rywhenwet and their work with Beyond Roe Collective @beyondroecollective.
Gloria Riviera and Samantha Bee are our hosts. Muna Danish is our supervising producer.</description></item><item><title>800 Miles to Freedom | The Defenders</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3677940002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3677940002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 1: Back in 2022, shortly after the fall of Roe, Brittany felt trapped. She was pregnant and stuck in an abusive relationship, totally cut off from her support system. She didn’t see a way out - until she happened to hear a radio story about the Midwest Access Coalition, an abortion fund helping people travel across state lines. We follow Brittany’s harrowing journey as she travels hundreds of miles, with the help of a group of volunteer pilots from Elevated Access.</description></item><item><title>The Defenders (Official Trailer) | The Defenders</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3677940003/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 19:44:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3677940003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Since the fall of Roe, people are asking, what do we do now? "The Defenders," from Lemonada Media, will take a closer look at the fight for reproductive rights and gender equity happening across the country. Co-hosts Samantha Bee and Gloria Riviera share the stories of a growing network of helpers who are fighting back and doubling down on reproductive freedom. Coming November 8. This series is supported by Charles and Lynn Schusterman Family Philanthropies, The William and Flora Hewlett Foundation, and Levi Strauss Foundation.</description></item></channel></rss>