<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/smoke-screen-my-fugitive-dad/</link><description>Recent content in Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/smoke-screen-my-fugitive-dad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>My Fugitive Dad | 3. The Last Randele | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520076/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520076/</guid><description>Podcast Description At a social security office in Boston, Ted Conrad is reborn as Thomas Randele. It was the first time this surname was ever recorded. Then he went about making friends and making excuses for why he didn’t have to work. Ashley sifts through her Dad’s past trying to figure out what he told her is actually true and what isn’t. She interviews her Mum, Kathy, who reveals that her Dad hadn’t wanted kids when they first met.</description></item><item><title>My Fugitive Dad | 2. The Hunt | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Introducing the Elliotts, the father-son pair who spent the better part of their lives with the singular mission of finding Ted Conrad. From the very start of this case, John Elliott made Ted his nemesis. It turns out the Deputy Marshal had his reasons to despise him. Hosts Jonathan and Ashley discover a letter her Dad wrote in the weeks after the heist.
Subscribe to The Binge to get all episodes of Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad, ad-free right now.</description></item><item><title>My Fugitive Dad | 1. Becoming Thomas Crown | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520002/</guid><description>Podcast Description The summer of 1968 one of the most iconic heist movies ever made came out. The Thomas Crown Affair starred Steve McQueen as a clever businessman who pulls off an elaborate robbery. Ted Conrad, a kid from Cleveland, admired this film so much he walked out of Society National Bank with hundreds of thousands of dollars in a paper bag. Some say he stole the money for the same reasons Crown did: to see if he could get away with it.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: My Fugitive Dad | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520003/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ashley’s Dad was her favorite person in the world. He drove fast cars and sold them for a living. He was a scratch golfer and the love of her Mum’s life. Ashley thought she knew him better than anyone. But at 38, she found out he wasn’t who he said he was. Inspired by his favorite movie the Thomas Crown Affair, he had pulled off a robbery in Cleveland then disappeared.</description></item><item><title>Introducing *Crime Waves: Cold Truth* | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 19:58:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520004/</guid><description>Podcast Description How far would you go to save the world from itself?
Dr. Eugene Mallove believed that a new form of world-changing free energy — cold fusion — was just around the corner. Even when his work was pushed to the fringes, he dreamed of a brighter future. But before Dr. Mallove could usher in that future, he was found dead in the driveway of his childhood home. Everyone had their own ideas of who killed him, and investigators were looking in all the wrong places.</description></item><item><title>Betrayal on the Bayou | 8. Approximation of Justice | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chad is charged on a long list of counts related to corruption. He isn’t just going to plead guilty. He’s going to trial. In court, he’ll face his informants and his right-hand men who betrayed him. But whether or not Chad gets what he deserved remains an open question. Is Chad a bad apple or is the DEA a rotten orchard?
Subscribe to The Binge to get all episodes of Smoke Screen ad-free right now.</description></item><item><title>Betrayal on the Bayou | 7. Inside the War Room | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520006/</guid><description>Podcast Description FBI Agent Chip Hardgrave and Chad Scott have a lot in common – they even went to the same high school in Baton Rouge – but now it’s Chip’s job to investigate the DEA’s star agent. This time, Chad’s misconduct isn’t going to get swept under the rug. His powerful allies can’t protect him. The FBI will take down Chad and anybody they catch along with him.
Subscribe to The Binge to get all episodes of Smoke Screen ad-free right now.</description></item><item><title>Betrayal on the Bayou | 6. Cops to Canaries | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520007/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the story of how Chad’s team gets caught. Rose Graham is a grandmother who becomes Johnny’s unlikely peddler for the drugs he’s been stealing from evidence. One fateful night, Rose goes to a lakeside restaurant and tries to sell cocaine to an undercover State Trooper. Soon, Chad’s team turns on him.
Subscribe to The Binge to get all episodes of Smoke Screen ad-free right now. Click ‘Subscribe’ at the top of the Smoke Screen: Betrayal On The Bayou show page on Apple Podcasts or visit GetTheBinge.</description></item><item><title>Betrayal on the Bayou | 5. Deal at the DoubleTree | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Boobie is an informant for Chad but all the while he’s making over $300,000 a month dealing cocaine. Some people say Chad lets him get away with it. When Boobie meets Chad at a Houston Doubletree, Chad puts Boobie on notice: he wants contacts, or Boobie’s freedom is over.
Subscribe to The Binge to get all episodes of Smoke Screen ad-free right now. Click ‘Subscribe’ at the top of the Smoke Screen: Betrayal On The Bayou show page on Apple Podcasts or visit GetTheBinge.</description></item><item><title>Betrayal on the Bayou | 4. A Sign of Good Faith | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520009/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chad’s luck is finally running out. The beginning of Chad’s downfall centers around Frederick “Boobie” Brown. He’s a high level drug trafficker who drives a $240,000 Bentley and provides dope to dealers all over the South. Chad says he’ll let Boobie walk free… if Boobie does exactly what Chad wants.
Subscribe to The Binge to get all episodes of Smoke Screen ad-free right now. Click ‘Subscribe’ at the top of the Smoke Screen: Betrayal On The Bayou show page on Apple Podcasts or visit GetTheBinge.</description></item><item><title>Betrayal on the Bayou | 3. Kid Gloves | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ron Woods is a Black DEA supervisor who landed in New Orleans and found himself in the perils of the swamp. He’s the agent who could have stopped Chad Scott before things got out of hand. Chad has always courted controversy. In fact, for his first big assignment for the DEA, Chad was toe-to-toe with none other than hip-hop legend James Prince.
Subscribe to The Binge to get all episodes of Smoke Screen ad-free right now.</description></item><item><title>Betrayal on the Bayou | 2. The A-Team | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520011/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Meet the A-Team, that’s what Chad called his ragtag group, also known as a DEA Task Force. Karl Newman is a real likable country dude with no moral quandaries. Johnny Domingue is the protege, fresh out of college, with a knack for making drug busts. Chad handpicked this team, and commanded them during operations. But little did he know that they were far out of his control.
Subscribe to The Binge to get all episodes of Smoke Screen ad-free right now.</description></item><item><title>Betrayal on the Bayou | 1. The White Devil | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520012/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chad Scott made an incredible number of cases by getting drug dealers to work for him as informants. His phone number was written on jailhouse walls because Chad was the guy who could get you out of a tough situation – if you give him what he wants. That if is what this whole story is about. We hear from Virgil Ard, a former drug dealer who navigated streets riddled with Chad’s snitches.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Betrayal on the Bayou | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520013/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520013/</guid><description>Podcast Description For almost two decades, DEA Special Agent Chad Scott ruled the streets just North of New Orleans. He controlled a network of snitches by convincing people he arrested to work for him as informants. Chad would stop at nothing to put drug dealers behind bars. His successes won awards at the DEA, but his willingness to bend the rules earned him a terrifying reputation on the streets. Some called him the Golden Boy.</description></item><item><title>Assassins, Heists, &amp; Nazis - The Untold Story of the Abortion Pill in America | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520014/</guid><description>Podcast Description You may have heard of the abortion pill, especially in the wake of the overturning of Roe v. Wade last year. But the story of how the pill became legal in America is closer to an action film than to a courtroom drama—with covert operations, heists, and even murder. On the new season of Cover Up: The Pill Plot, travel back to the ‘90s and join the ragtag group that plotted an international drug smuggling scheme and set up a secret lab to get the abortion pill to America.</description></item><item><title>Just Say You’re Sorry | 6. Closure Doesn’t Exist | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Driskill’s lawyers discover that he is theoretically eligible for parole after serving seven years of his sentence. But this is a long shot — it&amp;rsquo;s notoriously difficult to get released whilst still maintaining your innocence.
Chammah talks to a leading cold case prosecutor to ask how interrogations like Holland’s can be justified. And he seeks to understand the pain that Bobbie Sue Hill’s family will be confronted with if Driskill is cleared.</description></item><item><title>Just Say You’re Sorry | 5. The Serial Killer Whisperer | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520016/</guid><description>Podcast Description A young law student called Ashely is the first to read Driskill’s letter and becomes obsessed with his story. The Innocence Project of Texas take his case and begin working to find evidence that could clear his name.
Chammah hunts down crucial leads throwing serious doubt on the informant’s story and on the forensic sketch that led Holland to Driskill in the first place.
Holland&amp;rsquo;s star, though, is still rising.</description></item><item><title>Just Say You’re Sorry | 4. Memory, Taste and Odor | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Driskill is in jail ahead of a potential court case when an informant comes forward with information that seems to blow a hole in his claims of innocence.
Meanwhile James Holland moves on to his next case. It’s a story with eerie similarities to Driskill’s. Another veteran, Christopher Ax, is being investigated for the murder of a woman. But this time, things turn out very differently for Holland, and the first cracks start to appear in his legend.</description></item><item><title>Just Say You’re Sorry | 3. The Grand Canyon | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520018/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s Day 2 of Holland’s interrogation of Driskill. Over the course of several hours Holland uses a variety of extreme but legal tactics as he chases a confession. He lies to Driskill about the evidence they have against him and feeds the veteran a story to explain how he might have come to murder Bobbie Sue Hill. Holland is relentless and the interrogation stretches on, with no lawyer present.</description></item><item><title>Just Say You’re Sorry | 2. The Word of God | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chammah investigates the cop at the centre of the story – James Holland is so celebrated as an interrogator that he’s known in the media as ‘the serial killer whisperer.’ He’s a leading member of that legendary and storied police force, the Texas Rangers. Chammah traces Holland’s steps as he starts trying to close a cold case which has gone unsolved for more than a decade: the murder of a woman named Bobbie Sue Hill.</description></item><item><title>Just Say You’re Sorry | 1. Not That I Recall | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Texas Ranger James Holland approaches Air Force veteran Larry Driskill and asks him for help with a murder case. These are the first moments in a psychological battle that will end in Driskill confessing to a brutal killing. All while swearing he doesn’t remember the crime.
Incredibly, the whole thing is caught on tape. Through Holland&amp;rsquo;s recordings, journalist Maurice Chammah follows the men into the interrogation room&amp;hellip;
Subscribe to The Binge to get all episodes of Smoke Screen: Just Say You&amp;rsquo;re Sorry ad-free right now.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Just Say You're Sorry | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Texas Ranger James Holland is celebrated as the ‘serial killer whisperer’, solving dozens of murders through his legendary interrogation skills. But how far does he go to get confessions? And has he put innocent people in prison along the way? Smoke Screen: Just Say You&amp;rsquo;re Sorry uses shocking police tapes to reveal the psychological drama behind one murder case, and uncovers something rotten at the heart of the justice system.</description></item><item><title>Deadly Cure | 8. The Rattlesnake King | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Genesis II has recently gained a significant following in some South American countries, according to local reports. Hundreds of buyers have been lining up outside makeshift MMS distribution centers in poor rural communities as the pace of Covid vaccination falls behind that of major cities.
What does the story of MMS tell us about the future of public health in the U.S. and abroad? How we can foster informed, trusted dialogue around science and health globally?</description></item><item><title>Deadly Cure | 7. Doing Time | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520023/</guid><description>Podcast Description From prison in Colombia, to a detention facility in Texas to federal detention in Florida, the Grenons continue to fight for their freedom, and promote their product.
Meanwhile, Mark Grenon remains defiant. MMS, he insists, will never stop.
Want the full story? Unlock all episodes of Smoke Screen, ad-free, right now by subscribing to The Binge. Plus, get binge access to brand new stories dropping on the first of every month — that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.</description></item><item><title>Deadly Cure | 6. The Raid | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520024/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the summer of 2020, the government raided Grenon&amp;rsquo;s compound and arrested two of Mark Grenon’s sons. But where in the world were Mark and his other son?
This episode traces the Grenons’ moves around the world, and examines both how they rose to international stardom … and how they were ultimately brought down.
Want the full story? Unlock all episodes of Smoke Screen, ad-free, right now by subscribing to The Binge.</description></item><item><title>Deadly Cure | 5. Operation Quack Hack | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520025/</guid><description>Podcast Description As MMS continued its rise, so did the Federal Drug Administration’s attention on the so-called cure.
But MMS would prove difficult to clamp down on. Between eBay and Amazon, sales of the vials were reaching the millions. In 2019, a special agent with the FDA began buying MMS, gaining information on the church and its founders.
But the Genesis II Church would receive a major boost in March 2020, when the Covid-19 pandemic rattled the world.</description></item><item><title>Deadly Cure | 4. The Limelight | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Self-appointed archbishops Jim Humble and Mark Grenon begin hosting seminars around the world, and charging $450 per person to attend. But it wasn’t just locals expressing interest in the so-called cure: now, national media was catching wind of the group, thrusting the Genesis II Church further into the limelight.
Want the full story? Unlock all episodes of Smoke Screen, ad-free, right now by subscribing to The Binge. Plus, get binge access to brand new stories dropping on the first of every month — that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.</description></item><item><title>Deadly Cure | 3. The Martyr | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520027/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520027/</guid><description>Podcast Description What starts for Daniel Smith as an attempt to regain trust in medicine quickly becomes &amp;ldquo;Project Green Life&amp;rdquo; – a top distributor of MMS. Then, the feds catch wind of his operation, hoping to take him down.
The Grenons use Daniel&amp;rsquo;s prosecution as a rallying cry for the Genesis II church, claiming that their church status is what would insulate them from future attempts by the feds to shut them down.</description></item><item><title>Deadly Cure | 2. The Bleach Hunters | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fiona O&amp;rsquo;Leary is a fearless firebrand, and mother of four autistic children. She is also an online vigilante who will stop at nothing to take down proponents of MMS. She&amp;rsquo;s part of a loosely affiliated group of keyboard warriors known as &amp;ldquo;The Bleach Hunters.” Her Nemesis is Kerri Rivera, a former real estate agent who created something called &amp;ldquo;The Autism Protocols&amp;rdquo;, which promote using MMS as a &amp;ldquo;cure&amp;rdquo; for autism.</description></item><item><title>Deadly Cure | 1. Genesis | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520029/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Meet Mark Grenon, Jim Humble, and the Genesis II church. Mark Grenon, a missionary in the Dominican Republic, contracts MRSA. He discovers the Miracle Mineral Solution, and claims that it has miraculously cured him of numerous ailments.
This takes him to the founder of MMS, Jim Humble, a man who claims to be a billion-year-old god from the Andromeda galaxy, and has treated thousands of people with what he calls &amp;ldquo;my malaria solution.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Deadly Cure | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520030/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Smoke Screen: Deadly Cure is a podcast about a family on the fringe who convinced tens of thousands of people across the globe to buy a miracle liquid made of poison, the international conspiracy they ignited, and the people who fought to take them down.
Want the full story? Unlock all episodes of Smoke Screen, ad-free, right now by subscribing to The Binge. Plus, get binge access to brand new stories dropping on the first of every month — that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.</description></item><item><title>A New Investigation: The Last Days of the NXIVM Sex Cult | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520031/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Behind every infamous news story is a journalist trying to hold power to account. Join reporters Vanessa Grigoriadis and Gabriel Sherman as they take an in-depth look at the most explosive scandals of this century. From high-profile divorces to sex cults to the lies that started a war, they’ll guide you through the juiciest, most outrageous, celeb-filled stories of the last two decades, and give you a behind-the-scenes look at what it takes to shine an unflattering light on the world’s most powerful people.</description></item><item><title>GOING UNDERCOVER | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520032/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex Schuman, host of Puppy Kingpin, spoke to Deborah Howard, the president of CAPS, the Companion Animal Protection Society, and an undercover investigator who goes by the pseudonym Pete Paxton. In this bonus episode, they discuss the patterns they see breeders using to skirt laws, why the USDA falls short, and Deborah and Pete defend their use of undercover videos to expose what&amp;rsquo;s happening on the ground. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>A New Case: The Criminal Empire of Scam Calls | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520033/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chameleon: Scam Likely host, Yudhijit Bhattacharjee, sits down with Alex Schuman to chat about the newest season of the blockbuster Chameleon franchise. The duo dig into another scam you should be wary of - telefraud. Ordinary citizens all around the U.S. have lost their life savings to scam callers, many originating from India. These fraudsters often target especially vulnerable populations, including immigrants and the elderly. Listen as Yudhijit shares the jaw-dropping story of how a small team of investigators went on the hunt to dismantle the shadowy multinational mob behind the con in what became the biggest telefraud case in U.</description></item><item><title>A Q&amp;A with Smoke Screen host Alex Schuman | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520034/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Spectacle: True Crime host, Mariah Smith, sits down with Alex Schuman to chat all things about the newest season of Smoke Screen, Puppy Kingpin. She puts host Alex Schuman in the hot seat and they dig into true crime – how we report these stories, why we’re so fascinated with them and what this fascination says about us. Mariah gets juicy behind-the-scenes bits from Alex about reporting Smoke Screen: Fake Priest and Puppy Kingpin.</description></item><item><title>Puppy Kingpin | 7. Consequences | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520035/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jolyn Noethe faces a class action lawsuit that accuses her of a federal crime and might cost her up to 5 million. The puppy pipeline isn’t going to change overnight, but Alex meets with a breeder who has nothing to hide and hears about a movement among breeders to go above and beyond USDA requirements.
A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.
Unlock all episodes of Smoke Screen, ad-free right now by subscribing to The Binge.</description></item><item><title>Puppy Kingpin | 6. License to Sell | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520036/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520036/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Iowa AG’s lawsuit against Jolyn comes to a conclusion as she faces challenges from multiple sides. Alex looks more closely at the USDA as a growing number of breeders and animal rights activists think a USDA license doesn’t mean much anymore.
A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.
Unlock all episodes of Smoke Screen, ad-free right now by subscribing to The Binge. Plus, get binge access to brand new stories dropping on the first of every month — that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.</description></item><item><title>Puppy Kingpin | 5. Small Town Secrets | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520037/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex heads to Britt, Iowa where Jolyn Noethe grew up and her for-profit enterprise, J.A.K.’s Puppies, is headquartered. He discovers that a family dispute is part of the reason she started her own brokering business.
A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.
Unlock all episodes of Smoke Screen, ad-free right now by subscribing to The Binge. Plus, get binge access to brand new stories dropping on the first of every month — that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.</description></item><item><title>Puppy Kingpin | 4. A Kind of Identity Theft | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520038/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Multiple lawsuits now accuse Jolyn Noethe of creating rescues to sell commercially-bred puppies where they’ve been outlawed. Alex learns how the scheme reaches beyond the Midwest and meets Lizette Chanock. She claims her rescue’s name is being used to sell unhealthy puppies.
A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.
Unlock all episodes of Smoke Screen, ad-free right now by subscribing to The Binge. Plus, get binge access to brand new stories dropping on the first of every month — that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.</description></item><item><title>Puppy Kingpin | 3. Hobo K9 | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520039/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Authorities learn of unusual “rescue puppies” starting to turn up in Chicago and begin an investigation. Soon, they are on the trail of the secretive businesswoman responsible.
A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.
Unlock all episodes of Smoke Screen, ad-free right now by subscribing to The Binge. Plus, get binge access to brand new stories dropping on the first of every month — that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.</description></item><item><title>Puppy Kingpin | 2. Inside a Puppy Mill | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520040/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex sets out to learn more about Jolyn Noethe, but ends up getting an inside look at a puppy mill and how they operate legally. We’ll hear audio of the day authorities descended on the farm of Barbara Kavars, an Iowan breeder who got in way over her head.
A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.
Unlock all episodes of Smoke Screen, ad-free right now by subscribing to The Binge.</description></item><item><title>Puppy Kingpin | 1. Follow the Puppies | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520041/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520041/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Mindi Callison finds out a local pet shop might be selling puppies from a puppy mill, she takes action. Soon, she’s tracking dogs being transported from state to state and stumbles onto a company that hides the source of puppies.
A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production. Unlock all episodes of Smoke Screen, ad-free right now by subscribing to The Binge. Plus, get binge access to brand new stories dropping on the first of every month — that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.</description></item><item><title>Coming Soon: Puppy Kingpin | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Americans are used to being on the lookout for a scam, but authorities are warning of a new kind of fraud. Puppy Kingpin shines a spotlight on Jolyn Noethe, a secretive businesswoman from Iowa who is accused of laundering puppies like drug money. Over the course of 7 episodes, investigative reporter and host Alex Schuman exposes the scheme and an underground part of the industry bringing us the pets we love.</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode: Where's my money? | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520043/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last year, as the final episodes of The Sellout aired, LA TACO got a tip from a listener: for years, Jose Huizar had been awarding flashy scholarships to college-bound students from Boyle Heights and East LA. But some of those students say they never got the scholarship money promised to them. Was Huizar really stiffing high school students from his own neighborhood? After months of investigating, we&amp;rsquo;re ready to share what we found out.</description></item><item><title>The Sellout | 9: There's A Fire | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520044/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mariah talks to the Boyle Heights residents who watched as FBI agents raided Huizar’s home and offices. Three months into the pandemic, he’s arrested and pleads not guilty. The residents of CD14 are left in limbo. We look at what the FBI investigation reveals about Los Angeles’s housing and homelessness crisis.
A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.
Subscribe on Apple Podcasts to binge all episodes now or listen weekly wherever you get your podcasts.</description></item><item><title>The Sellout | 8: The Downfall | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520045/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Huizar’s carelessness starts to catch up with him. After more than a dozen all-expenses paid trips to Vegas with plenty of perks, Huizar gets played by one of his own. A businessman turned FBI informant gives Huizar an envelope with $15,000 in cash, and then tells the Feds all about it.
A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.
Subscribe on Apple Podcasts to binge all episodes now or listen weekly wherever you get your podcasts.</description></item><item><title>The Sellout | 7: The Coverup | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520046/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Huizar’s downfall started with a sexual harassment lawsuit. He didn’t have the hundreds of thousands of dollars to settle the suit on his own&amp;hellip; so the Feds say he relied on a new friend. A developer who had plans to build a 77-story hotel in downtown LA.
A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.
Subscribe on Apple Podcasts to binge all episodes now or listen weekly wherever you get your podcasts.</description></item><item><title>The Sellout | 6: The Heyday | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520047/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gentrification comes in waves. Over years, a piece of downtown LA transformed from Skid Row, to a bastion for young artists, to a hipster neighborhood with some of the highest rents in the city. By 2018, Huizar was allegedly collecting bribes from developers planning a luxury high rise just a couple blocks from where some of his constituents were getting evicted.
A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.</description></item><item><title>The Sellout | 5: How Downtown Was Won | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520048/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520048/</guid><description>Podcast Description No man is an island. Huizar couldn’t have pulled off the alleged corruption scheme without help. Host Mariah Castañeda tells the story of how Huizar allegedly built the criminal enterprise the FBI would eventually arrest him for. It all started when downtown was reassigned to his district.
A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.
Subscribe on Apple Podcasts to binge all episodes now or listen weekly wherever you get your podcasts.</description></item><item><title>The Sellout | 4. Progress Over People | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520049/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520049/</guid><description>Podcast Description When fancy new developments like The Gold Line expansion get proposed, residents of Boyle Heights wonder if it’s actually for them, or if these new new things are meant to attract future residents&amp;hellip; a.k.a. gentrifiers. A mechanic is harassed by the city of Los Angeles after he refuses to sell his land to make way for construction. And Huizar&amp;rsquo;s re-election campaign against Rudy Martinez gets petty.
A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.</description></item><item><title>The Sellout | 3. Red Flags | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520050/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alvin Parra worked for Huizar when he first got elected. He saw early warning signs that Huizar wasn’t the man of the people he made himself out to be. Parra tried to warn people about what he saw behind closed doors, but most of them weren’t ready to listen. He ends up doing something drastic to try to expose Huizar.
A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.</description></item><item><title>The Sellout | 2. Gentrification is Warfare | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520051/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520051/</guid><description>Podcast Description A militant organization called Defend Boyle Heights protests encroaching gentrification, by any means necessary. We dig into two origin stories: how Huizar emigrated at the age of 4 and ended up at Berkeley and Princeton, and how Boyle Heights has had a history of resistance and displacement.
A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.
Subscribe on Apple Podcasts to binge all episodes now or listen weekly wherever you get your podcasts.</description></item><item><title>The Sellout | 1. The Gem of Boyle Heights | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520052/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520052/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a working-class Latinx neighborhood in Los Angeles faces gentrification, residents are ready to fight to defend their turf. Mariachis lead a rent strike and ask their councilman Jose Huizar for help. But what they don’t realize is that he’s allegedly been taking bribes from developers building luxury housing right across the river, in downtown LA.
A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.
Subscribe on Apple Podcasts to binge all episodes now or listen weekly wherever you get your podcasts.</description></item><item><title>Introducing The Sellout and Smoke Screen Plus | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520053/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jonathan Hirsch, Neon Hum CEO and host of I Am Rama, introduces this season of Smoke Screen (it&amp;rsquo;s called The Sellout!) and our new paid subscription service, Smoke Screen Plus.
If you buy a paid subscription on Apple Podcasts, you’ll get three episodes of bonus content throughout the season. You’ll also get each episode without ads, and 24 hours early. And, if you don’t subscribe… that’s fine! You’ll still get access to all the episodes, free.</description></item><item><title>Coming Soon: The Sellout | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520054/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 19:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jose Huizar grew up in Boyle Heights – a working-class Latinx neighborhood in L.A. Eventually, he became their councilperson.
And, for the most part, people trusted Huizar&amp;hellip; until the day the FBI raided his home and offices, looking for evidence of corruption. The Feds would go on to say that Huizar led a criminal enterprise based in city hall. He stands accused of taking bribes from luxury developers as his constituents were displaced from their homes.</description></item><item><title>I Am Rama | 10. Legacy | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520055/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520055/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, we explore all that Rama left behind: students, a charitable foundation, music, books, and a complicated legacy.
A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.
Subscribe on Apple Podcasts to binge all episodes now or listen weekly wherever you get your podcasts.
Find more great podcasts from Sony Music Entertainment at sonymusic.com/podcasts. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>I Am Rama | 9. Conscience Bay | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520056/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Power trips to paradise and never-before shared knowledge &amp;ndash; were these golden times, or Rama’s way of saying goodbye? This episode explores the final years leading of Rama&amp;rsquo;s life. A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.
Subscribe on Apple Podcasts to binge all episodes now or listen weekly wherever you get your podcasts.
Find more great podcasts from Sony Music Entertainment at sonymusic.com/podcasts
Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>I Am Rama | 8. Public Opinion | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520057/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520057/</guid><description>Podcast Description As Rama’s image took a hit in the public sphere, his students circled the wagons around their teacher. In something of a last ditch effort to win over the media, Rama accepts an invitation to appear on Dateline. A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.
Subscribe on Apple Podcasts to binge all episodes now or listen weekly wherever you get your podcasts.
Find more great podcasts from Sony Music Entertainment at sonymusic.</description></item><item><title>I Am Rama | 7. Accused | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520058/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Multiple women accuse Rama of sexual misconduct and emotional manipulation. Many of Rama’s students defend their teacher. A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.
Subscribe on Apple Podcasts to binge all episodes now or listen weekly wherever you get your podcasts.
Find more great podcasts from Sony Music Entertainment at sonymusic.com/podcasts Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>I Am Rama | 6. Deprogramming | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520059/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rama finds himself in the crosshairs of the Cult Awareness Network, a group dedicated to extricating people from what they consider to be cults by “deprogramming” them. But Rama’s students tell a much different story.
A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.
Subscribe on Apple Podcasts to binge all episodes now or listen weekly wherever you get your podcasts.
Find more great podcasts from Sony Music Entertainment at sonymusic.</description></item><item><title>I Am Rama | 5. Brenda | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520060/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520060/</guid><description>Podcast Description A young woman follows Rama to New York, and mysteriously vanishes, leaving behind many to wonder what happened. In this episode, people who knew and loved Brenda Kerber piece her story back together. If you have any information about the death of Brenda Kerber that wasn’t reflected in this episode, please contact the White Plains Police Department in New York at https://whiteplainspublicsafety.com/submit-a-tip/ or 914-422-6111. A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.</description></item><item><title>I Am Rama | 4. Spiritual Contract | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520061/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Will Arntz is a man of many talents, from filmmaker to laser physicist. In this episode, Will relives the time he spent studying with Rama and how it changed his life. A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.
Subscribe on Apple Podcasts to binge all episodes now or listen weekly wherever you get your podcasts.
Find more great podcasts from Sony Music Entertainment at sonymusic.com/podcasts Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>I Am Rama | 3. California Dreaming | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520062/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rama’s growth as a spiritual teacher in the mid-80s starts in California but takes him and his students all over the country. Rama defines his doctrine, turning his attention to the potential of the computer industry. But for his students, it’s not always easy to keep up with their teacher, or stay in his good graces. A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.
Subscribe on Apple Podcasts to binge all episodes now or listen weekly wherever you get your podcasts.</description></item><item><title>I Am Rama | 2. Becoming | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520063/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520063/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode follows Frederick Lenz III from his early days and education through his introduction to spiritualism with his mentor, Sri Chinmoy, at the dawn of the New Age. Young Freddie becomes “Atmananda,” a recruiter for his mentor, until it becomes time to strike out on his own, as Zen Master Rama. If you want to know more about Rama’s early years, you can read more from the people who we interviewed for this episode.</description></item><item><title>I Am Rama | 1. Golden Light | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520064/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rama was a man of many faces: teacher, tech entrepreneur, friend - and to some, a scam artist. This episode introduces Rama, examining the world from which he came, the way he shaped those who entered his orbit for better and for worse, and the mysterious circumstances around his demise. A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.
Subscribe on Apple Podcasts to binge all episodes now or listen weekly wherever you get your podcasts.</description></item><item><title>Coming Soon: I Am Rama | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520065/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rama was a spiritual teacher in the 80s and 90s who inspired many of his students while helming what many of his detractors would describe as a cult. He defied society’s archetypal vision of a New Age leader, eschewing minimalism for wealth and celebrity. He was also a man ahead of his time, encouraging his students to develop careers in computer science before that was mainstream.
For some, following Rama&amp;rsquo;s lead worked out spiritually, and financially too.</description></item><item><title>Fake Priest | 9. How To Get Away With Fraud | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520066/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Until now, Father Ryan has mostly escaped punishment for stealing money from followers under false pretenses. What would it take for him to face a jury of his peers?
A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.
Subscribe on Apple Podcasts to binge all episodes now or listen weekly wherever you get your podcasts.
Find more great podcasts from Sony Music Entertainment at sonymusic.com/podcasts Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Fake Priest | 8. Origin Story | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520067/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex Schuman finally has his showdown with Father Ryan. But things don&amp;rsquo;t go as planned because Father Ryan has something to confess about his past that sheds light on why he wanted to become a &amp;ldquo;priest&amp;rdquo; in the first place.
A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.
Subscribe on Apple Podcasts to binge all episodes now or listen weekly wherever you get your podcasts.
Find more great podcasts from Sony Music Entertainment at sonymusic.</description></item><item><title>Fake Priest | 7. Two Dead Priests | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520068/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520068/</guid><description>Podcast Description In his autobiography, Father Ryan connects himself to two priests who died suspiciously. One he accuses of molesting children. The other? He says he teamed up with to publicly shame pedophile priests. What&amp;rsquo;s the truth?
A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.
Subscribe on Apple Podcasts to binge all episodes now or listen weekly wherever you get your podcasts.
Find more great podcasts from Sony Music Entertainment at sonymusic.</description></item><item><title>Fake Priest | 6. No Good Deed Goes Unpunished | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520069/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520069/</guid><description>Podcast Description The father-daughter investigator team discovers the cop who arrested Father Ryan may have an ulterior motive. They defend Father Ryan tooth and nail - until they get a troubling surprise of their own.
A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.
Subscribe on Apple Podcasts to binge all episodes now or listen weekly wherever you get your podcasts.
Find more great podcasts from Sony Music Entertainment at sonymusic.</description></item><item><title>Fake Priest | 5. Meet The Browns | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520070/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520070/</guid><description>Podcast Description A sheriff deputy arrests Father Ryan for taking more than $70,000 from an elderly follower. It&amp;rsquo;s looking like he might get 7 years in prison, but then he meets a father-daughter pair of private investigators who change everything.
A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.
Subscribe on Apple Podcasts to binge all episodes now or listen weekly wherever you get your podcasts.
Find more great podcasts from Sony Music Entertainment at sonymusic.</description></item><item><title>Fake Priest | 4. Llama Drama | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520071/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520071/</guid><description>Podcast Description After Father Ryan steals a follower&amp;rsquo;s money, her property and even her husband&amp;rsquo;s ashes, she hires a lawyer. A legal battle ensues over unpaid loans and a herd of llamas that Father Ryan leaves high and dry.
A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.
Subscribe on Apple Podcasts to binge all episodes now or listen weekly wherever you get your podcasts.
Find more great podcasts from Sony Music Entertainment at sonymusic.</description></item><item><title>Fake Priest | 3. The Teacher | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520072/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Even con artists need mentors. Meet the false prophet who teaches Father Ryan how to perfect his con. Father Ryan evades criminal charges again and Alex learns about an unspoken reason prosecutors could let many criminals go free.
A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.
Subscribe on Apple Podcasts to binge all episodes now or listen weekly wherever you get your podcasts.
Find more great podcasts from Sony Music Entertainment at sonymusic.</description></item><item><title>Fake Priest | 2. Coming Home | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520073/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex tracks down Father Ryan’s son, Jonathan Brady, and discovers Father Ryan was a scammer and manipulator long before he wore a priestly robe. Turns out he had plenty of practice committing fraud before he opened his first church in Wisconsin. A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.
Subscribe on Apple Podcasts to binge all episodes now or listen weekly wherever you get your podcasts.
Find more great podcasts from Sony Music Entertainment at sonymusic.</description></item><item><title>Fake Priest | 1. An Unholy Priest | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520074/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Investigative reporter Alex Schuman hears about a guy accused of swindling millions who has travelled the Midwest for decades pretending to be a priest. Alex starts his journey talking to two people who have long tried to expose the truth. Alex is hoping to finally figure out why anyone would try to pull off such an elaborate con.
A Neon Hum Media and Sony Music Entertainment production.
Subscribe on Apple Podcasts to binge all episodes now or listen weekly wherever you get your podcasts.</description></item><item><title>Introducing Smoke Screen: Fake Priest | Smoke Screen: My Fugitive Dad</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2772520075/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 00:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2772520075/</guid><description>Podcast Description For 30 years, a man claimed to be a priest. He performed baptisms and took confession. Every time he ran into trouble, Father Ryan would move on to another small Midwestern town and start his scheme all over again. Followers who once worshiped him, now accuse him of exploitation, fraud and abuse. In season one of Smoke Screen, join Alex Schuman as he unravels this con and gets answers from this white-collar criminal himself.</description></item></channel></rss>