<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Money Mondays on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-money-mondays/</link><description>Recent content in The Money Mondays on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 18:55:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-money-mondays/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Brad Lea &amp; Alex Neist on What It Really Takes to Grow 8-Figure Brands | EP48 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360048/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 18:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brad Lea founded LightSpeed VT, which has become a major player in the world of online education. His vision was to revolutionize the way people learn by creating a virtual training system that would outshine traditional methods. And he succeeded!
He’s also the host of “Dropping Bombs,” a podcast series that provides valuable insights and knowledge to his audience. In addition, he owns the YouTube channel “BRAD LEA TV” with over 118K subscribers and 5 million views.</description></item><item><title>Shaun Neff's Rise from Dollar Store Hats to Building Multiple $100M Brands 🧢 E47 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 22:47:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Explore the incredible journey of Shaun Neff's success in this episode. From humble beginnings creating hats sold in dollar stores to spearheading million-dollar brands like Neff Headwear, Shaun Neff shares his remarkable path to success. 🏆
Shaun Neff is a visionary entrepreneur known for revolutionizing the headwear industry. As the founder of Neff Headwear, his innovative designs and strategic marketing propelled the brand to global recognition.
Passionate about merging fashion with function, Neff&amp;rsquo;s creativity has reshaped streetwear culture.</description></item><item><title>Change Your Life with Celebrity Brain Expert Doc Amen | E46 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360002/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this eye-opening conversation with Dr. Daniel Amen, celebrity brain health expert who has scanned over 250,000 brains unveils the impact of brain health on every aspect of our lives. Discover the power of brain scans in understanding mental health, focus, performance, memory and success.
Doc Amen, renowned as a leading brain health expert, is a double board-certified psychiatrist and a pioneering figure in the field of neuroscience. With over 40 years of clinical experience, he has revolutionized mental wellness by emphasizing the critical link between brain health and overall well-being.</description></item><item><title>The Power of Social Media: Michael Sartain's Guide to Millions 🤑 E45 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360003/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Michael Sartain shares his journey from nightlife to business success, and offers strategies for utilizing social platforms to reach millions. Explore actionable insights on high-status networking, content creation, and transforming social media views into substantial wealth. Michael Sartain, a passionate entrepreneur and influencer, is known for his dynamic presence in the entertainment industry. With a background in marketing and event promotion, he thrives in the nightlife scene, establishing himself as a sought-after figure.</description></item><item><title>We Broke the Guinness World Record for World's Largest Toy Drive! 🎁 E44 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join me on this special episode dedicated to the power of charity. In this solo talk, I dive into the essence of giving back. We're not discussing the usual ventures today—this time, it's about the monumental World's Largest Toy Drive happening this December. I'll walk you through the 10-city tour, the impact we aim to create, and how you can be a part of this global movement. Let's make a difference together.</description></item><item><title>From Garage to Greatness: The Entrepreneurial Journey of Tai Lopez | E36 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360005/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 23:03:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tai Lopez, a renowned entrepreneur and influencer, has carved his niche in the digital world. Tai is known for his relentless pursuit of knowledge and business acumen. He gained prominence through his social media presence, dispensing advice on wealth, health, love, and happiness. Tai is a multifaceted individual, showcasing his ventures in real estate, e-commerce, and online education. His TEDx talk, &amp;quot;Why I Read a Book a Day,&amp;quot; catapulted him into the limelight, propelling his mission to inspire millions to live a fulfilling and prosperous life through continuous learning and self-improvement.</description></item><item><title>This Formula Guarantees Success &amp; Lexy Panterra on Monetizing Social Media 💸 E43 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan's Guaranteed Success Formula &amp;amp; Paving Your OWN Path with Lexy Panterra | E43
Start a Movement &amp;amp; Pave Your OWN Path with Lexy Panterra | E43
Use This Formula to Guarantee Success + Lexy Panterra on Breaking the Rules | E43
Use This Formula for Success + Lexy Panterra on the Business of Social Media 💸 E43
The three movements mentioned are:
333 Movement: Do three text messages per day, asking someone what they need.</description></item><item><title>The Power of MONEY: Andrew Cordle, Eddie Wilson, Scott Donnell | E42 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 15:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360007/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this special episode, join us as we explore the insights of Andrew Cordle, Eddie Wilson, and Scott Donnell on wealth, financial empowerment, and philanthropy. Discover the keys to success and how they have impacted the lives of countless individuals. 💪
Andrew Cordle, an entrepreneur with a passion for philanthropy and education, is dedicated to guiding individuals on their path to wealth and contentment. He emphasizes the concept of money as a driving force in people&amp;rsquo;s lives, influencing their daily choices, retirement, travel, and debt management.</description></item><item><title>Billionaire Grant Cardone’s BEST Advice for First-Time Home Buyers in 2024 | E41 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 14:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360008/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this special episode, billionaire Grant Cardone shares invaluable insights focused on real estate investments, challenging common beliefs and sharing a million-dollar investment strategy. Don't miss out on this opportunity for financial wisdom!
Grant Cardone is a renowned American entrepreneur, best-selling author, motivational speaker, and real estate mogul, celebrated for his boundless energy and unyielding ambition. Cardone overcame early struggles with addiction and poverty to become a self-made millionaire.</description></item><item><title>Jesse Itzler Shares His Formula to Retire Wealthy 💰 E40 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360009/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 14:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360009/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this special episode of Money Mondays, we dive deep into the secrets of wealth-building with entrepreneur extraordinaire, Jesse Itzler. Join us as Jesse shares his proven formula for making more money in your 40s and 50s. Discover his unconventional journey and unique perspective on money, risk, and family...
Jesse Itzler, a multifaceted entrepreneur, author, and motivational powerhouse, defies convention at every turn. Known for his limitless pursuit of life experiences, he co-founded Marquis Jet, a private jet card company, and has played a pivotal role in numerous successful startups, including Zico Coconut Water.</description></item><item><title>Gary Vee's ENTIRE Investing Strategy, Starting from $0 💸 E39 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 14:28:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360010/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, we dive deep into the mind of the legendary entrepreneur Gary Vaynerchuk, as he unveils his entire investing strategy, shares insights on his AI predictions, and breaks down how to start investing and making more money, even if you're starting from $0. Don't miss this opportunity to learn from one of the best in the industry. 💪
Gary Vaynerchuk, often referred to as Gary Vee, is a prominent entrepreneur, author, and social media personality.</description></item><item><title>Cody Sperber &amp; Rene Rodriguez TRANSFORMED The Real Estate Game | E38 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360011/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 16:26:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360011/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this special episode, we have guests Clever Investor Cody Sperber and Rene Rodriguez, two experts in real estate and wealth building, share valuable insights and financial strategies for making more money. Join us as we explore their journey to success and uncover the financial secrets they've used to thrive in the real estate industry.
Like this episode? Watch more like it 👇 Steve Weatherford &amp;amp; Brad Castleberry Get Real About MONEY 💰: https://youtu.</description></item><item><title>Elliot Roe Exposes How Your Subconscious Mind Tries to Sabotage Your Finances | E37 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 14:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Elliot Roe is a leading expert in Mindset Optimization for High Performers and is the world’s #1 Mindset Coach for Olympic medalists, UFC Champions, Hollywood Actors, Business Executives, Wall Street traders, and poker players. His poker clients have won over $100,000,000 and nearly every major tournament title, including the World Series of Poker Main Event.
Elliot&amp;rsquo;s unique mindset coaching system leverages the power of hypnotherapy to eliminate fears and breakthrough mental roadblocks allowing you to operate in a state of peak performance every day.</description></item><item><title>Breaking Down My EXACT Investing Strategy with Everbowl + Wyld Jungle 📈 E35 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 15:02:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360013/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this special investing strategy episode, Dan Fleyshman walks you through his investment strategy with Everbowl and breaks down some of his top investing tips for beginners as a serial investor and entrepreneur... Plus, the Wyld Jungle is NOW OPEN. The Real Tarzann (Mike Holston) shares the latest Wyld Jungle news and BIG ranch updates - find out how we&amp;rsquo;re developing the property for education, conservation and charity efforts.</description></item><item><title>From RICO Crimes to Global Stages: The Journey of Damon West | E34 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 14:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Damon is a renowned keynote speaker and best-selling author, known for his extraordinary journey from a jail cell to global stages. He emerged from a life marked by property crimes, notably as the leader of a group of meth addicts involved in burglary. Determined to turn his life around, Damon invested in himself and leveraged a Beverly Hills publicist to secure a People Magazine article, catapulting him into the spotlight.</description></item><item><title>Avoid These MISTAKES If You Want to Make $$ at Live Events | E33 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 15:31:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you ready to make more money and build your network at live events? In this video, we talk about the things you should avoid doing and give you some smart tips on how to make money with live events. Learn how to turn every event into a profitable opportunity and ensure your networking efforts lead to long-lasting, profitable connections... Like this episode? Watch more like it 👇 &amp;quot;A Private Jet WILL PAY FOR ITSELF&amp;quot; - Jas Mathur &amp;amp; Randall Kaplan: https://youtu.</description></item><item><title>Elevator Studio $60M Influencer Marketing Agency Masterclass | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 14:34:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Elevator Studio creates powerful stories that connect brands to people and culture. For our audiences that means really awesome content, that they love and share.
elevator.studio
Like this episode? Watch more like it 👇
Watch ALL Full Episodes Here: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLs0D-M5aH-0IOUKtQPKts-VZfO55mfH6k The Money Mondays is a business podcast here to teach you how to make money, invest money, and donate money by showcasing some of the world&amp;rsquo;s most successful people and how they do the same.</description></item><item><title>Dan wins Humanitarian Award &amp; Hurricane Hilary hits Blacksite Ranch | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 14:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Like this episode? Watch more like it 👇
Watch ALL Full Episodes Here: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLs0D-M5aH-0IOUKtQPKts-VZfO55mfH6k The Money Mondays is a business podcast here to teach you how to make money, invest money, and donate money by showcasing some of the world&amp;rsquo;s most successful people and how they do the same. Hosted by serial entrepreneur Dan Fleyshman, the youngest founder of a publicly traded company in history, this money podcast gives you an exclusive behind the scenes look at how the wealthiest celebrities, entrepreneurs, athletes and influencers make, invest and donate money.</description></item><item><title>Why I Bought Equity Stake in a $72M/Year Events Business 📈 E30 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 14:24:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join us for the greatest event to inspire your growth financially, professionally, and personally with guest speakers that will put you directly on the right path for 2023.
August 17th - New York City
September 28th - Chicago
October 12th - San Diego
November - Houston
December - Atlanta
SECURE YOUR SEAT TODAY 🎟️ https://www.aspiretour.com ---
Like this episode? Watch more like it 👇
Watch ALL Full Episodes Here: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Codie Sanchez &amp; Pace Morby on Making Money Fast 💸 E29 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 14:29:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Codie Sanchez is an experienced investor, entrepreneur, and YouTuber with a passion for empowering others achieve financial freedom. She is the founder of Contrarian Capital - a portfolio of &amp;quot;boring&amp;quot; businesses that do over $50 million+ in revenue... from businesses you’ve never heard of like carwashes, laundromats and everyday shops.. @CodieSanchezCT also runs a successful YouTube channel with over 625k subscribers, sharing her insights on business flipping, investing, entrepreneurship, and personal finance with a wide audience.</description></item><item><title>Jeezy's 'Adversity for Sale' Book Reveals Difficult Rise to Fame &amp; Fortune | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 14:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jay Jenkins, known by his stage name Jeezy (or Young Jeezy), is an American rapper who signed to Def Jam Records in 2004 and has never shied away from talking about his life in his music. But for this Grammy-nominated, BET Award-winning, platinum-selling hip-hop artist, this next project might be his most personal.
With the release of his new book, &amp;lsquo;Adversity for Sale: Ya Gotta Believe&amp;quot; - Jeezy reveals his difficult path from the Atlanta streets to the top of the Billboard charts to help other up &amp;amp; comers succeed despite all odds.</description></item><item><title>'Million Dollar Wheels' RD Whittington Sells Luxury Cars to A-Listers | E27 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 14:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360021/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a behind-the-scenes look at how RD Whittington connects the ultra-rich with their million-dollar luxury cars, planes and vehicles. RD Whittington is a captivating entrepreneur and the star of the hit TV show &amp;quot;Million Dollar Wheels.&amp;quot; With an insatiable passion for luxury cars, RD (@wiresonly on IG) rose to prominence by establishing an A-Lister exotic car dealership. His magnetic personality and expert business acumen have earned him a legion of buyers and clientele from all walks of life.</description></item><item><title>Tim Storey and Him500 on Generational Wealth &amp; Being Recession Proof | E26 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 14:31:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tim Storey is an acclaimed culture influencing thought-leader, life strategist, author, speaker and counselor. Known for his insight and coaching among high-profile individuals who find themselves in a place of personal recovery and discovery, he has been labeled as the Original Comeback Coach.
---
Wealth strategist Marcus Barney is a highly successful real estate investor and entrepreneur. He is the owner of recession proof, one of the biggest financial literacy communities.</description></item><item><title>Will Instagram’s Threads App REALLY Replace Twitter, The Wyld Jungle Overview, and Jim Kwik Shares His Best Secrets for Memory, Money &amp; Focus | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 14:10:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Meta just announced its new Instagram Threads App - and in this episode, we'll touch on why it may just take down Twitter before we dive into @THEREALTARZANN 's story of going from animal lover to successful social media influencer - plus how serial investor Dan Fleyshman helped him map out an entire business model behind his Instagram and YouTube channel with multiple streams of income including products, brand deals, sponsorships, affiliate revenue, and more.</description></item><item><title>Make More, Invest More with Sam Taggart &amp; Jerome Maldonado | E23 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 14:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Taggart is an accomplished business expert and entrepreneur known for his passion for sales and business development using door to door sales strategies in any industry. Sam's leadership skills and ability to think outside the box have enabled him to build multiple successful ventures at a young age.
Taggart helps people create custom training systems in direct sales to drive higher conversion rates and overall sales revenue with commission structures.</description></item><item><title>"A Private Jet WILL PAY FOR ITSELF" - Jas Mathur &amp; Randall Kaplan | E22 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 14:59:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jaspreet &amp;quot;Jas&amp;quot; Mathur is an accomplished Canadian Entrepreneur, Venture Capitalist and Innovator who launched his first business at age 12, creating and developing high traffic wrestling news websites. At 16, Mathur sold his first business to a media company and over the years he has founded and reinvented a series of successful companies in various industries, including, Satellite TV, Digital Surveillance, Downloadable Media, Online Dating And Online Gambling.
As the CEO of Emblaze ONE Inc.</description></item><item><title>Navy Seal Ray 'Cash' Care + Dan Dreyer Scaled to $100M+ Per Year | EP 21 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360026/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 14:13:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Like this episode? Watch more like it 👇
Watch ALL Full Episodes Here: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLs0D-M5aH-0IOUKtQPKts-VZfO55mfH6k The Money Mondays is a business podcast here to teach you how to make money, invest money, and donate money by showcasing some of the world&amp;rsquo;s most successful people and how they do the same. Hosted by serial entrepreneur Dan Fleyshman, the youngest founder of a publicly traded company in history, this money podcast gives you an exclusive behind the scenes look at how the wealthiest celebrities, entrepreneurs, athletes and influencers make, invest and donate money.</description></item><item><title>Cannabis Expert Matt Morgan &amp; Millionaire John Malott on Self-Made Success | E20 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360027/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 14:17:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360027/</guid><description>Podcast Description 0:00 - From Prison to Network Marketing Millionaire with John Malott
27:52 - Growing a Cannabis Business with Cannabis Expert Matt Morgan
Like this episode? Watch more like it 👇 Watch ALL Full Episodes Here: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLs0D-M5aH-0IOUKtQPKts-VZfO55mfH6k The Money Mondays is a business podcast here to teach you how to make money, invest money, and donate money by showcasing some of the world&amp;rsquo;s most successful people and how they do the same.</description></item><item><title>Cesar Millan &amp; Jen Gottlieb on MONEY, MINDSET, BUSINESS | E19 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360028/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 14:25:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360028/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Cesar Millan aka &amp;quot;The Dog Whisperer&amp;quot; is a renowned dog behaviorist, bestselling author, and TV personality. Born in Mexico, he developed a deep understanding and connection with canines from an early age. Cesar&amp;rsquo;s unique approach to dog training, rooted in calm assertiveness and balance, has made him a global phenomenon. He rose to fame as the star of the hit TV series &amp;quot;The Dog Whisperer,&amp;quot; where he showcased his remarkable ability to rehabilitate even the most challenging dogs.</description></item><item><title>Making Millions with Real Estate Investing 📈 Albert Preciado &amp; Cole Hatter | E18 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360029/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 14:37:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get access to exclusive interviews here: https://themoneymondays.com
Like this episode? Watch more like it 👇
Dean Graziosi + Joel Marion Share Their Secrets to Success | E16: https://youtu.be/7gn0rNubXbg
Codie Sanchez &amp;amp; Pace Morby on Acquisitions &amp;amp; Real Estate | E14: https://youtu.be/F0vWu6r0WMo
Watch ALL Full Episodes Here: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLs0D-M5aH-0IOUKtQPKts-VZfO55mfH6k Albert Preciado is the Founder and CEO of The Mortgage Guys, Ambiance Realty and Driven Enterprises. Albert is also a Real Estate Investor and has been in the mortgage industry since 2005 as a licensed Broker and Mortgage Originator.</description></item><item><title>Josh Snow + DJ Irie on Image, Branding &amp; Building Wealth | E17 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360030/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 14:25:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Like this episode? Watch more like it 👇
Dean Graziosi + Joel Marion Share Their Secrets to Success | E16: https://youtu.be/7gn0rNubXbg
'Lions Not Sheep' Sean Whalen + Boxing Champion Andre Berto 👊 | E12: https://youtu.be/kaeitVrwh0Q
Watch ALL Full Episodes Here: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLs0D-M5aH-0IOUKtQPKts-VZfO55mfH6k
Josh Snow is a visionary entrepreneur and skincare expert who has revolutionized the beauty industry with his innovative approach to teeth whitening. As the founder and CEO of Snow, Josh disrupted traditional beauty norms with a relentless commitment to quality and efficacy with Snow teeth whitening products.</description></item><item><title>Dean Graziosi + Joel Marion Share Their Secrets to Success | E16 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360031/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 14:25:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dean Graziosi is a highly successful entrepreneur, investor, and best-selling author who has transformed the lives of countless people through his teachings on personal development and financial success. Dean has written multiple New York Times best-selling books, including &amp;quot;Millionaire Success Habits&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;The Underdog Advantage.&amp;quot; He is also a well-known real estate investor and has been featured on numerous TV shows, including The Oprah Winfrey Show and Larry King Live.</description></item><item><title>He Makes Multi-Millions Trading PENNY STOCKS 💰📈 Timothy Sykes | E15 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360032/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 14:25:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Timothy Sykes is a world renowned stock trader, entrepreneur, and educator in trading penny stocks. With over two decades of experience, Sykes has established himself as a leading figure in the finance industry and gained recognition by turning his Bar Mitzvah gift money into a substantial trading portfolio, ultimately amassing millions of dollars in profits.
Tim Sykes is best known for his unconventional approach to trading. He teaches his trading strategies to help new traders achieve financial independence through his blog, social media, and trading programs.</description></item><item><title>Codie Sanchez &amp; Pace Morby on Acquisitions &amp; Real Estate | E14 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360033/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 13:54:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Codie Sanchez is an experienced investor, entrepreneur, and YouTuber with a passion for empowering others achieve financial freedom. She is the founder of Contrarian Capital - a portfolio of &amp;quot;boring&amp;quot; businesses that do over $50 million+ in revenue... from businesses you’ve never heard of like carwashes, laundromats and everyday shops.. @CodieSanchezCT also runs a successful YouTube channel with over 625k subscribers, sharing her insights on business flipping, investing, entrepreneurship, and personal finance with a wide audience.</description></item><item><title>He Taught Kobe Bryant AND Michael Jordan How To WIN - Tim Grover | E13 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360034/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 15:57:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tim Grover is a renowned sports performance coach and author, widely recognized for his work with some of the greatest athletes in history. With over three decades of experience, Grover has trained NBA legends such as Michael Jordan, Kobe Bryant, and Dwyane Wade, as well as NFL stars like Warren Sapp and Charles Woodson. Throughout his career, Grover has become famous for his intense, no-nonsense approach to training, and his ability to push athletes beyond their limits to achieve greatness.</description></item><item><title>Get Your Money In Order with Sean Whalen &amp; Boxing Champion Andre Berto 💰 | E12 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360035/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 14:35:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sean Whalen is a successful entrepreneur and speaker who founded “Lions Not Sheep,” which started as a social media movement and grew into a successful lifestyle brand. Whalen encourages individuals to live fearlessly and break free from societal norms which has struck a chord with many people, and Lions Not Sheep quickly gained a large following.
Whalen went on to found other successful businesses, including a real estate investment company and a technology company.</description></item><item><title>Jessie Lee Talks MONEY &amp; Eric Spofford Has a $115M Exit 📈 | E11 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360036/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 15:09:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Like this episode? Watch more like it 👇
Watch ALL Full Episodes Here: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLs0D-M5aH-0IOUKtQPKts-VZfO55mfH6k
Jessie Lee, popularly known as imbosslee, is a dynamic content creator and social media influencer known for her unique style and creative approach to online content. With a strong presence on various social media platforms, imbosslee has captivated audiences with her engaging personality, relatable anecdotes, and captivating visuals.
Born and raised in a small town, imbosslee&amp;rsquo;s passion for content creation was sparked at a young age.</description></item><item><title>Nick Santonastasso &amp; Adam Weitsman on Money &amp; Mindset | E10 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360037/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 14:40:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam Weitsman and Nick Santonastasso share money strategies, business advice and motivation tactics in Episode 10 of The Money Mondays podcast. https://themoneymondays.com
Adam Weitsman is a prominent entrepreneur and philanthropist, known for his successful ventures in the scrap metal, recycling and shipping industries. He is the owner of Upstate Shredding, one of the largest privately owned scrap metal processing facilities in the US, and also serves as the CEO of the shipping company, Empire Recycling Corporation.</description></item><item><title>World's Greatest Mentalist, Oz Pearlman Reveals His Money Secrets | E9 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360038/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 14:30:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Oz Pearlman is an American mentalist, magician, and athlete who performs as a mentalist under the name &amp;quot;Oz the Mentalist&amp;quot;, and has successfully appeared on America's Got Talent, winning third-place in Season 10. He's a full-time performer and professional mentalist and in this episode, he's revealing how he built his career and rising net worth.
Pearlman earned a bachelor’s degree in electrical engineering from the University of Michigan in 2003, while already earning income from magic.</description></item><item><title>7x Mr Olympia Flex Lewis &amp; Bedros Keuilian's TOP MONEY Tips | E8 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360039/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 14:30:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Flex Lewis, born James Lewis, is a professional bodybuilder who grew up with a passion for sports and fitness. He began lifting weights at the age of 15 and quickly developed a love for bodybuilding.
Lewis made a name for himself in the bodybuilding world, winning his first competition at age 17. He went pro in 2007 and won the IFBB 212 Mr Olympia title for seven consecutive years, from 2012 to 2018.</description></item><item><title>Dave Meltzer &amp; Ryan Pineda Share Investing Strategies You Need | E7 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360040/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 14:30:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360040/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Meltzer, a Forbes Top 10 speaker, author and entrepreneur, is the cofounder of Sports 1 Marketing and formerly served as CEO of the renowned Leigh Steinberg Sports &amp;amp; Entertainment agency, which was the inspiration for the movie Jerry Maguire.
His life’s mission is to empower OVER 1 BILLION people to be happy! This simple yet powerful mission has led him on an incredible journey of providing value for others through his many ventures.</description></item><item><title>Steve Weatherford &amp; Brad Castleberry Get Real About MONEY | E6 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360041/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 15:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Superbowl Champion Steve Weatherford &amp;amp; Bodybuilder Brad Castleberry Get Real About MONEY 💰 Episode 6
NFL Superbowl champion Steve Weatherford &amp;amp; world famous bodybuilder Brad Castleberry are sharing all their money secrets in this episode! Hear how two of the world&amp;rsquo;s most competitive athletes climbed their way to financial success.
&amp;ndash;
Steve Weatherford is a former NFL football punter who won Super Bowl XLVI over the New England Patriots as a member of the New York Giants.</description></item><item><title>Walter O'Brien &amp; Kent Clothier on ChatGPT, Investing &amp; Real Estate | E5 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360042/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 15:00:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Walter O'Brien on ChatGPT, AI, Psy-Ops &amp;amp; Money &amp;amp; Kent Clothier on Real Estate, Investing &amp;amp; Generational Wealth
Walter O'Brien (aka &amp;quot;Scorpion&amp;quot;) is the founder of https://scorpioncomputerservices.com, a global think tank for hire that provides “intelligence on demand” as a concierge service for “ANY funded need”. Walter was the Executive Producer of the hit CBS-TV drama &amp;quot;Scorpion&amp;quot; based on his life, the show airs in 188 countries to up to a billion viewers a week.</description></item><item><title>Dan Bilzerian Broke All the Rules &amp; It Paid Off BIG | E4 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360043/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan Bilzerian - the man, the myth, the legend. He wrote his own rules and it paid off with multi-millions in profits. In this episode, Dan opens up about his journey from world famous poker player to crypto investor to entrepreneur and ultimate bad boy, plus what's next on his journey living the INSANE Dan Bilzerian lifestyle. &amp;nbsp;
From IGNITE.co, his product line selling high quality CBD, nicotine, spirits, apparel and more - to Bilzerian Entertainment, his personal media production machine - Dan Bilzerian is an expert in marketing, brand development, social media growth, digital production, events, investing, poker and more.</description></item><item><title>Jay's Prehistoric Pets &amp; Tim Kennedy Reveal Their Money Secrets | E3 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360044/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 19:06:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jay's Prehistoric Pets founder Jay Brewer started from humble beginnings and has since gone on to create a successful business helping protect and preserve wild reptiles and other exotic animals. Founder of Jay's Reptile Zoo, a donation-based animal sanctuary in Fountain Valley, California, Jay has over 600 animals on display representing more than 100 species and shows his millions of fans online how to handle, protect and care for these rare reptiles.</description></item><item><title>Stormy Wellington &amp; Gary Brecka of 10X Health on Success | E2 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360045/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 16:00:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to The Money Mondays!
On this episode Dan interviews CEO Stormy Wellington &amp;amp; Gary Brecka of 10X Health.
Stormy Wellington has helped 42 families become 7-figure earners and is the highest paid network marketer in health &amp;amp; wellness. She built the world's largest meditation community for BIPOC women and in this episode she's sharing her behind-the-scenes secrets to making money, investing money and giving back to her community.</description></item><item><title>UFC Michael Chandler &amp; Wes Watson Talk MONEY | E1 | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 15:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to The Money Mondays!
On this episode Dan interviews UFC legend Michael Chandler &amp;amp; Entrepreneur Wes Watson.
“Iron” Michael Chandler is a UFC legend with a record of 23-8-0.
Winning multiple world titles has kept Michael a perennial top 10 lightweight in the world rankings. He has been involved in some of the most action packed fights in Mixed Martial Arts history being nominated for “Fight Of The Year” three different times.</description></item><item><title>The Money Mondays Trailer | Dan Fleyshman | The Money Mondays</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9032360047/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:13:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9032360047/</guid><description>Podcast Description “The Money Mondays” is primed to be a global brand in the business space, focusing on investments, cash flowing businesses, side hustles and very visual acts of charity.&amp;nbsp;
Viewers will be able to learn from experts, win weekly prizes and participate in charity efforts in an “MTV Cribs” style setting.
Many episodes of the podcast will be recorded with Celebrities, influencers &amp;amp; athletes inside of their homes, studios &amp;amp; corporate headquarters.</description></item></channel></rss>