<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>everybody has a secret on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/everybody-has-a-secret/</link><description>Recent content in everybody has a secret on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 18:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/everybody-has-a-secret/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>the text about me | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Friday, friends! It started with a text sent to the wrong group chat and ended with one mammoth dilemma. Today, Annabelle, Milo and Eilish break it all down. Thank you so much to Garnier for making this episode possible. Check out the Garnier website to find out more about the Glossy Pineapple Hair Food range. Your hosts today were Annabelle Lee (@annabe11e1ee) and Milo Hartill (@milohartill). This episode was audio produced by Chelsea Srinivasan, produced by Eilish Gilligan, and executive produced by Michelle Andrews and Zara McDonald.</description></item><item><title>the self-obsessed sister | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hellooo, secret keepers! Today, Gemma returns to help us unpack a health secret so big, that we needed to call in the big dogs (experts). Thank you so much to Garnier for making this episode possible. Check out the Garnier website to find out more about the Glossy Pineapple Hair Food range. Your hosts today were Annabelle Lee (@annabe11e1ee) and Gemma Dimond (@gemdimond). This episode was audio produced by Chelsea Srinivasan, produced by Eilish Gilligan, and executive produced by Michelle Andrews and Zara McDonald.</description></item><item><title>the win | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hello hellooo! Today, Dyl Buckley returns to help us unpack a money conundrum we guarantee you’ve all asked hypothetical questions about before… Thank you so much to Fizzer Seltzer and their new range, Fizzer Sour, for making this episode possible. Fizzer Seltzers are available in independent bottle-os, Dan Murphy’s, BWS, Liquorland, First Choice stores, and online. You can also score 20% off the Fizzer Seltzer range on their online store with code ‘SHAMELESS20’.</description></item><item><title>the restaurateur | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why hellooo, secret keepers! It started with a job interview and ended in&amp;hellip; a seven-month affair. Today, we untangle the whole damn thing with a brand new co-host. Big thanks to Elite Eleven for making this episode possible. To make the most of Elite Eleven’s sale, head in-store and online to get up to 70% from now until December 3rd. Your hosts today were Annabelle Lee (@annabe11e1ee) and Milo Hartill (@milohartill).</description></item><item><title>the pre-wedding confession | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hello hello! A proposition, a confession, and a wedding around the corner. Today, Louis and Annabelle are faced with a question they simply… cannot answer. Big thanks to the newest member of the Garnier Fructis Hair Food family - Glossy Pineapple - for making this episode possible. If you want to maintain and nourish your locks and leave them smelling and feeling fresh, you can pick up the Shampoo, Conditioner &amp;amp; Mask for 40% off this week at your local Coles or via Coles online.</description></item><item><title>the spare bedroom | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hello, secret keepers! Gemma is back! This time, to help us wade through a secret about a questionable friendship, told from an&amp;hellip; unlikely perspective. Big thanks to the newest member of the Garnier Fructis Hair Food family - Glossy Pineapple - for making this episode possible. To try the Garnier Fructis Hair Food range for yourself, you can pick up the Shampoo, Conditioner &amp;amp; Mask for 40% off this week at your local Woolworths or via Woolworths online.</description></item><item><title>the stay or go special (take two) | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hiya, friends! Last season, we did a fun little episode called ‘the stay or go special’. You guys loved it so much that we thought: well, why not do another? Big thanks to tbh Skincare for making this episode possible. Shop the tbh Skincare range online at tbhskincare.com or at your local Coles or Priceline today. Your hosts today were Annabelle Lee (@annabe11e1ee) and Louis Hanson (@louishanson). This episode was audio produced by Chelsea Srinivasan, produced by Eilish Gilligan, and executive produced by Michelle Andrews and Zara McDonald.</description></item><item><title>the spreadsheet | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550008/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re baaaaack! And boy are we stoked to be. To kick off season four, we’ve got a pretty epic episode for you today. Not only are we spilling a secret like nothing we’ve heard on the show before, but we welcome a new co-host to the roster by making him play our toughest game. Lots to get through - we can’t wait for you to listen. Thank you so much to Go-To Skincare for making this episode possible.</description></item><item><title>we're baaaaack... | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 03:36:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550009/</guid><description>Podcast Description See you on Friday, gossip fiends!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>what happened next | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fancy seeing you here, in-between seasons! You’re always asking us: but what happened next? So, we figured it was time to check back in with a few of our most popular secrets for any juicy updates. Big thanks to the newest Garnier Fructis Hair Food family member, Glossy Pineapple, for making this episode possible. If you are in need of a new haircare regimen to nourish your locks and leave them smelling and feeling fresh, then check out the Garnier website to find out more about the Glossy Pineapple Hair Food range.</description></item><item><title>the jealousy | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hiya, pals! A missed phone call, a TV show, and a jealous roommate. Today, to round out the season, we’re tackling one of the most bizarre stories of friendship betrayal we’ve ever heard on the show. Thank you so much to Benefit Cosmetics for making this episode possible. You can score 25% off Benefit’s POREfessional full-size product collection over on Adore Beauty’s website with the code ‘BENEFIT25’. That’s the code BENEFIT25 for 25% off.</description></item><item><title>the promise | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hello, legends! Today, Naomi tells us all about Lex. What happens when the death of someone you cared for not only elicits grief for that person, but grief over the life you were promised? Thank you so much to tbh Skincare for making this episode possible. You can score 15% off by using the code ‘EHAS15’ on their website until the end of the month. (This code will only last until May 31st.</description></item><item><title>the kiss that started it all | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey, everybody! Today, we hear from a secret sharer who kissed someone she definitely wasn’t supposed to. But as always, there’s a little more to it… Thank you so much to Ultra Violette for making this episode possible. If you wanna try Ultra Violette’s Preen Screen SPF50 Reapplication Mist out for yourself, you can purchase it on their website www.ultraviolette.com.au, or wait until it&amp;rsquo;s available in retailers from May 10th.</description></item><item><title>the "charity" | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550014/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Oh haaaiiiii, besties! Today, we chat through one helluva conundrum. What happens when you’re convinced your sister’s best friend is a compulsive liar, but the details are so delicate, you’re unsure how to prove it? Thank you so much to Ultra Violette for making this episode possible. If you want to try Ultra Violette’s Preen Screen SPF50 Reapplication Mist out for yourself, you can purchase it on their website www.</description></item><item><title>the manipulative mum | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hello hello! Today, we hear about Emma’s toxic dynamic with her mum, from the perspective of Emma&amp;rsquo;s friend. What happens when you’re so concerned about your friend’s family situation, but don’t know whether it’s your place to interfere? Thank you so much to Ultra Violette for making this episode possible. If you want to try Ultra Violette’s Preen Screen SPF50 Reapplication Mist out for yourself, you can purchase it on their website www.</description></item><item><title>the love square | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Friday, besties! Four people, one unexpected confession. Today, we hear all about Ella, Joel, Steven, and Clare. Thank you so much to Stan for making this episode possible. If you’d like to watch the brand new Stan Original Series, Totally Completely Fine, it’s now streaming, only on Stan. Start your 30-day free trial today. Got a secret you’re itching to spill? Email it to hotline@shamelessmediaco.com. Everything will be kept anonymous, of course.</description></item><item><title>the pregnancy | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hello, everybody! Today on the show, we&amp;rsquo;re tackling a big one. What happens when the family you’ve created with your partner is built on a life-altering lie? Thank you so much to Cashrewards for making this episode possible. Sign up to Cashrewards today with the code ‘SECRET’ to receive an additional $20 bonus cashback on your first shop. Got a secret you’re itching to spill? Email it to hotline@shamelessmediaco.</description></item><item><title>the uncle | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550018/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Friday, fam! Today, we’re talking about broken trust. What happens when one huge instance of betrayal within the walls of a family sparks a chain of even more secrecy and lies? Thank you so much to Cashrewards for making this episode possible. Sign up to Cashrewards today with the code ‘SECRET’ to receive an additional $20 bonus cashback on your first shop. Got a secret you’re itching to spill?</description></item><item><title>the stay or go special | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hello, secret keepers! This episode is a special one - a stay or go special, to be exact. Producer Eilish is shaking things up by surprising Annabelle and Louis with a few unexpected turns today. Thank you so much to Cashrewards for making this episode possible. Sign up to Cashrewards today with the code ‘SECRET’ to receive an additional $20 bonus cashback on your first shop. Got a secret you’re itching to spill?</description></item><item><title>the brother | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550020/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re back, baby! And today, like always, we’re tackling one complicated secret. What happens when your loving relationship has a major roadblock in the way? His brother. Thank you so much to Cashrewards for making this episode possible. Sign up to Cashrewards today with the code ‘SECRET’ to receive an additional $20 bonus cashback on your first shop. CLICK HERE TO COMPLETE THE LISTENER SURVEY (thank you!!). Got a secret you’re itching to spill?</description></item><item><title>the guilt | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hello, everyone! Today’s episode is a heavier one. Losing a loved one is difficult enough, then add all the elements that shape Georgia’s secret and this story becomes incredibly complicated. Thank you so much to Elite Eleven for making this episode possible. You can shop their epic range via the app or website at eliteelevensporting.com. Don’t forget to use the code ‘EHAS10’ for 10% off. Got a secret you’re itching to spill?</description></item><item><title>the love child | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Oh haiiii, everybody! On today’s show, we heard from someone tasked with keeping her best friend’s huge secret. What happens when you believe the truth needs to come out but you worry it’s not your place to unleash it? Thank you so much to Supré for making this episode possible. Use the code ‘EHAS15’ for 15% off sitewide on Supre.com.au. Got a secret you’re itching to spill? Write a letter addressed to ‘Annabelle Lee at Shameless Media’ and mail it to our PO BOX at 4091 Richmond East VIC 3121.</description></item><item><title>the dare | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550023/</guid><description>Podcast Description G’day, besties! It started with a game of truth or dare and ended with one mammoth lie. Today, listener Hailey&amp;rsquo;s secret submission got us asking the question of all questions: what degree of friendship betrayal is forgivable? Thank you so much to Frank Body for making this episode possible. Shop 20% off sitewide with Frank Body’s biggest sale of the year at frankbody.com. Got a secret you’re itching to spill?</description></item><item><title>the sugar daddy | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550024/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hello, everybody! Today, we hear one of the more serious secrets of the season: What happens when you’re struggling with money so you turn to a sugar daddy website, only to see a profile username that looks awfully familiar? Thank you so much to Frank Body for making this episode possible. Check out their awesome products this festive season, and score 15% off with the code ‘EHAS’ at the checkout.</description></item><item><title>the missing money | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550025/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hiya, friends! Today, we’re asking the big questions: what makes stealing wrong? What happens when you have the compulsion to pocket something without paying for it and you don’t know how to stop? Thank you so much to Go-To Skincare for making this episode possible. If you wanna try Go-To’s incredible products for yourself, use the code ‘EHAS’ on orders over $80 at the checkout for 15% off. Got a secret you’re itching to spill?</description></item><item><title>the test | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550026/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hello, everybody! Today, our secret keeper came to us with the ultimate relationship conundrum: what if your romantic partner treats other people differently to how they treat you? Thank you so much to MECCA MAX and their dream line-up of high-performing products for making this episode possible. Get your hands on the MECCA MAX Morning Glow Off Duty Trio for $46, the Pout Pencil for $14, and the Single Eyeshadows for just $8.</description></item><item><title>the elevator | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Helloooo, secret keepers! An elevator, a woman locked out of her fiancé’s hotel room, and a man on his way to get snacks for his girlfriend. You guessed it: Today, we&amp;rsquo;re talking about cheating. But as always on this show, it’s not entirely straightforward&amp;hellip; Thank you so much to MECCA MAX and their dream line-up of high-performing products for making this episode possible. Get your hands on the MECCA MAX Off Duty Blur Stick and Gloss Boss Lip Gloss for just $18, and the Mini Mix Eyeshadow Palette for $20.</description></item><item><title>the newlyweds | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550028/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550028/</guid><description>Podcast Description G’day, lovely people! Boy, do we have a killer secret for you today. What happens when the man you just married breaks your trust, leaving you with the ultimate dilemma to battle alone: head or heart? Thank you so much to Go-To Skincare for making this episode possible. If you wanna try Go-To’s incredible products for yourself, use the code ‘EHAS’ on orders over $80 at the checkout and score 15% off.</description></item><item><title>the con-artist dad | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550029/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hiya, friends! Today, we’re talking about colossal family secrets. What happens when you find out a parent who&amp;rsquo;s passed away was lying to everyone for years? Thank you so much to Quay Australia for making this episode possible. If you see something that tickles your fancy over on quayaustralia.com.au, use the code ‘SHADY’ for a cheeky 20% off. Don’t forget to keep your eyes peeled over on our socials for a few real tales of shadiness, brought to you by Quay.</description></item><item><title>the other woman | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550030/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550030/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re back, besties! And today, we’re delving into one complicated secret: What happens when you’ve slept with someone who’s in a relationship, you think his girlfriend deserves the truth, but there’s a major roadblock&amp;hellip; Thank you so much to Quay Australia for making this episode possible. If you see something that tickles your fancy over on quayaustralia.com.au, use the code ‘SHADY’ at checkout for a cheeky 20% off. Don’t forget to keep your eyes peeled over on our socials for a few real tales of shadiness, brought to you by Quay.</description></item><item><title>guess who's back... | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550031/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 03:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550031/</guid><description>Podcast Description season two is coming tomorrow, october 7.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>the best man | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550032/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hello! We’re ending the first season of the show with one juicy, juicy secret.
What happens when you’re about to get married to the man of your dreams but there’s just one problem? You can’t stop thinking about his best man.
Thank you so much to MECCA MAX for making this season possible. Pick up MECCA MAX’s Zoom Shadow Sticks for $19 and Liners for $17 in Mecca stores or online via mecca.</description></item><item><title>the texts | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550033/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Heya pals!
Today, Sam and Annabelle discuss our listener’s secret sexts. What happens when you’re sending texts to someone outside your relationship, convinced what you’re doing doesn’t constitute cheating?
Thank you so much to MECCA MAX for making this season possible. Pick up their Brow Guru Super Soap in Mecca stores or online via mecca.com.au or meccabeauty.co.nz for $16. Don’t forget to follow MECCA MAX on Instagram or TikTok for the latest beauty trends and tips.</description></item><item><title>the estranged dad | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550034/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Friday, secret spillers!
In this episode, we’re talking about lying. What happens when you tell your friends a lie so mammoth, that coming clean to them feels almost impossible?
Thank you so much to MECCA MAX for making this season possible. Pick up their Spot Dot Blemish Busting Pimple Patches in Mecca stores or online via mecca.com.au or meccabeauty.co.nz. You can get a 12 pack for $10 or a 36 pack for $26.</description></item><item><title>the boyfriend's addiction | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550035/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi everyone!
Today, we’re unpacking quite the complicated secret: what happens when the secret you’re keeping is somebody else’s? When the boyfriend you love deeply is hiding his addiction from almost everyone but you?
If you or a loved one is struggling with a gambling addiction, you can access support by visiting Gambler&amp;rsquo;s Help, Lifeline, or here for services from the Victorian Responsible Gambling Foundation.
Thank you so much to MECCA MAX for making this season possible.</description></item><item><title>the fling | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550036/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hellooooo! We’re back in your ears to spill another killer secret.
A student. A married couple with kids. A secret affair inside their family home. How the hell did it all transpire?
Thank you so much to MECCA MAX for making this season possible. Pick up their Off Duty BB Cream With SPF 15 in Mecca stores or online via mecca.com.au or meccabeauty.co.nz for $20. Don’t forget to follow MECCA MAX on Instagram or TikTok for the latest beauty trends and tips.</description></item><item><title>the ex teacher | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550037/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Secret spillers! Secret keepers! Hello!
In this episode, we’re talking about secret sex with an ex-teacher. What’s so wrong with that? Today, Flex and Annabelle break it all down.
Thank you so much to MECCA MAX for making this season possible. Pick up their Off Duty Sticks in Mecca stores or online via mecca.com.au or meccabeauty.co.nz for $18. Don’t forget to follow MECCA MAX on Instagram or TikTok for the latest beauty trends and tips.</description></item><item><title>the faker | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550038/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550038/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re baaaack!
And today, we’re delving into one helluva secret: What happens when you fake your identity and can’t shake the guilt years later?
Thank you so much to MECCA MAX for making this season possible. Pick up their Mini Max Eyeshadow Palettes in Mecca stores or online via mecca.com.au or meccabeauty.co.nz for $20. Don’t forget to follow MECCA MAX on Instagram or TikTok for the latest beauty trends and tips.</description></item><item><title>the man on the phone | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550039/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hello there! It’s officially time! This is the first-ever episode of ‘everybody has a secret’. Today, we’re unpacking quite the juicy one: what if your dad… isn’t actually your dad at all?
Thank you so much to MECCA MAX for making this season possible. Pick up the new EYE MAX Mega Volume Mascara in Mecca stores or online via mecca.com.au or meccabeauty.co.nz for $24. Don’t forget to follow MECCA MAX on Instagram or TikTok for the latest beauty trends and tips.</description></item><item><title>who's ready? | everybody has a secret</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6408550040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 05:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6408550040/</guid><description>Podcast Description season one is officially on its way.
see you on may 6&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>