<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>After Hours on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/after-hours/</link><description>Recent content in After Hours on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/after-hours/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Appreciating Late Bloomers and a Big Bank | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370204/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370204/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix and Mihir discuss how JPMorgan has managed to succeed where others fail and how late bloomers manage to succeed after sometimes failing. Transcript</description></item><item><title>Magnificent Markets and Conflict on Campus | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 15:50:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix and Mihir discuss the meaning and impact of the increasing concentration of stock market performance via the “Magnificent 7” and the source and resolution of conflicts on campuses. Transcript</description></item><item><title>Turbulence at OpenAI — Our Take-Aways | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix and Mihir discuss how Sam Altman was fired and reinstated over the course of just a few days. Was the board right to dismiss Altman? Does the turmoil change how we think about hybrid organizations that combine nonprofit and for-profit motives? What does the episode teach us about the future of AI? Plus, we look at the reasons why men now die even earlier than women. What do the numbers say about being male today?</description></item><item><title>The Future of Africa and Empty Lots | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Will Africa fulfill its remarkable promise in the next several decades? Is a land tax the best kind of tax? Would it solve our housing crisis? All that and more on this episode of After Hours. Transcript</description></item><item><title>Does AI Have a Copyright Problem? | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 05:34:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix and Mihir discuss how copyright applies to AI-generated works. Are AI companies guilty of mass infringement? Could users be sued if they use AI to generate texts and images? Wouldn’t it be right to compensate authors for their contributions to AI models? Plus, a decade in, what has the corporate purpose movement accomplished? We look back and take a glimpse at the future.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>House Music | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 18:08:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix, Sarah and Mihir consider whether real estate brokers add value, how the world of brokers will be transformed by a recent lawsuit and consider whether investors should be buying music as an asset class.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The U.S. economy is stellar. So why are we all so mad? | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370006/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Mihir and Felix discuss consumer finances, which are remarkably healthy. The average U.S. household now has a net worth of more than a million dollars. But if things are this good, why are we so angry? Why lament the state of the economy? Plus, we talk about Tesla and the market for electric vehicles. Has it reached its nadir?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bond Market Bedlam | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix and Mihir are back, and it’s time to unpack bond market bedlam!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Magnificent Markets and Conflict on Campus | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix and Mihir discuss the meaning and impact of the increasing concentration of stock market performance via the “Magnificent 7” and the source and resolution of conflicts on campuses. Transcript</description></item><item><title>Going out with a bang: Recommendations for this summer | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370009/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is it, dear friends of the After Hours podcast. We end our sixth season with a long list of recommendations: shows to watch, books to read, foods to savor, places to visit...
Thank for spending your time with us. We will be back after our summer break, sometime in September. Have a wonderful summer everyone!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Summer Stories to Savor | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix and Mihir are joined by friends to discuss their stories to watch this summer, including the bust up of Sequoia, pricing, Gen AI, sports stories, the FTC and PBMs, Amazon in healthcare, and the future of theatres, travel, unions, brand activism, energy tax credits, interest rates and the war in Ukraine. Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Portfolio Life: Being Productive and Happy | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix and Mihir are joined by Christina Wallace to discuss the meaning of a portfolio life and why U.S. workers are happier than ever but less productive. Transcript</description></item><item><title>Taking a week off! | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 14:19:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Taking a week off!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Sunny Side of Bankruptcy | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix, Mihir and their colleague Kristin Mugford debate the merits of using bankruptcy to shield companies from consumer lawsuits. Should we allow companies to bundle lawsuits, place them in a designated subsidiary with few assets and let that subsidiary go bankrupt? Might this actually be better for consumers who claim to have been hurt by defective products? Doesn’t everyone deserve their day in court? Plus, what is happening to prices of luxury goods?</description></item><item><title>What’s Your Personal Brand? Is Brand Building Worth it? | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix, Mihir and Jill Avery consider the merits of personal branding and how to think about the value of a brand. Why do people want to consider their personal brand? And, why do we still struggle to understand the value of brands given all the data we swim in? Transcript</description></item><item><title>Strike in Hollywood | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370015/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s episode, Felix, Mihir and Bloomberg’s Sarah Green Carmichael discuss the writers’ strike in Hollywood. Why do we suddenly see a strike during “the golden era of television” and amidst intensifying streaming wars? What are the thorniest issues? How do they speak to challenges for knowledge workers more generally? Plus, why you should love meetings. (We are not kidding!)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Everything’s Coming up AI! | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix, Mihir and Charlotte Howard discuss the recent earnings season with a spotlight on ExxonMobil, Chevron, Autozone, Apple, UPS, Microsoft and PDD – and what it all means for the economy.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Better Ways to Say Thank You | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix, Mihir and their colleague Kathleen McGinn discuss the role of gratitude at work and at home. Gratitude can be incredibly effective, so why don’t we thank others more often? What goes wrong when a thank you seems shallow and inauthentic? Can gratitude even be an impediment to change? Plus, we debate early retirement. Clearly, it is what people want. Why don’t we give it to them?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Betting on Netflix, Co-CEOs and India | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix and Mihir discuss the state of Netflix and streaming, the co-CEO model, and Incredible India.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Taming AI | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370019/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Felix and Mihir debate with their colleague Deborah Spar, Senior Associate Dean for Business and Global Society at Harvard Business School, the role of government in regulating AI. How do we make sure we get the best out this groundbreaking technology? Should we keep government out of the way, at least for the time being? Is industry self-regulation sufficient to prevent the worst? Are we contending with an existential threat?</description></item><item><title>The Renaissance of Barnes &amp; Noble and Dark Ages for Commercial Real Estate? | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix and Mihir discuss the durability of a book retailer's turnaround, the future of commercial real estate and whether all the doomsaying is correct.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Women at Work—First-time Managers | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 15:57:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix is joined by Bloomberg’s Sarah Green Carmichael and Harvard Business Review editor Amy Bernstein to discuss the particular challenges that women face when they first assume managerial roles. Why is it that women do not experience the increase in personal satisfaction that is typical for men? What can companies do to better support first-time managers, women and men? Plus, we talk about the booming gaming business. Will it swallow all of entertainment?</description></item><item><title>The Future of Venture Financing and Philanthropy | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix, Mihir and Christina Wallace consider the SVB business model, what its loss means for entrepreneurial finance and what they make of new models of philanthropy. Transcript</description></item><item><title>Woke CEOs—the Backlash | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370023/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Felix, Mihir and Semafor’s Liz Hoffman debate the backlash against woke CEOs. Did America’s corporate leaders go too far when they embraced broad social and political goals? Does corporate activism ultimately undermine political action? What’s the cost of cutting business ties with corporations that are deemed too woke? Plus, we ask Liz Hoffman about her new book, Crash Landing: The Inside Story of How the World’s Biggest Companies Survived an Economy on the Brink.</description></item><item><title>After Hours Special: The Crisis in Banking | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370024/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 18:40:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mihir and Felix think about the current crisis in banking. Why did Silicon Valley Bank fail? Is the demise of Credit Suisse a result of the contagion in the United States? And what’s the future of banking? Will the big banks get even bigger? Even more prone to fail? Would we be better off if all deposits were insured? If banks were kept to a smaller size?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Primary Care Acquisitions and Wage Compression | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix, Mihir and Charlotte Howard of The Economist consider why retailers are buying primary care providers and if wage compression will last and what it means for the economy.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Finally-- A Clinically-Proven Way to Lose Weight. Now what? | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix, Mihir and The Economist’s Charlotte Howard debate the merits of a new class of weight-loss drugs that drastically lower a person’s weight. Is this incredible scientific advance the solution to the obesity epidemic that is sweeping the planet? Should health insurance companies cover the pricey drugs? Will obesity become even more prevalent now that we have effective medication? Plus, we discuss the roller coaster that is Moderna. What’s next for one of the pandemic’s biggest winners?</description></item><item><title>The Promise and Peril of AI | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370027/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix, Sarah and Mihir discuss Chat GPT, if AI is truly transformational, the future of search, and how to digitally detox from all this AI talk. Transcript</description></item><item><title>Turmoil in Energy Markets | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mihir and Felix are joined by Rawi to talk about the far-reaching consequences of the current turmoil in energy markets. Is Qatar the next Saudi Arabia? Are the oil majors actually saying goodbye to renewables? Are we seeing the de-industrialization of Europe? Plus, we debate the consequences of shrinking populations. Will it blow up social security? Could it be good news?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bed, Bath and Beyond Annuities! | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370029/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix and Mihir debate the latest phase of meme-stock craziness and the wisdom of retirement planning without annuities.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sports! | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370030/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370030/</guid><description>Podcast Description In our first-ever After Hours sports episode, we ask why sports teams have become so valuable (is it really just the vanity of billionaire owners), debate the merits of paying amateur athletes, and explore why tennis pros receive such a small fraction of the sport’s overall revenue. Can hedge fund icon Bill Ackman save tennis? Transcript</description></item><item><title>The End of Google and Fruit Beetles? | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370031/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370031/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Felix, Mihir and Sarah consider the merits of the most recent antitrust actions against Google, the ethics of unpaid labor, and the end of Noma.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Workplace Problems—Fixed! | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370032/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 15:12:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix, Mihir and Frances Frei discuss why many workplace issues seem so vexing—and how to fix them. We also talk about Jacinda Ardern’s resignation as New Zealand’s prime minister. Is she leaving too early? How do you best choose your exit?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Lunar New Year Special: BYD, EVs and Chinese Capital Allocation | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370033/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix and Mihir celebrate Lunar New Year by talking about BYD, Electric Vehicles, and capital allocation in China.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Banning TikTok, Lessons from Southwest’s Meltdown | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370034/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 16:56:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sarah Green Carmichael and Felix discuss the ban of TikTok by India and the U.S. Federal Government. Do these bans keep us safe? How nervous should we be on social media apps? Is the U.S. next to build a Chinese-style walled garden that keeps out unwanted companies and governments? Also, we review Southwest’s operational collapse during the holidays. Is legacy technology to blame? Did the company really underinvest?</description></item><item><title>Our Predictions for 2023 | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370035/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Curious about 2023? Youngme, Mihir and Felix are back with their celebrated predictions episode. Who will acquire Spotify? Will Twitter implode? What’s the trend in inflation and energy prices? Who will top the music charts? Space travel for all? Listen in as the hosts outguess each other what the new year will bring.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>2022-The Stories We Loved (and a Few Others) | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370036/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370036/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Youngme, Mihir and Felix share what they loved about 2022. Listen in to get their take on the end of magical thinking, quiet CEOs, the latest in sneaker fashion, and the collapse of FTX. Plus, we have an After Hours poem for you. (And no, we did not write it ourselves. Thank you, ChatGPT!)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>China, Chips, Child Poverty &amp; Measuring Inequality | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370037/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix and Mihir are joined by The Economist’s Charlotte Howard and they discuss the geopolitical battle over semiconductors and the surprising victories in battling poverty.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why Are Financial Regrets So Common? | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370038/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mihir, Felix and Bloomberg’s Sarah Green Carmichael talk about financial regrets. Why are they so widespread? Do people really make grave financial mistakes? Do they lack the information required to make smart choices? Plus, we debate the return of Disney’s Bob Iger. Will he shine once more?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Holding a Global Sports Event in Qatar? | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370039/</guid><description>Podcast Description We debate the choice of Qatar as the host of FIFA’s World Cup. Was it a mistake to hold the tournament in a country that criminalizes homosexuality? Was this exactly the right thing to do? Who is to judge? Mihir, Felix and their colleague Tsedal Neeley struggle with the question when to say no to countries’ hosting ambitions. Plus, we debate the ongoing workplace revolution. Where will it all end?</description></item><item><title>The Thanksgiving Food Episode! | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370040/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 20:08:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370040/</guid><description>Podcast Description In celebration of Thanksgiving, Felix and Mihir are joined by Youngme to talk about all things food! Join them as they talk about everything from the future of Kellogg’s to the explosion in Korean food around the globe. They also riff on the evolution of restaurant plating, the proliferation of QR menus, the best depictions of food in movies and television, the failure of recycling, and innovations in rice farming.</description></item><item><title>Washington Gridlock—How Will the Markets Respond | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370041/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mihir, Felix and Charlotte Howard discuss how companies will respond to political gridlock in the United States. Is it good for business? Will it really lift markets as many observers expect? Also: We speculate how the tech layoffs will influence the job market and the long-term prospects of tech talent.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Workplace Big Brother and Fresh Starts | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370042/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Felix and Mihir are joined by Katy Milkman to discuss workplace surveillance and the value of a fresh start.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Who Is Afraid of Woke Capitalism? | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mihir, Felix and NYU’s Dolly Chugh discuss the pressure on business leaders to conform to the demands of woke capitalism. Should you give in? Push back? What are the risks and rewards? Also: Feeling low lately? Chances are you are just getting older. We speculate why most people go through some sort of midlife crisis and talk about ways to better cope with life’s seemingly inevitable ups and downs.</description></item><item><title>The limits of Goldman and technology | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 14:05:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix and Mihir consider the future of Goldman Sachs and the limits of technology in human interactions.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>War in Ukraine—How will it end? | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370045/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rawi joins Mihir and Felix to discuss the war in Ukraine: What is most surprising about the evolution of the conflict? Are the sanctions working? How is the war reshaping geopolitics? Will the Putin regime deploy nuclear weapons? And, most importantly, how will the hostilities end?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Twitter under Musk and Bonds, Bonds, Bonds! | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370046/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370046/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week's episode, Felix, Sarah, and Mihir discuss the future of Twitter under Musk and bond market craziness.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mark Cuban doesn’t believe in following your passions | ReThinking w/Adam Grant | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370047/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 14:34:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mark Cuban has gone from selling garbage bags door-to-door to selling internet companies for billions, acquiring an NBA team, and becoming a beloved “Shark” on Shark Tank. Mark reveals to Adam how he turns problems into opportunities in entrepreneurship, basketball, and investing. They discuss his latest venture–disrupting the healthcare industry with an online pharmacy and a price-slashing philosophy that makes hundreds of drugs affordable–and why following your passion is not the best way to maintain your motivation.</description></item><item><title>Quiet Quitting | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370048/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have members of your team quit quietly? Is that even a thing? And if not, why is everybody talking about it? In this episode, Bloomberg’s Sarah Green Carmichael, Mihir and Felix discuss how to make sense of current trends in the workplace. Also, Felix has a proposal what to do about online harassment. Quite possibly, it is a terrible idea.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We’re Back! | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370049/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix, Mihir, and Youngme kick off a new season of After Hours with a host of random questions, including: Are we witnessing the slow death of Facebook? Does Adam Neumann (WeWork) deserve a second chance? Is the War for Talent real? Plus, thoughts on everything from Serena, to Kim Kardashian, to House of the Dragon, and more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Mega-Recommendations Episode for the Summer | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370050/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme joins Felix and Mihir to offer recommendations for the summer on things to read and watch, places to visit, food to eat, and lots more!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Are we witnessing a sharp decrease in income inequality? And: Why is Mihir watching inventory levels? | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370051/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 13:53:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370051/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Felix and Mihir discuss stories they will follow this summer. These include the fate of neobanks, credit conditions in the United States, a major advance in AI, as well as changes in income inequality. Plus, Mihir makes a major prediction how founders will spend their time now that the stock market has imploded.
Our predictions: https://www.lapecorabianca.com/ and https://www.airalo.com/
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to fix commuting and the legacy of Sheryl Sandberg | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370052/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 16:32:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix, Mihir and Sarah discuss how to fix commuting and the legacy of Sheryl Sandberg. Transcript</description></item><item><title>Index investing and the future of airline mergers | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370053/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370053/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the latest episode, Felix and Mihir discuss the potential dark side of the rise of index investing and who should end up owning Spirit Airlines, JetBlue or Frontier.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Super-Sized Edition | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370054/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370054/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this super-sized episode, Felix and Mihir are rejoined by their friend Youngme to discuss everything from Magical Thinking to Elon Musk. Recommendations:
Slow Horses (Apple)
Old Enough (Netflix)
Copykat.com
Supercook.com
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Time to Panic? | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370055/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 17:06:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix and Mihir discuss the turmoil in financial markets and how best to respond as an investor or a corporate executive. Is it time to panic? What is the longer-term outlook for the economy? Will the Federal Reserve be able to tame inflation without causing a recession? They also discuss the fate of Upstart, an AI-supported lending platform. The former Wall Street darling lost much of its value, seemingly overnight.</description></item><item><title>Managing the Chip Shortage and the Future of Ride Sharing | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370056/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 11:43:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370056/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Felix, Mihir and Charlotte discuss what countries and companies should do about the chip shortage and discuss the future of Uber, Lyft and Doordash.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ring the Bell? | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370057/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 18:04:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370057/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Sarah, Felix and Mihir discuss startups that piqued their interest. Bet there are some names you have not heard of? Who will go public first? Who is doomed to fail? Also: Mihir’s CRY for help.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is the four-day work week ever going to happen? | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370058/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 15:04:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Should you bet on a four-day work week? Felix, Mihir, and Sarah discuss the sports betting industry and the future of the work week.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is this the end of globalization? | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370059/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 10:32:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix, Mihir and Stephanie Mehta debate if we are witnessing the end of an era, the slow but steady demise of globalization. We also discuss the future of Zoom. With its stock sharply down and growth slowing, will the star of the COVID period have to sell itself to survive?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Vibe Economy and Amazon Moves into Space | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370060/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix, Mihir and guest host Stephanie Mehta discuss the recent spate of companies going public without profits and what Amazon’s moves into space mean for their competitors and consumers.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Unionization Makes a Comeback! Really? | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370061/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix, Mihir and The Economist’s Charlotte Howard discuss the return of Howard Schultz to Starbucks. Can he win over a restive workforce and suppress recent unionization efforts at the company? We also debate the recent uptick in drug use at work. Is this the return of the Mad Men?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Will the SEC and Disclosure Solve the Climate Crisis and Further Divide the China and the US? | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370062/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 17:56:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370062/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Felix and Mihir are joined by Charlotte Howard of the Economist and discuss the impact of new disclosure rules for geopolitical relations between China and the U.S. and the future of climate. Are these changes fundamental to the future of climate and the world, window dressing, or a manifestation of deeper problems?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to Fight Fake News | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370063/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 10:55:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix, Mihir and Sarah Green Carmichael debate how to best fight misinformation. What is the role of liability? Can we leave the battle against fake news in the hands of the internet platforms? Can we fact-check our way out of this crisis? The three hosts also discuss the corporate withdrawal from Russia.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The War in Ukraine | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370064/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 15:01:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370064/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this bonus episode, Felix and Mihir welcome back their colleague and friend Rawi Abdelal to discuss the origins of the conflict, the effects of the sanctions, and how the situation might evolve. Transcript</description></item><item><title>Let’s Talk About Your Salary, Shall We? | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370065/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sarah, Felix and Mihir discuss the new laws that require greater salary transparency. Is this a good idea? Will pay increase or decrease as a result? Who will benefit most? We also debate the surge in activist investing. Why do activists now resemble private equity investors?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Peloton, the Fitness Industry, and Microsoft's Acquisition of Activision | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370066/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370066/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is the future of Peloton and the fitness industry? And, what should we make of Microsoft’s proposed acquisition of Activision? On this episode, we welcome Sarah Greene Carmichael and discuss these developments.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Future of Mobility and Economic Lessons from the Pandemic | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370067/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370067/</guid><description>Podcast Description What are the most exciting companies and development in mobility today? What have we learned about how to provide income support during economic downturns? Mihir and Felix discuss the evidence from the pandemic and consider today's most exciting mobility solutions.
Our recommendations are:
The Anomaly
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is the Great Resignation real? | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370068/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix and Mihir debate the state of the labor market. Is the Great Resignation real? Are we confused about the data? We also discuss earnings releases that caught our eye: Time to flee fintech? UPS anyone?
Recent picks:
Checks and Balance (podcast): Left Side Story
Gary Shteyngart (book): Our Country Friends: A Novel
Jennifer Senior (article): It’s Your Friends Who Break Your Heart
This American Life (podcast): The Trojan Horse Affair</description></item><item><title>Our Predictions for 2022! | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370069/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Felix and Mihir share their predictions for 2022! Join them as they share their predictions about everything ranging from cryptocurrencies to Oscar winners…
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
Mo Amer (Netflix)
Whale Wisdom (website)
The Remarkable Tablet (digital writing tablet)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Our Year-End Award Episode! | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370070/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Felix and Mihir look back on 2021 and share their picks for Business Person of the Year, Story of the Year, Trend of the Year, and Buzzword of the Year!
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
Uma Ali (Felix’s Person of the Year) Sunday's Illness (Netflix)
The Beatles: Get Back (documentary)
Putting It Together (James Lapine)
The White Lotus (HBO)
Hacks (HBO)
The Queen’s Gambit (Netflix)
Succession (HB0)</description></item><item><title>The Future of Twitter and GE | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370071/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 13:26:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix and Mihir contemplate the future of Twitter and GE as Jack Dorsey leaves Twitter and GE splits into three separate companies. What do these events tell us about these companies and this moment? Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
The Premier League
Ronald Sullivan on the Rittenhouse Verdict
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Holiday Travel Headaches! | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370072/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 19:09:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Felix and Mihir invite their friend and colleague, Professor Ryan Buell, onto the show to discuss the travel headaches experienced by air travelers and hotel visitors. What’s behind all of the disruptions, and when will things get better?
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
AirPass (American Airlines) PassPlus (United Airlines)
Elite Status Matching (The Points Guy)
The Misery Map (FlightAware website)
The Book of Awesome (Neil Pasricha)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Food Episode! | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370073/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Felix and Mihir talk all things food, including TikTok recipes going viral, the chicken sandwich wars between fast food chains, the proliferation of milk alternatives in the supermarket, OpenTable vs. Resy, and more!
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
Burnt Toast and Other Disasters (Cal Peternell)
Opopop (popcorn)
Meringue Cookies (recipe) Pete Wells reviews Eleven Madison Park (The New York Times)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Can Hertz turn it around? Are Crocs back? Plus, Are Generational Stereotypes Fair? | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370074/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Felix and Mihir discuss whether Hertz can make a comeback, why everyone seems to be wearing Crocs, and whether generational stereotypes are accurate or helpful.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
My Climate (website)
Notability (app)
In Case You Get Hit By A Bus (Abby Schneiderman and Adam Seifer) Transcript</description></item><item><title>Intel Attempts a Turnaround; Plus Zillow, Utopian Cities, and More | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370075/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 12:53:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Felix and Mihir discuss Intel’s attempts to stage a turnaround in the all-important chip industry; plus Zillow, utopian cities, and more.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
· Izipizi Eyewear
· Far Flung: A Black Utopia in North Carolina (podcast)
· A History of Future Cities (Daniel Brook)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Much Should We Fear Inflation? Plus, The Meta Rebrand and More | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370076/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Felix and Mihir discuss how fearful we should be about inflation; they also discuss the Facebook rebranding (Meta) and the prospects for Snap.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
Kottke.org
The French Dispatch (Wes Anderson)
Patagonia Provisions
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is Netflix winning the Streaming Wars? | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370077/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 12:18:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Felix and Mihir discuss the long-term sustainability of Netflix’s content strategy; plus content trends in streaming.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
Summer of Soul (Questlove)
The Velvet Underground (Apple TV+)
Beethoven x The AI Project (YouTube)
Have We Already Been Visited By Aliens? (The New Yorker)
Extraterrestrial: The First Sign of Intelligent Life Beyond Earth (Avi Loeb)
We invite you to email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: afterhours@hbs.</description></item><item><title>Nike, Walmart, and Costco Defying the Odds, plus Letters from Listeners | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370078/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Felix and Mihir discuss how legacy retailers like Nike, Walmart and Costco have managed to defy the odds and outperform expectations, despite an onslaught of fresh competition. They also respond to more letters from listeners, including questions about President Biden’s $3.5 trillion spending plan and more. Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
The Rescue (National Geographic documentary)
Seinfeld (Netflix)
Weeds (Netflix)
The Best Tinned Fish
We invite you to email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: afterhours@hbs.</description></item><item><title>Rivian Electric Vehicles, Duolingo, Gingko Bioworks, Moderna, Unicorn Valuations, Facebook, and More | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370079/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 11:23:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Felix, and Mihir discuss the red hot IPO market, highlighting a few of the companies reflecting a “sign of the times” including: Rivian Automotive, Duolingo, and life science companies like Gingko Bioworks and Moderna. They also answer a few letters from listeners, including questions about the soaring valuations of private company unicorns, the latest Facebook scandal, and more.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
· Private Company Unicorns (Crunchbase)</description></item><item><title>The Global Housing Crisis, Amazon’s Newest Employee Benefit, Women Outpacing Men in College Enrollments, Carbon Capture Goes Online, and More | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370080/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 12:28:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Housing prices are on the rise in cities all around the world, and Youngme, Felix and Mihir discuss whether there’s an end in sight. Plus they discuss other headlines, including: Amazon’s decision to start paying for college tuition for its workers; women outpacing men in college enrollments; the first major carbon capture facility going online; and more.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
· Ministry for the Future (Kim Stanley Robinson)</description></item><item><title>Why Are Shelves Still Empty? Supply Chain Woes, plus Other Economic Takeaways from the Pandemic | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370081/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why are items still missing from grocery store shelves? Why are package deliveries being delayed? Youngme, Felix and Mihir unpack the global supply chain mess, while warning listeners to start their holiday shopping early! They also share their personal economic takeaways from the pandemic.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
· The White Lotus (HBO)
· Flour Water Salt Yeast (by Ken Forkish)
We invite you to email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: afterhours@hbs.</description></item><item><title>Has Apple Peaked? Plus, Celebrities Changing Hollywood | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370082/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370082/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been 10 years since the death of Steve Jobs. Has Apple peaked after 10 years of Tim Cook’s leadership or is the best yet to come? Youngme, Felix and Mihir debate the prospects for Apple; they then discuss the celebrities changing the way Hollywood does business, including Reese Witherspoon, Rihanna, and more.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
· Google Lens (App)
· PictureThis (Botanist in your pocket App)</description></item><item><title>China Cracks Down, Fox Launches a Weather Channel, Visa Buys an NFT, and More | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370083/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 12:51:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Mihir and Felix talk about how to make sense of China’s crackdown on industries ranging from Big Tech to Videogaming. They also share thoughts on other stories in the news, including people behaving badly on planes, Fox launching a Weather Channel, Visa buying an NFT, and Boston Dynamics’ latest robot video.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
· Boston Dynamics Robots in Action
· What Bobby McIlvane Left Behind (by Jennifer Senior in The Atlantic)</description></item><item><title>We’re Back! Our Summer Round-Up | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370084/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Mihir, and Felix discuss some of the biggest stories from the summer, including their thoughts on the Robinhood IPO, what’s going on in the current labor market, whether the Olympics matter anymore, Simone Biles, and more.
Tina (HBO Max documentary on Tina Turner)
Quartr (Investor Relations App)
Tillamook Ice Cream
Beautiful Trampoline Art (Yoann Bourgeois et Rachid Ouramdane)
Trampoline Parks
You can visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.com. You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Season 4 Finale: Stories We’re Watching This Summer and a Mega-Round of Recommendations | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370085/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 13:40:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme , Mihir , Felix , Rebecca , and Rawi share the stories they will be watching this summer, before doing a mega-round of recommendations for things to read, watch, listen, and do. Each week, the hosts give their recommendations for reading, watching, and more. Here are This Week’s Picks:
After Hours T-Shirts (by Moon Girl Landing)
@timotechanut (Tik Tok)
Space Visualization
Muscle Wiki
Future Me
Long Distance Footpaths in England, Wales, and Scotland</description></item><item><title>United States–Russia Relations and YOLO! | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370086/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 13:50:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mihir , Rawi , and Felix debate whether or not the U.S. pays too much attention to Russia, a relatively small economy without important trade relations. They also try to make sense of YOLO (you only live once). Are we becoming too narcissistic?
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
“Dustland” (The Killers)
“The Rise and Fall of Carlos Ghosn” (HBR IdeaCast)
El Yucateco Black Label Reserve Chile Habanero (Hot sauce)
Clarkson’s Farm (Amazon Prime Video)
You can visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.</description></item><item><title>Naomi Osaka and the G7’s Global Minimum Tax | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370087/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 13:56:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rawi and Mihir discuss Naomi Osaka’s departure from the French Open and the G7’s effort to cooperate on corporate taxation.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
“Loki“
International Spy Museum and Spyscape
Dwight Garner’s Garner’s Quotations
You can visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.com. You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.com. You can follow Youngme, Mihir, Rebecca, and Rawi on Twitter at: @YoungmeMoon, @DesaiMihirA, @RebeccaReCap, and @RawiAbdelal.</description></item><item><title>Old Habits and New Rituals (with Mike Norton) | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370088/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 13:47:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme and Felix invite their friend and bestselling author, Harvard Business School professor Mike Norton , to discuss the old habits and new rituals we have formed over the past year, during the pandemic.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
Pique (an app to spur curiosity)
“Inside Baseball” (an episode from the podcast, The Uncertain Hour)
[How to Change](https://www.amazon.com/How-Change-Science-Getting-Where-ebook/dp/B08KPFPSNS/ref=sr11?dchild=1&amp;amp;keywords=how+to+change&amp;amp;qid=1622853151&amp;amp;sr=8-1) (Katy Milkman)
You can visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.com. You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>The Shopping Episode: Retail Trends We’re Watching | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370089/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 13:53:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme , Mihir , and Felix share their shopping habits and the retail trends they’re keeping an eye on.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
S’more Recipe (Epicurious.com)
Herb Gardens
Shabaka Hutchings (jazz artist)
You can visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.com. You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.com. You can follow Youngme, Mihir, Rebecca, and Rawi on Twitter at: @YoungmeMoon, @DesaiMihirA, @RebeccaReCap, and @RawiAbdelal.</description></item><item><title>Diversity and Inclusion in the Workplace (with Frances Frei) | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370090/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 13:55:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme and Felix invite their friend and celebrated author, consultant, and Harvard Business School professor Frances Frei , to discuss the challenges of bringing true diversity and inclusion into the workplace. Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
Scribble (a virtual collaborative whiteboard)
The Man Who Sold His Skin (movie)
Rad Power Bikes (electric bikes)
You can visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.com. You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Raising the Capital Gains Tax, and Creating Better Simpler Strategy | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370091/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 14:47:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme , Mihir , and Felix debate whether it makes sense to raise the capital gains tax. They also discuss how companies can create better and more creative competitive strategies – the topic of Felix’s new book, [Better Simpler Strategy](https://www.amazon.com/Better-Simpler-Strategy-Value-Based-Exceptional/dp/B08Y639VC9/ref=sr13?dchild=1&amp;amp;keywords=better+simpler+strategy&amp;amp;qid=1621186962&amp;amp;sr=8-3).
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
Better Simpler Strategy (Felix Oberholzer-Gee)
[Making Great Strategy](https://www.amazon.com/Making-Great-Strategy-Organizational-Advantage/dp/0231199481/ref=sr12?crid=1ZQLDE65RDK4F&amp;amp;dchild=1&amp;amp;keywords=making+great+strategy+arguing+for+organizational+advantage&amp;amp;qid=1621187182&amp;amp;sprefix=making+great+strategy%2Caudible%2C257&amp;amp;sr=8-2) (Jesper B. Sorensen and Glenn Carroll)
The Department of Salad (newsletter by Emily Nunn)
You can visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.</description></item><item><title>Earnings Roundup: Crocs, Danone, PayPal, and More | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370092/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 14:37:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is Danone an example of failed stakeholder capitalism? Why did Zynga acquire Chartboost?
Rebecca , Rawi, and Felix discuss earnings and the recent performance of Crocs, Danone, PayPal, HelloFresh, BP, and Zynga.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
Max Richter (composer)
“Super Natural Simple” (by Heidi Swanson)
Ponzu
You can visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.com. You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.com. You can follow Youngme, Mihir, Rebecca, and Rawi on Twitter at: @YoungmeMoon, @DesaiMihirA, @RebeccaReCap, and @RawiAbdelal.</description></item><item><title>Biden’s Climate Change Plan and Europe’s Super League | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370093/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 14:01:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Will President Biden’s plan to cut greenhouse gas emissions by 50 percent in the next decade make a real difference? Rebecca , Rawi , and Felix discuss the parts of the plan that are most likely to be implemented and how U.S. climate change policy will influence global efforts to slow climate change. Plus, they debate why the idea for a European soccer Super League failed in spectacular fashion.</description></item><item><title>The Art of Negotiation | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370094/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 14:01:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme , Mihir , and Felix invite their friend and negotiations expert, Harvard Business School professor Deepak Malhotra , to discuss the art of negotiation, as well as his new science fiction novel, The Peacemaker’s Code.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
The Peacemaker’s Code (Deepak Malhotra)
[The Spy and the Traitor](https://www.amazon.com/Spy-Traitor-Greatest-Espionage-Story-ebook/dp/B0782X9PFP/ref=sr11?dchild=1&amp;amp;keywords=the+spy+and+the+traitor&amp;amp;qid=1619273204&amp;amp;sr=8-1) (Ben Macintyre)
Arrival (movie)
Stories of Your Life and Others (Ted Chiang)
The United States vs. Billie Holiday (Hulu)
neeva.</description></item><item><title>The Future of Substack and Amazon’s Failed Union Effort | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370095/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 13:59:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is the newsletter platform Substack the new media wunderkind or a flash in the pan? What can we learn from the failed effort to unionize Amazon workers in Alabama?
Rebecca , Mihir , and Felix debate how Substack might change news consumption and competition for talented writers. Plus, they examine why the Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union failed to unionize an Amazon warehouse in Alabama.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:</description></item><item><title>CEOs Speak Out on Politics and the Future of Digital Currencies | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370096/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 14:13:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rawi , Rebecca , and Mihir discuss how and why CEOs are speaking out on politics and what China’s digital renminbi means for economics and politics.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
Fela Kuti
Line of Duty (Amazon Prime)
[Will in the World](https://www.amazon.com/Will-World-Shakespeare-Became-Anniversary/dp/0393352609/ref=sr11?dchild=1&amp;amp;keywords=will+in+the+world&amp;amp;qid=1618336227&amp;amp;sr=8-1) (Stephen Greenblatt)
You can visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.com. You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.com. You can follow Youngme, Mihir, Rebecca, and Rawi on Twitter at: @YoungmeMoon, @DesaiMihirA, @RebeccaReCap, and @RawiAbdelal.</description></item><item><title>The Future of Restaurants, Take-Out, and More | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370097/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 14:07:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme , Mihir , and Felix discuss the future of food delivery, ghost kitchens, virtual restaurant brands, and more.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
Ice Cream Makers
My Mister (Netflix)
Nomadland (Jessica Bruder)
You can visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.com. You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.com. You can follow Youngme, Mihir, Rebecca, and Rawi on Twitter at: @YoungmeMoon, @DesaiMihirA, @RebeccaReCap, and @RawiAbdelal.</description></item><item><title>Our Wellness Episode | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 13:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme , Mihir , and Felix discuss the wellness trends they love, hate, and aren’t quite sure about – from the fitness wars to touchless spas and more. Plus, they share their personal wellness habits and hacks.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
Counterpart (Amazon Prime Video)
The Bureau (Amazon Prime Video)
Klara and the Sun (Kazuo Ishiguro novel)
You can visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.com. You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>The NFT Craze and the Future of Spotify and Streaming Music | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370099/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 13:54:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme , Mihir , and Felix discuss the hype surrounding NFTs (non-fungible tokens). They also dig into recent music industry trends and what they mean for the future of Spotify and other streaming players.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
Counterpart (Amazon Prime Video)
The Bureau (Amazon Prime Video)
Klara and the Sun (Kazuo Ishiguro novel)
You can visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.com. You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>The Shecession and the Meaning of Harry and Meghan | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370100/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 14:04:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why did the Covid-19 recession affect women disproportionately and what can we do about it? Plus, what might Oprah’s recent interview with Harry and Meghan tell us about the future of the monarchy?
Rebecca , Rawi , and Mihir discuss the impacts of the pandemic recession on women and why the Harry and Meghan interview was so mesmerizing.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
The Good Place
Last Chance U
Turkish Get-up
You can visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.</description></item><item><title>Mandatory Vaccinations and the Big Freeze in Texas | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370101/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 14:03:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Should businesses require their employees to get vaccinated before they can return to work? Rebecca , Mihir , Rawi , and Felix debate the pros and cons of mandatory vaccinations. They also discuss why the energy market in Texas failed during a recent winter storm and how best to encourage investments in infrastructure resilience.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
Jeffrey Eugenides quote (Fresh Complaint: Stories)
Anouar Brahem
Radiolab: “Facebook’s Supreme Court”
Codenames
You can visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.</description></item><item><title>The New U.S. Stimulus Package and the Meaning of Brexit | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370102/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 13:02:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Does the U.S. economy need more help right now, and is the latest stimulus package well designed for the moment? Plus, Brexit has fully arrived – what happens next?
Felix , Rawi , and Mihir discuss the new $1.9 trillion stimulus package in the U.S. and the departure of the UK from the European Union.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
“The Most Comprehensive List of Film Festivals on the Internet” (New York Film Academy)
Remote physical therapy (Kevin Wagner)
“Ratatouille” (movie and musical)
You can visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.</description></item><item><title>The Future of WFH and Competing Against the Giant Internet Platforms | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370103/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 13:49:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme , Mihir , Felix , and Rawi discuss whether companies should allow employees to work from home permanently. They also debate whether it’s possible for small players to compete against the giant internet platforms.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
Give Directly (charity)
Minari (movie)
Whereabouts: A novel (Jhumpa Lahiri)
You can visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.com. You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Companies We’re Watching: Affirm, Patagonia, Clubhouse, and More! | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370104/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 13:54:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme , Mihir , and Felix discuss companies they’re keeping an eye on, including fintech lender Affirm, outdoor clothing brand Patagonia, social media app Clubhouse, and one that may surprise you.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
Lupin (Netflix)
Call My Agent (Netflix)
Made Me Smile (subreddit)
Oddly Satisfying (subreddit)
Laderach Global Locations (chocolate)
You can visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.com. You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Bezos Steps Down as Amazon’s CEO and Raising the Minimum Wage | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370105/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 14:04:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370105/</guid><description>Podcast Description What are Jeff Bezos’s most significant accomplishments at Amazon? What’s troubling about the business that he built? Rebecca , Rawi , and Felix look back at Jeff Bezos’s career.
They also discuss the proposal to increase the federal minimum wage in the U.S. to $15. Would we really see more unemployment?
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
“All We Can Save: Truth, Courage, and Solutions for the Climate Crisis” (Ayana Elizabeth Johnson)
“The Everything Store: Jeff Bezos and the Age of Amazon” (Brad Stone)
“Postcards From Italy” cover (Florence &amp;amp; The Machine)
Visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.</description></item><item><title>Tesla and Bitcoin: Are You a Believer? | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370106/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 14:14:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme , Mihir , and Rawi discuss Tesla as the competition gets heated in the electric vehicle market. They also discuss how to make sense of the bitcoin craze.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
KenKen founder documentary (New Yorker documentary)
Spelling Bee (New York Times puzzle)
Derek DelGaudio’s In &amp;amp; Of itself (Hulu)
Apollonia Poilane Cookbook (for the Punition cookie recipe)
Visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.com. Email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode: GameStop Traders Rock the Financial Industry | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370107/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 14:33:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme , Mihir , and Rawi share their thoughts on how a group of individual investors went head-to-head with Wall Street hedge funds, pushing up GameStop’s stock price and raising questions for the entire financial industry.
Visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.com. Email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.com. Follow Youngme, Mihir, Rebecca, and Rawi on Twitter at: @YoungmeMoon, @DesaiMihirA, @RebeccaReCap, and @RawiAbdelal.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Google’s Dominance, and Smart Cities | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370108/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 13:37:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is Google so successful because it excels at building incredibly smart products? Or is it dominant in many markets because it stifles innovation and abuses its market power, as several antitrust lawsuits allege?
Rebecca, Mihir, and Felix discuss the merits of recent antitrust actions against the search giant. They also debate the promise of smart cities, and why Cisco and Google pulled back from their smart-city initiatives. Should we stop dreaming of living in smarter cities?</description></item><item><title>PACs and SPACs! | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370109/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 15:19:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Were corporations right to stop political giving in a targeted way after the violence at the U.S. Capitol, and what is going on with SPACs?
Felix , Rebecca , and Mihir discuss the role corporations should play in politics and debate the merits of special purpose acquisition companies (SPACs) as an alternative to the broken IPO process.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
OpenSecrets.org
FollowTheMoney.org
War: How Conflict Shaped Us
Garlic Herb Butter Roast Chicken recipe
You can visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.</description></item><item><title>Big Tech Bans, and the Alleged Russian Hacking | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370110/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 14:01:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme , Felix , and Rawi discuss Twitter and Facebook banning Trump from their platforms, as well as Apple, Google, and Amazon banning the Parler app. They also discuss the alleged Russian hacking of U.S. government and military systems.
You can visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.com. You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.com. You can follow Youngme, Mihir, Rebecca, and Rawi on Twitter at: @YoungmeMoon, @DesaiMihirA, @RebeccaReCap, and @RawiAbdelal.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode: Reflections on the Tumult in Washington D.C. | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370111/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 02:16:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370111/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this bonus episode, Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , Mihir Desai , and Rebecca Henderson share their thoughts and reflections on the violence at the U.S. Capitol.
You can visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.com. You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.com. You can follow Youngme, Mihir, Rebecca, and Rawi on Twitter at: @YoungmeMoon, @DesaiMihirA, @RebeccaReCap, and @RawiAbdelal.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Year-End Mega-Episode! Our Predictions for 2021 | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370112/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 14:30:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , and Mihir Desai invite their new co-hosts, Harvard Business School professors Rebecca Henderson and Rawi Abdelal , onto the show to share their predictions for 2021, covering everything from business to politics to fashion.
You can visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.com. You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.com. You can follow Youngme, Mihir, Rebecca, and Rawi on Twitter at: @YoungmeMoon, @DesaiMihirA, @RebeccaReCap, and @RawiAbdelal.</description></item><item><title>We’re Back! Our Reflections on 2020 | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370113/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 14:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370113/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this first episode of Season 4, Youngme, Felix, and Mihir share their reflections on 2020 and discuss what they learned from the pandemic. They also offer their recommendations for what to watch, read, and do over the holiday break.
To join the After Hours mailing list, click here: After Hours Sign-Up. You can visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.com. You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Season 3 Finale: Stories to Watch This Summer and Summer Recommendations | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370114/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 13:54:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370114/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this final episode of the season, Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , and Mihir Desai discuss the stories they’ll be watching this summer, including how businesses will re-open. They also offer an extended set of recommendations for watching, reading, and other projects during the summer months.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
White Lines (Netflix)
Space Force (Netflix)
Dark (Netflix)
Terrace House (Netflix)
Delhi Crime (Netflix)
Money Heist (Netflix)
The Bureau (Sundance Now)
Midnight Diner: Tokyo Stories (Netflix)
Gomorrah (Netflix)
The Last Panthers (Amazon Video)
Escape: A Mansion of Thieves (A virtual escape room, by Nick Huntington Klein)
“The Memory Police” (Yoko Ogawa)
“The Enlightenment of the Greengage Tree” (Shokoofeh Azar)
“Hidden Valley Road” (Robert Kolker)
“On Earth We’re Briefly Gorgeous” (Ocean Vuong)
“The Glass Hotel” (Emily St.</description></item><item><title>Earnings Reports from Apple and Facebook, and Warning Signs for Uber and Lyft | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370115/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 14:06:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , and Mihir Desai debate what they’ve learned from first quarter earnings reports from Apple, Facebook, and others. They also discuss warning signs for Uber and Lyft, and share their thoughts about the recession.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
“The Complete Robuchon” (Joel Robuchon)
Chef Gabrielle Hamilton’s Story in the New York Times
The Mind of a Chef: Gabrielle Hamilton (PBS)
Home Pasta (Bon Appetit)
Listeners are invited to join our mailing list by signing up here: After Hours Sign-Up.</description></item><item><title>Companies and Consumers Show Their True Colors During the Crisis | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370116/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 14:16:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , and Mihir Desai discuss how companies, industries, and consumers are revealing their true colors during the Covid-19 crisis.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
The Barnes Foundation
Walker Art Museum
The Palace Museum
The Last Dance (ESPN)
Dutch Baby (recipe)
Listeners are invited to join our mailing list by signing up here: After Hours Sign-Up. You can visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.com. You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Apple and Google Team Up for Contact Tracing, and the Federal Reserve’s Rescue Plan | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370117/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 14:05:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , and Mihir Desai debate Apple and Google’s Covid-19 contact tracing plan. They also discuss the Federal Reserve, which has taken a series of unprecedented actions to prop up the economy.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
Wallander (TV Show)
Khan Academy
Songlines (World Music site)
Listeners are invited to join our mailing list by signing up here: After Hours Sign-Up. You can visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.</description></item><item><title>Predictions for the New Normal | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370118/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 14:25:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , and Mihir Desai debate how the world will be changed by coronavirus. Their predictions for the “new normal” span healthcare, education, the sharing economy, working from home, and more.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
Andrea Bocelli Live Concert
“Shadow” (Netflix)
Only Connect (British Quiz Show)
Listeners are invited to join our mailing list by signing up here: After Hours Sign-Up. You can visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode: Reimagining Capitalism (with Rebecca Henderson) | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370119/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 14:06:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix Oberholzer-Gee welcomes a guest to the podcast, Harvard Business School professor Rebecca Henderson, who argues that capitalism needs to be reimagined in light of the urgency associated with climate change.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
“Reimagining Capitalism in a World on Fire” (by Rebecca Henderson)
About Rebecca Henderson
Listeners are invited to join our mailing list by signing up here: After Hours Sign-Up. You can visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.</description></item><item><title>Standout Companies and Breakout Phenomena | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370120/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 16:15:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , and Mihir Desai discuss companies that are standing out during the coronavirus crisis, including Zoom and World Central Kitchen (founded by Chef José Andrés‎). They also discuss breakout phenomena associated with the widespread shutdown.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
Just Capital
“The Korean Clusters” (Reuters)
World Central Kitchen
“Spillover” (David Quammen)
Podcast about Spillover (Scientific American
“From Bats to Human Lungs, the Evolution of a Coronavirus” (Carolyn Kormann, The New Yorker)
DonorsChoose.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode: Letters from Listeners | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370121/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 15:19:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Listeners around the world write in to ask questions and share their experiences of Covid-19 with Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , and Mihir Desai.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
Li Ziqi: Watch Her Make Beer
Bon Appetit YouTube Channel
Netflix Party (Chrome Extension)
To join our mailing list, click here: After Hours Sign-Up. Visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.com. Email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>The Varying International Responses to Covid-19, and the U.S. Stimulus Package | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370122/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 15:01:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix Oberholzer-Gee and Mihir Desai discuss how and why countries have differed in their responses to Covid-19, with a particular emphasis on their public health and economic responses. They also debate whether or not the recent U.S. stimulus package, including the bailouts, is designed appropriately.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
The Institute for Health Metrics and Evaluation
“Tiger King” (Netflix)
To join our mailing list, click here: After Hours Sign-Up.</description></item><item><title>The Housing Crisis, and Helping Renters During the Pandemic | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370123/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 19:51:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370123/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , and Mihir Desai discuss the housing crisis and what the coronavirus pandemic means for renters, in particular.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
The NerdWallet Refinance Calculator
“The Death and Life of Great American Cities” (Jane Jacobs)
To join our mailing list, click here: After Hours Sign-Up. Visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.com. Email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode: Coronavirus News and Industry Bailouts | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370124/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 15:42:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370124/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this bonus episode, Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , and Mihir Desai discuss the latest coronavirus news, debate whether the airlines deserve a bailout, and share some of their personal reflections on the crisis.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
Brian Eno
STAT News
To join our mailing list, click here: After Hours Sign-Up. Visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.com. Email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Reflections on the Ongoing Coronavirus Crisis | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370125/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 22:33:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon and Mihir Desai discuss the latest economic fallout from the coronavirus crisis and share some of their personal reflections from the week.
To join our mailing list, click here: After Hours Sign-Up. Visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.com. Email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.com. Follow Youngme and Mihir on Twitter at: @YoungmeMoon and @DesaiMihirA.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Making Sense of the Economic Impact of the Coronavirus | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370126/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 17:57:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , and Mihir Desai discuss the impact of the coronavirus on the economy. How alarmed should people be about swings in the stock market? Should the Federal Reserve cut interest rates further? What should be the government’s fiscal policy response?
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
Myth Busters: Busting Myths about COVID-19 (World Health Organization)
To join our mailing list, click here: After Hours Sign-Up.</description></item><item><title>Healthcare Companies We’re Watching, and Productivity Hacks | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370127/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 14:02:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , and Mihir Desai discuss some of the healthcare companies they’re keeping an eye on, before sharing their favorite productivity hacks. (Listeners are invited to join our mailing list by signing up here: After Hours Survey.)
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
Wolf Hall (Hilary Mantel)
I Lost My Body (Animated Movie)
The Great Buenos Aires Bank Heist (GQ Magazine)
Visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.</description></item><item><title>The Future of Movie Theaters, and Radical Salary Transparency | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370128/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 13:50:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , and Mihir Desai debate the future of movie theaters, as well as the controversial notion that companies should make everyone’s salary transparent to all employees. (Listeners are invited to join our mailing list by signing up here: After Hours Survey.)
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
Gramophone Classical Music Reviews
Hair Love (Animated Short)
Knives Out (movie)
Visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.com. Email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Casper and DTC Brands, Plus California’s New Freelancer Law | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370129/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 17:26:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , and Mihir Desai debate the fate of DTC brands like Casper mattresses and whether independent contractors should be classified as employees under California’s new AB5 law. (Listeners are invited to fill out the After Hours Survey.)
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
The Points Guy
Exhalation: Stories (Ted Chiang)
Visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.com. Email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus, 5G, and Earnings Season | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370130/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 15:04:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , and Mihir Desai discuss the impact of the coronavirus; the advertising hype surrounding the rollout of 5G; earnings reports from Tesla and the big banks; and what Google’s earnings tell us about YouTube.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
Wonderstruck (BBC America)
Be My Eyes (app)
97,196 Words: Essays (Emmanuel Carrere)
Visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.com. Email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Academy Awards Episode: “Parasite” and “American Factory” | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370131/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 14:09:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , and Mihir Desai celebrate Academy Awards week by discussing two of their favorite nominations: the film “Parasite” and the documentary “American Factory.”
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
Shoplifters (movie)
Disney Shorts (Disney Plus)
63 Up (documentary)
Visit our website at HarvardAfterHours.com. Email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.com. Follow Youngme and Mihir on Twitter at: @YoungmeMoon and @DesaiMihirA.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Remembering Clayton Christensen (with Harvard Business School Dean Nitin Nohria) | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370132/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 14:58:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Harvard Business School professor Clayton Christensen died January 23, 2020. Christensen, one of the world’s leading business thinkers, is remembered in this conversation with Harvard Business School Dean Nitin Nohria.
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.com. You can follow Youngme and Mihir on Twitter at: @YoungmeMoon and @DesaiMihirA.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Alcohol Trends and Super Bowl Political Advertising | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370133/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 14:17:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , and Mihir Desai mark “Dry January” by discussing trends in the alcohol industry. Then they discuss the decision by Trump and Bloomberg to purchase Super Bowl ads for their campaigns.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
HarvardAfterHours.com (website)
Google’s Transparency Report and Facebook’s Ad Library Report
ProRepublica’s Head to Head (compare voting records of congress members)
Google Maps Download
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Tabloid Edition: Fugitive Carlos Ghosn and Royal Family Drama | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370134/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 14:08:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , and Mihir Desai debate whether former Nissan executive Carlos Ghosn was justified in fleeing Japan, before discussing the British Royal Family drama and what’s next for Harry and Meghan.
Recent picks, and recommended reading/websites:
HarvardAfterHours.com (website)
Honeyland (documentary)
Little Women (movie)
Federica Fragapane (information illustrator)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.com. You can follow Youngme and Mihir on Twitter at: @YoungmeMoon and @DesaiMihirA.</description></item><item><title>Predictions for 2020 | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370135/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 14:48:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , and Mihir Desai review last year’s predictions for business, technology, politics, and culture. Then they debate their new predictions for 2020.
Some Recent Picks:
HarvardAfterHours.com (website)
Jane The Virgin (Netflix)
ROW-cub (Radio Atlas)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.com. You can follow Youngme and Mihir on Twitter at: @YoungmeMoon and @DesaiMihirA.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>2019 Awards Episode! | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370136/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 14:22:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , and Mihir Desai hand out their “awards” for 2019, including best/worst trend of the year, their sleeper award, comeback of the year, most under-reported story of the year, most over-hyped story of the year, and person of the year.
Some Recent Picks:
HarvardAfterHours.com (website)
The Man in the High Castle (Season 3, Amazon Prime Video)
Miznon
Sous Vide Cooking
“The Jungle Prince of Delhi” (New York Times article)
The Overstory (book by Richard Powers)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>The Good and Bad of Modern Airports and the End of an Era at Google | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370137/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 15:39:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , and Mihir Desai discuss the good and bad of modern airports. They also discuss the end of an era at Google/Alphabet, with the co-founders now stepping away from their operating roles.
Some Recent Picks:
Sous Vide Cooking
“The Jungle Prince of Delhi” (New York Times article)
The Overstory (book by Richard Powers)
“My 27-Hour Vacation in Singapore’s Changi Airport” (New York Times article)
HarvardAfterHours.</description></item><item><title>Under-the-Radar Companies, including OYO Hotels, Carbon Engineering, Whim, and more! | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370138/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 14:07:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370138/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , and Mihir Desai discuss some of the under-the-radar companies that they think people should be paying more attention to.
Some Recent Picks:
Dolly Parton’s America (podcast)
Ole &amp;amp; Steen
Sugarfish (restaurant)
KitchenAid Stand Mixer
Radio Garden (app and website)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.com. You can follow Youngme and Mihir on Twitter at: @YoungmeMoon and @DesaiMihirA.</description></item><item><title>The FOOD Episode! | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370139/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 14:45:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370139/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this special Thanksgiving edition taped a few days before the holiday, Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , and Mihir Desai discuss all things food, including food halls, the plastic problem, vertical farming, CBD menu sightings, culinary tourism, and fast whiskey.
Some Recent Picks:
Sugarfish (restaurant)
KitchenAid Stand Mixer
Radio Garden (app and website)
Flighty (app)
Downbeat (magazine)
Jokes Seth Can’t Tell (YouTube)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>The Launch of Disney+, the War on Billionaires, and the 4-Day Work Week | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370140/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 14:38:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , and Mihir Desai discuss several topics from a busy news week, including the launch of Disney+ (what does it mean for Netflix?), the growing public animosity towards billionaires, and proposals to move to a 4-day work week.
Some Recent Picks:
Flighty (app)
Downbeat (magazine)
Jokes Seth Can’t Tell (YouTube)
NPR Marketplace (podcast)
Catalyst cases
The Economist Audio Edition
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Biggest Money Mistakes People Make, and the Rise of the Micro-Influencer | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370141/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 14:51:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , and Mihir Desai discuss the biggest money mistakes people make when managing their personal finances. They also discuss the rise of the social media “micro-influencer.”
Some Recent Picks:
NPR Marketplace (podcast)
Catalyst cases
The Economist Audio Edition
“Agent Running in the Field” (by John Le Carre)
Big Little Lies, season 2 (HBO)
“The Meritocracy Trap” (by Daniel Markovits)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Google Buys Fitbit, and Twitter Bans Political Ads | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370142/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 14:24:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , and Mihir Desai discuss Google’s announcement that it’s buying Fitbit and what this tells us about the future of wearable computing. Later in the show, they discuss how Twitter and Facebook are handling political advertising.
Some Recent Picks:
“Agent Running in the Field” (by John Le Carre)
Big Little Lies, season 2 (HBO)
“The Meritocracy Trap” (by Daniel Markovits)
Conan O’Brien talks to Stephen Colbert (podcast, starting from 26:00)
Parasite (movie)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>TikTok, Museums, the Audio Explosion, and Other Trends in Entertainment | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370143/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 14:34:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , and Mihir Desai discuss a variety of trends from the world of entertainment — including TikTok, the resurgence of museums, the audio explosion, newspaper paywalls, spiked seltzer, entertainment genres, and binge-watching vs. appointment-viewing.
Some Recent Picks:
“The Meritocracy Trap” (by Daniel Markovits)
Conan O’Brien talks to Stephen Colbert (podcast, starting from 26:00)
Parasite (movie)
“In Hoffa’s Shadow” (by Jack Goldsmith)
“Dopesick” (by Beth Macy)
Dear White People (Netflix)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Making Sense of the China-NBA Firestorm, and Debating the Wealth Tax | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370144/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 14:13:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370144/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , and Mihir Desai try to make sense of the firestorm sparked by the NBA’s clash with China. They also debate the merits of a wealth tax of the kind proposed by Elizabeth Warren and Bernie Sanders.
Some Recent Picks:
Conan O’Brien talks to Stephen Colbert (podcast, starting from 26:00)
Parasite (movie)
“In Hoffa’s Shadow” (by Jack Goldsmith)
“Dopesick” (by Beth Macy)
Dear White People (Netflix)
1619: The Birth of American Music (podcast)
PRI’s The World (podcast)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Amazon Under Attack, and Household Financial Stress | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370145/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 14:57:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , and Mihir Desai discuss the problem of household financial stress. They also debate whether current criticisms of Amazon are justified.
Suggested Reading
“Is Amazon Unstoppable?” (Charles Duhigg, The New Yorker)
“Jeff Bezos’s Master Plan” (Franklin Foer, The Atlantic)
Some recent picks:
“In Hoffa’s Shadow” (by Jack Goldsmith)
“Dopesick” (by Beth Macy)
Dear White People (Netflix)
1619: The Birth of American Music (podcast)
PRI’s The World (podcast)
American Factory (Netflix)
Darren Brown: Secret (Broadway)
Succession (HBO)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>The Race for Space, and the Invasion of the Electric Scooters | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370146/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 14:11:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Does Space represent a real economic opportunity or are expensive endeavors like SpaceX a form of billionaire hubris? Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , and Mihir Desai discuss the Race for Space, before debating the viability of the electric scooter market in cities around the world.
Some recent picks:
1619: The Birth of American Music (podcast)
PRI’s The World (podcast)
American Factory (Netflix)
Darren Brown: Secret (Broadway)
Succession (HBO)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Apple, Facebook, Amazon, Google – Who Won the Summer? Plus, WeWork’s Fall from Grace | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370147/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 13:21:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370147/</guid><description>Podcast Description After Hours is back for Season 3! Youngme Moon , Felix Oberholzer-Gee , and Mihir Desai debate which of the Big Tech companies (Apple, Facebook, Amazon, or Google) had the best/worst summer, before digging into the WeWork saga.
Some recent picks:
American Factory (Netflix)
Darren Brown: Secret (Broadway)
Succession (HBO)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.com. You can follow Youngme and Mihir on Twitter at: @YoungmeMoon and @DesaiMihirA.</description></item><item><title>Looking Back, Looking Ahead | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370148/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 15:10:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370148/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a wrap for Season 2, as Youngme Moon, Felix Oberholzer-Gee, and Mihir Desai head off on a summer hiatus. Note to listeners: After Hours will return for Season 3 in the fall.
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.com. You can follow Youngme and Mihir on Twitter at: @YoungmeMoon and @DesaiMihirA.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Stories to Watch This Summer | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370149/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 16:07:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wrapping up Season 2, Youngme Moon, Felix Oberholzer-Gee, and Mihir Desai count down the top stories they’ll be keeping an eye on over the summer. A note for listeners: After a summer hiatus, After Hours will return for Season 3 in the fall.
Some recent picks:
Masters of Scale Live Show (podcast)
DuckDuckGo (search engine)
National Bureau of Economic Research
Ingredients: A Visual Exploration of 75 Additives and 25 Food Products (Dwight Eschliman)
Bel Canto (Ann Patchett)
Chernobyl (HBO)
Fleabag (Amazon Prime Video)
“The Best Green Salad in the World” (The New York Times)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Mailbag Episode: Questions from Listeners | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370150/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 13:52:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon, Felix Oberholzer-Gee, and Mihir Desai answer questions from listeners and end up discussing everything from the U.S.-China trade dispute to Disney, CVS Health, short-termism, and how to express an opinion persuasively.
Some recent picks:
National Bureau of Economic Research
Ingredients: A Visual Exploration of 75 Additives and 25 Food Products (Dwight Eschliman)
Bel Canto (Ann Patchett)
Chernobyl (HBO)
Fleabag (Amazon Prime Video)
“The Best Green Salad in the World” (The New York Times)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Should Vaping Among Teens Be Banned? And the Promise of Precision Medicine | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370151/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 13:49:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon, Felix Oberholzer-Gee, and Mihir Desai debate whether the FDA should crack down on teen vaping. They then discuss whether the promise of precision medicine is real or hype.
Some recent picks:
Ingredients: A Visual Exploration of 75 Additives and 25 Food Products (Dwight Eschliman)
Bel Canto (Ann Patchett)
Chernobyl (HBO)
Fleabag (Amazon Prime Video)
“The Best Green Salad in the World” (The New York Times)
Dark (Netflix series)
Mind Fixers (Anne Harrington)
Trello (organization app)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Facial Recognition Fears and Rihanna + LVMH | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370152/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 14:58:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon, Felix Oberholzer-Gee, and Mihir Desai debate the pros and cons associated with the increased use of facial recognition technology and whether San Francisco’s ban on such technology makes sense. They then discuss whether Rihanna represents the future of the world’s largest luxury conglomerate, LVMH.
Some recent picks:
Chernobyl (HBO)
Fleabag (Amazon Prime Video)
“The Best Green Salad in the World” (The New York Times)
Dark (Netflix series)
Mind Fixers (Anne Harrington)
Trello (organization app)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Debating the Sackler Family Role in the Opioid Crisis, and Using AI Bots to Conduct Job Interviews | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370153/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 15:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370153/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon, Felix Oberholzer-Gee, and Mihir Desai discuss whether pharmaceutical players like the Sackler family members should be held accountable for the current opioid crisis. They then debate the growing reliance on artificial intelligence bots by human resource departments in the job screening process.
Some recent picks:
Dark (Netflix series)
Mind Fixers (Anne Harrington)
Trello (organization app)
“The Comforting Fictions of Dementia Care” (Larissa MacFarquhar, in The New Yorker)
@BryanDruzin (Twitter account)
Knock Down the House (Netflix documentary)
Sec.</description></item><item><title>Beyond Meat, and Facebook’s Pivot to Privacy | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370154/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 16:57:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon, Felix Oberholzer-Gee, and Mihir Desai talk about the Beyond Meat IPO and whether plant-based meat alternatives like Beyond Burger and Impossible Burger will become mass-market products. They then discuss Facebook’s announcement that it is pivoting to put greater emphasis on user privacy.
For interested listeners:
“How much does animal agriculture and eating meat contribute to global warming?”
Some recent picks:
“The Comforting Fictions of Dementia Care” (Larissa MacFarquhar, in The New Yorker)
@BryanDruzin (Twitter account)
Knock Down the House (Netflix documentary)
Sec.</description></item><item><title>Quick Takes on Uber, Apple/Qualcomm, Pinterest, Brexit, and More | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370155/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 15:41:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon, Felix Oberholzer-Gee, and Mihir Desai offer short takes on six different topics, including: Uber’s S-1, Apple and Qualcomm settling their lawsuit, Pinterest’s prospects as a public company, Brexit, and the best TV shows about business.
Some recent picks:
Sec.gov (to download S-1s)
Billy Eilish
#MidtownUniform
Eater.com
Cribsheet: A Data-Driven Guide to Better, More Relaxed Parenting (Emily Oster)
Pitchfork (Music Recommendations)
Homecoming King (Hasan Minhaj on Netflix)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Disney+, Notre Dame Donations Spark a Backlash, and Mihir’s New Book! | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370156/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 16:01:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Felix, and Mihir discuss the upcoming launch of Disney’s new streaming service (Disney+), as well as the backlash sparked by billionaires pledging money to repair Notre Dame Cathedral. They then do a bonus segment about Mihir’s new book, How Finance Works.
Some recent picks:
Eater.com
Cribsheet: A Data-Driven Guide to Better, More Relaxed Parenting (Emily Oster)
Pitchfork (Music Recommendations)
Homecoming King (Hasan Minhaj on Netflix)
Delhi Crime (Netflix)
Business Insider Briefings (subscription required)
How to enjoy Game of Thrones season 8 if you haven’t seen the show (Kjerstin Johnson)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Big Tech vs. the EU, and Why Is College So Expensive? | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370157/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 14:03:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370157/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Felix, and Mihir debate the effectiveness of the European Union’s attempts to regulate Big Tech. They then discuss the reasons underlying the soaring price of college in the U.S.
Some recent picks:
Pitchfork (Music Recommendations)
Homecoming King (Hasan Minhaj on Netflix)
Delhi Crime (Netflix)
Business Insider Briefings (subscription required)
How to enjoy Game of Thrones season 8 if you haven’t seen the show (Kjerstin Johnson)
Station Eleven: A Novel (Emily St.</description></item><item><title>Has Car Ownership Peaked, and Is Joe Biden Too Physical? | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370158/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 16:13:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370158/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Felix, and Mihir discuss whether we have officially reached “peak car” — meaning can we now expect a steady decline in private car ownership? They then debate whether Joe Biden’s physical displays of affection are appropriate.
Some recent picks:
Delhi Crime (Netflix)
Business Insider Briefings (subscription required)
How to enjoy Game of Thrones season 8 if you haven’t seen the show (Kjerstin Johnson)
Station Eleven: A Novel (Emily St.</description></item><item><title>Apple’s Big Event, Plus Is Corporate Debt at a Crisis Level? | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370159/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 14:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Felix, and Mihir share their reactions to Apple’s big event announcing the launch of its new TV+ service. They then discuss whether corporate debt levels are reaching crisis potential.
Some recent picks:
Station Eleven: A Novel (Emily St. John Mandel)
How Finance Works (Mihir Desai)
Netflix Subgenre Codes
Bang Bar (New restaurant by David Chang)
Games Magazine
Museum of Failure
Episode: “Aliy” from Losers (Netflix Series)
Ash is Purest White (Movie)
Dynasties (Nature Series)
After Life (Netflix)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Peloton and Partisan Political Prejudice | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370160/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 14:58:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370160/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Felix, and Mihir debate Peloton, the high-flying exercise startup. They then discuss why partisan political prejudice is worse in some parts of the country than others.
For interested listeners:
US Countries and Partisan Prejudice (The Atlantic)
Some recent picks:
Games Magazine
Museum of Failure
Episode: “Aliy” from Losers (Netflix Series)
Ash is Purest White (Movie)
Dynasties (Nature Series)
After Life (Netflix)
Shoplifters (Movie)
Motif (Photobooks)
Hopper (App)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Food Delivery Wars and Boeing’s Crisis Management | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370161/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 16:18:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370161/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Felix, and Mihir discuss the food delivery war between DoorDash, Uber Eats, Grubhub, and others. Then they evaluate Boeing’s crisis management performance in the wake of two recent air disasters.
Some recent picks:
Reputation Rules (Daniel Diermeier)
Aloft: Thoughts on the Experience of Flight (William Langewiesche)
Stratechery (Ben Thompson, subscription required)
Ash is Purest White (Movie)
Dynasties (Nature Series)
After Life (Netflix)
Shoplifters (Movie)
Motif (Photobooks)
Hopper (App)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Airbnb, Plus Lessons from Kraft Heinz and Zero Based Budgeting | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370162/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 15:58:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370162/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Felix, and Mihir debate how well Airbnb is managing growth amid backlash from cities like New York City. They also discuss Kraft Heinz’s controversial zero-based budgeting approach to management.
Some recent picks:
Ash is Purest White (Movie)
Dynasties (Nature Series)
After Life (Netflix)
Shoplifters (Movie)
Motif (Photobooks)
Hopper (App)
Free Solo (National Geographic Documentary)
Dreyer’s English: An Utterly Correct Guide to Clarity and Style (Benjamin Dreyer)
Interesting as F*** (Reddit subreddit)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>IPO Fever, and Do Bullies Make Good Bosses? | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370163/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 17:20:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Felix, and Mihir discuss why so many high-profile companies (Uber, Lyft, Pinterest, Airbnb, Slack, Postmates, Casper, Peloton, etc.) are planning to go public this year. They also debate whether it’s acceptable for bosses to throw temper tantrums at work.
Some recent picks:
Shoplifters (Movie)
Motif (Photobooks)
Hopper (App)
Free Solo (National Geographic Documentary)
Dreyer’s English: An Utterly Correct Guide to Clarity and Style (Benjamin Dreyer)
Interesting as F*** (Reddit subreddit)
BA Magic Videos (British Airways)
General Social Survey Visualization Tool
Chef’s Knife Mac MTH-80
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Walmart’s Strategy to Beat Amazon, and Millennial Socialism | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370164/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 18:38:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370164/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Felix, and Mihir discuss how Walmart is trying to compete against Amazon and whether the strategy is working. They also debate the rise of socialism in U.S. millennials — is it a healthy phenomenon or a dangerous one?
Some recent picks:
Free Solo (National Geographic Documentary)
Dreyer’s English: An Utterly Correct Guide to Clarity and Style (Benjamin Dreyer)
Interesting as F*** (Reddit subreddit)
BA Magic Videos (British Airways)
General Social Survey Visualization Tool
Chef’s Knife Mac MTH-80
Goodbye Big Five: Life Without the Tech Giants (Kashmir Hill, for Gizmodo)
Minding the Gap (Hulu documentary)
Andy Warhol retrospective (Whitney Museum)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>WeWork, and Can the Government Really Print as Much Money as It Wants? | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370165/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 17:21:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon, Felix Oberholzer-Gee, and Mihir Desai discuss whether WeWork’s success is sustainable. Plus, can the government really spend as much money as it wants without worrying about deficits? What in the world is Modern Monetary Theory and does it actually make sense?
Some recent picks:
BA Magic Videos (British Airways)
General Social Survey Visualization Tool
Chef’s Knife Mac MTH-80
Goodbye Big Five: Life Without the Tech Giants (Kashmir Hill, for Gizmodo)
Minding the Gap (Hulu documentary)
Andy Warhol retrospective (Whitney Museum)
Cassette (app)
Seven Days Out: Ep 2: Eleven Madison Park (Netflix)
Tsutaya Bookstores (Japan)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Medicare for All, plus Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez, Amazon HQ2, Marie Kondo, Toys, Spotify and Podcasting, and More | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370166/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 19:46:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370166/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Felix, and Mihir debate Medicare for All and ask whether the U.S. healthcare system is broken. They then offer quick takes on everything from Amazon’s latest HQ2 news, Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez’s influence, Marie Kondo, the toy industry, Spotify’s aggressive push into podcasting, and more!
Some recent picks:
Goodbye Big Five: Life Without the Tech Giants (Kashmir Hill, for Gizmodo)
Minding the Gap (Hulu documentary)
Andy Warhol retrospective (Whitney Museum)
Cassette (app)
Seven Days Out: Ep 2: Eleven Madison Park (Netflix)
Tsutaya Bookstores (Japan)
Richard Brody’s Review of Roma (New Yorker)
The Tangled Tree (David Quammen)
Mary Oliver poetry
Money Heist (Netflix)
Patrick Radden Keefe’s Profile of Mark Burnett (New Yorker)
Cooking by Ear (Podcast)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Fears About Huawei, and Facebook Earnings (What We Learned) | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370167/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 17:35:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Felix, and Mihir debate U.S. fears about Huawei and implications for U.S.-China relations. They also offer their interpretation of Facebook’s latest earnings results, before sharing their After Hours picks for the week.
Some recent picks:
Richard Brody’s Review of Roma (New Yorker)
The Tangled Tree (David Quammen)
Mary Oliver poetry
Money Heist (Netflix)
Patrick Radden Keefe’s Profile of Mark Burnett (New Yorker)
Cooking by Ear (Podcast)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Taxing the Rich, and the “Woke” Advertising Trend | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370168/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 17:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Felix, and Mihir debate two of the dramatic and controversial tax ideas being proposed by Democrats (a 70% marginal income tax rate and a 2% wealth tax), before discussing the trend among brands like Gillette, Nike, and Pepsi to launch “woke” advertising campaigns. They also offer their After Hours picks for the week.
Some recent picks:
Money Heist (Netflix)
Mark Burnett profile in The New Yorker (by Patrick Radden Keefe)
Cooking by Ear (Podcast)
Salt Fat Acid Heat (Netflix)
Turing Tumble (toy)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>High CEO Churn, and the 401(k) Turns 40 | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370169/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 16:49:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Felix, and Mihir discuss why CEO departures are occurring so frequently, before unpacking the flaws in our 401(k) system. They also offer their After Hours picks for the week.
Some recent picks:
Salt Fat Acid Heat (Netflix)
Turing Tumble (toy)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.com. You can follow Youngme and Mihir on Twitter at: @YoungmeMoon and @DesaiMihirA.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Apple in China, and Payday Lending | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370170/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 20:18:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Felix, and Mihir discuss Apple’s position in the Chinese market; debate whether payday lending is good or bad for workers; and ask whether companies should be doing more to help employees manage cash shortfalls. They also offer their After Hours picks for the week.
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.com. You can follow Youngme and Mihir on Twitter at: @YoungmeMoon and @DesaiMihirA.</description></item><item><title>New Year’s Crystal Ball Episode | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370171/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 15:45:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370171/</guid><description>Podcast Description Taped a few days before heading off for the holidays, Youngme, Felix, and Mihir share their After Hours Predictions for 2019, covering everything from Big Tech, to food, to finance, to entertainment.
Some recent picks:
Hilma af Klint Exhibit (Guggenheim Museum)
Prime Suspect (Amazon Prime Video – Britbox)
Atavist Magazine
Atlanta, Season 2 (Netflix)
Bloomberg article (“Wall Street Rule for the #MeToo Era: Avoid Women At All Cost“) and Response from Jefferies CEO Richard Handler
The Value of Everything, by Mariana Mazzucato
21c Museum Hotels
The Truth As Told By Mason Buttle (by Leslie Connor)
TikTok (phone app)
Today, Explained Podcast, Nov.</description></item><item><title>2018 Awards Episode | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370172/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2018 13:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Taped a few days before heading off for the holidays, Youngme, Felix, and Mihir share their After Hours Awards for 2018, including their awards for Best/Worst Trend of the Year, Biggest Fail of the Year, Sleeper of the Year, Comeback of the Year, Work Cut Out for Them Next Year, Most Under-Reported Story of the Year, Most Over-Hyped Story of the Year, Person of the Year, and Favorite Entertainment of the Year.</description></item><item><title>Not Everyone Can Build a Digital Ad Business, Plus Debating Radical Transparency | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370173/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 15:20:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370173/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Felix, and Mihir discuss Verizon’s write-down on Oath (Yahoo, AOL) and the challenges with building a digital advertising business. They also debate the notion of Radical Transparency, before sharing their After Hours picks for the week.
Some recent picks:
Bloomberg article (“Wall Street Rule for the #MeToo Era: Avoid Women At All Cost“) and Response from Jefferies CEO Richard Handler
21c Museum Hotels
The Truth As Told By Mason Buttle (by Leslie Connor)
TikTok (phone app)
Robert Stavins (follow on Twitter)
FRED (Federal Reserve Economic Data)
RBG (Documentary on Amazon Video)
The Man in the High Castle (Amazon Video)
The Ringer website
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>The Student Debt Crisis, and the FIRE Movement | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370174/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 17:05:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370174/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Felix, and Mihir discuss staggering student debt levels, the FIRE (Financial Independence, Retire Early) Movement, and share their After Hours picks for the week.
For interested listeners:
The Basics of FIRE
Mr. Money Moustache (FIRE blog)
Some recent picks:
Today, Explained Podcast, Nov. 30 Episode (Humans 2.0)
Babylon Berlin (Netflix)
“The Prison Inside Me” (Reuters)
Robert Stavins (follow on Twitter)
FRED (Federal Reserve Economic Data)
RBG (Documentary on Amazon Video)
The Man in the High Castle (Amazon Video)
The Ringer website
Janesville (Amy Goldstein)
Airtable (software)
Small Fry (Lisa Brennan-Jobs)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Microsoft Trending Up, Apple Trending Down…? Plus, The Marriott Data Breach | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370175/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 15:35:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370175/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Felix, and Mihir debate whether Microsoft is trending up while Apple is trending down, before discussing the Marriott (Starwood) data breach. They also share their After Hours picks for the week.
Some recent picks:
Robert Stavins (follow on Twitter)
FRED (Federal Reserve Economic Data)
RBG (Documentary on Amazon Video)
The Man in the High Castle (Amazon Video)
The Ringer website
Janesville (Amy Goldstein)
Airtable (software)
Small Fry (Lisa Brennan-Jobs)
Educated (Tara Westover)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Tackling Climate Change, and Making Sense of the Nissan-Renault Drama | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370176/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 19:54:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370176/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Felix, and Mihir tackle climate change, discuss the Nissan-Renault soap opera, and share their After Hours picks for the week.
For interested listeners:
The National Climate Assessment
Some recent picks:
The Man in the High Castle (Amazon Video)
The Ringer website
Janesville (Amy Goldstein)
Airtable (software)
Small Fry (Lisa Brennan-Jobs)
Educated (Tara Westover)
Burn After Reading (Netflix)
Janelle Monae
Company (Stephen Sondheim musical)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Grading The New York Times’ News Coverage, and Quick Takes on Random Things | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370177/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 07:24:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370177/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme and Felix decide to “grade” The New York Times’ news coverage, before sharing their quick takes on other random things. They also share their After Hours picks for the week.
For interested listeners:
AG Sulzberger Interview with Kara Swisher (Recode Decode Podcast)
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.com. You can follow Youngme and Mihir on Twitter at: @YoungmeMoon and @DesaiMihirA.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Uber Prepares to Go Public, and China’s Social Credit System | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370178/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 15:00:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370178/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Mihir, and Felix discuss how much Uber is worth as it prepares to go public, before debating China’s controversial Social Credit system. They also share their After Hours picks for the week.
You can email your comments and ideas for future episodes to: harvardafterhours@gmail.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Can Netflix Keep Winning? And Why People Are Fleeing Latin America | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370179/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 19:34:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Mihir, and Felix debate whether Netflix’s success is sustainable, before trying to wrap their heads around the unthinkably high murder rate in Latin America. They also share their After Hours picks for the week.
For interested listeners:
Latin America is the Murder Capital of the World (Wall Street Journal)
You can email Youngme, Mihir, and Felix with your comments and ideas for future episodes at: harvardafterhours@gmail.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Bad is Airline Service, Really? And Other Customer Service Complaints | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370180/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 21:35:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme and Mihir welcome their colleague Ryan Buell to discuss whether airlines deserve their reputation for terrible customer service. They also share other customer service pet peeves, as well as their personal “Customer Experience Picks.”
For interested listeners:
Ryan Buell in HBR: The Parts of Customer Service That Should Never Be Automated
You can email Youngme, Mihir, and Felix with your comments and ideas for future episodes at: harvardafterhours@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Is Retail Dying? Plus, How Are Companies Spending their Tax Cuts? | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370181/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 20:33:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Mihir, and Felix discuss whether the “retailpocalypse” is real, try to figure out how companies are spending their Trump tax cuts, debate whether share buybacks are a good thing or a bad thing, and offer their picks for the week.
For interested listeners:
The future of retail? A report from Deloitte
Mihir’s take on tax reform
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Debating Minimum Wage, and Reflections on a Year of #MeToo | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370182/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 19:49:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370182/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme, Mihir, and Felix are back with Season 2 of After Hours! In this episode, they debate whether the federal minimum wage should be raised, offer their personal reflections on a year of the #MeToo movement, and share their picks for the week.
For interested listeners:
Early evidence on the $15 minimum wage, including the research cited by Felix
Slides from a recent classroom discussion Mihir led on #MeToo
Transcript</description></item><item><title>New Media and Predictive Policing | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370183/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 19:19:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370183/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Felix and Mihir explore the prospects for media outlets like Vice and Buzzfeed, discuss their thoughts on predictive policing, and offer their After Hours picks for the week.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trade and Soccer | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370184/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 20:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370184/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Mihir and Felix discuss trade, soccer, offer their After Hours picks.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Food, food, and more food! | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370185/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 20:23:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370185/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this light-hearted episode taped a couple of weeks ago, Youngme, Mihir and Felix discuss the #eatclean movement, their most/least favorite food trends, and offer their After Hours picks for the week.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The #MeToo Movement and Its Impact on Business (Live) | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370186/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 20:27:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370186/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this LIVE! episode taped in front of an audience of Harvard Business School alumni, Mihir and Youngme discuss the #MeToo Movement and its impact on business.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is the Job of the Presidency Too Big? Plus, Vaping Among Teens | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370187/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 20:30:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370187/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Youngme, Felix and Mihir debate whether the job of the presidency is too big even for the most competent of executives; discuss whether the vaping trend among teenagers should have us worried; and offer their After Hours picks for the week.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Brainstorming Gun Control Ideas, and the Affordable Housing Dilemma | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370188/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 20:33:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370188/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Youngme, Mihir and Felix brainstorm out-of-the-box ideas for gun control; discuss whether cities like Boston should be trying to attract companies like Amazon despite the affordable housing crunch created; and offer their After Hours picks for the week.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Conversation with Teens | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370189/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 20:36:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370189/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this special episode, Youngme asks three teenagers (including her own son) a set of 10 random questions that address everything from how they think about social media, to bullying in high schools, to how optimistic they are about the future.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Antitrust and Big Tech, and Is Corporate Lobbying A Good or Bad Thing? | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370190/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 20:39:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370190/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Youngme, Mihir and Felix discuss antitrust and whether we should be concerned about the size of the big tech companies; debate the propriety of corporate lobbying; and offer their After Hours Picks for the week.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why Management Practice Matters | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370191/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 23:18:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370191/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Mihir sits down with HBS economist Rafaella Sadun, who has dug deep into why and how management practices matter with award-winning large-sample empirical work. Rafaella discusses the problems and promise of family ownership, why Americans do IT better, the secrets of her productive partnership and how she came to economics, and her recommendation for a biography of a pioneering female economist.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Rise of Voice Assistants like Amazon Echo, and How to Punish Wells Fargo | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370192/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 20:59:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370192/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Youngme, Felix, and Mihir discuss why voice assistants like Amazon Echo and Google Home are all the rage; debate how to punish Wells Fargo for criminal wrongdoing; and offer their After Hours picks for the week.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Future of Newspapers, and Debating Big Tech | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370193/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 21:10:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370193/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Youngme, Felix, and Mihir discuss whether there’s a market for a Netflix for News; debate the future of newspapers like The New York Times; argue about which Big Tech company (Apple, Alphabet, Amazon, Facebook) is most and least vulnerable; and offer their After Hours picks for the week.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why They Do It: White Collar Criminals | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370194/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 23:18:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370194/</guid><description>Podcast Description Youngme Moon interviews Eugene Soltes, who talks about "Why They Do It: Inside the Mind of the White Collar Criminal." Among other things, Eugene discusses his unique relationship with Bernie Madoff, the motivations behind white collar crime, how firms can prevent such crimes from occurring, and his most memorable conversations with criminals he has interviewed. Eugene also shares an After Hours recommendation.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Gender Wage Gap, and Debating the Benefits of Retail Medicine | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370195/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 22:15:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370195/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Youngme, Felix, and Mihir debate what it would take to close the gender wage gap; discuss whether retailers like Walmart and CVS entering the medical care space is good or bad for consumers; and share their After Hours picks for the week.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Zuckerberg Faces Congress, and the Plight of the Post Office | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370196/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 22:25:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370196/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Youngme, Felix, and Mihir give their quick takes on Mark Zuckerberg’s appearance before Congress; discuss the plight of the U.S. Post Office; and share their picks for the week.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trump’s Trade War, and the Fate of Tesla | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370197/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2018 22:28:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370197/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Youngme, Felix, and Mihir vent about trade deficits and potential tariffs against China; they also debate the future of Tesla. Plus, their After Hours picks for the week.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Fixing the Culture at Uber | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370198/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 22:30:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370198/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Youngme talks to Professor Frances Frei, who was hired by Uber last year to help rebuild a broken culture. Frances describes how toxic the culture at Uber actually was and how she dealt with difficult work scenarios. She also talks about what should be done about “bad people doing bad things” and the link between strategy and culture. Plus, she gives a behind-the-scenes look at preparing for her TED talk.</description></item><item><title>How Money Can Buy Happiness | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370199/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 23:26:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370199/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Youngme talks to her friend and colleague, Professor Mike Norton, about how to spend money to create happiness. Mike's tips include spending money on experiences rather than on "stuff," "buying time," and investing in others. Youngme adds a few tips of her own.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Debating Universal Basic Income, plus Google and the Right to be Forgotten | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370200/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 23:30:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370200/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Youngme, Mihir, and Felix debate the idea of a Universal Basic Income; discuss Google and the Right to be Forgotten; and offer their After Hours picks for the week.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Making Sense of Online Reviews, Our Best/Worst Service Experiences, plus Debating the Future of Spotify | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370201/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 23:35:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370201/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Youngme, Mihir, and Felix try to make sense of online reviews, dish about their best/worst service experiences, and offer their thoughts on Spotify. Plus, their After Hours recommendations for the week.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The #NeverAgain movement, Facebook and the Russian Influence Campaign, Should Pornography Be Banned, and Oscar Picks | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370202/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 23:37:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370202/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this pilot episode, Youngme, Mihir, and Felix discuss the NRA and whether the #NeverAgain movement has a chance; disagree about Facebook and the Russian influence campaign; and debate the idea of banning pornography. Plus, they offer their After Hours recommendations for the week and reveal what movies they’re rooting for (and against) at this year’s Oscars.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Introducing After Hours | After Hours</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3926370203/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 23:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3926370203/</guid><description>Podcast Description Listen in as Harvard Business School faculty discuss hot topics at the intersection of business and society. (Trailer)
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>