<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>How Other Dads Dad with Hamish Blake on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/how-other-dads-dad-with-hamish-blake/</link><description>Recent content in How Other Dads Dad with Hamish Blake on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 17:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/how-other-dads-dad-with-hamish-blake/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Wild Rule Breaking Season 2 Finale with Dr Billy Garvey | How Other Dads Dad with Hamish Blake</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8942100001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8942100001/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s back! The episode where Hamish tears up the HODD rule book, by going over an hour AND talking to an expert. And not just any expert, but leading behavioural paediatrician at the Royal Children’s Hospital, Dr Billy Garvey. Wild, right? In the sequel to his awesome Season 1 Episode, Dr Billy has been beyond generous with his time and has picked some choice moments from Season 2 to unpack with Hame and look at the clinical evidence behind the parenting gut work.</description></item><item><title>How Ben Crowe Dads | How Other Dads Dad with Hamish Blake</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8942100002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8942100002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mindset coach to some of the world’s finest athletes, Ben Crowe reflects on his dadding journey so far. Given Ben is used to helping other people discover their story rather than delving into and analysing his own, we are really grateful to him for his openness and honesty, in what was a fascinating chat with Hame. Ben is the first to admit, like all of us, he’s continually making mistakes as a parent, and that putting all his professional knowledge into practice as a dad is far easier said than done.</description></item><item><title>How Craig Foster Dads | How Other Dads Dad with Hamish Blake</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8942100003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8942100003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Craig Foster - former Socceroo captain, legendary sports broadcaster, social justice champion… but his most important job? You guessed it… Good 'ol Dad!
As a compassionate and thoughtful leader who spends much of his time helping those who don't have a voice, Craig talks about why justice and fairness are core tenets of his and how this informs his parenting. Fozz also discusses shepherding his kids though the teenage years and the almost comical lengths he’s gone to keep a watchful eye.</description></item><item><title>How Russel Howcroft Dads | How Other Dads Dad with Hamish Blake</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8942100004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8942100004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Russel Howcroft has been talking to Australians about how they are sold things for years on the much loved TV show Gruen - Now he lets us in on the secret of how he sells things to his kids! (Hint: like any good client pitch, it’s more guiding, less telling
In a free ranging chat that follows the whims of Russ’s very active mind, he explores with Hame how his own upbringing influences the choices he now makes as a father, how he has actively fostered creativity in his kids, and why it can be scary to do so.</description></item><item><title>How Sam Wood Dads | How Other Dads Dad with Hamish Blake</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8942100005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8942100005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Health and fitness industry expert and entrepreneur Sam Wood has a beautifully honest chat with Hame about his dadding journey. From what’s like to begin your dadding with a 9 year old step daughter, to then only eight short years later having 4 daughters, Sam shares with Hame the struggles he’s had learning on the job with a teenager, how he tries to instil adventurousness and positivity into his kids each day and how the death of his mother when he was a teenager completely reframed the relationship with his own father.</description></item><item><title>How Scott Pape Dads | How Other Dads Dad with Hamish Blake</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8942100006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8942100006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Scott Pape, or perhaps as he’s better known The Barefoot Investor, has been teaching Australians about finances for almost 20 years. These days he’s also investing heavily in his 4 kids - and he’s got some great advice for all of us.
Scott tells Hame about his mantra that “These are the good ‘ol days” and explains how it helps him stay focused on what matters most to him.</description></item><item><title>How Maggie Dent Helps Dads Dad | How Other Dads Dad with Hamish Blake</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8942100007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8942100007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hold on, it’s another Wild Rule Breaking Episode, this time with an EXPERT MUM! The legendary Maggie Dent, one of Australia's most trusted voices on raising kids and helping families.
Last season, Hamish made some bold statements about not having experts on this pod, unless it’s ones he really likes, like Maggie Dent for example. Well, blow me down… Maggie got in touch and said she’d love to have a chat (and a weak almond cap with one).</description></item><item><title>How Beau Miles Dads | How Other Dads Dad with Hamish Blake</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8942100008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8942100008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adventurer, filmmaker, outdoor education specialist, dad… Beau Miles has got lots of cool descriptors. He’s also infectiously positive and creative, and he put all these things to amazing use in this very different, very outdoorsy and very wet episode.
Exactly 345 km from their respective houses, on a little island in the middle of a giant hydro lake somewhere in the snowy mountains, Hamish and Beau recorded this episode while doing some pretty unique memory making with their kids.</description></item><item><title>How Scott Cam Dads | How Other Dads Dad with Hamish Blake</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8942100009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8942100009/</guid><description>Podcast Description We all know Scott Cam from The Block, but a few years ago, some words of wisdom from Scott Cam The Dad provided Hamish with some of the inspiration to create this pod. So, we advise you to Tools Down and listen in to a dad that takes his fathering trade really seriously… especially if it involves being a bit silly. And even more so if it means blowing off school!</description></item><item><title>How Eddie Betts Dads | How Other Dads Dad with Hamish Blake</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8942100010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8942100010/</guid><description>Podcast Description He may have played 350 games of AFL - but as Eddie’s wife always reminds him - his job is only just beginning… for his kids, and for his people.
Eddie, with his wife Anna, have 5 young children, so pre-season training pales in comparison to the high contact sport of dadding that many kids. His lunch box game is elite! But as Hame learns in this fascinating chat, for Eddie, supporting a family is linked inextricably with a supportive community.</description></item><item><title>How Christian O'Connell Dads | How Other Dads Dad with Hamish Blake</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8942100011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8942100011/</guid><description>Podcast Description An old friend of Hame, and according to his daughters an old dad, Christian O’Connell is a bona fide legend of radio broadcasting. And really, he’s not even old!
In this super funny, yet super heartfelt episode, Christian uses all 19 years of his dadding experience to distil down for us some really amazing insights and advice. He’s thought about this dadding caper a lot, so from explaining his mantra of “no small moments”, to advice on how to negotiate with teenagers, Christian has put his formidable gift for communication to wonderful use for us in this episode.</description></item><item><title>How Tim Minchin Dads | How Other Dads Dad with Hamish Blake</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8942100012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8942100012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tim Minchin has created the most amazing, diverse and groundbreaking body of work. Significant to this episode is that he also co-created 2 kids with his wife, Sarah.
Tim was extremely generous to sit down with Hame and share some of his 17 years or so of dadding experiences and learnings. He explains how he tries to shepherd his kids rather than control them, his family's experience with neurodiversity and ASD, and how he applies reason, logic and in his words “anti-drama” to his dadding.</description></item><item><title>How Martin "Rac" Heppell Dads | How Other Dads Dad with Hamish Blake</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8942100013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8942100013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former teacher and assistant principal, current powerhouse of enthusiasm and expertise, Martin Heppell, or just Rac as he is known to friends, blows Hame away in this episode. Yes, there are some crazy stories, but also some amazing insights that can only be gained from spending thousands of hours helping kids to be their best. Oh, and having 3 kids of his own.
Rac comes to How Other Dads Dad care of The Resilience Project where he is one of the key facilitators, working with thousands of kids every year.</description></item><item><title>How Joe Brumm Dads | How Other Dads Dad with Hamish Blake</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8942100014/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8942100014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 2 kicks off with our top requested guest, Joe Brumm, creator of the global smash show Bluey &amp;amp; perhaps Australia’s favourite dad, Bandit Healer. More importantly, he’s also father to two children in real life.
Whether your kids are young, or now approaching adulthood themselves, the themes of Bluey are universal and timeless to us all, and Joe has managed to capture the experiences of parenting young children in a most beautiful, funny, and insightful way.</description></item><item><title>Season 2 Trailer | How Other Dads Dad with Hamish Blake</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8942100015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8942100015/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’ve finally got our act together, and we’re back, baby! Episode 1 of Season 2 drops next Friday, 25th August. But while we get the finishing touches on a few things, here is a little taste of what’s to come in Season 2. Spoiler: It’s chock full of wonderful dads, and as an extra special treat, one mega expert mum.
Next week, episode 1 kicks off with our #1 requested dad… Joe Brumm, the creator of perhaps Australia’s greatest dad, Bandit Healer, and his amazing and inexhaustible daughters Bluey and Bingo.</description></item><item><title>Wild Rule Breaking Season Finale with Dr Billy Garvey | How Other Dads Dad with Hamish Blake</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8942100016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8942100016/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a double rule breaking season finale, Hamish goes over his 1 hour &amp;amp; 3 minute episode time limit AND talks to an expert! Our special guest is Dr Billy Garvey, a Behavioural Paediatrician at the Royal Children’s Hospital (Melbourne) and leading expert on childhood development. (And he’s also a dad).
As a wonderful surprise to us, it turns out Dr. Billy has listened to some of the podcast (which made Hamish blush) and upon Hames getting in touch with Billy, he told us something really interesting… that heaps of stuff our guest dads were stumbling across or bringing up anecdotally, actually had some scientific evidence behind it.</description></item><item><title>How Mark Donaldson Dads | How Other Dads Dad with Hamish Blake</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8942100017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8942100017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Decorated soldier, Mark Donaldson VC kindly joins Hame on the HODD couch to share tales from his dadding journey so far.
Mark shares his experience of trying to be available to his kids and playing and existing in their world, even if he’d just returned from a deployment. The guys discuss the idea that all kids have “their version of trying” and the challenges of not projecting our own standards onto them (that we have probably only come to appreciate and understand in adulthood!</description></item><item><title>How Ben Lee Dads | How Other Dads Dad with Hamish Blake</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8942100018/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8942100018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Creativity and dadding combine in a fascinating chat with prolific singer songwriter, Ben Lee. After a chance meeting between Hame and Ben, where the chat quickly turned to their kids, Hame had the good sense to ask Ben if he’d like to slightly formalise the conversation and record it. And thanks to Ben’s generosity, we’ve got Episode 10 as a result!
From his search for a different kind of life and love with wife Ione, to taking on the responsibility of a stepdaughter and his early missteps - Ben talks openly and passionately about his dadding style and journey.</description></item><item><title>How Pat Cummins Dads | How Other Dads Dad with Hamish Blake</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8942100019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8942100019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Australian Test Cricket Captain, Pat Cummins was rated the world's best bowler in March 2022. But at the very same time, he was a brand new parent trying to figure out how this dadding thing works.
Pat very kindly sat down with Hame to chat about his first year of being a dad. The pain of extended time apart from family, the challenge of making time count when he is at home and the inspiration that his own parents give him (even if they did forget his little sister at soccer practise once - but he is one of 5 kids, so cut ’em some slack we say).</description></item><item><title>How Dave Hughes Dads | How Other Dads Dad with Hamish Blake</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8942100020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8942100020/</guid><description>Podcast Description A legend of Australian comedy, Hughesy is used to dealing with a tough crowd at times. But it seems his three kids provide the best heckles!
Hamish was backstage at Rove many years ago when Hughesy and his wife Holly brought their very fresh newborn baby in, and it all seemed very grown up…especially for Hughesy! Since then, Dave has had two more kids, and away from the microphone Hamish has had the great pleasure of chatting with Hughesy about his very thoughtful and highly empathetic approach to dadding.</description></item><item><title>How Max Gawn Dads | How Other Dads Dad with Hamish Blake</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8942100021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8942100021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fresh off winning the AFL Grand final in 2021, Max Gawn hit the jackpot again three weeks later with the birth of his first child.
Captain of the Melbourne Football Club, five time All Australian Ruckman, and all round good guy, Max first became friends with Hame because they liked riding bikes up big hills. Now they share stories about their other passion… not the Melbourne Football Club (this time), but their kids.</description></item><item><title>How Nazeem Hussain Dads | How Other Dads Dad with Hamish Blake</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8942100022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8942100022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nazeem Hussain is stand-up royalty in Australia and a perennial headliner of festivals at home and abroad. But perhaps his biggest gig is being a dad to two young kids. Naz and Hame laugh a lot in this episode, but Naz also generously shares stories from his childhood, which largely saw him and his sister raised solo by their Mum. He talks about seeking out father figures as a kid, and now as a father himself, the search for dadding wisdom continues (which mostly consists of him reading just the first few pages of tons of parenting books!</description></item><item><title>How Ben Shewry Dads | How Other Dads Dad with Hamish Blake</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8942100023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8942100023/</guid><description>Podcast Description With his famed restaurant Attica, Ben Shewry is a guy that has made an indelible mark on the culinary world through his creativity, dedication &amp;amp; undoubtedly some really deep thought. As a mate, Hamish has been lucky enough to see Ben apply this same thoughtful approach to his Dadding over the years, and in this episode he really does get some golden practical tips on opt-in-parenting from Ben. We just made up “opt-in-parenting”.</description></item><item><title>How Hugh van Cuylenburg Dads | How Other Dads Dad with Hamish Blake</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8942100024/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8942100024/</guid><description>Podcast Description As founder of The Resilience Project, a program that reaches 500,000 kids around Australia every year, Hugh van Cuylenburg has been talking to parents for ages. However, he’s the first to admit being a parent is a whole different story! In this episode, Hugh shares with Hame some bloody funny stories, but also some really raw reflections on Dadding. Hugh’s honesty is one of a kind, and it led to a chat with Hame that we are sure will leave many listeners nodding in silent appreciation of a shared experience.</description></item><item><title>How Stan Grant Dads | How Other Dads Dad with Hamish Blake</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8942100025/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8942100025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Proud Wiradjuri man, father of 4 and icon of Australian journalism, Stan Grant goes deep with Hame in this episode with his philosophies on Dadding. He shares brutal stories about the Australia that his father was forced to endure, and for which he was preparing Stan to live in. He describes the pain of a relationship ending and how protecting the children was central. And as a dad to now older children, he reminds Hame that this thing called parenting goes by so, so, so fast and to treasure it, because you don’t get another shot!</description></item><item><title>How Adam Hills Dads | How Other Dads Dad with Hamish Blake</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8942100026/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8942100026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam Hills talks to Hame about everything from the art of negotiating with kids who won't stay in bed, to his subconscious fears of becoming a father. He shares stories from his own childhood that only now, as a dad, are beginning to make sense, and he &amp;amp; Hame discuss the amazing power of telling your kids you are sorry and that you stuffed up. Adam Hills has been a mainstay of Australian and UK entertainment for, well… ages.</description></item><item><title>How Rob Sitch Dads | How Other Dads Dad with Hamish Blake</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8942100027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8942100027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rob Sitch is not only a prolific creator of some of Australia's most beloved comedy characters, TV shows and films, he is also one of the very first friends that Hamish got to see dadding up close. Many years ago, backstage on Thank God You Are Here, and well before his own dadding journey started, Hamish started talking to Rob about his philosophies on being a parent, and so it is only fitting that Rob is on the first episode of How Other Dads Dad.</description></item><item><title>What is How Other Dads Dad?! | How Other Dads Dad with Hamish Blake</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8942100028/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 10:10:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8942100028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish has been working on a little passion project, and it’s all about dadding. Keenly aware that his own dadding playbook was made up from the tips, tricks and hacks he had nabbed from friends and colleagues - Hamish decided it might be time to formalise his acquisition of wisdom, so that it might be shared (and helpfully add to the 1 billion podcasts now in existence). In each episode he’ll have a chat with a dad that he admires (and who he was able to easily text) and discuss how they go about dadding; the tips, the tricks, the pitfalls and the moments of pure joy.</description></item></channel></rss>