<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-dan-le-batard-show-with-stugotz/</link><description>Recent content in The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 20:20:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-dan-le-batard-show-with-stugotz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Austin Ekeler on Chargers Changes | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590264/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 20:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590264/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stugotz, Billy and Mikey A. react to Week 15. The guys play a game of If The Season Ended today and tell you who would move on in the current playoff matchups. Austin Ekeler joins the show to discuss the Chargers letting go of HC Brandon Staley and GM Tom Telesco. Stugotz has his Top 5 QBs who didn&amp;rsquo;t start the season as their team&amp;rsquo;s starter. Billy has his weekly BBBBBB picks headed into MNF.</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: Mason Rudolph...is...BACK! | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590265/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590265/</guid><description>Podcast Description The chunk of flesh ripped out of Tua&amp;rsquo;s arm leads us to a conversation on the expense of tattoos, and Billy has a question for Chris before we end the show. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: What's in Billy's Bag? | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590266/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590266/</guid><description>Podcast Description We kick off Hour 2 with QB talk: Jameis Winston brought a briefcase to work to be an inspiration, the &amp;ldquo;yeah, no&amp;rdquo; of NFL quarterbacks, the Trevor Lawrence question, and Lamar Jackson&amp;rsquo;s case for MVP. Then, would you go on a 9-month long cruise? The Shipping Container has some strong opinions on cruise ship food. Plus, Jessica has decided who from the show she&amp;rsquo;d want to be stuck in an elevator with, Billy takes a look through his bag, the crew watches what may be the worst layup attempt of all-time, and Stugotz has nothing left in the tank.</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: 'pologies | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590267/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590267/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mike&amp;rsquo;s limited fake Ed Orgeron forces Dan into some reckless speculation. Jessica believes Red Zone should be discounted through the rest of the NFL season, and Chris can&amp;rsquo;t believe the dissension he&amp;rsquo;s hearing in the room over the delightful Scott Hanson. Then, two incredible sound bites from Jake Browning and David Njoku, too much Tucci, and Mark Zuckerberg&amp;rsquo;s doomsday compound leads the crew to discuss how they&amp;rsquo;d handle the end of the world.</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: Huh... No Piss | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590268/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590268/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan is embargoing his Dolphins and NFL thoughts, so we&amp;rsquo;ll get to those later. First, Billy&amp;rsquo;s phone is racist, no one can find the proper networks on their televisions, and do you have a speaker in your bathroom? Then, Leeman got stuck in an elevator over the weekend, and it leads us to discuss HOW you&amp;rsquo;d want to get stuck. Do you want someone in there with you? Would you lay down?</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: I'm Just Spitballing | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590269/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590269/</guid><description>Podcast Description God Bless Football will come out later today since Billy and Stugotz have an interview scheduled with Austin Ekeler, so we get FRESH TAKES from the duo on the NFL. Then, Stugotz tries to get a sponsorship, Mike Ryan has information but is not a journalist, and the transfer portal has some incredible message-boarding going on. Plus, Chip Kelly has an idea for the future of College Football, Jessica runs out of breath giving takes, and&amp;hellip;is Miami going to miss out on its QB?</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: Hodgepodgin' It! | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590259/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 18:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590259/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s a Postgame Show hodgepodge of content! First, Pablo Torre provides us with a segment from today&amp;rsquo;s Pablo Torre Finds Out where he, Katie Nolan, and Dan Soder chat about urology and gym memberships. So, ya know, standard #sports stuff. Then, The Hockey Show with Roy is here as Roy and David Dwork discuss the Florida Panthers before Dimitri Filipovic of The Hockey PDOcast joins the duo for a &amp;ldquo;10-minute misconduct&amp;rdquo; to explain why Aleksander Barkov is headed to a Selke Trophy and to touch on other topics around the NHL.</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: GEN CFB | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590260/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590260/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jessica and Lucy are fascinated by the Panera Charged Lemonade that has been killing people* and the memes that have spawned from it. Amin walks a dangerous line, and Lucy teaches Dan why his opinion on Liquid Death&amp;rsquo;s water is out of touch. Then, the crew discusses the weirdest stretches of land in Florida as Charlotte teaches us about Hussey&amp;rsquo;s General Store that sells &amp;ldquo;guns, wedding gowns, and cold beer.</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: Old Aches and Pains | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590261/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590261/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan&amp;rsquo;s costume kink rears its head once again as he has a suggestion for God Bless Football, John Skipper gets upset at a thumbs down emoji, and the crew goes to the Bucket of Death. Then, Colby Covington takes a shot at LeJaron James as his MAGA character continues to make him famous. Is it a bit? Does it matter? Plus, Stugotz actually listens, an old Luke Appling video brings the entire show the most joy they&amp;rsquo;ve felt all week, and Chris Cote updates the polls.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: The Affable Chris Cote | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590262/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590262/</guid><description>Podcast Description Everyone on the show is exhausted from a long week behind the scenes. Dan is on a mission to determine who the most athletic person is on the show, and he also has his first ever claim that a team quit mid-game. Then, Peter King loves to wash the dishes, Brandon Staley does yoga, and we were stolen of a moment. Plus, the always jubilant, affable, and jolly Chris Cote is ready to lose his mind.</description></item><item><title>GBF- Peter King, Quincy Williams, Simms, Golic, Juju and more! | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590263/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 13:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590263/</guid><description>Podcast Description Billy and Stugotz react to a horrific TNF game between the Chargers and the Raiders. Peter King and Billy bond over their love for doing dishes. Quincy Williams thinks Robert Saleh&amp;rsquo;s beard is painted on. Stu Ya Gotz. Chris Simms has never felt better about Tyreek Hill being the MVP. Golic and Stugotz were left to their own devices. Juju joins Carl, SherBear, Gordie and K-Funk to make their weekly picks.</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: Quadrupling Down | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590254/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 19:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590254/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris continues to try to defend his Kadarius Toney take, and did Tom Hanks have two careers? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: Who Will He Chews? | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590255/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 19:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590255/</guid><description>Podcast Description First, what does it mean when the NBA says Draymond Green will receive counseling? We examine the story with the crew from Oddball before JuJu delivers today&amp;rsquo;s Thursday Thunder. Then, Mina Kimes is back to talk Zach Wilson, Josh Allen, talent evaluation, game managers, Amin&amp;rsquo;s incredible Geno Smith prediction, a new game show idea, and to absolutely roast both Chris and Lucy. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: Lucy's Dog Problem | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590256/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 17:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590256/</guid><description>Podcast Description After Jessica explains the issue dogs are having in Miami, the crew has a debate over a polarizing decision Lucy has made to adopt a shelter dog for a day. Then, Adnan Virk and David Samson are here to deliver their Top 5 Musical/Comedy Golden Globe Winning Films, and Amin has opinions&amp;hellip;he just won&amp;rsquo;t say them. Plus, has Jack Nicholson been coasting off movies from 50 years ago? Did Oppenheimer ruin the movie-going experience?</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: JuJu Gotti's Wake and Take | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590257/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 16:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590257/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stugotz explains why he is so grateful to be handing Wake and Take off to JuJu Gotti, a man who Dan wants to name the &amp;ldquo;General Caretaker&amp;rdquo; of the show. JuJu explains the way the show helped him during dark times, and the show explains how JuJu&amp;rsquo;s helped us feel more joy. (The crew also discusses Cam Newton&amp;rsquo;s game manager take and Stu has some thoughts.) Then, IT&amp;rsquo;S TIME FOR JUJU GOTTI&amp;rsquo;S WAKE AND TAKE FEATURING FANS OF THE SHOW!</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: LINE SHIFT! | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590258/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590258/</guid><description>Podcast Description After listening to a gorgeous Dan Le Batard inspired Christmas song submitted by a fan of the show, our &amp;ldquo;first shift&amp;rdquo; includes Amin and Charlotte with Dan and the Shipping Container discussing all the funniest parts of the Bucks-Pacers squabble over who should get the game ball after Giannis Antetokounmpo set the Bucks franchise record with 64 points. Did YOU know a game ball is like a fine wine?</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: Soda Jerks | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590249/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 18:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590249/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeremy is angry about the response to his song, Charlotte wants to try Utah soda, and Mike, Chris, Amin, and Tony react to the show. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: Gabagool, New York, New Yoooooooork | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590250/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 18:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590250/</guid><description>Podcast Description Charlotte has ideas of what Travis Kelce should do for Taylor Swift&amp;rsquo;s birthday, and who do you think of when you think of COVID first starting? Then, Dave &amp;amp; Buster&amp;rsquo;s, Cam Newton talks about game managers in a weird hat, and the Cowboys, 49ers, Dolphins, and Lions. Plus, Jeremy used his time &amp;ldquo;floating&amp;rdquo; to deliver a song everyone immediately hates, and we play everyone&amp;rsquo;s favorite game: AGAINST! THE! SPREAD!</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: The Magic Crate of Content Returns! | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590251/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 17:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590251/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan has a message for the Shipping Container after our Rob Delaney interview, and it somehow ends up as content for the show. Should Dan take a break? Was JuJu actually mad earlier? Should we be discussing&amp;hellip;any of this? Then, congrats to Ron Magill, Pablo Torre as Michael Wilbon, and the Magic Crate of Content returns to save the show. Plus, we head back to discuss Dan&amp;rsquo;s new shirts and Sleeveless A.</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: Laughter and Grief Go Together | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590252/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 16:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590252/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan discusses on and off air disagreements, and as he name-drops Chris Long, the Dolphins are one of the biggest. Then, Football™ keeps happening to quarterbacks and our security guard, Frankie, LOVED our White Elephant gift exchange. Plus, Rob Delaney stops by to discuss his book &amp;ldquo;A Heart That Works,&amp;rdquo; about the death of his son and the grief that comes from it, and as Dan wants to gain some words of wisdom after the passing of his brother, they both want to find a way to make the interview funny.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: Fuhgeddaboudit | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590253/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 16:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590253/</guid><description>Podcast Description Billy is dressed as an old-timey baseball player named Billy Two Legs in honor of the Tungsten O&amp;rsquo;Doyle Bucket of Death punishment. Charlotte and Amin are here to celebrate the Draymond Green punch and Tommy Devito and Zach Wilson being named the NFC and AFC Offensive Players of the Week. Then, David Samson is here to celebrate loopholes MLB owners take to manipulate their finances. Plus, Sean Stellato, Tommy Devito&amp;rsquo;s National Italian American Hall of Fame bound agent, joins the show to share Italian phrases and meanings, his story, and sound exactly how you&amp;rsquo;d hope.</description></item><item><title>PTFO - Why a Soccer Super-Fan Taken Hostage by Hamas Is Still a 'Ray of Hope' in Israel | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590243/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 20:10:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590243/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hersh Goldberg-Polin was devoted to an Israeli football club fighting for peace. Supporters of its rival include far-right Israeli politicians like a national-security minister hellbent on war — and a racist mob. If you want help understanding the Israel-Hamas conflict, Hersh&amp;rsquo;s abduction by terrorists is a window to the world. Correspondent Amos Barshad interviews his loved ones and finds a silver lining.
(Read the companion article at The Lever)</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: Greg's Lobos | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590244/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 19:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590244/</guid><description>Podcast Description Greg&amp;rsquo;s Manny Diaz takes, Jeremy&amp;rsquo;s Top 5 Silliest Payments in Baseball in 2024, and a Greg&amp;rsquo;s Lobos update! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: Who Should Host a Game Show? | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590245/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590245/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mike and the crew try to teach Greg Cote how the Hard Network Out actually works, and it seems as though he may be coachable. Then, Greg and Roy are destined for a Turk-Off, Mike takes down Giannis and claims he&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;surrounded by losers,&amp;rdquo; and Lucy, Jeremy and Dan (?) are sick of the fat-shaming of Zion Williamson. Plus, Chris Cote wants to know which celebrity would make the best future Game Show host, and Jeremy and Billy want to throw their hats into the ring to host one themselves.</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: Killy Gil | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590246/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590246/</guid><description>Podcast Description Esteemed Meadowlark Intern Mike Schur is here to discuss the Shohei Ohtani contract, the Braves payroll, Juan Soto, and Billy Kill. Then, Lucy has faced her first adversity as a member of the DLS Show, but we try to save her with Royalty Free Music. Plus, we play a quick game of &amp;ldquo;How Old Are They?,&amp;rdquo; and Greg discusses the Dolphins history of sizzling in December. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: The Top 5 Three-way | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590247/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 17:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590247/</guid><description>Podcast Description Billy continues our discussion on Shohei Ohtani and his record-setting contract with the Dodgers, the contract deferments, TV contracts and stardom, and whether or not the Dodgers owners will sell the team before paying Ohtani. Then, Jeremy won&amp;rsquo;t shut up, and we get to three Top 5 lists at the same time: Stugotz&amp;rsquo;s teams you don&amp;rsquo;t want to face in the NFL Playoffs, Chris Cote&amp;rsquo;s teams you DO want to see in the NFL Playoffs, and Greg Cote&amp;rsquo;s teams you&amp;rsquo;d be ambivalent about seeing in the NFL Playoffs.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: Geraldo's Vault | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590248/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590248/</guid><description>Podcast Description 🎶 My nuts roasting on an open fire 🎶 The crew kicks things off with a beautiful tune from the sultry sounds of Greg Cote. After last night&amp;rsquo;s Dolphins watch party with show fans, we discuss the laughable results of the game as the Dolphins did something horrible that hasn&amp;rsquo;t happened in years. Are you DolphIN or DolphOUT? The crew is taking notes on who left their fandom aside after last night&amp;rsquo;s game.</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: THE BATTLE COURT! | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590237/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590237/</guid><description>Podcast Description Whdtevwr. I&amp;rsquo;n dine. Thr Crwta Cublines hfve a bug metch. Muke abd Cjris aew ecvited. Lusten hwrw. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: Yeah, But Come On | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590238/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 18:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590238/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jrrmyey is reslly syrugfling wuth thos lemp shhde. Dud you knew Easton Stick wrnt to Nurth Dakota State? A sultry, sexy, saucy Tuny delibers his trademerk Tomy&amp;rsquo;s Top 4. Then, Jrssica joined Faceboik like a boomer for Facebook Marketblace, therw&amp;rsquo;s never been a butter time to go ti the Post Officw, and it&amp;rsquo;s tume for everyone&amp;rsquo;s fsbirute game: AGAINDT! THR! SPTEAD! Plus, Dan wantd hys own Topn3, and why do Strrlers fens want to fure Mike Tomlijn?</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: But Don't Ya Think...? | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590239/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590239/</guid><description>Podcast Description This lsmp shade is grtting vwry frustratinb. Stugitz kicks things pff with his Weekens Observations,. Them, after our 11-minute bresk where Stu bothers Dam with his tskes, we welcome our contedt winner Mike and his friends to the stydio. Plus, Lane Johnson stats will bliw your mund, Brick Pordy is superb, and the rumor mill around thr $hohei Ohtsni contract. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: Being In the Moment These Days | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590240/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 17:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590240/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeremy continyuez to wear a lsmp shad2 on his head to wrote these descriptiona. We kick things off with Alvin Kamsra&amp;rsquo;s receiving stats adn Stephen A. Smith calling out Zion Williamdon. Then, Shawn Kemp, the new McDonalf&amp;rsquo;s Coffee Chain, and being in the moment likw LeBrin James seemd to be with Bronny. Plus, why don&amp;rsquo;t we care sbout the Heidman Trophy? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: The Best Play That Never Happened | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590241/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590241/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeremy is wearing a lamp shade on his hesd for todau&amp;rsquo;s show whoch makes it very difficult to type today&amp;rsquo;s descriptipns. After Dsn tells us about the longest weekend of his life, the Bulls-Chiefs game has everyone revvvving and ready to go after Kadarius Toney had an offensive offsides to cost us one of the ciilest plays in NFL history. We discuss Pstrick Mahomes&amp;rsquo; fruatrations postgame, Travis Kelce and Taylor Swoft, the NFL referee inconsistencies, and more.</description></item><item><title>Monday Hangover- You Love To See It | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590242/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 14:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590242/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lucy is back from our National Championship, the Army Navy Game! Billy is back from a week off and has a new segment You Love To See It! Stugotz wants a playoff transfer portal and has his MVP of the season through this week and this week&amp;rsquo;s Super Bowl matchup. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Post-Postgame Show: Pablo Torre Cameowashes George Santos | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590230/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590230/</guid><description>Podcast Description We have an excerpt of today&amp;rsquo;s Share &amp;amp; Tell on Pablo Torre Finds Out with Pablo Torre, Mina Kimes, and Dan Le Batard. Pablo pays for a cameo from George Santos for Mina and Dan, and it launches them into a debate on what Santos represents in modern American politics and celebrity. Here&amp;rsquo;s the question: Is George Santos funny? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: Elite, Good, Average, Ass | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590231/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590231/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome back to Roy&amp;rsquo;s Hockey Show, now officially named &amp;ldquo;The Hockey Show&amp;rdquo; with Roy. He and David Dwork of The Hockey News begin their conversation with some Panthers talk. They discuss the biggest factors in the Cats&amp;rsquo; success this season and how their health is just now coming together. Then, Roy and David sort the teams across the NHL into tiers by referring to them as Elite, Good, Average, and Ass.</description></item><item><title>Sporting Class: Why Is Mark Cuban Selling the Mavericks?; CFP Selection Secrets: Is it All Rigged!? | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590232/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590232/</guid><description>Podcast Description Meadowlark Media CEO John Skipper and Nothing Personal&amp;rsquo;s David Samson are back with another episode with Pablo Torre Finds Out host&amp;hellip; Pablo Torre to host! Welcome to the Sporting Class! Mark Cuban is selling the Dallas Mavericks! No one had seen that one coming. Let’s discuss this deal. The truths. The rumors. Speculating on the WHY! Then, the College Football Playoff was announced. Alabama in. Florida State out. Did ESPN have something to do with this?</description></item><item><title>#BecauseMiami: Moms For Taking Liberties | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590233/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590233/</guid><description>Podcast Description The state of Florida is severely lacking in education but that&amp;rsquo;s not important. What&amp;rsquo;s important to state politicians is outing transsexual high school athletes. Billy Corben discusses that with Jennifer Solomon of Equality Florida. David Samson joins Billy to talk about how the war between Israel and Hamas is causing an increase of hate crimes in America. Reporter Bob Norman joins the program to talk about the ménage à trois between Christian Ziegler, the chairman of the GOP of Florida, his wife, Bridgette, a co-founder of Moms for Liberty, and their former lover.</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: Your Favorite Meadowlark Duos | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590234/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590234/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jessica and Lucy are back with their Unnamed College Football Show formerly known as F*** G**** to discuss EVERYTHING from conference championship weekend, the College Football Playoff Committee&amp;rsquo;s decision making, the upcoming bowl season, and more. Then, we check in with the Oddball crew of Amin and Charlotte! After Charlotte moderated a panel in a partnership between Allen Iverson, Dominic “The Surgeon&amp;quot; Ciambrone, Reebok, and Draft Kings, the crew has a celebration of all things Iverson and the way he loves the game despite being vilified for things that are mainstream in the league now.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: Happy Chanukah! | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590235/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590235/</guid><description>Podcast Description The show celebrates the first day of Chanukah in a very special way. Plus, Hard Knocks continues to be great in showing the personalities of the Miami Dolphins, Tony brings back his Miami jingles and the crew goes to the Bucket Of Death. Also, The Athletic&amp;rsquo;s Dianna Russini stops by to talk about her week, breaking the Zach Wilson news and much more. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>GBF - Where's Billy? Emmitt Smith, Golic, Simms and Ekeler | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590236/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590236/</guid><description>Podcast Description (0:00) Golic is really upset about how FSU got left out of the College Football playoff and has a big problem with Zach Wilson not wanting to return to the starting lineup for the Jets. (23:27) Emmitt Smith joins the show to talk about the Cowboys Super Bowl chances as well as his willingness to take the head coaching job at Florida if he was offered it. (37:36) StuYaGotz.</description></item><item><title>Stupod - Joe Benigno and All the Jets Pain | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590224/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 19:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590224/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stugotz and Mikey A are joined by WFAN and Jets fan legend Joe Benigno to talk about the crazy week and his relationship with Robert Saleh. Joe reminisces on decades of being a suffering Jets fan and what he hopes for the future. Plus, they play a little game of &amp;ldquo;Bro or No&amp;rdquo;. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: An Apology to Dan | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590225/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 18:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590225/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s time to laugh at the new Jim Harbaugh contract proposal and apologize to Dan for making fun of his outfit. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: Minute Kimes Show pt. 2 | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590226/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 18:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590226/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mina Kimes is back and might be delivering her analysis in song, with speed, or&amp;hellip; normally. She takes us through all the fun topics of the NFL including Aaron Rodgers, Zach Wilson, Jake Browning, the Ravens, and Dan&amp;rsquo;s outfit. Plus, the Cesta Cyclones are ready for primetime as they have a huge matchup coming up, Lucy is ready for Army-Navy, and the Victor Wembanyama-Jaime Jaquez Jr. debate takes shape.</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: Stat of the Day (Taylor's Version) | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590227/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590227/</guid><description>Podcast Description Caitlin Clark continues to blow us all away, and Lucy leads our crew&amp;rsquo;s excitement over her superstardom. This sparks a conversation on NIL and its influence over whether or not stars like Caitlin Clark might stay in college. Then, we give our producer Taylor Vippolis an on-air platform for Stat of the Day, but will his nerves force him to mess everything up? Wait to see&amp;hellip; Plus, Dan is a ramblin&amp;rsquo; man again, we may have an early Suey nominee, and Zach Wilson&amp;rsquo;s face may be his biggest issue.</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: I'm Just a Girl | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590228/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590228/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jim Larrañaga joins the show to discuss the Canes Basketball program, why he loves teaching, Hamilton the Musical, the evolution of basketball, and more. Then, Jessica and Lucy are late for Segment 2 and they&amp;rsquo;re in HUGE trouble with Dan. That said, Jess has brought new energy to the show, and Lucy has a great excuse. Plus, Adnan Virk and David Samson are here to discuss their Top 5 War Movies, but first, David is upset with being an afterthought at this company.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: Dan, The Divorced Dad | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590229/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 15:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590229/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan is not wearing a hat and IS wearing a flannel for today&amp;rsquo;s show, and someone is dressed as the Stay Puft Marshmallow Man (and holding an Emmy). Then, the crew has a conversation about gambling regulations for broadcasters and team partners and the ease of betting and how it can influence the ethics behind individual games as Dan questions where this is all headed. Plus, Lucy is a Top 24 College Football personality, the Steelers and Patriots game is a comedy, and small towns may be better equipped for the NIL era.</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: Texting Etiquette | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590219/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590219/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mike, Tony, and Chris help Jeremy solve a dilemma he&amp;rsquo;s been having over texting people on the West Coast. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: ALL THE SMOKE! | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590220/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590220/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matt Barnes is here to celebrate our new partnership with All the Smoke and share some stories about his vibe check with Dan, role players who get in trouble, fights with Doc Rivers, and more. Then, Chris and Jeremy want to compete with an assistant, and Mike has an idea of where college football may be headed with a new football subdivision. Plus, broadcasting youth football, and Aaron Rodgers goes after the media on behalf of Zach Wilson.</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: Lord, Dan Was Born a Ramblin' Man | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590221/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590221/</guid><description>Podcast Description After Dan finishes rambling, the show has a huge announcement: All The Smoke is coming to Meadowlark Media and the Draft Kings Network! We discuss welcoming Matt Barnes, Stephen Jackson, and All The Smoke Productions to the crew. Then, it&amp;rsquo;s time for everyone&amp;rsquo;s favorite game&amp;hellip;AGAINST! THE! SPREAD! Plus, did you see that Titans punter injury? And it&amp;rsquo;s time for Tony&amp;rsquo;s Top deadmau5, and Billy laughs at Chris Cote. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: Taking Dan's Breath Away | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590222/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590222/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is the evolution of NFL player empowerment going to be certain players just&amp;hellip;not playing until the playoffs? Then, Jeremy desperately wants to get a George Santos podcast off the ground, Tony continues to be a volume shooter on QB evaluation, Mike discusses FSU Football spiraling out of control, and and Stugotz, the snake, hangs around Dan&amp;rsquo;s neck. Plus, Stu has gained weight, and a debate breaks out over the relevance of the NBA In-Season Tournament.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: You're...A...Crook, Captain Hook! | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590223/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590223/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan is dressed as Captain Hook but looks like at least 10 other celebrities with mustaches, and Tony is struggling with a deadmau5 head cutting off his vision. We try to discuss the Winter Meetings with David Samson, but his audio continues to act the way it has the last several weeks, and we guarantee this one is NOT a bit. Then, Dick Fitts, Tim Boyle, and Jaelen Phillips on Hard Knocks.</description></item><item><title>PTFO - Are You Smarter Than an NFL Quarterback? | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590213/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 19:54:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590213/</guid><description>Podcast Description A fierce debate — about no less than the meaning of intelligence itself — has broken out in the world of football scouting, as star quarterback C.J. Stroud puts together one of the best rookie QB seasons ever&amp;hellip; after bombing the new Wonderlic test. But can this S2 Cognition exam actually predict how your brain impacts athletic performance? Pablo puts himself to the ultimate test of mental agility, with a little help from Alex Smith — and with a LOT of expletives.</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: The Death of the ACC | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590214/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 18:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590214/</guid><description>Podcast Description Does FSU&amp;rsquo;s exclusion from the CFP actually signal the death of the ACC, and we have John Skipper to blame? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: The Nathan Peterman Award | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590215/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 18:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590215/</guid><description>Podcast Description Greg Cote is running out of steam as we approach the end of the show, but first we have to get to his horse paying dividends, the Bucket of Death, and Jer-emmy Tache. Then, we had out the first ever Nathan Peterman Award for worst QB of all-time and discuss if there was anything FSU could have done to make the Playoff. Plus, we continue our conversation on the dehumanization of athletes and if there was any money you&amp;rsquo;d take to experience pain both mentally and physically later in life.</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: Dan Le Batard's Official College Football Playoff Rankings | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590216/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 17:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590216/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s International Cheetah Day, so there&amp;rsquo;s no better person to bring in a man who&amp;rsquo;s slept in a bed with a cheetah: Ron Magill. Then, Dan finally reveals his official Top 6 teams in his College Football Playoff Rankings, and he&amp;rsquo;s followed the committee&amp;rsquo;s criteria for an impressive resume. Plus, our video team has worked diligently to create GTA characters based on show cast members, Greg doesn&amp;rsquo;t to &amp;ldquo;the tox,&amp;rdquo; we watch Lucy&amp;rsquo;s video from the SEC title game featuring JuJu Gotti, and Jim Harbaugh is getting the credit he deserves.</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: The Art of Trash Talking | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590217/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 17:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590217/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wes Welker says Tyreek Hill is better than Randy Moss, and he has a pretty great case, but Tyreek Hill is making sure to share his success with Tua. Then, Christian Wilkins is here to discuss having fun in the NFL, trash talk as an art form, the most important player on the Dolphins offense, and more. Plus, Lucy finally unleashes her football analysis&amp;hellip;unfortunately it&amp;rsquo;s while surrounded by feet.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: Who Put Pablo in Charge? | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590218/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 15:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590218/</guid><description>Podcast Description Greg Cote is here on book release Tuesday for The Pride of a Lion. He&amp;rsquo;s feeling proud, and we ain&amp;rsquo;t lyin&amp;rsquo;. Dan has sent in his vote for the Heisman Trophy and has some major regrets over not voting for Iowa&amp;rsquo;s punter, we spend some time trying to promote Greg&amp;rsquo;s old book FINS AT 50, and the feelings from yesterday&amp;rsquo;s merch store discussion are still hanging over the show.</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: Sunday Night Live With Tony &amp; JuJu | NFL Postgame Show Week 13 | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590207/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590207/</guid><description>Podcast Description The BIGGEST NFL Postgame show in the world brings you everything that happened in Week 13 of the NFL. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: Mike Ryan's Hot Dad | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590208/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 19:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590208/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mike Ryan&amp;rsquo;s Handsome Dad™ joins the show IN-STUDIO as the crew fawns all over him and proposes Meadowlark Media&amp;rsquo;s own version of The Golden Bachelor. Then, today is one of the best Dolphins Mondays of his lifetime, so why doesn&amp;rsquo;t Chris Cote feel that way? Plus, Stugotz&amp;rsquo;s Weekend Observations and Dan&amp;rsquo;s experience with cash at the valet. Also, is Dan going to make a mockery of the Heisman Trophy voting?</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: Heinie McGee | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590209/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590209/</guid><description>Podcast Description The New England Patriots are impossibly bad, and our Miami-based crew is reveling in it. Dan is still upset about the merch store. Was that a bit? Jess is still upset about &amp;ldquo;Foot Girls.&amp;rdquo; Was THAT a bit? Then, Spencer Hall is here to tell us about all the wildly hilarious parts of what happened with the CFP committee yesterday and to explain why College Football is a perfect microcosm for America.</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: The College Football Playoff | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590210/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 16:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590210/</guid><description>Podcast Description The whole crew has strong takes on the College Football Playoff Selection Committee after FSU was excluded from the Playoff after an undefeated season, Georgia was discarded, and Alabama found its way to the party. Does the regular season not matter? Are losses better than wins? Is this JUST a made-for-TV event? Should Jordan Travis have broken his leg sooner? The conversation continues as Chris Cote seems to see every side of the debate, Jessica rails against Michigan&amp;rsquo;s inclusion in the Playoff after cheating, and Stugotz flip-flops in his opinion that the regular season should matter most.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: It's Time to Take Advantage of Our Audience | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590211/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590211/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan &amp;ldquo;The Urinator&amp;rdquo; Le Batard is taking a break from his normal balanced perspective to celebrate the No. 1 seed in the AFC, the Miami Dolphins! Dan, Stugotz, and the Shipping Container discuss Tua, Tyreek Hill&amp;rsquo;s dominance, the Dolphins becoming the Chiefs, and more after the Fins blowout victory. Then, Dan ruined David Samson&amp;rsquo;s weekend because David ruined Dan&amp;rsquo;s merch store with exorbitant prices that take advantage of the audience and profits that &amp;ldquo;trickle down&amp;rdquo; to the Shipping Container.</description></item><item><title>Monday Hangover: Poor FSU and Ryan Tannehill | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590212/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590212/</guid><description>Podcast Description Billy took a vacation that nobody knew about so Chris Cote joins the show. Do the Packers have another quarterback for the next 15 years that the Jets will eventually sign to run their team? Lucy is back from the SEC Championship game and she shares her existential crisis for how heartbroken she is for FSU for being left out of the playoff, but completely understands the decision. Fuentes gives his top 5 list and Mikey A fills in on the BBBBB.</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: Jeremy Tache vs. Mike Ryan | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590201/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 18:07:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590201/</guid><description>Podcast Description There is legitimate tension in the studio as our internal investigation reveals who was first on the Jaime Jaquez Jr. takes on the Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz. HINT: It&amp;rsquo;s the person writing this episode description. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: Mike's Big Man Brain | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590202/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 18:01:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590202/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan, Stugotz, and the Shipping Container look back at the video introduction of Foot Girls, Jessica and Lucy&amp;rsquo;s new and triumphant success for Meadowlark Media. They also discuss how many teams in the NFL can actually win the Super Bowl this year. Then, people are ECSTATIC about our move to MAX, Elon Musk is weaponizing X, and Tim Boyle stinks. Plus, Pablo Torre, Katie Nolan, and Dan discuss Saudi Arabia through a segment of Pablo Torre Finds Out.</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: Foot Girls | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590203/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 17:34:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590203/</guid><description>Podcast Description The crew takes a trip to the Bucket of Death and need to draw for a number of Shipping Container members who are missing. Then, it&amp;rsquo;s time to discuss Dak Prescott and the Cowboys winning and whether the Eagles or 49ers are the best team in the NFC. Plus, it&amp;rsquo;s the OFFICIAL introduction of FOOT GIRLS as Jess, Lucy, and Charlotte (women empowerment!) take a look at the world of College Football.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: That Doesn't Sit White With Me | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590204/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 17:15:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590204/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stugotz has a swagger in his waddle this morning because of his massive success with Chris Cote on Bob Does Sports. We take a look at the video of his golf game, and today might be a day you want to watch the show, too. Then, Thursday Night Football was spectacular, and DK Metcalf reminded us (in sign language) why he&amp;rsquo;s capable of being such a dominant receiver. Plus, the Dan vs.</description></item><item><title>South Beach Sessions - Nicky Jam | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590205/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590205/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t know if God brung me here to get a lot off my chest&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
Nicky Jam, a beloved Latin icon recognized around the world as a Reggaeton pioneer, shares with Dan the harsh truth about the isolating nature of fame, his battle through addiction, and the chaotic struggle for authentic connections in the spotlight.
In what Nicky describes as “the best interview I’ve ever done”, Dan guides him through the demons he had to confront in his family dynamics and artistry in the quest for inner peace and happiness beyond the superficial trappings of success.</description></item><item><title>GBF: The BCS Returns + Jevon Holland, Mostert, Ekeler &amp; More | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590206/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 13:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590206/</guid><description>Podcast Description (0:00) The guys recap a good TNF game between the Seahawks and the Cowboys. (8:43) Jevon Holland won America 98 inch TVs after his Hail Mary return. (20:45) The final BCS rankings of the year are revealed to Golic. Who made the playoffs? (38:54) Raheem Mostert reacts to the Dolphins loss of Jaelan Philips, the best strategy for picking up his kids from school and to invite Stugotz out for some drinks.</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: The Thing About Being 17 | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590191/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590191/</guid><description>Podcast Description Riley Leonard has taken to The Transfer Portal Dating App, and it has all of us remembering how stupid we were at 17 and imagine having to make a massive decision on where to attend college and get paid thousands of dollars. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: Minute Kimes | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590192/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 18:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590192/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mina Kimes is here to discuss a wide array of topics around the NFL, but can she do it in turbo speed? Tune into The Minute Kimes Show to find out! She also brings up the ever-flowing debate over wedding meals vs. hor dourves. Plus, JuJu delivers an electric Thursday Thunder, Deion Sanders wins SI Sportsperson of the Year, and the crew dishes out some of their greatest fears (and joys) when they&amp;rsquo;re high.</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: You Have a Booger In Your Nose | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590193/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 18:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590193/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adnan Virk and David Samson join the show to discuss the Top 5 Ben Stiller movies as he turns 57 today. They also get into the recent Elon Musk comments telling advertisers who don&amp;rsquo;t want to advertise on Twitter to &amp;ldquo;Go F*** Yourself.&amp;rdquo; Then, Charlotte has been obsessed with The Golden Bachelor and has some scorching hot takes after Gerry was exposed as a fraud by an ex-girlfriend. This conversation takes a dive toward using pickup lines, confidence in farting, and old folks getting freaky.</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: Bring Back Kevin Pollak! | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590194/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 16:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590194/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shaq has gotten mad at both Dan and Amin and has &amp;ldquo;3&amp;rdquo; words to describe Heat Culture. Charlotte continues to tell INCREDIBLE jokes, and Jess and Lucy discuss the new imaging for their College Football show that&amp;rsquo;s definitely not called Foot Girls™️. Plus, we&amp;rsquo;re all rooting for CFP chaos, College Gameday is changing, and Disney&amp;rsquo;s Bob Iger caves to the &amp;ldquo;go woke, go broke&amp;rdquo; mentality. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: The Chicken of the Trees | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590195/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 15:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590195/</guid><description>Podcast Description After Amin Elhassan reveals he&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;not a good breather,&amp;rdquo; Dan wants to have a conversation with the Oddball crew and the Shipping Container about iguanas taking over South Florida. Then, Mike still hates K*** L**** of the Miami Heat, Chris wants us to appreciate their recent years of success, and Erik Spoelstra&amp;rsquo;s divorce leads us to discussing the loneliness and unhappiness in coaching. Plus, Charlotte freezes, Mark Cuban getting out of NBA ownership could mean a sign of something more, and JuJu and Amin tell us about an impromptu stand-up show they witnessed last night.</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: Spotify Wrap It Up | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590196/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 22:07:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590196/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;Stop sharing your Spotify Wrapped.&amp;rdquo; - Billy, and not JuJu. Plus, the Kelce empire continues to grow. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: YGFY...Or Else | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590197/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 22:06:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590197/</guid><description>Podcast Description Twista is doing something the rap game has never seen before: rapping over machine guns firing AND&amp;hellip;ventriloquism. Then, how in the world can Arkansas need to vet Bobby Petrino when his transgressions happened under their watch? A segment featuring Petrino, Art Briles, Jon Gruden and some good, clean fun. Plus, Aaron Rodgers&amp;rsquo; practice window has opened and he seemingly has a message for Dan, Amin and Jess have a debate over the best Monopoly game, and Tony almost gets arrested while delivering his Tony&amp;rsquo;s Top 5.</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: BOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590198/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590198/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is Julius Randle one of the best New York Knicks of the last 20 years? How much of a narcissist is Gregg Popovich for asking the San Antonio Spurs crowd to stop booing Kawhi Leonard? Then, it&amp;rsquo;s time to play everyone&amp;rsquo;s favorite game AGAINST THE SPREAD and listen to this week&amp;rsquo;s Useless Sound Montage. Plus, we&amp;rsquo;ve met the Stugotz of the movie industry, and Billy has a new life hack that can hopefully make him a huge profit.</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: The Remarkable Belt Revelation | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590199/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 16:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590199/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two heartbreaking losses for basketball fans in Miami lead the conversation after the Blue Blood Canes were taken down by Kentucky and the Heat dropped their In-Season Tournament game to Damian Lillard and the Bucks. Then, the cast of Oddball (Amin Elhassan &amp;amp; Charlotte Wilder) join us and it leads us to an unbelievable moment of unity around the use of belts. Plus, Airplane Repo, Amin&amp;rsquo;s new friend, Knicks fans need a fake title, and the potential end of the Golden State Warriors as Klay Thompson&amp;rsquo;s play diminishes.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: Whose Fault is This? | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590200/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 16:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590200/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Samson and his connectivity issues are here for his Wednesday Local Hour as we kick things off with the huge news of Mark Cuban selling his majority stake in the Dallas Mavericks. Then, Jessica used to work for Sports Illustrated and leads our conversation on the bombshell story of their use of Artificial Intelligence and passing it off as human writers. Plus, KFitz makes us Fall Apart, Billy has an update on Hard Knocks, and Jess may disagree with Lucy for the first time&amp;hellip;ever.</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: Cannibalism? | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590179/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 18:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Folks, we have a brand new edible mascot: The Pop Tarts Bowl has unveiled its newest creation. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: Serum Gate | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590180/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 18:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan finally admits how much he loves costumes and offers to build a statue, we watch Lucy&amp;rsquo;s video from Ohio State-Michigan, and Jeremy, Stugotz, and Greg take a trip to the Bucket of Death. Then, Jay Glazer joins the show to process the aftermath of Serum Gate and share his love of love. He also discusses the ever-breaking quarterback position, meddlesome owners, and more storylines across the NFL. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: Your Opinion of My Opinion Doesn't Matter As Much as My Opinion | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590181/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 16:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Did you know The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz once held a live event at a Japanese restaurant in Doral called Soo Woo? Well, we remember, and we take a look back at the video. Then, Dan has a meandering but shocking Top 5 involving last night&amp;rsquo;s Clippers-Nuggets game, Greg and Chris Cote are legitimately hurting each other&amp;rsquo;s feelings, and Jer Bear might have a new t-shirt in the works.</description></item><item><title>The Truth About Magic Johnson's Tweets, and More of the Internet's Most Important Mysteries | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590182/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 16:28:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590182/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who runs Magic&amp;rsquo;s extraordinarily earnest Twitter account? Is Wu-Tang really that good at chess? Just how racist is the Oklahoma Sooner mascot? Is Victor Wembanyama the end of human evolution? Also: cotton balls, buttholes, and trolls. You asked, we investigated — with a little help from Rob Lowe, Method Man, Masta Killa, and Killers of the Flower Moon author David Grann.
Watch on YouTube: https://youtu.be/zAJhIrX1vBs Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: What Is Going On? | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590183/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 16:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590183/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pablo Torre joins us to give his best ideas for a Greg Cote mascot and to rail against the new Meadowlark Media logo before discussing the right&amp;rsquo;s attack on Deadspin after a child in a racist costume at the Kansas City Chiefs game (just slightly less racist than we thought) was posted to their site. Then, the crew gets into a heated debate over the merits of the NBA In-Season Tournament ahead of tonight&amp;rsquo;s showdown between the Heat and Bucks.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: The Doddering Old Man | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590184/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 15:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590184/</guid><description>Podcast Description There&amp;rsquo;s a lot going on this morning as Greg Cote joins us for his first appearance on MAX and immediately takes the show in the one direction we don&amp;rsquo;t want it to go. Then, an explosive signing for the Dolphins, fireworks in the Florida Panthers game, and the end of Frank Reich means an ungodly amount of money. Plus, Canes Football talk leads to some eye rolling from the back of the class.</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: Sunday Night Live With Tony &amp; JuJu | NFL Week 12 | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590185/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590185/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tony and JuJu break down everything you need to know for Week 12 of the NFL on Sunday Night Live. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: There, I Said It | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590186/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590186/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dolly Parton had a moment on Thanksgiving in Dallas, and Chris Cote said the thing you think he said. Then, Alex Smith is great on TV, the Shohei Ohtani sweepstakes are taking off, Adam Driver has a wild response to a fan, and something&amp;rsquo;s gotta give. Plus, Stugotz doesn&amp;rsquo;t want more Heat, and Mike Ryan has his hate for Deion Sanders rewarded by Colorado&amp;rsquo;s record this season. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: Stugotz Didn't Say It | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590187/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590187/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stugotz kicks things off with his Weekend Observations and struggles to hit his own benchmarks. Then, NFL games need to be flexed, Stu believes Joe Buck needs to mention him on Monday Night Football, Jalen Milroe claims the Heisman, and Mike cries over a commercial for The Home Depot. Plus, Tyrese Haliburton is a star, Iowa is offensive to watch, and Tony brings us his All-Squint Team. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: Mother Dorothy | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590188/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 17:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590188/</guid><description>Podcast Description We have some breaking NFL news including two of the worst owners in the league, David Tepper and Jim Irsay, and also Irsay&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Black Mother, Dorothy.&amp;rdquo; Then, Saturdays football was way better than Sundays, Stugotz has some Justin Herbert takes, and one college football coach was trampled while another rode out of the tunnel on an ATV&amp;hellip;one of those coaches kept his job. Plus, Tim Boyle is soooooooooooo much better than Zach Wilson, Mike McDaniel steals your girl, and Tua loves Secret Santa.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: Zip-Lining in Connecticut | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590189/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590189/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan, Stu, and the Shipping Container are pumped up for their first day on MAX! The crew discusses if GoFundMe is the modernized version of begging, feeling bad for Mac Jones, truly terrible NFL offenses, and the Oregon Ducks mascot&amp;rsquo;s lack of fear. Then, it&amp;rsquo;s time to discuss how the current NFL standings make absolutely zero sense. Plus, Jake Tapper is here to welcome us to MAX and discuss his Philadelphia Eagles, Jalen Hurts, talking smack to Wolf Blitzer, and what an eagle can do to a buffalo.</description></item><item><title>Monday Hangover- Watch Out For The Broncos | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590190/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 15:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590190/</guid><description>Podcast Description Billy took a cold shower and is on one. Lucy is back from The Game and breaks down an exciting weekend in college football. We play a new game of Lucy or Goosey, Top 5 People/Teams Who Owe An Apology, Top 5 Coach of the Year candidates and BBBBBB! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Best Of DLS: Jim Brockmire | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590176/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 16:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590176/</guid><description>Podcast Description We close out this day after Thanksgiving Best Of fiesta with the very best from Jim Brockmire. He&amp;rsquo;s talking Donald Trump, the Oakland A&amp;rsquo;s, Denver Nuggets, and Babe Ruth. Also, he&amp;rsquo;s insulted by mere the existence of David Samson. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Best of DLS: ALL THINGS FOOTBALL | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590177/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 16:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590177/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s ALL THINGS FOOTBALL as we continue this day after Thanksgiving Best Of. Stugotz thinks Jake Owen is Aaron Rodgers, nobody understands the rules of the Pro Bowl besides Peyton Manning, we check in with Lucy Rohden at the Tennessee/Florida game, and David Pollack joins the show. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Best of DLS: The Sodfather + Stephen A. Smith + Bert Kreischer | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590178/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 15:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590178/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s the day after Thanksgiving. You&amp;rsquo;re tired. So sit back relax and enjoy some Best Ofs. We have Stan Van Gundy giving hot movie takes, Dan tells Stephen A. Smith he doesn&amp;rsquo;t like what he&amp;rsquo;s done to sports television, and we talk to Bert Kreischer about how Dan ruined his podcast with Bill Burr. But that&amp;rsquo;s not all. We also discuss why Will Arnett hates Dan, why Adnan Virk hates Tom Cruise, why The Sodfather hates Eddie Mangan, and why Mike Schur hates David Samson.</description></item><item><title>THOMAHAWK - Shared Showers, Locker Room Hijinks &amp; Best Thanksgiving Dishes | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590169/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome back to The ThomaHawk Show! This week hosts Andrew Hawkins and Joe Thomas and the ThomaFlawk, Phat Nattt &amp;amp; Juju Gotti debate the controversy of sideline reporting, as well as the news of Patrick Mahomes wearing the same underwear every game. This leads to a rabbit hole conversation about nasty NFL habits, for example, Hawk claims that most NFL players pee their pants during the game&amp;hellip;They also talk football and share their favorite thanksgiving.</description></item><item><title>UNDERDOGS - An NFL Three (Turkey) Leg Parlay | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590170/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 15:19:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590170/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s Thanksgiving week and “Underdogs” co-hosts Jordan Brenner and Peter Keating are here to help you sound like the smartest sports fan at your holiday table. The guys have done the research for you on a three-leg Thanksgiving Day NFL parlay that could help you win big. Plus, they’re giving some insight on other ways to cash in on Turkey Day. Then, they draft their best underrated side dishes.</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: The Hockey Show with Roy and David | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590171/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590171/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is not a best of. But it is Roy and David Dwork of The Hockey News talking hockey with ESPN&amp;rsquo;s John Buccigross. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Best of DLS: The Day the Lights Went Out In The Elser | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590172/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590172/</guid><description>Podcast Description While you continue to enjoy your dry cornbread and even drier turkey, here is some more Best Of. The show is embarrassed on another national platform as the electricity said bye-bye while Dan was on The Dan Patrick Show. Speaking of goodbyes, we say goodbye to Chris Wittyngham, who went on to greener pitches. And Jessica has a list for Witty. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.</description></item><item><title>The Best of DLS: Farewell Clevelander | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590173/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590173/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gobble gobble. We continue the Best Of with some memories. We talk about leaving The Clevelander and remember the garage. We don&amp;rsquo;t necessarily want to keep those memories. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Best of DLS: Would You Attend Their Funeral?! | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590174/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 13:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590174/</guid><description>Podcast Description We continue this Thanksgiving Best Of with Billy and Chris doing the Miami Marlins spring training broadcast, Dan and David Samson played their favorite game, &amp;ldquo;Would you attend their funeral?!&amp;rdquo;, and we talk to UFO expert Jeremy Corbell. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Best of DLS: Gymtimidation | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590175/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590175/</guid><description>Podcast Description GOBBLE GOBBLE!! This Thanksgiving we are going down memory lane. We start with the crew discuss feeling intimidated at the gym and Sarah Spain joins us to discuss street fighting and the job Billy is doing as ruler of the Bucket of Death. Also. Amin Elhassan has a Top 5 list involving a zombie apocalypse. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>God Bless Thanksgiving Football! | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590163/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 22:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Thanksgiving from the GBF crew! Chris Simms assures us that he doesn&amp;rsquo;t tackle kids at his family&amp;rsquo;s Thanksgiving Day game. Mike Golic is impressed by Billy&amp;rsquo;s solution to the CFP committee&amp;rsquo;s playoff conundrum. Austin Ekeler shares his thoughts on his team&amp;rsquo;s loss and Stugotz puts him in an uncomfortable spot. Juju Gotti is back and joins the guys to make picks this week! Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: I'm Trying To Warn Travis | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590164/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590164/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stu has some choice words for the media, KC fans and Swifties. He also says he can do the job of any sports radio host in the country. We also update the polls for the week. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: A Chorus of Fake Zagackis | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590165/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Le Batard, Stugotz and the crew do Against The Spread, we find out what Billy Gil is growing in his fridge, and we spin the wheel of topics for our chorus of fake Joe Zagackis. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: After The Game with Roy.. Sometimes.. But Not Before Thanksgiving | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590166/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590166/</guid><description>Podcast Description Le Batard, Stugotz and the crew discuss the first episode of Hard Knocks with the Miami Dolphins, we try to understand the launch strategy for Roy&amp;rsquo;s new hockey shows, and we talk about the Hall &amp;amp; Oates lawsuit with Mike Schur. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Big Suey: Fried Flinstone | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590167/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan got through 7 minutes of the new Barry Sanders documentary before turning it off - Stu says the Lions won the Stafford/Goff trade even though the Rams won a Super Bowl. Plus, Joe Buck joins the show from a yacht and the Useless Sound Montage returns. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: Don't Bruin The Segment | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590168/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590168/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Samson tries (and fails) to discuss Stephen Ross selling a minority stake in the Miami Dolphins. Plus, the crew asks if there is yet another &amp;lsquo;must-win&amp;rsquo; game for Mario Cristobal and the University Of Miami. Black Friday will be a disorienting day for South Florida sports fans with the Dolphins, Canes, Heat and Panthers all playing. Also, Roy has how many hockey shows on the network? Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>PTFO - How Sam Bankman-Fried Sportswashed an $8 Billion Crypto Fraud, Starring Tom Brady and Steph Curry | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590151/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 00:06:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590151/</guid><description>Podcast Description The FTX founder was a &amp;ldquo;martian&amp;rdquo; to the sports world. Why did he spend so much on arena naming rights and superstar endorsements? And how the hell did SBF become friends with TB12? Authors Michael Lewis (Going Infinite) and Zeke Faux (Number Go Up) witnessed the rise and fall of a crypto king. Now we can do the postmortem: “Moneyball, on steroids, gone wrong.” Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: Do People Like the Manning Cast? | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590152/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 19:02:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why is LeBron recruiting Jeremiah Smith on behalf of Ohio State? Is there real estate for Kevin Hart to host a ManningCast type show for the NBA? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: Too Many Candles For Joe Biden | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590153/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 17:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590153/</guid><description>Podcast Description Le Batard, Stugotz and the crew discuss Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s birthday cake, Angel Reese disappearing from the LSU women&amp;rsquo;s basketball team, and Brian Stelter joins the show. Also, we go to the Bucket of Death. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: Are You Scared of Tim Boyle? | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590154/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 17:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jim Harbaugh was weird during a press conference. Chris Cote apparently is afraid of the unknown. That unknown&amp;hellip;is Tim Boyle. The Commanders had only cold water for the visitor showers. Is Apple TV a place celebrities go to hide? And Dan is old. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: TaylorCyst? | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590155/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Friend of the show Brad Williams was getting after it on the jumbotron at the Denver Broncos game, Stugotz clearly isn&amp;rsquo;t listening and Tom Brady has become &amp;lsquo;back in my day NFL guy&amp;rsquo;. Plus, Ron Magill joins to answer all animal related questions and promote his new book &amp;lsquo;Pride Of A Lion&amp;rsquo;. Also, Lucy talks about her experience at Clemson this weekend and the quirky things that happen on gameday.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: Ever Caulked A Hole? | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590156/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590156/</guid><description>Podcast Description The crew asks if you ever need a show with your ice cream, Stu owes a bunch of punishments and needs to pay them off and Billy makes a potentially unjust ruling as the Iron fisted commissioner of the &amp;lsquo;BOD&amp;rsquo;. Plus, does Travis Kelce need to start focusing on football, the Chiefs pass catchers seem to all have butterfingers and Jalen Carter almost made the most incredible play in NFL history.</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: Get Lost | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590157/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590157/</guid><description>Podcast Description The crew remembers when getting lost on the road was just par for the course of life, now it means you&amp;rsquo;re an idiot. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: Stugotz's Weekend Observations | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590158/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 18:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590158/</guid><description>Podcast Description Le Batard, Stugotz and the crew discuss Charissa Thompson admitting to making up sideline reports, whether or not we trust Waze when we&amp;rsquo;re driving, and Stugotz has his Weekend Observations. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: Nothing Better Than a Good Buffet | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590159/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fox Sports college football analyst Joel Klatt joins the show to talk about how impeccable he is. The Lions are historically good&amp;hellip;for them. Jerry Jones will never die. Plus, Andscape contributor Justin Tinsley joins us to talk about Diddy and Cassie Ventura&amp;rsquo;s civil lawsuit. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: The Fart Game | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590160/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590160/</guid><description>Podcast Description More football injuries, including the one that wrecked FSU QB Jordan Travis&amp;rsquo; season. Tim Legler doesn&amp;rsquo;t like us anymore and it&amp;rsquo;s all because of our years-long obsession with his Halloween decorations. The Browns are good. The Jets are not. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: Winded | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590161/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590161/</guid><description>Podcast Description Charissa Thompson made it all up and now every media member is angry. Jalen Ramsey sacrificed his breathing ability to secure a Dolphins victory. Another ambulance drove onto an NFL field. The Miami Hurricanes basketball team won an in-season tournament. And the Chargers have failed Justin Herbert. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Monday Hangover- Super Bowl Recap/Preview | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590162/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 15:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590162/</guid><description>Podcast Description The guys get ready for the rare Super Bowl rematch that this also a preview. Lucy&amp;rsquo;s back from Seattle and Clemson! Stugotz shares his Top 5 things that he knows. Billy&amp;rsquo;s has a fresh set of BBBBBB picks. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>PTFO - Share &amp; Tell (OnlyDans Edition) with Mina Kimes, Dan Le Batard, and Pablo | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590001/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 21:05:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590001/</guid><description>Podcast Description How close did Dan get to death&amp;rsquo;s door on ketamine? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: After the Week with Roy | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590002/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Roy Bellamy hosts a new version of &amp;ldquo;After the Game with Roy&amp;rdquo; called &amp;ldquo;After The Week with Roy,&amp;rdquo; featuring David Dwork and his recently torn ACL. The Florida Panthers have been playing some great hockey while dealing with injuries, and the duo explains how they&amp;rsquo;ve been able to get it done. Then, Roy and David discuss Jaromír Jágr&amp;rsquo;s upcoming jersey retirement, goaltenders heading to the Hall of Fame, some NHL rule changes, and a couple of Connors cuttin&amp;rsquo; it up.</description></item><item><title>#BecauseMiami: Managed Retreat | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590003/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Damian Pardo, who is running against Sabina Covo for a commissioner&amp;rsquo;s seat in Miami&amp;rsquo;s District 2&amp;rsquo;s run-off election, and James Torres, who ran against Damian Pardo just recently in the general election, joins Billy Corben in-studio to talk about political partnerships and Covo&amp;rsquo;s wooing of Torres for his support. Also, NBC 6 hurricane specialist John Morales joins the show to talk about that vicious storm that happened in South Florida this week.</description></item><item><title>Sporting Class: The Great Streaming Lie - It Was Never Going to Be Cheaper Than the Cable Bundle | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590004/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Meadowlark Media CEO John Skipper and Nothing Personal&amp;rsquo;s David Samson are back with another episode with Pablo Torre Finds Out host&amp;hellip; Pablo Torre to host! Welcome to the Sporting Class! We start today off with streaming! We’re going streaming! Remember when everyone thought that streaming would cost less than cable? Who lied to us!? Then, the last of the streamers to get into the sports world… Netflix. Are they ready for live sports?</description></item><item><title>South Beach Sessions - Marcellus Wiley | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590005/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590005/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a rare glimpse into the soul of a man who&amp;rsquo;s not afraid to tackle any situation - a front-row seat to the unfiltered wisdom of Marcellus Wiley.
Dan and Marcellus toss aside the small talk and dive straight into the sacrifices necessary for chasing dreams, battling doubts, complacency, and the pivotal moments that drive them forward. Marcellus also lays bare his regrets on his fatherhood, unpacking the heavy baggage of shame around his insecurities, and reflects on how he and Max Kellerman navigated the uncharted waters of on-air vulnerability and developed a brotherhood that stands the test of time.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: That's a Good List | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590006/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590006/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;Things are moving fast around here.&amp;rdquo; Dan is throwing food into his mouth like a pelican, and Chris Cote&amp;rsquo;s daughter is more liked than Willow. Dan and the crew discuss the ever-changing workplace as more and more people elect to work from home, Complicated Joe Zagacki makes an appearance to share his opinion, and Amin discusses the end of the Actor&amp;rsquo;s Strike. Then, everyone goes to the Bucket of Death, and Dan, Mike, and Lucy break down what a Miami win over Louisville would mean in a game for the Schnellenberger Trophy that is somehow not a mustache or pipe.</description></item><item><title>GBF- Will Anderson, Juju Gotti, Ekeler, Boselli | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590007/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 14:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590007/</guid><description>Podcast Description (0:00) Juju Gotti joins Stugotz, Mikey and Billy to recap TNF&amp;rsquo;s multiple injuries and the Stugotz of sideline reporters. (8:38) Will Anderson believe his QB should be Rookie of the Year and MVP. (19:53) Chris Simms isn&amp;rsquo;t out on Josh Allen and has interesting interception stats in regards to the top QBs in the NFL. (39:22) Stu Ya Gotz. (44:16) In an unexpected twist Austin Ekeler has a pitch for the guys.</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: Tony's Top 5 | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tony delivers his Top 5 on a Thursday live from Domino Park. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: Can I Be The Awful Person In The Room? | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 18:51:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can Aaron Rodgers win Comeback Player of the Year? Jessica is enjoying her shift to the back row and very intrigued by Arkansas redshirt players watching Polar Express in the locker room at halftime. How does Chip Kelly feel about his career? Mike continues to bask in Victor Wembenyama&amp;rsquo;s struggles and the gang discusses Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s popularity in the wake of his announced A24 biopic. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: Scape Goat or Sacrificial Lamb with Mina Kimes | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 18:23:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andre 3000 is dropping a new album, but it&amp;rsquo;s all flute. How does Draymond keep getting away with this? Then Mina Kimes returns with a brand spankin new backdrop to discuss what&amp;rsquo;s wrong in Buffalo, merging families for Thanksgiving, Justin Herbert, her likability compared to other show personalities and misunderstood defensive statistics. Plus Amin&amp;rsquo;s Top 5 Evil Billionaires. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: I DO Know About Sports | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590011/</guid><description>Podcast Description We ask the quintessential questions: are people more or less honest on the internet? Was Rudy Gobert fined for being French? And, most importantly, where is Lucy going this weekend? Plus, Chris Cote hates love. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: An Embarrassment of Riches | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 16:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Brad Williams joins the show today&amp;hellip;as does Lucy, who was shamed back into the studio after taking a couple of days off for self-care. Also, do you like street poets? Plus, the Useless Sound Montage barely makes in time. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: Scorching Hot Holiday Music Takes | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 18:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris Cote wants to find the holiday that DOESN&amp;rsquo;T have its own song. Jessica introduces us to a Thanksgiving horror film. Billy tells us about a Publix holiday commercial that makes us cry. And, Jeremy teaches us about The Monster Mash, and, despite warning from the group, he is going after Mariah Carey. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: Stugotz Is On The Hot Seat? | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590014/</guid><description>Podcast Description We watch the video of Lucy taking her trip to Washington and running into some huge fans of the show. The fire alarms continue in the studio, Amin workshops another limited fake and this time it&amp;rsquo;s Emmanuel Acho, and Roy&amp;rsquo;s vampire gives him a new voice. Then, it&amp;rsquo;s time for everyone&amp;rsquo;s favorite game: AGAINST! THE! SPREAD! Plus, Mike&amp;rsquo;s secret fist pump, Deshaun Watson&amp;rsquo;s injury, and coaches who will never be fired.</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: We're Sorry About the Fire Alarm | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590015/</guid><description>Podcast Description A U.S. Senator wants to fight the leader of the Teamsters, and Bernie Sanders might be the referee? Then, we need to stop body-shaming Stugotz, everyone hates Rudy Gobert, and Amin workshops his limited fake Antonio Banderas. Plus, Stugotz believes he has definitive proof of why the ring cam footage of a supposed Bill Belichick is DEFINITELY Bill Belichick in &amp;ldquo;The Worcester Walk of Shame.&amp;rdquo; Also, the Panera Charged Lemonade, chaos in the workplace, and Dan Campbell recommends diapers.</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: 13 Seconds | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 16:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dion Dawkins embraces body positivity, JuJu Gotti is furious with the Buffalo Bills for scapegoating Ken Dorsey, and did you remember the Bengals made the Super Bowl the year of the Bills-Chiefs game? Then, would Stugotz actually kill for Josh Allen to be his QB? And Jessica is doing some private jet tracking. Plus, Garrett Graff wrote the book on UFO&amp;rsquo;s and is definitely not himself an alien. He explains what he&amp;rsquo;s learned in his search for extra terrestrial life including weird junk in the sky, FOAF Tales, and more.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: I Am Not a Kook | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590017/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Samson is here for his Wednesday Local Hour, but first, we have to get to the recent success of the local teams and Roy and Stugotz&amp;rsquo;s Bucket of Death punishments. David discusses the potential relocation of the Oakland A&amp;rsquo;s, Brian Cashman being &amp;ldquo;done&amp;rdquo; in New York, Trevor Bauer, a U.S. Senator trying to throw hands, and more. Plus, the impossibly sweet Pablo López joins the show to share the details of his upcoming &amp;ldquo;Pickleball for Pets&amp;rdquo; event in Miami as we try to get him to say something mean.</description></item><item><title>PTFO - Why Listening to Action Bronson Makes Us Happy | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590018/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 21:15:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Action Bronson raps, cooks, paints, hosts, and acts (for Martin Scorsese, at least). He also has philosophical explanations for why A) he never wears pants, B) his go-to move is the headbutt, and C) nothing is better than a VHS tape. But Action Bronson had still never heard of the Accidental Bronson tribute account. Until now. Plus: AOL screennames, robot vacuum murder, and saggy balls.
Watch on YouTube: https://youtu.</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: Law (Taylor's Version) | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590019/</guid><description>Podcast Description The crew takes a trip to the Bucket of Death before discussing the kiss seen around the world between Travis Kelce and Taylor Swift. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: Kids Schmids | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590020/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590020/</guid><description>Podcast Description The show erupts over the news of Ken Dorsey being fired in Buffalo! Then, Greg&amp;rsquo;s alliterative takedowns of Hypocrite Harbaugh and Kids Schmids, Dan&amp;rsquo;s anger over Michigan vs. Penn State, and Greg Cote&amp;rsquo;s Back in my Day. Plus, we get to today&amp;rsquo;s Stat of the Day, Jess updates us on some potential problems for F1 this weekend in Las Vegas, and we hear from a new voice with a limited fake Joe Zagacki.</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: JT's on the River | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris Cote wants to know what the most frustrating penalty is in the NFL, and the rest of the crew has some strong opinions. Then, Greg&amp;rsquo;s wife, the Unnamed Attorney, mother of Oliver or Charlie, Earleen Cote joins us to discuss all the ways Greg has been gaslighting us throughout today&amp;rsquo;s show. Plus, our conversation on tipping continues into the nuanced places, Bally social media, and our favorite new restaurant.</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: Is The Big Dipper a Big Tipper? | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 16:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Action Bronson doesn&amp;rsquo;t wear pants, but Greg &amp;lsquo;The Big Dipper&amp;rsquo; Cote has some issues with the definition of &amp;ldquo;pants.&amp;rdquo; Greg continues to share some giant lies including being a good tipper and knowing how to accept when he&amp;rsquo;s wrong. Then, Ron Magill is here to share actual copies of the new book he and Greg wrote called &amp;ldquo;The Pride of a Lion,&amp;rdquo; with a special deal for those who order today.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: That's Why They Call it Window Pane | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Billy is ruling with an iron fist, so Greg Cote has his hand in a jar of mayo and Jeremy is the show&amp;rsquo;s waiter today, and for some reason he has a bad New York (?) accent. The Bills and Broncos Monday Night Football game has the crew asking some questions like: Is Russell Wilson back to being a Hall of Famer? Does Josh Allen indeed have a stupid face?</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: UFC 295 LIVE From The Mecca | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tony takes you inside MSG for UFC 295 where the Heavyweight (interim) and Light Heavyweight Title are won in real time. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: Stephen A. Smith Loves Latina Women | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 19:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590025/</guid><description>Podcast Description The CMAs had some interesting award winners, and none greater than Jelly Roll and Tracy Chapman&amp;rsquo;s victory 35 years after the release of her song. Then, the Dan&amp;rsquo;s time is precious, UFC welcomes the right wing to the festivities, and Stephen A. Smith professes his love for Latina women. Plus, Tommy DeVito lives with his parents, Josh Dobbs thrives in Minnesota, Austin Burke&amp;rsquo;s slogan, and Nolan Ryan can still bring it.</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: James Harden IS the System | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590026/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 18:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 1 kicks off with Stugotz&amp;rsquo;s Weekend Observations! Then, it&amp;rsquo;s time to talk about the flailing Clippers and James Harden wanting to be &amp;ldquo;the system&amp;rdquo; of whichever team he&amp;rsquo;s on. Plus, Mike believes everyone is misinterpreting his Wemby take, Billy accidentally locks his daughter in the car, and he loves his Apple Watch. Enter now at www.millertimemiami.com Presented by @millerlite #ad No purchase necessary. Open to legal US residents, age 21 and older.</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: Get Your Chips in Order | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590027/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stugotz is doing his football research. The problem is he recorded God Bless Football hours ago. Dan has questions about gas station food in the south and why it&amp;rsquo;s better than the north.Then, CJ Stroud leads a wacky football Sunday, pass rushers are on another level, Zach Wilson throws a Hail Mary, and it&amp;rsquo;s Jameis Time, baby. Plus, Billy and Tony have suggestions for the fired Jimbo Fisher, Dan Campbell is Dan Campbelling everywhere, and Michigan Football is a comedy.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: A Guardian of the Great Game of Basketball | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590028/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 15:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Duncan Robinson, huh? After discussing the Chargers excellence in losing and Mike Tomlin and the Steelers continuing to win ugly, Dan, Stu, and the crew Duncan Robinson dominating Victor Wembanyama and the San Antonio Spurs. Then, Bill Belichick and the struggling Patriots, the ever-confusing Baltimore Ravens, and Antonio Pierce&amp;rsquo;s Raiders. Plus, Mike continues his crusade against Wemby, and while watching last night&amp;rsquo;s game, found support from an interesting ally in his movement.</description></item><item><title>GBF- $76 MIllion To Do Nothing | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590029/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 13:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jimbo Fisher was fired by Texas A&amp;amp;M and will get paid $76 million to not coach. Would the guys ever work again if they had that deal? Exciting day in the NFL if you like FGs as 5 games ended on FGs and all the Jets and Raiders wanted to do was kick FGs. Did Mikey A. get his field pass in Vegas? Billy is back with his BBBBBB, has a list of the Top 5 People Doing Their Part in the Caleb Williams Sweepstakes.</description></item><item><title>#BecauseMiami: The Post-Debate Show | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590030/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590030/</guid><description>Podcast Description The circus that was the GOP debate has left Miami. David Weigel, political reporter for Semafor, and Marc Caputo, national political reporter for The Messenger, joins Billy Corben to give the postmortem on the Republican debate shenanigans. And Billy gives an update on the elections for the city of Miami&amp;rsquo;s Districts 1 and 2, as well as an update on the Ball &amp;amp; Chain civil lawsuit. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: Jessica And Lucy Explain The College Football World | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590031/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jess and Lucy are back with their Unnamed College Football Segment a.k.a. The Michigan MANifesto. They discuss Connor Stalions and Michigan Football, their upcoming game against Penn State, the CFP rankings, the Washington-USC shootout, previews of this week&amp;rsquo;s game, and more. Then, we have an excerpt from the podcast &amp;ldquo;Sports Explains the World&amp;rdquo; and their episode &amp;lsquo;Spider&amp;rsquo;s Web&amp;rsquo; which explores the death of American Alpine skier Vladimir Peter Sabich at the hands of his girlfriend Claudine Longet, who claimed it was an accident.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: The High Road Loses | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590032/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is &amp;lsquo;The Fall of the House of Usher&amp;rsquo; about Usher? Dan discusses his inability to spend more money on another streaming service to watch South Park&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Panderverse&amp;rdquo; before the crew goes to the Bucket of Death. Then, Peter Rosenberg joins us to discuss his new podcast &amp;ldquo;Over the Top&amp;rdquo; with Michelle Beadle, working with Don La Greca, doing what he loves, taking the high road, Kendrick Lamar, and more.</description></item><item><title>GBF- Paul Finebaum, Swagu, Ekeler, Golic &amp; Simms | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590033/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590033/</guid><description>Podcast Description (0:00) After months of notice Golic and Simms still haven&amp;rsquo;t been able to get Mikey A. sideline passes for this weekend&amp;rsquo;s Jets game in Las Vegas that they&amp;rsquo;re both covering. Golic previews this weekend&amp;rsquo;s other games and refuses to take his shirt off. (20:24) Paul Finebaum is not a fan of James Franklin and shares conspiracy theories from Alabama fans. Check out the full Finabaum interview on this week&amp;rsquo;s episode of Stupodity.</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: Love on The Weekend | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590034/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 19:17:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stephen A. Smith tells us which day of the week is the best to have sex. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: Jack Spade | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590035/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 19:15:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590035/</guid><description>Podcast Description George &amp;ldquo;The Iceman&amp;rdquo; Gervin joins the show to discuss his career, his new book, what he learned from growing up in the inner city, and to listen to Mike&amp;rsquo;s Victor Wembanyama take. Then, Dillon Brooks loves attention, and Emma Hayes may be the greatest hire in U.S. Soccer history. Plus, a former show guest was named People Magazine&amp;rsquo;s Sexiest Podcaster, Joe Burrow and Josh Allen call each other buddy, pal, brother, and man, and we introduce the world to Jack Spade.</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: Tony's Tears | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590036/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 18:16:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590036/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s time for Tony&amp;rsquo;s Top 5, shirtless from the gym, and while we may not get Tony&amp;rsquo;s Tiers, we seem to get Tony&amp;rsquo;s Tears. Then, Thursday Thunder, the MLB GM meetings get sent to Tummy Ache City, and Mike continues his campaign against Wemby. Plus, Adnan Virk and David Samson join us to discuss their Top 5 movies from 2011-2020. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: Being Fat and Not Getting Hard | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590037/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 17:37:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590037/</guid><description>Podcast Description We kick off the Big Suey with more Tyler Van Dyke talk and whether college players can &amp;ldquo;not have it,&amp;rdquo; how much coaching has to do with college player success, and more. Then, the Cesta Cyclones are BACK, no one can protect their Quarterback, Al Michaels may hate Kirk Herbstreit, and Arthur Smith and Fred Smith are getting doxed. Plus, comedian Stavros Halkias is in Florida this week and introduces us to &amp;ldquo;Ronnie the Ravens fan&amp;rdquo; and discusses the highlights of his career.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: The Panthers Seventh Defenseman | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590038/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 16:24:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan questions his own leadership after &amp;ldquo;After the game with Roy (sometimes)&amp;rdquo; failed to produce a show after one of the best Panthers wins of the season. Mike believes the Panthers made one of the best trades in South Florida history, and he&amp;rsquo;s also been hate-watching Dame Lillard and the Milwaukee Bucks. Then, Donald Trump is a favorite to win the Republican nomination &amp;ndash; even if he ends up in jail &amp;ndash; and he held a rally in Hialeah last night opposite the Republican debate.</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: Saying No to Jeff Bezos | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 18:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan was shocked by Colorado upsetting &amp;ldquo;Kim Mulkey&amp;rsquo;s LSU Tigers,&amp;rdquo; and Jess &amp;amp; Lucy explain how and why it happened. Stugotz and Billy are here to make fun of JJ Watt. Also, Jeff Bezos is moving to Miami, and Dan has a friend who&amp;rsquo;s made it more difficult. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: The Well Beautiful Jim Trotter | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jim Trotter joins the show to discuss his lawsuit against the NFL for racial discrimination. He shares the details of what went down with management, why he believes he did not have his contract renewed, the behind the scenes conversations and actions that led him to this lawsuit, details of team owner comments, and much more. Then, Dan is stuck on the fact that he&amp;rsquo;s never felt sexy, and Lucy is headed to Washington, and it may be the fall of democracy.</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: Analytics is the New Woke | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590041/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 18:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Piggybacking off of our conversation about the very sexy Jason Kelce, Dan laments that he&amp;rsquo;s NEVER felt sexy, but Jess believes there&amp;rsquo;s a &amp;ldquo;sexy you&amp;rdquo; inside everyone. We discuss what it takes to feel sexy regardless of how you view your personal appearance. Then, Mad Dog Russo is indignant about managerial hires, Connor Stalions was selling vacuums, and we investigate the underwear of someone on the Eagles sideline. Plus, Stugotz reveals what his fortune cookie told him last night, and we play everyone&amp;rsquo;s favorite game: AGAINST THE SPREAD!</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: Dan Challenges Aaron Rodgers to a Debate | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 17:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jason Kelce has been nominated for People Magazine&amp;rsquo;s Sexiest Man Alive, and the entire crew has takes on how and why this came to be including Taylor Swift adjacency, body hair, hipster takes, and more. Then, we finally have the right Brian Cashman sound. Plus, after Billy&amp;rsquo;s take on Aaron Rodgers&amp;rsquo; fake achilles injury, Dan doubles down by, as a journalist, challenging Rodgers to a debate about his &amp;ldquo;fake doctors.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: LeBron James Cost Dwyane Wade His Proper Legacy | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590043/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Samson is here for his Wednesday Local Hour to discuss the concept of the lucky $2 bill, Greg Cote being a great dad, Peter Bendix joining the Marlins, Craig Counsell joining the Cubs, Brian Cashman, and Steve Cohen. Then, LeBron James fired off some hilarious tweets last night that reignites our decade-long argument about LeBron, Heat Culture, and Dwyane Wade&amp;rsquo;s legacy. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.</description></item><item><title>PTFO EXCLUSIVE - Donald Trump's Secret Weapon Is a Quarterback | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 01:12:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Johnny McEntee went viral before virality, as a trick-shot QB at UConn. He foresaw the rise of Donald Trump, while ordering him KFC on the campaign trail. He was straight out of central casting, but suddenly &amp;ldquo;Johnny Mac&amp;rdquo; the quarterback became enforcer-in-chief for the commander-in-chief, running a presidential &amp;ldquo;Gestapo&amp;rdquo; and hand-picking cabinet secretaries. Correspondent Devin Gordon meets a Trumpworld action figure and asks: How did this in-over-his-head loyalist get so powerful?</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: They Were Pretty Good With Mark Richt | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590045/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590045/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;Complicated Legacy Joe Zagacki&amp;rdquo; makes his return to the program. Plus, Dan listened to the Dolphins AM Radio Broadcast this weekend and questions whether Joe Rose&amp;rsquo;s enthusiasm can be real before suggesting a replacement for the &amp;lsquo;Miami Dolphins Number 1&amp;rsquo; theme song. Enter now at www.millertimemiami.com Presented by @millerlite #ad No purchase necessary. Open to legal US residents, age 21 and older. Ends November 16. See Official Rules for details.</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: A Long History of Doing Stupid Stuff | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590046/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Molly Jong-Fast of Fast Politics joins the show to discuss Election Day, polling in the United States, Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s felony charges, Trump vs. Biden, and much more across American politics. Then, after discussing our own political load management, the crew gets to their Stat of the Day and discusses Tony&amp;rsquo;s NEW nomination for the best jingle of all-time. Plus, there was a great viral moment from a fan making a shot at a Milwaukee Bucks game, and Stugotz, Billy, and Greg go to the Bucket of Death.</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: Hee-Haw Three | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590047/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 18:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stugotz loves the way Troy Aikman ripped Zach Wilson last night, but he has a problem with the way Dan and others are discussing the Craig Counsell news. Then, Josh &amp;ldquo;Jobs&amp;rdquo; Dobbs a.k.a. the Passtronaut is a sensation, but we have some concerns about how much the QBs across the NFL have been neutered by play-calling and check downs. Plus, does political polling still work if no one has a landline?</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: When Billy Showed Up at One O'Clock | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590048/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stugotz is at it again with another &amp;ldquo;overpromise and underdeliver&amp;rdquo; situation. The crew takes a look at last night&amp;rsquo;s Heat Culture court, Greg Cote admits he was wrong about a Messi take, and we learn more about &amp;lsquo;After The Game on Thursdays Depending on the Schedule featuring Roy.&amp;rsquo; Then, Mike Ryan believes the Canes are title contenders in Men&amp;rsquo;s Basketball, Dan is against due process, and Chris Simms bullies Billy Gil.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: The Aaron Rodgers Achilles Conspiracy | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590049/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 16:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan is questioning why the company paid for Chris Cote to go to Germany if he was going to be drunk the whole time, but Chris thought the assignment was simply &amp;ldquo;be Chris in Germany.&amp;rdquo; Also, Billy and Stugotz are having some complications with the God Bless Football schedule. Then, Billy unleashes an Aaron Rodgers conspiracy theory regarding his &amp;ldquo;torn achilles&amp;rdquo; and how he may be pulling the wool over all of our eyes.</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: Top 5 Cheaters | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590050/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 18:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590050/</guid><description>Podcast Description After discussing the Jim Harbaugh cheating scandal at Michigan, Stugotz delivers his Top 5 Cheaters in Sports. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: Sex Advice with Adam McKay | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590051/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 18:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590051/</guid><description>Podcast Description The crew discusses &amp;ldquo;The Grandpa Shake,&amp;rdquo; where old people squeeze your hand too tight and won&amp;rsquo;t let go. Then, CJ Stroud is a star, and the Michigan Football story continues to get more and more wild. Then, with the help of a new suggestion by McKinsey consultants, Adam McKay is here for his Climate Stat of the Day and some sex advice. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: Threatening to Throw Down | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590052/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 17:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590052/</guid><description>Podcast Description DeMarcus Ware is here and can&amp;rsquo;t believe what he&amp;rsquo;s been seeing from a speed and strength standpoint in the NFL and their pass rushers. Then, we&amp;rsquo;re talkin&amp;rsquo; Josh Dobbs, Clayton Tune, and Tyson Bagent. Plus, the NFL goal line may be the most dangerous place on earth, we learn about the Thiccer Kicker, and Stugotz is here with his Weekend Observations. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: Blue Bloods | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590053/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 16:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mike Ryan is outfitted by boosterism and is here to discuss the University of Miami&amp;rsquo;s Blue Blood basketball program as College Basketball gets going today. Lucy met a HUGE Le Batard fan at Bedlam, and we watch the video of her experience. Then, Jess wants the federal government to intervene in ACC football, Jer Bear&amp;rsquo;s puns aggravate the group, and Billy learns he&amp;rsquo;s not a good protester. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: The Duke Stakes His Reputation | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590054/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 15:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stugotz is struggling after a weekend away from watching football, Lucy was in tears at Bedlam, Jessica is done with weddings, and Billy stakes his reputation on a Buffalo Bills take. Then, Tyler Van Dyke and the Canes offense continues to struggle, and the Dolphins might not be as elite as we once thought. Plus, Stugotz is jealous of Jason Kelce, the Marlins have a new President of Baseball Operations, and Josh Dobbs saves the Day.</description></item><item><title>Monday Hangover: Miami Fraudphins? | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590055/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 14:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are the Dolphins frauds after their loss to the Kansas City Chiefs in Germany? Does it matter? Lucy returns from Bedlam where she and Rose almost got killed! Send Us Stuff returns and someone sent Lucy a 3D printed UFO lamp! We have two Top 5 lists, Billy&amp;rsquo;s Bets Big Board Brought to you By: is back and Billy&amp;rsquo;s hot. Will Stugotz owe Austin Ekeler $2,000 after tonight&amp;rsquo;s game?</description></item><item><title>PTFO - Share &amp; Tell (Dark Triad Edition) with Katie Nolan, Dan Le Batard, and Pablo Torre(s) | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590056/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 19:42:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Would you clone your dying dog? Why are burner accounts still a thing? And how much do you REALLY care about what other people think about you? Also: Stephen A. Smith mispronouncing Pablo&amp;rsquo;s name (twice), Dan sobbing shirtless in a convertible, and Pablo defending the relative scale of his narcissistic, psychopathic Machiavellianism.
Further reading:
Are Pet Cloners Happy With Their Choice? The Atlantic
HBO Bosses Used ‘Secret’ Fake Accounts to Troll TV Critics Rolling Stone</description></item><item><title>#BecauseMiami: The Toxic Revenger | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590057/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ron DeSantis&amp;rsquo; presidential campaign continues to be a disaster. Investigative reporter Jason Garcia updates Billy Corben on the ongoing court battle between Florida&amp;rsquo;s governor and The Walt Disney Company. Lisa Zayas of Florida Watch joins us to talk about DeSantis&amp;rsquo; bad polling numbers and bad PR. Plus, the Wheel of Despair. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: SPORTS! | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590058/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 13:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jess and Lucy are back for their Unnamed College Football Segment after kicking John Skipper and Dan out of the studio. They discuss the craziness of the Big 12 and ACC, the initial College Football Rankings, the coup at Iowa, the World&amp;rsquo;s Largest Outdoor Cocktail Party, Alabama vs. LSU, and more. Then, Roy, David Dwork and Chris Cote are back with The Talking Hockey with Roy Show to discuss the Florida Panthers, their injuries and additions, Chris Cote as a sneaky Swiftie, and their partying ways with Sara Civian at last year&amp;rsquo;s All-Star Game.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: The Fake Pregame Show | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590059/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 12:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590059/</guid><description>Podcast Description The show is sending Chris Cote to Germany to cover Dolphins-Chiefs which means the triumphant return of The Fake Pregame Show. Then, the crew visits the Bucket of Death, and Dan threatens Tony&amp;rsquo;s job status after Tony said people need to slack at their jobs more. Plus, there was a naked man who stole a cop car in Vegas, and it may or may not have been Mike Ryan.</description></item><item><title>Keyshawn Johnson's Getting A Haircut | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590060/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 12:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Keyshawn Johnson joins the show while his barber Vic cuts his hair. Key discusses Halloween decorations, the job Eric Bieniemy has done in Washington and how that has affected the Chiefs, what his time after ESPN has been like with Skip Bayless and has a few words for Dan Le Batard&amp;rsquo;s minions. #KLB #KHB Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>GBF- Marquez Valdes-Scantling, The Nigerian Nightmare Christian Okoye, Austin Ekeler &amp; More | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590061/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stugotz, Billy and Mike react to the release of the CFP rankings &amp;amp; realize they may be coming around on 9:30 games. (8:18) Billy gets too comfortable with Chris Simms and offers to leave him his spleen in his will as an apology. (29:50) Marquez Valdes-Scantling discusses Charmin toilet paper &amp;amp; his game in Germany. (38:50) Stugotz &amp;amp; Mikey A. are rooting against Austin Ekeler this week, Stu promises to donate to Austin&amp;rsquo;s charity if he doesn&amp;rsquo;t score a TD against the Jets.</description></item><item><title>South Beach Sessions - Joy Taylor | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590062/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joy Taylor is a beacon of strength.
In this emotionally charged and moving heart-to-heart, Joy shares the moments that tested her spirit and the lessons that propelled her to rise above adversity and find purpose in the face of challenges. Together, with candor and vulnerability, they uncover the profound connections that bind them as Joy reveals to Dan the pivotal role that Dan&amp;rsquo;s brother, David &amp;ldquo;Lebo&amp;rdquo; Le Batard, played in shaping her path.</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: Manual Cars | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590063/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 18:27:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris Cote has a question: What happened to manual cars? Chris, Tony, Mike and Jeremy discuss cars, bikes, magic, and more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: Rules for Red Eye Flights | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590064/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 18:23:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Liam Neeson has a new movie coming out and the crew is PUMPED about the name. Then, the Saudis are getting away with sportswashing, we hear the Useless Sound Montage, and we learn about our new favorite sports owner: John Textor. Plus, the Connor Stallions story has continued to evolve, we recap the Polls, and we dive into the rules for red eye flights. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: Pathological Liar | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590065/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 17:44:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Movie critic Adnan Virk and former baseball president David Samson join the show to tease a Top 5 before breaking down the now-over World Series. Then, John Feinstein joins us and doesn&amp;rsquo;t hold back on Bobby Knight. Plus, Mike Schur is here to defend the Heat, deliver multiple stats of the day, and grace us with a new Top 5. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: YEAR HE! YEAR HE! | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590066/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 16:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590066/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s time to discuss the University of Miami and Tyler Van Dyke&amp;rsquo;s continued struggles before Dan and Mike sing the praises of Rueben &amp;ldquo;Hurricane&amp;rdquo; Bain, the 6-star . Then, Jeremiah Tachington III continues his reign as the show presents Thursday Thunder, and limited fake Joe Zagacki is here to be honest about Bobby Knight&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;complicated&amp;rdquo; legacy. Plus, the World Series ended last night, huh? Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: Dan Blew The Joke | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590067/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 15:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590067/</guid><description>Podcast Description After last night&amp;rsquo;s Heat collapse against the Brooklyn Nets, Mike Ryan is being driven mad. Amin Elhassan is here to begin our analysis before Mike and Jeremy get into it over Miami&amp;rsquo;s roster and performance as Dan asks Tony and Chris about the different kinds of Heat fandom. Then, the crew discuss Chris Cote&amp;rsquo;s upcoming trip to Germany to cover the Miami Dolphins. Plus, we take a look back at the foot in Chris Cote&amp;rsquo;s bathroom stall and begin to eulogize Bobby Knight in the best way we can.</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: The (Pee) Bucket of Death | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590068/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jessica takes a trip to the Bucket of Death before the crew discusses the phrase &amp;ldquo;if it&amp;rsquo;s yellow, let it mellow&amp;rdquo; and the use of porta potties at tailgates. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: The Weaponization of the Peanut | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590069/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jessica tried to watch a scary movie at home alone last night, and it leads Dan, Amin, and the Shipping Container to a conversation on the best movie detectives. Then, is this generation missing out on delicious candy because of the peanut being weaponized? Amin launches an investigation. Plus, using cassettes to tape your favorite shows or music, John Taffer ruining a Coconut Grove staple, and the toxicity around the Arizona Cardinals organization.</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: That's From SpongeBob | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590070/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590070/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s time for the most competitive game on the show and our greatest creative venture: AGAINST! THE SPREAD! Then, Rich Eisen joins the show to discuss the upcoming Dolphins vs. Chiefs game in Germany on NFL Network, signing a contract on his honeymoon, the best SportsCenter anchors of all-time, and more. Plus, Tony delivers his Top 5 as Peter Pan in front of the Pedro Pan statue in Downtown Miami.</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: The Trolley Problem | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590071/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stugotz and Billy have some major takeaways from Halloween, but Stugotz&amp;rsquo;s have the rest of the crew a little concerned. Then, it turns out Lucy was not almost hit by a car (truck or van), but a trolley bus. Mike continues to despise Victor Wembanyama, Stugotz leaves to go golfing, Amin Elhassan joins the show, and we hear Kendrick Perkins&amp;rsquo; comments on James Harden&amp;rsquo;s performance in the 2012 NBA Finals.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: Reggie October | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590072/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590072/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Samson joins us for the first two segments of today&amp;rsquo;s Local Hour to discuss the Shipping Container&amp;rsquo;s lack of Halloween participation, his viral moment on CBS, former Marlins thriving in the postseason, Corey Seager, and the Marte Parte. Then, Billy has words for &amp;ldquo;Reggie October&amp;rdquo; and Samson explains why he&amp;rsquo;s mad about the time the Raiders made their firings. Plus, Tony has a pitch for the greatest commercial jingle of all-time while dressed as Peter Pan, Lucy almost got hit by a car&amp;hellip;again, and Nicholas Cage&amp;rsquo;s new movie trailer is perfect.</description></item><item><title>PTFO - Inside the Forbidden Love of Michael Jordan's Son and Scottie Pippen's Ex-Wife | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590073/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 19:22:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590073/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s Shakespearean. It&amp;rsquo;s Freudian. It&amp;rsquo;s a Greek myth with a Real Housewife. Yes, sports fans: Marcus Jordan and Larsa Pippen are getting married. But are they just a reality-TV couple engineered to goose the algorithm? Or is this true romance? Pablo, Cortes, and &amp;ldquo;Oddball&amp;rdquo; host Charlotte Wilder listen to their podcast so you don&amp;rsquo;t have to&amp;hellip; then confront the Romeo and Juliet of our time with the awkward and essential questions about Michael and Scottie.</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: Cooper Flagg and the Flaming Pitchfork | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590074/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cooper Flagg committed to Duke, and the visuals of him holding a flaming pitchfork are&amp;hellip;something. Plus, a discussion on the movie theater experience thanks to Five Nights at Freddy&amp;rsquo;s. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: Bring Back Sameness! | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590075/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 17:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590075/</guid><description>Podcast Description The crew continues to dissect the Dabo Swinney sound before getting to Greg Cote&amp;rsquo;s Back in my Day on uniforms. Then, Stugotz keeps saying he doesn&amp;rsquo;t care about sports, and Billy has a new proposal: we should implement spoiler alerts with sports. Plus, Greg Cote went to Cuba, and a few members of the Shipping Container go to the Bucket of Death. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: Tyler! | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590076/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mike normally hates Colorado, and that&amp;rsquo;s been made clear, but he&amp;rsquo;s furious over what happened to their team over the weekend. We also hear from Pat Narduzzi who knows &amp;ldquo;it starts with me&amp;rdquo; when his team struggles. Then, Dabo Swinney got into it with a Clemson fan named Tyler, and it seems Tyler may have been so out-of-bounds in his criticism that Lucy and Mike are somehow #TeamDabo. Plus, Shea Serrano and Jason Concepcion have teamed up for a new podcast &amp;ldquo;Six Trophies,&amp;rdquo; and they join us for a segment with some of the best video in show history and worst audio in show history.</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: Love Dies | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590077/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Greg Cote is fired up about the placement of the Cheez-It in the grocery store, K&amp;rsquo;wasi the Lion, and couples who hold hands in public. Billy thinks his phone might be racist and has some thoughts on love. Then, we watch the video of Lucy&amp;rsquo;s trip to Jacksonville for Georgia-Florida (GO DAWGS! WOOF WOOF!) and try to decide where she&amp;rsquo;s headed next. Plus, a radio host rips Zach Wilson for apple picking, and Stugotz talks to Keyshawn Johnson while he gets a haircut.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: The Ken Le Batard Show | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590078/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Halloween! Dan is Ken, Lucy is the Ghost of Iowa&amp;rsquo;s Offense, the rest of the show is&amp;hellip;a disappointment. The crew reacts to the Heat&amp;rsquo;s loss to the Bucks last night and their 1-3 start to the season. They also break down the huge news that broke overnight: James Harden has been traded to the Los Angeles Clippers. Then, the Florida Panthers are &amp;ldquo;banged up,&amp;rdquo; Stugotz is going to celebrate Halloween without his kids, Lucy shares some thoughts from Florida-Georgia, and the ACC schedule release has Mike Ryan asking some questions.</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: Sports Bars | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590079/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590079/</guid><description>Podcast Description After Jess experienced the power of handling the remote at a sports bar over the weekend, the crew discusses if we&amp;rsquo;re headed toward the extinction of the GREAT sports bar. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: Joe Meatandpotatoes | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590080/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrew Hawkins sticks around to share his thoughts on Halloween and why he&amp;rsquo;s always in costumes. Dan, Hawk, Stugotz and the crew discuss Taylor Heinicke, Gardner Minshew, and the show&amp;rsquo;s made up nicknames for athletes, the University of Houston jersey controversy, DeAndre Hopkins&amp;rsquo; resurgence, and Flavor Flav&amp;rsquo;s National Anthem. Then, the show discusses the sexual assault lawsuit filed against Dwight Howard and the way it has been covered by people across the sports media landscape.</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: Harbor for Harbaugh | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590081/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590081/</guid><description>Podcast Description HEYYYYYYY JUUUUUUUDE. The crew kicks off Hour 1 with Stugotz&amp;rsquo;s Weekend Observations before watching an electric clip from El Chiringuito. After the clip, Stugotz lashes out for having to cut his Weekend Obs short due to the clocks. Then, we dive into the Michigan Football news and all the details that continue to leak out about Jim Harbaugh and the program. Plus, Andrew Hawkins joins us to discuss Pickle Coverage, the awful Jets-Giants game, Patrick Mahomes&amp;rsquo; greatness, and Tyreek Hill.</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: Who's the Apollo Creed in That Book? | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590082/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 15:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stugotz can&amp;rsquo;t believe LeBron is still playing basketball on Sunday nights, Chris Cote has been hate-watching NBA basketball, and Mike Ryan is furious we didn&amp;rsquo;t lead the show with Miami and Rueben &amp;ldquo;Hurricane&amp;rdquo; Bain&amp;rsquo;s win over Virginia. Then, the Francis Ngannou vs. Tyson Fury fight may have been a huge step for the sport of boxing. Plus, it&amp;rsquo;s time for the Climate Stat of the Day, and have the Kansas City Chiefs failed Patrick Mahomes?</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: Like My Sport, Please | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590083/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 14:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan is back in Miami with Stugotz and the Shipping Container, and he claims to have missed everyone&amp;hellip;how long with THAT last? The crew discusses college coaches whose careers have tanked the most, Stugotz&amp;rsquo;s Top 5 Guys Who Should be the Vikings QB, Will Levis as Dan Marino, and Jalen Ramsey&amp;rsquo;s frustration with Adam Schefter. Then, Billy is done with Europe, the Dolphins have a huge challenge ahead with the Chiefs in Germany, and Dan offers to pay for everyone&amp;rsquo;s gas.</description></item><item><title>Monday Hangover: Disco Tile Football | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590084/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stugotz has his Top 5 QBs that will replace Kirk Cousins after an QB injury filled weekend. Lucy is back from the World&amp;rsquo;s Largest Outdoor Cocktail Party! What surprises might we have in this week&amp;rsquo;s first CFP Rankings of the season? Coming off of a 3-0 week on his Billy&amp;rsquo;s Bets Big Board Billy has 3 more locks for this week. Plus a new segment: Send Lucy Things to Disco Tile!</description></item><item><title>PTFO - Share &amp; Tell with John Skipper and David Samson (or: Rich Guys OnlyFans) | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590085/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 16:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is the NBA&amp;rsquo;s TV bubble about to burst? Is how we consume sports about to change forever? Hear from the man who reshaped the business itself. Plus: Who’s to blame for our misinformation minefield? And what the hell happened to retirement? The jamokes from The Sporting Class explain. PTFO-approved reading: House of Strauss: I&amp;rsquo;m Not Sure How the NBA Triples Its Rights Fees in a TV Recession https://www.houseofstrauss.com/p/im-not-sure-how-the-nba-triples-its Vanity Fair: Inside the New York Times Debate Over Its Gaza Hospital Bombing Coverage https://www.</description></item><item><title>STU- Captain Lee Rosbach | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590086/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Billy enlists nautical expert Lorenzo to make sure their interview with Captain Lee goes smoothly. Stugotz becomes fast friends with the captain and makes some promises he might not be able to deliver on. Lee tell the guys about his podcast Salty with Captain Lee, his upcoming one man show in Las Vegas, how he felt about Scandoval and he makes some NFL picks! Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>#BecauseMiami: C-O-V-O | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590087/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Miami commissioner Sabina Covo has unleashed a mass negative ad campaign against three candidates running against her in District 2&amp;hellip;Damian Pardo, Eddy Leal, and James Torres. Well, we have all three respectively joining Billy Corben on the show. Also joining us is Quinn Mitchell, a 15 year old from New Hampshire who has been holding Florida governor Ron DeSantis accountable at his campaign stops. So much so that Quinn has been harassed by DeSantis&amp;rsquo; goons while trying to ask questions.</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: The Talking Hockey While Nobody Is Here Show | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590088/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Roy Bellamy chats with David Dwork about all things NHL! Roy and David kick things off with an update on the hometown Florida Panthers, a look around the Atlantic Division, and the potential return of Connor McDavid. Then, ESPN Senior NHL Writer Greg Wyshynski enters &amp;ldquo;The Penalty Box&amp;rdquo; with Roy and David to discuss the Shane Pinto gambling suspension, the Calgary Flames struggles, the NHL&amp;rsquo;s reversal on &amp;ldquo;themed tape,&amp;rdquo; and the Frozen Frenzy on ESPN.</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: Mina Kimes Saves The Day | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590089/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590089/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;How Childhood is about Kirk Cousins.&amp;rdquo; Mina Kimes, the most popular person in the DLS universe, joins Dan and Mike in Los Angeles to talk all things NFL: Myles Garrett, the Tush Push, Micah Parsons, Brock Purdy, Tua Tagovailoa, Kirk Cousins, Aaron Rodgers, Deshaun Watson, and more. Plus, we find out if Dan and Mina are DolphIN or DolphOUT. Then, Mina explains how the early stages of motherhood feel for her as she simultaneously has more and less time, watches a ton of football, and learns how to keep another human alive.</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: Mike Schur's Miami Heat Declaration | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590090/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 14:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan is worried the Los Angeles show is jumping the shark, so he and Mike Ryan brought in Meadowlark Intern Mike Schur to save the day. The trio discusses Mike Ryan hating on Victor Wembanyama, the sports media world&amp;rsquo;s reaction to Mad Dog Russo&amp;rsquo;s Phillies bet, the upcoming World Series featuring the Arizona Diamondbacks, and the NHL&amp;rsquo;s reversal on Pride Tape. Then, they finally get to Mike Schur&amp;rsquo;s Miami Heat declaration after one game of the NBA season.</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: Adam Schefter's Very Sad Existence | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590091/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam Schefter joins the show to discuss why he misses Halloween every year, his Top 5 Takeaways from the First Few Days of the NBA Season, the NFL Trade Deadline, gummies, and more. Then, Tony Calatayud and Miami comedian/Only In Dade Host Carlos Hernandez chat about &amp;lsquo;Nadie Sabe Lo Que Va A Pasar Mañana,&amp;rsquo; Bad Bunny&amp;rsquo;s newly released album. (This is just a snippet of their conversation with the full episode airing on the LeBatard Show YouTube channel.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: We're Here, Fam | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590092/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590092/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Miami crew has reached the end of their work week and wants to hand out letter grades for their own performances. Lucy shows off her multiplication skills while getting undermined by Tony, and the crew goes to the Bucket of Death. Then, Jessica Smetana, Lucy Rohden, and producer Taylor Vippolis continue their unnamed college football segment and talk about Michigan&amp;rsquo;s sign-stealing scandal, the Ohio State/Penn State defensive battle, North Carolina&amp;rsquo;s historic loss, mousetraps, and much more from the wild world of college football.</description></item><item><title>GBF- The BCS, Captain Lee, Ekeler, Simms and Golic | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590093/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590093/</guid><description>Podcast Description (0:00) Golic gets us ready for the football weekend. (13:24) The guys unveil this season&amp;rsquo;s first BCS rankings with the help of Chris Cote. (26:53) Stu Ya Gotz. (31:06) Austin Ekeler&amp;rsquo;s cheat days. (47:17) Captain Lee from Below Deck picks some NFL games and shares his thoughts on the Michigan scandal. (58:44) Chris Simms is shocked with how little Dolphins the guys wanted to talk about after the Eagles game.</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: Impressing Your Partner's Parents | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590094/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 17:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ed Kelce had some positive thoughts to share about Taylor Swift that spark a conversation between Stugotz and the Shipping Container on how to best impress your partner&amp;rsquo;s parents. Then, Lucy is headed to Jacksonville, and the Rice Owls eat some gummy worms. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: An Intimate and Vulnerable Hour | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590095/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan and Mike begin this hour with a conversation surrounding grief and prioritizing family over work after Dan read the story of Marvin Jones Jr. stepping away from the NFL. Dan reveals some sobering details of what the Le Batard family has been going through over the last couple of years. He also explains WHY he and parts of the crew have spent these last two weeks in Los Angeles.</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: The Evolution of the Take | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590096/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 16:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan, Mike, GoJo, and Brad keep things rolling out in L.A. and kick off Hour 1 by getting into the Jim Harbaugh Michigan Cheating Scandal and what advantages can be found from this type of cheating in football. Then, the crew breaks down the evolution of &amp;ldquo;the take&amp;rdquo; in sports media before discussing Caleb Williams and Lincoln Riley&amp;rsquo;s futures at USC. Plus, David Samson and Adnan Virk join the show with horrible zoom backgrounds to give us their first thoughts on Killers of the Flower Moon and deliver their Top 5 John Lithgow Movies.</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: The Awkward Handshake | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590097/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 16:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590097/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Miami crew kicks off the Big Suey by updating the Polls from the week, listening to sound of Don La Greca ripping Mad Dog Russo, and dishing out this week&amp;rsquo;s picks for Thursday Thunder. Then, we head to Los Angeles with Dan, Mike Ryan, Mike Golic Jr., and Brad Williams. Brad and GoJo discuss the dynamics of their awkward handshake before Brad shares the revelation that he is not good at comedy.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: What's The Rush? | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590098/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 15:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stugotz and the Miami crew recap the Heat&amp;rsquo;s first game of the season after they escaped with a 1-point victory over Detroit. Then, Billy Donovan is on the hot seat after one game, Chris Cote believes there are players more important to the Dolphins than Tyreek Hill, and clips from Billy Gil&amp;rsquo;s FIU broadcast blow us away. Plus, Chris had a wild plan on how to handle taking care of his sick daughter, Billy launches a hashtag, Lucy tells us where she&amp;rsquo;s headed this weekend, and Tony breaks down Victor Wembanyama&amp;rsquo;s NBA debut.</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: A Fun Ref | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590099/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 17:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590099/</guid><description>Podcast Description The crew wonders how they can make unsportsmanlike penalties more fun. Plus, everyones favorite game - Against The Spread! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: We're All Gonna Die Some More | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590100/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590100/</guid><description>Podcast Description The crew in Los Angeles gets into Amin&amp;rsquo;s spirituality. Dan finally figures out that Lucy is spending a ton of Meadowlark Media money. Plus, Adam McKay brings us another Climate Stat of the Day. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: L.A....It's Fantastic | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590101/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590101/</guid><description>Podcast Description The crew in Los Angeles are talking about the start to the NBA season. Mike Schur joins them to talk about the strike. Plus, they get into Aaron Rodgers and Joe Rogan. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: Top 5 Things Of The World Series With David Samson | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590102/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 15:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590102/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Samson joins the crew to discuss his Top 5 things to look out for this World Series, fan engagement in baseball, his thoughts on Chris &amp;lsquo;Mad Dog&amp;rsquo; Russo&amp;rsquo;s retirement bet and the show laughs at Phillies fans. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: BTW Don't Be Alarmed | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590103/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 14:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590103/</guid><description>Podcast Description The crew tells Lucy to not be worried if her water at home smells like chlorine for a little while, she also puts her fate into the fans&amp;rsquo; hands with deciding where she should go this weekend in CFB. Plus, a friend of God Bless Football has acquired a CFB bowl game, somewhat of a Miami Heat season opening preview and Stugotz&amp;rsquo;s Weekend Observations. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>PTFO Halloween Investigation: Why So Many Athletes Have Tattoos of the Joker | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590104/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 21:09:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590104/</guid><description>Podcast Description The most important Joker on the court isn&amp;rsquo;t Nikola Jokic or Novak Djokovic. Indeed, the most popular tattoo among our sports heroes is a villain, and PTFO correspondent Wyatt Cenac is here to interview them about it&amp;hellip; as Batman… with a mask on. Could Joker Mode become the new Mamba Mentality?
Watch on YouTube: https://youtu.be/Sc3d9M3jLGI Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: It's A Serum Not A Moisturizer | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590105/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 16:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jay Glazer talks about the start of his career, his skincare routine and the Miami Dolphins. Plus, Lucy Rohden starts an investigation. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: Jay Glazer's Natural Musk | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590106/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jay Glazer joins Dan and the crew in LA to discuss his natural musk without cologne, the mental health landmines in being an NFL insider, training with some of the toughest athletes on the planet like Randy Couture and more. Plus, a bevy of NFL topics. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: NBA Opening Night! | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590107/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 15:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amin Elhassan, Charlotte Wilder and Jorge Sedano join Dan and Mike Ryan to get you ready for NBA Opening Night. Did LeBron James show a lack of respect for his teammates and the game by eating take-out on the bench? The wait is finally over as Mike Schur joins the show to preview the Celtics&amp;rsquo; season. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: Greg Goes To The Bucket + Dan Orlovsky | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590108/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Greg Cote makes an argument that he is worth more than just an occasional &amp;ldquo;Back in My Day.&amp;rdquo; Meanwhile, Billy is still backed into the &amp;ldquo;Kirk Cousins guy&amp;rdquo; corner and Roy finds a tool to help the show find out if he belongs in the hall of fame. This leads the show down a rabbit hole of what quarterbacks should and should not be in the hall. Dan Orlovsky joins the show to discuss best teams in the NFL and peeing in the shower.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: Mankind | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590109/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 14:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Billy dresses as Mankind to fulfill a punishment while Rece Davis is confused and here to talk college football. Greg is here on a Greg Cote Tuesday and trying his best not to blame the refs for the Dolphins loss in Philadelphia. Meanwhile, Billy is painted into a corner as the Kirk Cousins guy. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: Lucy or Goosey | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590110/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 19:31:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan, Mike Ryan and Luis join the show from Los Angeles! The team recaps what happened throughout the day and play one of GOD BLESS FOOTBALL’s signature games: LUCY OR GOOSEY! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: Close Friends | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590111/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 18:58:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrew Hawkins joins the show to discuss important topics like Instagram’s Close Friends feature and what defines a close friend. Also, Hawk tells Billy that he is an idiot for calling Kirk Cousins a first ballot Hall of Famer while the show takes off recapping the NFL weekend that was and who is on the hot seat in the NFL. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: Fair Catch, Huh? | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590112/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 18:11:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Spencer Hall joins the show to recap another crazy weekend of college football while validating all of Chris Cote’s ridiculous questions. Taylor gives his UNC football observations and Chris Cote is concerned about Instagram’s “close friends” story feature. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: Done With Days | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590113/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 17:21:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590113/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s national TV Talk Show Host Day. Stugotz loves a good Nut Day. Chris Cote is done with national days. What’s the best day for Halloween? Why is Bernie Kosar hanging out with Taylor Swift? Does Travis Kelce play better with Taylor Swift in attendance? Billy, Chris and Tony try to figure out what Taylor&amp;rsquo;s optimal flight time from Japan to the Super Bowl the next day. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: Skeleton Crew | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590114/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 16:27:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590114/</guid><description>Podcast Description A sobering Dolphins Sunday night game has what remains of the show in their feelings and searching for answers. Is the Philly Brotherly Shove cheating? Can the Dolphins offense travel? Have they beaten a good team, in other words are the 2-4 Chargers a good team? Chris Cote returns from Oktoberfest with a pro german stance and a horrifying outdoor bathroom story. Billy dives into his coffee habits, while Chris and Tony raw dog it, and Stugotz gets straight to it with a double espresso.</description></item><item><title>Monday Hangover: Tony and Juju | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590115/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stugotz, Billy, and Mikey A don&amp;rsquo;t want to be the show that blames the refs for everything that happened on Sunday, but at the same time, it was kind of their fault. Tony and Juju join the show to give their thoughts on what is going on with Bills and Lions. Stugotz ranks his top 5 questionable teams in the NFL through week 7. Billy gives us his BBBBBB for the 49ers and Vikings game.</description></item><item><title>PTFO - Share &amp; Tell with Katie Nolan &amp; Dwayne Johnson's Friend Ariel Helwani | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590116/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why did Ariel Helwani, our planet’s leading combat sports reporter, use ring girls as human shields at a televised Logan Paul melee? What video game is Katie Nolan mostly living inside? Do you remember the time The Rock actually broke the news that Osama bin Laden had been assassinated? And more. PTFO-approved content: https://nymag.com/intelligencer/article/shams-charania-nba-insider-the-athletic-new-york-times-profile.html https://www.theparisreview.org/blog/2023/10/16/were-more-ghosts-than-people/ https://arielhelwani.substack.com/ Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CINEPHILE - A "Killers of the Flower Moon" Extravaganza | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590117/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 19:12:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adnan recaps his private screening of Killers of the Flower Moon and gives his review. We&amp;rsquo;re talking to production designer Jack Fisk and casting Director Ellen Lewis and hear from the legend himself, Marty Scorsese talking about the film. Also, Adnan swears he has never called in sick… in America. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>South Beach Sessions - Gabriel Iglesias | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590118/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Success required a lot of sacrifices for Gabriel Iglesias and that&amp;rsquo;s no joke.
Gabriel &amp;ldquo;Fluffy&amp;rdquo; Iglesias may be one of the most beloved comedians in the world, but it&amp;rsquo;s in Los Angeles, performing in front of sold-out crowds at Dodger Stadium where he feels most at home and equally on top of the world. Dan meets Gabriel in Los Angeles for a special conversation that goes well beyond what he&amp;rsquo;s ever shared on stage or anywhere before.</description></item><item><title>#BecauseMiami: Democrats Never Miss An Opportunity... | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590119/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590119/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;hellip;to miss an opportunity. Billy Corben wrote an opinion piece for Medium that ties Miami politicians boarding a free trip to Qatar involving the World Cup to the Israel-Hamas conflict. Before that, however, we make fun of his life as a child actor. We have Jeb Lund on to talk about the New College&amp;rsquo;s foray into athletics despite its athletes lagging in their academics. Plus, CBS Miami&amp;rsquo;s Jim DeFede comes on to talk about his new documentary, “WAREHOUSED: The Life and Death of Tristin Murphy.</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: The Miami Local Hour From L.A. | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590120/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590120/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Dan Le Batard Show may be out in L.A., but that won&amp;rsquo;t stop Dan and the crew from discussing Miami. Joy Taylor and Jorge Sedano join Dan to chat about the Mike McDaniel and the Miami Dolphins before Mike Ryan slides back into the conversation to talk University of Miami Football. Then, Meadowlark Intern Mike Schur stops by to deliver not one but TWO Stats of the Day and to share his thoughts on &amp;ldquo;fame replacing good.</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: CFB + UFC | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590121/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 13:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590121/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s an hour of Shipping Container expertise as we kick things off with Jessica and Lucy&amp;rsquo;s Unnamed College Football Show as they take you through the week that was in College Football including new facial hair, a blue vase, and more. They also preview the biggest games this weekend. Then, Tony chats with MMA Junkie&amp;rsquo;s Danny Segura in another edition of the MMA Hangout where the duo breaks down all things UFC.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: Mr. Baby | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590122/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stugotz and the crew take a quick trip to the Bucket of Death as the reaper makes his triumphant return. Then, Brooks Koepka stops by to chat about the Florida Panthers, sneakers, being a new dad, Augusta, LIV Golf&amp;rsquo;s event this weekend, and more. Plus, Jessica leads our conversation with Mr. Baby Lando Norris as he discusses his career path, the end of this F1 season, Max Verstappen&amp;rsquo;s dominance, and plays a riveting game of Lando or Land-no.</description></item><item><title>GBF- Ekeler + Mostert, Mack Brown + Chris Simms, Golic &amp; More! | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590123/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590123/</guid><description>Podcast Description (0:00) Mike Golic previews Sunday night&amp;rsquo;s game between the Dolphins and the Eagles and describes his perfect college football Saturday lineup. (21:28) Austin Ekeler tells us about the pregame fight between the Chargers and the Cowboys and is joined by Raheem Mostert. (32:39) Raheem talks about his fast start this season and agrees to let Stugotz housesit for him while he&amp;rsquo;s playing in Germany. (41:57) Stu Ya Gotz. (46:37) The guys surprise Chris Simms with his former coach, and current HC of the #10 Tar Heels, (53:19) Mack Brown.</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: Back to Miami | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590124/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590124/</guid><description>Podcast Description The crew in Miami waited around for HOURS to deliver you an update on the Polls and a perfectly vetted Thursday Thunder. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: Horrifying Climate Stat of the Day | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590125/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam McKay joins Dan out in Hollywood to share his Horrifying Climate Stat of the Day and to steamroll Dan at every turn. Then, Dan, Amin, Charlotte, and Brad Williams try to remember a time before sponsored content on social media and whether or not people understand Twitter is not real life. Plus, Mike sits back down with the group to share his desire to laugh at Deion Sanders.</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: National WHAT Day? | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590126/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brad Williams joins Dan and the L.A. crew to discuss comedy in America and Hasan Minhaj. Then, Mike&amp;rsquo; Morrissey story, Dan&amp;rsquo;s baboon story, and Brad introduces us to an unfortunate holiday. Plus, John Elway is a horrible executive, and Mike McDaniel is weird. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: Comfort Shows | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590127/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joy Taylor joins Dan, Charlotte, and Amin in Los Angeles! The group discusses their comfort shows because Charlotte cannot stop talking about The Great British Bake Off. Then, Dan loves working in L.A., but it leads to a conversation on some of the issues in the city. Plus, Shannon Sharpe&amp;rsquo;s makeup disaster, Caleb Williams and NIL talk, and we hear more of Amin&amp;rsquo;s impressions. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: What's a Rutger? | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590128/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tony teaches us a way to know how things feel without actually touching them&amp;hellip; Then, Stugotz and the crew discuss &amp;ldquo;the spirit of the rule&amp;rdquo; in sports, find out why certain colleges have their names, and Jess breaks down the Aces WNBA championship run. Plus, takes on Amin&amp;rsquo;s takes on flights, Best Buy&amp;rsquo;s evolution toward appliances, and Billy worries about getting a haircut. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: Sports on the West Coast | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590129/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590129/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Los Angeles and Miami crew&amp;rsquo;s reunite to cap off today&amp;rsquo;s show. Dan is startled by how much more enjoyable it is to watch sports on the West Coast, and the crew examines how the ghost of Phillip Rivers haunts Justin Herbert and the Chargers. Dan also loses it over Stugotz&amp;rsquo;s Zach Wilson-Aaron Rodgers take. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: The Unthinkable | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590130/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590130/</guid><description>Podcast Description The L.A. crew discusses the Aaron Rodgers and Pat McAfee relationship and making business decisions for content companies. Then, Amin believes Jada Pinkett Smith has done THE IMPOSSIBLE. Plus, the crew looks at the mental health terror it must be to be Shams, Woj, or any of the news breakers. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: Charlotte's Family Meeting | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590131/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 16:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590131/</guid><description>Podcast Description We head back out to Los Angeles with Dan, Mike, Charlotte and Amin as Mike Golic Jr. joins the show. Charlotte shares how she feels her families merging between GoJo and Oddball, but Dan feels like Amin is limiting Charlotte. GoJo shares the differences between real fights and football fights and has a Taylor Swift take. Then, the size of professional athletes, Victor Wembanyama, and athlete reactions to Player Lists from media members.</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: Tony's Troubles | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590132/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 15:40:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stugotz and the crew decide how big of a game the Dolphins are playing on Sunday against the Eagles and plays a guessing game involving Brock Purdy&amp;rsquo;s extremely low salary. Then, we examine what plagues Tony and dive into his lowest moments before he shares a conundrum he&amp;rsquo;s facing headed into the weekend. Plus, it&amp;rsquo;s time for Against the Spread, and Lucy wants to stop finding out more details about Jada Pinkett Smith.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: The Best Fans in Baseball | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590133/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 15:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590133/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Samson joins us for the start of our Wednesday Local Hour and helps Stugotz take a torch to the Phillies fan base before naming his Top 5 Fan Bases in Baseball. Then, an update on the Marlins GM search, learning about Jessica&amp;rsquo;s mean best friend, and figuring out &amp;ldquo;the face of baseball.&amp;rdquo; Plus, Stugotz delivers his Weekend Observations and names his Top 5 Names in Sports Who Connote a Courtroom.</description></item><item><title>PTFO EXCLUSIVE — How Hollywood Forgot Mike Schur's "Field of Dreams" Reboot | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590134/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 21:33:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael Schur is a legendary comedy writer who calls his TV reboot of the classic baseball film &amp;ldquo;the best thing I&amp;rsquo;ve ever written.&amp;rdquo; (He&amp;rsquo;s written for SNL, The Simpsons, The Office, Parks and Rec, Brooklyn Nine-Nine, The Good Place&amp;hellip;) So why didn&amp;rsquo;t his version of &amp;ldquo;Field of Dreams&amp;rdquo; ever get made? Also: what happened to the actual baseball field that he built, out there in the cornfields of Iowa?</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: C.O.W.D.I.I. | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590135/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590135/</guid><description>Podcast Description The LA and Miami crews come together to wrap up today&amp;rsquo;s show. Dan finally has a chance to confront Lucy for leaving the Colorado game early and ask the rest of the Miami team how today&amp;rsquo;s show went with Greg, Jer Bear, and more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: Every Second Matters | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590136/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan, Mike, Amin, and Charlotte are out in Los Angeles and already have some amazing stories to share. After learning the spelling of the word cummerbund, the crew discusses words people say wrong and the advances in robot technology that scare them. Then, Amin and Dan share their celebrity encounters from their flights into L.A. and Charlotte tells us about a Zooey Deschanel Christmas Concert. Plus, Mike Golic Jr.</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: Do You See What I See? | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590137/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 17:27:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ron Magill joins the show to discuss his new book with Greg, the Colorado mascot fraud, kissing your own wife, catching pythons, and more. Then, Greg and Billy share their thoughts on Kim Ng and the Marlins parting ways before Lucy and Greg head to the Bucket of Death. Plus, Mad Dog Russo is here to react to Stephen&amp;rsquo;s A-List, purposefully ruining Halloween for children, his favorite Christmas songs, the MLB Postseason, gummies, and more.</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: Making Out at Halloween Parties | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590138/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 15:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590138/</guid><description>Podcast Description After Greg shares his thoughts on Mario Cristobal, the crew takes a look at the way NIL will impact recruiting long-term. Then, it&amp;rsquo;s time we talk about going all out on couple&amp;rsquo;s costumes for Halloween. Plus, Lucy prepares us for a potential catastrophe that the College Football sickos will love: Iowa could potentially make the College Football Playoff. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: The Snaggletoe | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590139/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Billy has returned from Jury Duty, Tony had a horribly bad beat, and Jer Bear is&amp;hellip;dressed as a bear. Billy gives us his takeaways after listening to yesterday&amp;rsquo;s show, including a note about Stugotz&amp;rsquo;s fake laugh. Then, Greg Cote is here and tells us about his new book with Ron Magill and the sweet love his words made with Ron&amp;rsquo;s hands on experience. Plus, Greg&amp;rsquo;s great toe is feeling particularly great these days.</description></item><item><title>Postgame Show: The L.A. Crew | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590140/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 18:15:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan, Mike, Amin and Charlotte join us from L.A. to talk Orange Juice pulp, Zach Wilson getting crushed publicly, and Mike&amp;rsquo;s new Bears take. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hour 2: The Gang Does Hour 2 | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590141/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 18:07:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chemistry is the most important thing in podcasting, and this crew has a whole bunch of it. Then, the flag football game of the century, a Zach Wilson-Aaron Rodgers hypothetical, Hawk doesn&amp;rsquo;t believe in the Aaron Rodgers video, and a conversation on bad parkers. Then, Jay Glazer joins the show to take a deep dive into mental health and answer our rapid fire NFL questions. Plus, Jessica is finally starting to understand the life of Billy Gil.</description></item><item><title>Hour 1: Brian Hoyer is a Human Being | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590142/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 16:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590142/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Samson joins the show to discuss the Marlins and Kim Ng mutually parting ways and what it means for the future of the franchise. Then, Andrew Hawkins joins the show! Hawk discusses a potential flag football challenge against the Pat McAfee show, why the Dolphins are the best team in the NFL, Bill Belichick&amp;rsquo;s legacy, why he loves Brian Hoyer, lacrosse, and more. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>The Big Suey: Big Penix Energy | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590143/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 16:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stugotz is upset with College Football getting buried by the NFL weekend, so the crew makes sure to take some time to dunk on the Hurricanes post-UNC lost. Then, Billy is on Jury Duty, no one should be mad at Lucy, and what is the Le Batard Show&amp;rsquo;s equivalent of a fumble? Plus, Mike Golic Jr. joins the show to discuss Chris Cote&amp;rsquo;s take on the Kelce brothers, GoJo and Jessica&amp;rsquo;s Notre Dame texts, Oregon and Washington&amp;rsquo;s excellence, and much more across College Football.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: This Week is a Lazy River | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590144/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590144/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stugotz is in the driver&amp;rsquo;s seat this week as Dan and Mike are in Los Angeles, and the show is riding the lazy river. The crew takes a look around the NFL including the happiest guy on a losing team, Josh McDaniels&amp;rsquo; failures, PJ Walker and Zach Wilson winning, and, of course, the Miami Dolphins. Plus, news breaks during the live show that Kim Ng and the Miami Marlins have parted ways.</description></item><item><title>Monday Hangover: God Bless Chris Cote | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590145/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 13:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stugotz and Mikey A are joined by Chris Cote filling in for Billy who is out for jury duty. Chris has a big problem with the Kelces and it has nothing to do with Taylor Swift. Lucy is recaps leaving the Stanford Colorado game early and plays Lucy or Goosey. Stugotz ranks his top 5 QBs through week 6. Chris tries to fill in for Billy on his BBBBBB and it goes wrong.</description></item><item><title>PTFO EXCLUSIVE - Share &amp; Tell with "Celebrity Jeopardy!" Winner Katie Nolan + Gasbags Dan Le Batard and Pablo Torre | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590146/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 20:43:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590146/</guid><description>Podcast Description What does it feel like to kick a$$ on a game show? Like an athlete in the Albanian brain zone who can&amp;rsquo;t do math. Why doesn&amp;rsquo;t Bill Belichick have to defend his conditional genius? Because we owe him the benefit of sudden doubt. Are you convincing yourself that you don&amp;rsquo;t need therapy? You gotta place your vulnerability somewhere, you know. Plus: Pablo&amp;rsquo;s Process (again), Christopher Meloni&amp;rsquo;s mad energy, Dan&amp;rsquo;s digestive tract&amp;hellip; and some tears.</description></item><item><title>Sporting Class: Why Do Sports Leagues Speak Out? Why Are the NFL and NBA So Desperate to Go International? | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590147/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Meadowlark Media CEO John Skipper and Nothing Personal&amp;rsquo;s David Samson are back with another episode with Pablo Torre Finds Out host&amp;hellip; Pablo Torre to host! Welcome to the Sporting Class! We start today off with what’s going on within the Israeli-Palestinian conflict and the business of it. Sports leagues are speaking out. Players are speaking out. Fans are speaking out. Then, where do we stand on the global sports power rankings currently?</description></item><item><title>#BecauseMiami: Nice Jewish Boy | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590148/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Billy Corben during public comment in a Coral Gables commission meeting got into a testy confrontation with mayor Vince Lago that, to Billy, felt anti-semitic. Plus, we have former state Rep. Carlos Guillermo Smith on to talk about how Florida governor Ron DeSantis covered up statewide COVID data. During the Wheel of Despair in the second segment, there is a story involving a suicide. If you are having thoughts of suicide, you can call or text 988 to reach the National Suicide Prevention Lifeline.</description></item><item><title>Local Hour: Let's Do The Polka! | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590149/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 13:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan, Stu, and the crew discuss the miserable summer of NBA Champion Nikola Jokic and how we&amp;rsquo;re supposed to feel about Urban Meyer being paraded around on TV. Jess and Lucy are backed for their Unnamed College Football Show™️ to preview this weekend&amp;rsquo;s games. And the crew goes to the Bucket of Death and experiences one of the most controversial helmet selections of the season. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>GBF- Breece Hall, Austin Ekeler, Simms, Golic and Picks! | The Dan Le Batard Show with Stugotz</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8827590150/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8827590150/</guid><description>Podcast Description (8:44) Breece Hall discusses his big week, his love for Oreos, movies, video games and more. (20:52) Chris Simms is in the Oklahoma Hall of Fame? (38:35) Austin Ekeler declares that he is 99% back this week and shares his thoughts on the rules of UNO. (52:41) Stu Ya Gotz. (56:26) Mike Golic previews Week 7 in College Football. (1:09:22) Georgia Tech HC, Brent Key celebrates his team&amp;rsquo;s win over Miami.</description></item></channel></rss>