<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Kurzgesagt on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/categories/kurzgesagt/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Kurzgesagt on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 23:56:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/categories/kurzgesagt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>1.000km kabel ka Béntang-Skyhook ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/su/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 23:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/su/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkrip ﻿Kéngingkeun rohangan hese.
Ayeuna, éta sapertos angkat dina gunung dina tempat anu teu sesat
anu nganggo kantong pinuh ku bahan peledak.
Sacara anéh laun, anjeun moal tiasa ngangkut seueur barang, sareng anjeun maot.
Rokét kudu ngahontal laju kira-kira 40,000km sajam pikeun lolos tina Bumi.
Pikeun ngahontal laju éta, rokét téh biasana wadah bahan bakar kalayan tip gajih leutik.
Ieu anu goréng upami anjeun badé angkat ka planét anu sanés.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Motive Pentru Care Marijuana Ar Trebui Să Rămână Ilegală - dezbătute ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ro/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 23:46:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ro/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcriere ﻿În jurul lumii,
marijuana devine decriminalizată sau chiar legalizată.
Dar este asta o idee bună?
În dezbaterile online, dezavantajele ei sunt trecute cu vederea.
Haideți să ne uităm la cele mai puternice trei argumente împotriva legalizării marijuanei
Argumentul numărul unu:
În ultimele decenii,
Marijuana a fost ajustată să fie mult mai potentă decât înainte.
În ziua de azi, Marijuana este atât de potentă încât a devenit un drog puternic care poate cauza psihoză,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 סיבות למה אנרגיה גרעינית מדהימה! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/he/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 23:23:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/he/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>וידאו טְק֡ס֙ט ﻿3 סיבות שבגללן אנחנו צריכים להמשיך להשתמש באנרגיה גרעינית:
אנרגיה גרעינית מצילה חיים בשנת 2013, מחקר של נאס&amp;quot;א גילה שאנרגיה גרעינית מנעה
בערך 1.8 מיליון מיתות.
אפילו אם כוללים את ההרוגים באסונות צ&amp;rsquo;רנוביל ופוקושימה,
אנרגיה גרעינית מדורגת במקום האחרון ביחס בין מספר המיתות לכמות האנרגיה שמופקת.
אפילו שפסולת גרעינית היא רעילה ביותר, בדרך כלל היא מאוחסנת במקום כלשהו,
בעוד שהשאריות הרעילות של שריפת דלקי מאובנים נפלטות אל האוויר</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Itsekeskeinen argumentti maailman parantamisen puolesta - egoistinen altruismi. ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/fi/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 23:21:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/fi/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkriptio ﻿Viime aikoihin asti, suurin osa maailman ihmisistä työskenteli maatiloilla
ja maailman markkinoiden kokonaistuotanto
oli enimmäkseen viljelyn kokonaistuotos.
Ja tämä tuotos oli sidottuna maapinta-alaan.
Markkinoiden kokonaisutuotto ei vaihdellut paljoakaan vuosi vuodelta.
Piirakan koko oli rajallinen; maailma oli nollasummapeliä
Tällaisessa paikallaan polkevassa maailmassa, ainoa tapa tulla paremmin toimeen oli jos joku muu tulee huonommin toimeen.
jos otat isomman palan piiraasta, joku muu saa vähemmän.
Jos haluat enemmän ruokaa, silloin valloittaminen, ryöstäminen ja varastaminen ovat loistavia strategioita.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 motivi per cui la marijuana dovrebbe rimanere illegale, esaminati ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/it/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 23:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/it/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Video Trascrizione ﻿In tutto il mondo la marijuana viene depenalizzata o addirittura legalizzata
Ma è davvero una buona idea?
Diamo un&amp;rsquo;occhiata ai tre argomenti più importanti contro la legalizzazione della marijuana
Argomento numero uno: negli ultimi decenni
La marijuana è stata progettata per diventare molto più potente
Oggi la marijuana è così potente che in realtà è diventata un farmaco forte che può causare psicosi.
Il principale principio attivo della marijuana è il THC e c&amp;rsquo;è una forte evidenza che il THC sia correlato alla psicosi</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Dünyanı daha yaxşı bir yer etmək üçün özünü düşünən bir mübahisə. ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/az/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 23:10:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/az/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkriptlər ﻿Son vaxta qədər dünya əhalisinin əksəriyyəti fermalarda işləyirdi
və dünya iqtisadiyyatının ümumi istehsalı
əksərən kənd təssərrüfatı idi.
Və bu istehsal torpağın müəyyən ölçüsü ilə məhdudlaşdırılmışdı.
İqtisadiyyatın ümumi hasilatı ildən-ilə dəyişmirdi.
Kökənin ölçüsü müəyyənləşdirilmişdi; dünya sıfır-cəmli oyun idi.
Belə bir durğunlaşmış dünyada, faydalanmağın yeganə yolu başqasının zərərlənməsindən ibarət idi.
Sən kökənin böyük hissəsini götürsən, başqası balacasını gotürməli olur.
Sən daha çox qida istəyirsənsə, onda fəth, qarət və oğurluğ etmək yaxşı ideyadır.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Yıldızlara Uzanan 1.000 km&#39;lik Kablo - Gök Kancası ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/tr/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 23:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/tr/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkript ﻿Uzaya çıkmak epey zordur.
Sırt çantanız patlayıcılarla dolu bir şekilde ve tek tekerlekli bir bisiklet ile dağa çıkmak gibidir bu aynı.
Aşırı yavaştır, fazla şey taşıyamazsınız ve belki de çıkarken yolda ölebilirsiniz.
Bir roketin Dünya&amp;rsquo;dan kurtulup uzaya çıkabilmesi için gereken hız 40 bin km/s&amp;rsquo;dir.
Bu hıza ulaşabilmek için&amp;hellip;
&amp;hellip;roketler, çoğunlukla yakıt konteynırları olup içlerinde sadece azıcık yük taşıyabilirler.
Başka gezegenlere gitmek istiyorsanız eğer bu hiç de iyi bir şey değildir.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 argumenty, prečo by mala marihuana zostať nelegálna, preskúmané ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/sk/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 23:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/sk/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Video Prepis ﻿Na celom svete
sa marihuana dekriminalizuje, alebo dokonca legalizuje.
Ale je to naozaj dobrý nápad?
V on-line diskusii
sú škodlivé účinky často zľahčované.
Tak sa pozrime na tri najsilnejšie argumenty
proti legalizácii marihuany.
Argument číslo 1:
V posledných desaťročiach
Bola marihuana šľachtená tak, aby sa stala oveľa silnejšou.
Dnes je tak účinná,
že v skutočnosti to je dnes už silná droga, ktorá môže spôsobiť psychózu.
Hlavnou aktívnou zložkou marihuany je THC</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Reasons Why Nuclear Energy Is Terrible! 2/3 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 22:47:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿three reasons why we should stop using nuclear energy
one. nuclear weapons proliferation
nuclear technology made a violent entrance onto the world stage
just one year after the world&amp;rsquo;s first-ever nuclear test explosion in
1944
two large cities were destroyed by just two single bombs
after that, reactor technology slowly evolved as a means of generating
electricity but it&amp;rsquo;s always been intimately connected with nuclear
weapons technology
it&amp;rsquo;s nearly impossible to develop nuclear weapons without access to reactor</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>우주를 향한 1000킬로미터의 케이블 - 스카이후크 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ko/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 22:45:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ko/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>비디오 대본 ﻿우주로 가는 것은 어려운 일입니다. 지금으로서는 마치 가방에 폭발물을 잔뜩 진 채 외발자전거를 타고 산을 오르는 것과 같습니다. 믿을수 없을 정도로 느리</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 причини, поради които ядрената енергия е страхотна! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/bg/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 22:38:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/bg/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>Видео Транскрипция ﻿Три причини, поради които трябва да продължим да използваме ядрена енергия.
Първо: ядрената енергия спасява животи.
През 2013, проучване, проведено от НАСА, показва, че ядрената енергия е предотвратила
около 1.8 милиона смъртни случая.
Дори ако включите смъртните случаи от Чернобил и Фукушима,
ядрената енергия застава на последно място при отношение смърт на единица произведена енергия.
Ядрените отпадъци, които са много токсични, най-често се съхраняват някъде,
докато токсичните вторични продукти от изкопаеми горива са изпомпвани във въздуха,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Um argumento egoísta para tornar o mundo um lugar melhor - Altruísmo egoísta. ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/pt-pt/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 22:38:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/pt-pt/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>Vídeo Transcrição ﻿Até recentemente, a vasta maioria da população mundial trabalhou em fazendas
e a produção total da economia mundial
foi em maior parte a produção agrícola total
E esta produção estava limitada pelo tamanho fixo da terra
A produção total da economia não mudou muito ano a ano
O tamanho da torta era fixo; o mundo era um jogo de soma zero
Num mundo assim estagnado, a única maneira de se dar bem é se outra pessoa se der mal</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 motive pentru care energia nucleară este minunată! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ro/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 22:27:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ro/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcriere ﻿Trei motive pentru care ar trebui să continuăm să utilizăm energia nucleară.
1: Energia nucleară salvează vieți.
În 2013, un studiu realizat de NASA a descoperit că energia nucleară a prevenit circa 1.8 milioane de decese.
Chiar dacă incluzi decesele datorate exploziilor de la Cernobîl și Fukushima,
energia nucleară se află pe ultimul loc în ceea ce privește decesele pe unitate de energie produsă.
Reziduurile nucleare sunt, întradevăr, foarte toxice, dar sunt stocate în spații închise,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 redenen waarom kernenergie vreselijk is! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/nl/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 22:23:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/nl/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcriptie ﻿Drie redenen waarom we zouden moeten stoppen met kernenergie.
Een: Nucleaire proliferatie
Nucleaire technologie maakte oorspronkelijk een gewelddadige opkomst
Slechts één jaar na de eerste testexplosie in 1944,
werden twee steden vernietigd door slechts twee afzonderlijke bommen.
Daarna kwam langzaam reactortechnologie op
als een manier om electriciteit te genereren,
maar het heeft altijd een nauwe band gehad met nucleaire wapens.
Het is bijna onmogelijk nucleaire wapens te ontwikkelen</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 motivi per cui l&#39;energia nucleare è fantastica! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/it/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 22:12:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/it/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>Video Trascrizione ﻿Tre ragioni per cui dovremmo continuare ad usare l&amp;rsquo;energia nucleare.
L&amp;rsquo;energia nucleare salva vite. Nel 2013 uno studio condotto dalla NASA ha dimostrato
che l&amp;rsquo;energia nucleare ha prevenuto circa 1,8 milioni di morti.
Perfino se si includono le morti causate da Chernobyl e Fukushima,
L&amp;rsquo;energia nucleare si conferma ultima nella lista delle morti per unità di energia prodotta.
Sebbene le scorie nucleari siano molto tossiche,
di solito sono conservate da qualche parte.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 причины, почему ядерная энергия ужасна! 2/3 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ru/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 21:57:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ru/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>Видео Транскрипт ﻿Есть три причины, по которым мы должны отказаться от атомной энергии.
Во-первых, увеличение количества ядерного оружия.
Ядерные технологии весьма жестоко явились на мировую сцену:
спустя год после первого в мире пробного ядерного взрыва в 1944 году
два крупных города были уничтожены лишь двумя небольшими бомбами.
C тех пор, ядерные технологии медленно развивались
как способ генерации электричества,
но всегда были тесно связаны с технологиями ядерного вооружения.
Практически невозможно разработать ядерное оружие,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Een egoïstisch argument voor het verbeteren van de wereld. ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/nl/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 21:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/nl/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcriptie ﻿Nog niet zo lang geleden werkten de meeste mensen op boerderijen
en de totale productie van de wereldeconomie was vooral de totale landbouwproductie.
En die productie was beperkt door een vaste oppervlakte land.
De hele productie van de economie veranderde niet zoveel met de jaren.
De grootte van de taart lag vast.
De wereld was een nulsomspel.
Je krijgt het in zo&amp;rsquo;n stagnerende wereld enkel beter&amp;hellip;
als iemand het slechter krijgt.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Argumente gegen die Marihuana-Legalisierung geprüft ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/de/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 21:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/de/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkript ﻿Auf der ganzen Welt
wird Mariuhana zurzeit entkriminalisiert, oder sogar legalisiert.
aber ist das wirklich eine gute Idee ?
In Onlinediskussionen
werden die ungesunden Nebenwirkungen oft verharmlost.
Also lasst uns die drei wichtigsten Argumente gegen die Legalisierung von Marihuana betrachten.
Intro * Argument Nummer 1:
In den letzten Jahrzehnten, wurde Marihuana modifiziert und wurde viel potenter
Heute ist Marihuana so stark
dass es tatsächlich eine so starke Droge ist, die Psychosen auslösen könnte</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 raisons pour lesquelles l&#39;énergie nucléaire est néfaste ! (2/3) ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/fr/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 21:30:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/fr/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>Vidéo Transcription ﻿Trois raisons pour lesquelles ont devrait arrêter d&amp;rsquo;utiliser l&amp;rsquo;énergie nucléaire.
Premièrement: la prolifération des armes nucléaires.
La technologie nucléaire a fait une violente apparition sur la scène internationale:
seulement un an après le tout premier test mondial d&amp;rsquo;explosion nucléaire en 1944,
deux grandes villes ont été détruites par seulement deux bombes.
Après quoi, la technologie des réacteurs a lentement évolué
en un moyen de générer de l&amp;rsquo;électricité,
mais ça a toujours été intimement lié avec la technologie des armes nucléaires.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 syytä, miksi ydinenergia on mahtavaa! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/fi/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 21:28:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/fi/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkriptio ﻿Kolme syytä, miksi meidän pitäisi jatkaa ydinvoiman käyttöä.
Ydinvoima pelastaa henkiä. Vuonna 2013, NASAn teettämä tutkimus totesi että ydinvoima on ehkäissyt
arviolta 1.8 miljoonaa kuolemaa.
Vaikka laskisit mukaan Chernobylin ja Fukushiman uhrit,
ydinvoima aiheuttaa vähiten kuolemia tuotettua energiaa kohden.
Vaikka ydinjäte onkin erittäin haitallista, se varastoidaan yleensä jonnekin,
kun taas haitalliset saasteet fossiilisista polttoaineista pumpataan ilmaan
jota hengitämme joka päivä.
Niinpä, vain vähentämällä fossiilisten polttoaineiden käyttöä, lukemattomia syöpäkasvaimia</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>1000km dây cáp tới các vì sao - Skyhook ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/vi/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 21:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/vi/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>Video Bản trích ﻿Du hành vào không gian hiện vẫn còn rất khó khăn
Như việc bạn đi leo núi trên chiếc xe đạp một bánh
đeo ba lô chứa đầy chất nổ
Cực kì chậm; bạn không thể mang nhiều thứ được và bạn có thể chết
Tên lửa cần đạt vận tốc khoảng 40.000km/h để thoát khỏi Trái đất
Để có được tốc độ như trên
phần đa thân tàu được dùng để chứa nhiên liệu</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>ارزیابی سه استدلال اصلی مخالف با قانونی شدن ماریجوانا ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/fa/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 21:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/fa/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>ویدئو متن ﻿در گوشه و کنار جهان،
ماریجوانا در حال جرم زدایی یا حتی قانونی شدن است.
اما واقعا فکر خوبیه؟
در مناظرات آنلاین،
اغلب جنبه های آسیب زا کمرنگ تر جلوه داده می شود.
پس بیایید نگاهی بیاندازیم به سه تا از قوی ترین استدلالها
در مخالفت با قانونی شدن ماریجوانا.
استدلال شماره 1:
در طی چند دهه گذشته،
ماریجوانا بطور پیوسته برای افزایش قدرت اثر مهندسی شده است.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>1 000 km dlouhé lano ke hvězdám - Vesmírný hák ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/cs/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 21:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/cs/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripce ﻿Dostat se do vesmíru je těžké.
Právě teď je to jako šplhat na horu na jednokolce
s batohem plným výbušnin.
Velice pomalé, nemůžete s sebou mít mnoho věcí a můžete umřít.
Raketa musí dosáhnout rychlosti 40 000 km/h aby unikla zemské gravitaci.
Aby bylo této rychlosti dosaženo, rakety jsou hlavně kontejnery na palivo
s malou špičkou s nákladem.
Tohle není výhodné, pokud se chcete dostat na jiné planety,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Un argument egoist pentru a face lumea un loc mai bun - altruism egoist. ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ro/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 21:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ro/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcriere ﻿Până de curând, marea majoritate a populației globului lucra în ferme,
iar produsul total al economiei mondiale
era, practic, reprezentat de producția agricolă.
Și această producție era limitată de suprafața fixă de pământ.
Produsul brut nu se schimba semnificativ de la an la an.
Mărimea „plăcintei” era predeterminată; lumea era un joc de sumă nulă.
Într-o astfel de lume stagnantă, singurul mod de a te dezvolta e ca altcineva să sufere.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 കാരണങ്ങൾ നൂക്ലിയർ ശക്തി അതിനുള്ളതാണ്! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ml/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 20:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ml/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>വീഡിയോ അപൂർണ്ണം ﻿ഞങ്ങൾ തുടരാൻ മൂന്ന് കാരണങ്ങൾ ആണവ ഊർജ്ജം ഉപയോഗിച്ച്.
ഒന്ന്: ആണവ ജീവിതങ്ങൾ സംരക്ഷിക്കുന്നു.
2013 ൽ നാസ നടത്തിയ പഠനത്തിൽ കണ്ടെത്തി ആണവ തടഞ്ഞു എന്ന്
ഏകദേശം 1.8 ലക്ഷം മരണങ്ങളും.
നിങ്ങളിൽ നിന്ന് മരണം ടോൾ ഉൾപ്പെടുന്നു പോലും ചെർണോബിൽ ഫുകുഷിമ,
ആണവ മരണം ശതമാനം കഴിഞ്ഞ റാങ്ക് ഊർജ്ജ യൂണിറ്റ് നിർമ്മിക്കുന്നത്.
ആണവ മാലിന്യങ്ങൾ ശരിക്കും വിഷo തന്നെ, സാധാരണ എവിടെയോ സംഭരിച്ചു,
ഫോസിൽ ഇന്ധനങ്ങളുടെ വിഷ അറയിലെ അതേസമയം വായുവിൽ പമ്പ് ചെയ്യുന്നു
ഓരോ ദിവസവും ശ്വസിക്കാൻ.
അതിനാൽ, ഫോസിൽ തുക കുറയ്ക്കുകയും ഇന്ധനങ്ങൾ വെന്തു, കാൻസർ എണ്ണമറ്റ കേസുകൾ</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Razones por las que la energía nuclear es increíble! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/es-419/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 20:42:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/es-419/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcripción ﻿3 razones por las cuales deberíamos continuar utilizando la energía nuclear
La energía nuclear salva vidas En 2013, un estudio realizado por la NASA
encontró que la energía nuclear ha prevenido alrededor de 1.8 millones de muertes
Incluso si incluyes las muertes ocasionadas en Chernobyl y Fukushima
la energía nuclear ocupa el último lugar por
unidad de energía producida. Aunque los residuos nucleares
son muy tóxicos, usualmente son almacenados en algún lugar,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Egoista altruizmus - avagy önző érvek a világ jobbá tétele mellett ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/hu/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 20:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/hu/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>Videó Tranzkript ﻿Egészen a közelmúltig a világ népességének túlnyomó többsége a mezőgazdaságban dolgozott
és a világgazdaság össztermelése
szinte teljesen a mezőgazdaságból származott.
A termelékenységet a termőföldek fix mérete szigorú korlátok közé szorította.
Hiába teltek az évek, a gazdaság teljesítménye nem változott sokat évről évre.
A torta mérete tehát fix volt, ezt a közgazdaságtanban nulla összegű játéknak nevezik.
Egy ilyen stagnáló világban ahhoz hogy jól járj, valaki másnak rosszul kell járnia.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Das 1.000km-Kabel zu den Sternen – Der Skyhook ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/de/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 20:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/de/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkript ﻿In den Weltraum zu kommen ist schwierig
Im Moment ist es, als würde man einen Berg auf einem Einrad hochfahren
mit einem Rucksack voller Sprengstoff:
Unglaublich langsam, man kann wenig transportieren und man könnte sterben
Eine Rakete braucht eine Geschwindigkeit von ungefähr 40 000 km/h um der Erde zu entkommen
Um zu dieser Geschwindigkeit zu gelangen
sind Raketen hauptsächlich Behälter für Treibstoff mit einem winzigen bisschen Nutzlast
Das ist schlecht, wenn man zu anderen Planeten will</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Егоистички алтруизам је себични аргумент за учинак света бољим местом. ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/sr-cyrl/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 20:08:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/sr-cyrl/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>Видео Транскрипт ﻿Донедавно, велика већина светске популације је радила на пољским добрима
и укупна производња светске економије
била је претежно укупни пољопривредни добитак.
И овај добитак је ограничен фиксном величином државе.
Укупна економска производња се није мењала много из године у годину.
Величина колача се није мењала. Свет је био игра са позитивном нулом.
У таквом стагнирајућем свету, једини начин да се постане имућан је да неко други осиромаши.
Ако узмеш веће парче колача</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Důvody, proč je jaderná energie úžasná! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/cs/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 19:58:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/cs/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripce ﻿Tři důvody, proč bychom měli pokračovat v užívání jaderné energie.
Zaprvé, jaderná energie zachraňuje životy.
NASA provedla v roce 2013 studii,
podle níž jaderná energie zabránila asi 1,8 milionu úmrtím.
I když zahrnete počty obětí z Černobylu a Fukušimy,
jaderné energii patří poslední místo v počtu úmrtí na produkci energie.
I když je jaderný odpad velmi toxický, obvykle je někde uložen.
Toxické vedlejší produkty fosilních paliv oproti tomu vypouštíme do vzduchu,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Argumen egois untuk membuat dunia menjadi tempat yang lebih baik - Altruisme egois. ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/id/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 19:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/id/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripsi ﻿Hingga baru-baru ini, mayoritas dari populasi di dunia bekerja dibidang pertanian,
dan kebanyakan total produksi dari ekonomi dunia
adalah dari bidang pertanian.
Dan hasil ini dibatasi oleh ukuran lahan yang tetap.
Output total dari ekonomi tidak berubah banyak dari tahun ke tahun.
Ukuran dari painya tidak berubah; dunia adalah sebuah zero-sum game.
Dalam dunia yang sempit tersebut, satu-satunya cara untuk menjadi lebih baik adalah bila orang lain menjadi lebih buruk.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 powody, dlaczego energia jądrowa jest okropna! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/pl/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 19:19:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/pl/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkrypcja ﻿Trzy powody dla których powninniśmy przestać używać energii nuklearnej.
Po pierwsze: rozpowszechnianie broni nuklearnej/
Technologia nuklearna miała gwałtowne wejście na scenę światową:
tylko jeden rok po pierwszej na świecie próbnej eksplozji nuklearnej w 1944,
dwa duże miasta zostały zniszczone tylko przez dwie pojedyncze bomby.
Po tym technologia reaktorowa zaczęła powoli ewoluować
dążąc do generowania elektryczności,
jednakże zawsze była intymnie połączona z technologią broni nuklearnych.
To niemalże niemożliwe, żeby wytworzyć broń nuklearną</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 סיבות לכך שמריחואנה צריכה להישאר בלתי חוקית - סקירה ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/he/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 19:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/he/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>וידאו טְק֡ס֙ט ﻿בכל רחבי העולם, צריכת מריחואנה עוברת הליכי אי-הפללה ולעיתים אפילו נעשית חוקית
אך האם זה באמת רעיון טוב?
בדיונים ברחבי הרשת,
הנזקים לרוב מוצגים כלא חשובים
אז בואו נראה את שלושת הטיעונים החזקים ביותר נגד הפיכת המריחואנה לחוקית.
מוסיקת מבוא * טיעון מס&amp;rsquo; 1: [קנאביס הינו סם קשה]
בעשורים האחרונים,
צמח המריחואנה הונדס להיות הרבה יותר מרוכז,
היום צמח המריחואנה מרוכז,
עד כדי כך שהוא סם חזק העלול לגרום לפסיכוזה.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Dahilan Kung Bakit Ang Enerhiyang Nuklear Ay Masama! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/tl/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 19:13:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/tl/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripsyong ﻿tatlong dahilan kung bakin kailangan nating ihinto ang paggamit ng nuclear energy
Panguna. Ang paglaganap ng nuclear weapons
Ang teknolohiya ng nuclear ay nakagawa ng marahas na pagpasok dito sa daigdig
isang taon lang ang nakalipas mula sa pinakaunang nuclear test explosion noong
1944
dalawang malalaking lungsod ang nawasak mula sa dalawang bomba
pagkaraan, ang teknolohiya ng reaktor ay unti-unti nang lumaki bilang isang paraan ng pagbuo ng</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 أسباب تجعل الطاقة النووية رائعة! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ar/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 18:58:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ar/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>فيديو نص ﻿ثلاثة أسباب لماذا يجب علينا أن نواصل إستخدام الطاقة النووية.
أولاً: الطاقة النووية تنقذ الأرواح.
في عام 2013، دراسة أجرتها وكالة ناسا وجدت أن الطاقة النووية قد منعت
حوالي 1.8 مليون حالة وفاة.
حتى لو قمنا بتضمين عدد القتلى من كارثتي تشيرنوبيل وفوكوشيما،
فالطاقة النووية تحتل المرتبة الأخيرة في نسبة الوفيات لكل وحدة طاقة منتجة.
بينما تعد النفايات النووية سامة حقًا، لكنها عادة ما تكون مخزنة في مكان ما،</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 arsyet pse energjia bërthamore është e tmerrshme! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/sq/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 18:29:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/sq/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripte ﻿3 arsyet pse ne duhet te ndalojme perdorimin e energjis berthamore.
Nje
teknologji bërthamore bërë një dhunshme hyrje në skenën botërore
vetëm një vit pasi në botë shpërthim testi i parë-ndonjëherë bërthamore në
1944
dy qytete të mëdha u shkatërruan nga vetëm Dy bomba të vetme
Pas kësaj, teknologjia reaktori ngadalë evoluar si një mjet për të gjeneruar
të energjisë elektrike, por ajo ka qenë gjithmonë lidhur ngushtë me nukleare</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 argumenta zašto bi marihuana trebala ostati ilegalna ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/hr/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 18:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/hr/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripcija ﻿Diljem svijeta, marihuana se dekriminalizira i čak postaje legalna.
No je li to dobra ideja? U internetskim debatama, štetne strane su često zanemarene.
Pogledajmo tri snažna razloga protiv legalizacije marihuane.
[UVODNA GLAZBA]
Prvi argument:
U zadnjih nekoliko desetljeća,
marihuana je modificirana kako bi postala što snažnija.
Danas je marihuana toliko potentna da je zapravo postala snažna droga koja bi mogla prouzročiti psihozu.
Glavni aktivni sastojak marihuane je THC i postoje snažni dokazi da je THC povezan s psihozom,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>1,000公里的星際纜線 - 天空鉤 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/zh-hant/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 18:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/zh-hant/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>影片 文字稿 ﻿進入太空很難 現在，這就像騎著獨輪車上山，背著裝滿炸藥的背包…… &amp;hellip;非常慢， 你不能運送太多東西，否則可能會死亡。 火箭需</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>1,000 كم كابل إلى النجوم - السكايهوك ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ar/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 18:19:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ar/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>فيديو نص ﻿يعد الوصول إلى الفضاء أمرًا صعبًا في الوقت الحالي ، فهو يشبه الصعود إلى أحد الجبال في رحلة مع حقيبة تحمل على الظهر متفجرات
بطيئة بشكل لا يصدق. لا يمكنك نقل الكثير من الأشياء وقد تموت
يحتاج الصاروخ للوصول إلى سرعة حوالي
40،000 كيلومتر في الساعة للهروب من الأرض للوصول إلى تلك الصواريخ الصواريخ هي في معظمها
حاويات للوقود مع طرف صغير من الحمولة
هذا سيء
إذا كنت تريد الذهاب إلى كوكب آخر لأنك تحتاج إلى الكثير من الأشياء الثقيلة</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>วิเคราะห์ 3 ข้อโต้แย้งว่าทำไมกัญชาถึงยังไม่ถูกกฎหมาย ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/th/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 18:18:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/th/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>วิดีโอ สรุป ﻿ทั่วโลก
กัญชาผิดกฎหมายน้อยลง กระทั่งทำให้ถูกกฎหมาย
แต่มันเป็นความคิดที่ดีแล้วจริงหรือ?
การถกเถียงในโลกออนไลน์
ส่วนมากด้านแย่ๆ มักจะถูกกล่าวถึง
มาดู 3 เหตุผลใหญ่ๆ
ที่ต่อต้านการทำกัญชาให้ถูกกฎหมายกัน
ข้อโต้แย้งที่ 1
ในช่วงไม่กี่สิบปีก่อน
กัญชาได้ถูกปรับปรุง ให้มีฤทธิ์แรงมากขึ้น
กัญชาในปัจจุบันจึงออกฤทธิ์ได้แรงมาก
แรงขนาดทำให้ก่อภาวะทางจิตได้เลย
ส่วนประกอบหลักของกัญชาคือ สาร THC
และก็มีหลักฐานหนักแน่นว่า สารนี้ก่อให้เกิดโรคทางจิตได้
แม้จะไม่นับอาการเสี่ยงอื่นๆ
กัญชายังมีสารประกอบอีกตัวที่เรียกว่า CBD
ซึ่งดูเหมือนจะมีผลต้านกันกับ THC
กระทั่งมีการทดสอบโดยการรักษา โรคจิต และผู้มีอาการซึมเศร้า
แต่เพราะสารตัวนี้แหละ ที่ไม่ทำให้คุณเมายา
ในช่วงไม่กี่สิบปีที่ผ่านมา
ผู้ผลิตจึงลดปริมาณ CBD ลง
ในขณะที่เพิ่มปริมาณ THC
ปริมาณ THC ในตัวอย่างที่ถูกทดสอบ ถูกเพิ่มขึ้นจากราว 4% ในช่วงปี 90
เป็นราว 12% ในปี 2014
เปลื่ยนอัตราส่วน THC ต่อ CBD จาก 1 ต่อ 14 ในปี 1995
ไปเป็น 1 ต่อ 80 ในปี 2014
แต่ก็ไม่รู้ว่าผลการทดสอบเหล่านั้นแม่นยำขนาดไหน
โดยรวมกล่าวได้ว่า ยิ่งคุณเสพกัญชามากเท่าไร</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3个原因说明核能是可怕的！ ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/zh-hans/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 18:14:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/zh-hans/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>视频 文字稿 ﻿不再使用核能的三个理由。 一：核武器扩散 核科技以一种残暴的方式登上世界舞台： 1944年世界上第一次核弹实验之后仅仅一年， 两个大型城</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Argumentos por los que la Marihuana Debería Permanecer Ilegal Revisados ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/es-es/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 18:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/es-es/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcripción ﻿Alrededor del mundo, la marihuana está siendo despenalizada, o incluso legalizada
¿Pero es esto realmente una buena idea? En el debate en línea, los efectos dañinos suelen ser minimizados
Echémosle un vistazo a los tres argumentos más poderosos contra la legalización de la marihuana
Argumento número 1: en las últimas décadas
la marihuana ha sido alterada para ser mucho más potente
hoy en día la marihuana es tan potente que se considera una droga fuerte que puede causar psicosis.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 argumentai, kodėl marihuana turėtu likti neteisėta – apžvalga ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/lt/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 18:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/lt/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripcija ﻿Aplink pasaulį
marihuana yra dekriminalizuojama ar net daroma teisėta.
Bet ar tai tikrai gera idėja?
Diskusijų internete metu
žalingos pusės dažnai yra per prastinamos.
Taigi pažvelkime į tris galingiausius argumentus
prieš marihuanos legalizavimą.
[Intro - Kurzgesagt]
Argumentas numeris 1:
Per pastaruosius kelis dešimtmečius
marihuana buvo auginama tapti kur kas stipresne.
Šiandien marihuana yra tokia stipri,
kad tai iš tikrųjų yra stiprus medikamentas, kuris gali sukelti psichozę.
Pagrindinis marihuanos ingredientas yra THC</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Gründe warum Atomkraft schrecklich ist! 2/3 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/de/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 17:43:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/de/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkript ﻿3 Gründe warum wir aufhören sollten, nukleare Energie zu benutzen:
Nummer 1: Die Vermehrung von nuklearen Waffen.
Nukleare Technologie machte einen gewaltsamen Schritt auf die Weltbühne.
Nur ein Jahr nach der allerersten nuklearen Testexplosion im Jahre 1944,
wurden 2 große Städte von nur 2 einzelnen Bomben zerstört.
Kurz darauf entwickelte sich Reaktortechnologie lamgsam zu einem
Mittel um Strom herzustellen, aber es wird immer inniglich mit nuklearen
Waffen verbunden sein.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>1.000 km de Cabo para as Estrelas - O Skyhook ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/pt-pt/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 17:42:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/pt-pt/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>Vídeo Transcrição ﻿Ir para o espaço é difícil.
Atualmente, é como subir uma montanha com um monociclo
com uma mochila cheia de explosivos.
Incrivelmente devagar, você não pode transportar muita coisa e, você pode morrer.
Um foguete precisa alcançar uma velocidade de aproximadamente 40 mil quilômetros por hora para sair da Terra
Para chegar a essa velocidade, os foguetes são basicamente recipientes para combustível
com uma pequena ponta de carga.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Argumen Mengapa Ganja Harus Tetap Ilegal Diulas ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/id/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 17:38:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/id/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripsi ﻿Di seluruh dunia,
ganja sedang dalam proses didekriminalisasi, bahkan dilegalkan.
Tapi, apakah ini ide yang bagus?
Di dalam debat online,
sisi-sisi buruknya sering diremehkan.
Jadi, mari kita lihat pada tiga argumen terkuat
terhadap legalisasi ganja.
[Intro - Kurzgesagt] Sub by: Ali Ribat R
Argumen pertama: Ganja adalah obat yang kuat
Dalam beberapa dekade terakhir,
Ganja telah dibuat untuk menjadi lebih ampuh.
Saat ini, marijuana sangat ampuh,
hingga dapat menyebabkan penyakit kejiwaan.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>1,000km Cable to the Stars - The Skyhook ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 17:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Getting to space is hard.
Right now, it’s like going up on a mountain on a unicycle-
with a backpack full of explosives.
Incredibly slow, you can’t transport a lot of stuff, and you might die.
A rocket needs to reach a velocity about 40,000km an hour to escape from Earth.
To get to that speed, rockets are mostly containers for fuel with a tiny tip of payload.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>關於為什麼大麻應該不合法的三個爭論點 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/zh-hant/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 17:28:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/zh-hant/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>影片 文字稿 ﻿大麻在全世界正被除罪化甚至合法化 但這真的是個好主意嗎？ 在網路論戰中，有害的一面經常被淡化 所以讓我們來檢視三個反對大麻合法化的主要</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 põhjust, miks tuumaenergia on kohutav! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/et/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 17:26:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/et/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkriptsioon ﻿3 põhjust, miks me peaksime lõpetama
tuumaenergia kasutamise.
Tuumarelva levik. Tuumatehnoloogia sisenes maailmalavale vägivaldselt.
Kõigest aasta pärast esimest
tuumaplahvatuse katset aastal 1944,
hävitati kaks suurt linna vaid kahe pommiga.
Seejärel arenes vaikselt elektritootmise
reaktoritehnoloogia, kuid see on alati olnud
lähedalt seotud tuumarelvatehnoloogiaga.
Peaaegu võimatu on arendada tuumarelvi
ilma juurdepääsuta reaktoritehnoloogiale.
Tuumarelva leviku piiramise leping teenib eesmärki,
levitada reaktoritehnoloogiat tuumarelva levitamata,
üksnes piiratud eduga.
40 aasta jooksul on viis riiki loonud oma tuumarelvad</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Аргумента Почему Марихуана Должна Оставаться Незаконной ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ru/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 17:18:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ru/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Видео Транскрипт ﻿Во всем мире марихуана декриминализуется или даже становится законной
Но действительно ли это хорошая идея?
В онлайн-дебатах вред часто преуменьшается
Итак, давайте рассмотрим три самых веcких аргумента против легализации марихуаны
KURZGESAGT
KURZGESAGT -вкратце-
Аргумент номер один:
За последние несколько десятилетий марихуана была спроектирована,
чтобы стать намного более сильнодействующей.
Сегодня марихуана настолько мощна, что на самом деле
это сильный наркотик, который может вызвать психоз.
Основным активным веществом марихуаны является ТГК (Тетрагидроканнабинол),</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3个原因为什么核能是很棒的！ ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/zh-hans/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 17:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/zh-hans/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>视频 文字稿 ﻿三个理由为什么我们需要继续使用核能源。 第一：核能源挽救生命。 在2013年，由NASA进行的一项研究发现，核能源阻止了 大概1千8百</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>1,000ก.ม. เชือกสู่ดวงดาว - The Skyhook ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/th/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 17:11:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/th/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>วิดีโอ สรุป ﻿จะไปอวกาศได้ช่างยากเย็น
ในตอนนี้ มันเปรียบเหมือนกับการขี่จักรยานล้อเดียวขึ้นภูเขา
พร้อมกับกระเป๋าเป้ที่เต็มไปด้วยระเบิด
ไปได้อย่างเชื่องช้า ขนของเยอะแยะก็ไม่ได้ และอาจถึงตายได้
จรวดลำหนึ่งจะต้องมีความเร็วประมาณ 40,000 กม./ชม. ถึงจะหลุดพ้นจากโลกได้
จะไปให้ถึงอัตราเร็วนั้นได้ จรวดก็ต้องบรรจุเชื้อเพลิงเป็นส่วนมาก โดยบรรจุสัมภาระได้เพียงน้อยนิด
ซึ่งเป็นเรื่องแย่สุด ๆ ถ้าคุณอยากจะไปดาวเคราะห์ดวงอื่น
เพราะคุณต้องมีของหนัก ๆ หลายอย่างถ้าอยากอยู่รอด และบางทีอาจจะต้องเดินทางกลับอีก
แล้ว, มีวิธีไหนบ้างล่ะที่จะท่องอวกาศได้โดยใช้เชื้อเพลิงน้อยลง แต่บรรทุกสัมภาระได้มากขึ้น
สิ่งดี ๆ อย่างหนึ่งที่ช่วยแก้ปัญหาการขนส่งได้มากที่สุดบนโลกคือสิ่งที่คุณเรียกกันว่า โครงสร้างพื้นฐาน
ไม่ว่าจะเป็นถนนสำหรับรถยนต์, ท่าเรือสำหรับเรือ, หรือรางสำหรับรถไฟ
เราเดินทางไปที่ต่าง ๆ ได้ง่ายขึ้น
เราสามารถแก้ปัญหาเดียวกันนี้ได้กับการเดินทางในอวกาศ
โครงสร้างพื้นฐานทางอวกาศจะช่วยให้เข้าสู่วงโคจรหรือทะยานออกจากดวงจันทร์, ดาวอังคาร, และที่ห่างไกลได้ง่ายขึ้นและราคาถูกกว่า
เยี่ยมเลย, แต่จริง ๆ แล้วโครงสร้างพื้นฐานทางอวกาศมันคืออะไรกันแน่
มันไม่เหมือนกับลิฟต์อวกาศบนโลก ที่ยังคงเป็นนิยายวิทยาศาสตร์อยู่
ยังมีเทคโนโลยีอันเรียบง่าย ที่ไม่ต้องใช้วิทยาการแขนงใหม่
วัสดุวิเศษ หรือการลงทุนครั้งใหญ่
และถูกทดสอบในวงโคจรสำเร็จเรียบร้อยแล้ว
สายเคเบิลกับตัวถ่วงน้ำหนัก
ที่รู้จักกันว่า สายล่าม
แนวคิดของมันช่างง่ายดาย จนน่าประหลาดใจ
ถ้าเกิดเรานำสายล่าม
ที่ยาวกว่าร้อยหรือพันกิโลเมตร ไปไว้ในอวกาศ และมียานอวกาศ
ใช้มันเป็นบันไดเพื่อไต่ระดับให้สูงขึ้นและเพิ่มอัตราเร็วล่ะ
แนวคิดนี้รู้จักกันในชื่อของ Skyhook
มันจะทำงานได้ดียิ่งขึ้น ถ้าทำให้มันหมุน
ตัวถ่วงน้ำหนักจะยึดสายเคเบิลให้อยู่กับที่ ในขณะที่มันหมุนเป็นวงกลม
สายล่ามที่หมุนอยู่จะช้าลงเมื่อปลายของมันอยู่ด้านล่างเมื่อเทียบกับพื้นโลก
และเคลื่อนที่เร็วขึ้นเมื่อขึ้นไปสูงสุดเหมือนกับเครื่องยิงก้อนหิน
นั่นหมายความว่าคุณสามารถถ่ายโอนพลังงานจากสายล่าม</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Redenen waarom kernenergie geweldig is! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/nl/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 16:54:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/nl/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcriptie ﻿Drie redenen waarom we kernenenergie zouden moeten blijven gebruiken:
Ten eerste: Kernenergie redt levens.
Een onderzoek van NASA uit 2013
toonde aan dat kernenergie ongeveer 1,8 miljoen doden heeft voorkomen.
Zelfs als je de dodentallen van Tsjernobyl en Fukushima meetelt,
staat kernenergie op de laatste plaats,
uitgedrukt in doden per energie-eenheid.
Hoewel kernafval erg giftig is, wordt het doorgaans opgeslagen
terwijl giftige afvalgassen van fossiele brandstoffen in de lucht worden gepompt die we dagelijks inademen.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Gründe, warum Atomenergie super ist! 3/3 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/de/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 16:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/de/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkript ﻿3 Gründe warum wir weiterhin nukleare Energie benutzen sollten:
Nummer 1: Nukleare Energie rettet Leben!
Im Jahre 2013 wurde durch eine Studie welche von der NASA geführt wurde,
festgestellt dass nukleare Energie 1.8 Millionen Tode verhindert hat.
Selbst wenn die Tode beachtet werden, die durch Fukushima und Chernobyl
verursacht worden sind, steht nukleare Energie auf dem letzten Platz von den
Toden pro Kilowatt die produziert worden sind.
Da nuklearer Abfall sehr toxisch ist, wird es normalerweise irgendwo gelagert,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3個原因為什麼核能很棒！ ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/zh-hant/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 15:56:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/zh-hant/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>影片 文字稿 ﻿三個原因為什麼我們要繼續使用核能 第一： 核能拯救了不少生命 在2013年，一份NASA做的報告指出 核能預防了180萬個死亡數 就算你包</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 argumenter for hvorfor marihuana skal forblive ulovligt vuderet ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/da/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 15:47:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/da/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Video Transskription ﻿Verden over
bliver cannabis dekriminaliseret eller endda lovliggjort.
Men er dette egentligt en god ide?
I den offentlige debat
bliver de skadelige sider ofte bagatelliseret.
Så lad os kigge på de tre stærkeste argumenter
imod legalisering af cannabis.
Første argument:
I de seneste årtier
er cannabis blevet genmanipuleret til at være langt mere potent.
I dag er cannabis så potent,
at det faktisk er et stærkt narkotikum, der kan forårsage psykoser.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 grunde til hvorfor atomenergi er fantastisk! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/da/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 15:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/da/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>Video Transskription ﻿Tre grunde til, hvorfor vi skal forsætte med at bruge atomkraft.
Første: atomkraft redder liv.
I 2013, vidste et studie fra NASA, atomkraft har afværget
omkring 1,8 millioner dødsfald.
Selv, hvis du inkluderer dødstalene fra Chernobyl og Fukushima,
ranksere atomkraft sidst i døde pr. energi enhed produceret.
Selvom atomaffald er meget giftigt er det normal at opbevare det et sted,
hvorimod, de gifitige biproduktor af fossile brændstoffer bliver pumpet ud i luften</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 επιχειρήματα που η μαριχουάνα πρέπει να μείνει παράνομη ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/el/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 15:45:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/el/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Βίντεο Αποσπάσματα ﻿Σε όλο τον κόσμο, η κάνναβη αποποινικοποιείται ή ακόμα γίνεται και νόμιμη.
Είναι όμως αυτό καλή ιδέα; Στις διαδικτυακές διαμάχες, οι βλαβερές πτυχές της κάνναβης συχνά υποβαθμίζονται,
για αυτό, ας δούμε τα τρία πιο ισχυρά επιχειρήματα κατά της νομιμοποίησης της κάνναβης.
Εισαγωγή - Kurzgesagt
Επιχείρημα νούμερο 1: Τις τελευταίες δεκαετίες,
η μαριχουάνα έχει σχεδιαστεί για να είναι πολύ πιο δραστική.
Σήμερα, η μαριχουάνα είναι τόσο ισχυρή, που στην πραγματικότητα είναι ένα δυνατό ναρκωτικό ικανό να προκαλέσει ψύχωση.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3เหตุผลที่พลังงานนิวเคลียร์เยี่ยมยอด! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/th/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 15:41:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/th/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>วิดีโอ สรุป ﻿สามเหตุผลว่าทำไมเราควรใช้พลังงานนิวเคลียร์ต่อไป
หนึ่ง: พลังนิวเคลียร์ช่วยชีวิตเรา
ในปี ค.ศ. 2013 การศึกษาของนาซ่าพบว่าพลังงานนิวเคลียร์ได้ขัดขวาง
การตายของชีวิตราวหนึ่งล้านแปดแสนชีวิต
แม้คุณจะรวมยอดผู้เสียชีวิตจากเหตุการณ์เชอร์โนบิล และ ฟุกุชิมะ
พลังงานนิวเคลียร์ก็ยังอยู่ในอันดับท้ายสุดของการเสียชีวิตต่อพลังงานที่ผลิตได้
ขณะที่กากนิวเคลียร์ที่มีพิษมากนั้น ถูกเก็บไว้ที่ไหนสักแห่ง
พิษที่เป็นผลพลอยได้จากเชื้อเพลิงฟอสซิลนั้นกลับถูกปล่อยไปในอากาศ
ที่เราหายใจทุกๆวัน
ดังนั้น เพียงแค่ลดปริมาณการเผาเชื้อเพลิงฟอสซิล ก็เท่ากับหลีกเลี่ยง
สาเหตุของโรคมะเร็ง หรือโรคปอด และอุบัติเหตุในเหมืองถ่านหิน
ถ้าเราสามารถเลือกระหว่างสิ่งที่อันตรายซึ่งฝังไว้ในหลุมลึก
กับสิ่งที่อันตรายมากกว่า ซึ่งปล่อยสู่ชั้นบรรยากาศ
อย่างแรกดูจะมีเหตุผลมากกว่า
พลังงานนิวเคลียร์ดูจะรู้สึกเหมือนว่าอันตรายมากกว่า แม้ว่า
จะเกิดเหตุการณ์เพียงแค่ครั้งเดียว แต่มันจะตราตรึงอยู่ในความทรงจำของเรา ขณะที่ถ่านหินและน้ำมันเป็นภัยเงียบ
เหมือนกับอัตราการเสียชีวิตจากการบินเมื่อเทียบกับการขับรถ
แม้ในกรณีที่ดีที่สุด ต้องใช้เวลาอย่างน้อยสี่สิบปีเพื่อเปลี่ยน
ไปใช้พลังงานหมุนเวียน 100%
ดังนั้น ตราบใดที่เรายังใช้เชื้อเพลิงฟอสซิลต่อไป พลังงานนิวเคลียร์จะช่วย
อีกหลายชีวิตไม่ให้ถูกทำลาย
สอง: พลังงานนิวเคลียร์ลดการปล่อยคาร์บอนไดออกไซด์
มีข้อสนุบสนันว่าพลังงานนิวเคลียร์เป็นอันตรายต่อสิ่งแวดล้อมน้อย
ในส่วนของการเปลี่ยนแปลงสภาพบรรยากาศน้อยกว่าเชื้อเพลิงฟอสซิลที่เป็นแหล่งพลังงานส่วนใหญ่ของเรา
ตั้งแต่ปี ค.ศ. 1976 ประมาณ 64 กิกะตัน ของก๊าซเรือนกระจก
ไม่ถูกปล่อยออก ต้องขอบคุณพลังงานนิวเคลียร์
และกลางศตวรรษที่ 21 สามารถเพิ่มขึ้นเป็น 80-240 กิกะตัน
การบริโภคพลังงานของมนุษยชาติจะมีความมั่นคงมากขึ้น
ตามที่รัฐบาลสหรัฐฯ ประมาณการ แค่ประเทศจีนเพียงประเทศเดียว
จะต้องสร้างโรงไฟฟ้าถ่านหิน 600 เมกะวัตต์ ทุกสิบวัน สำหรับสิบปีข้างหน้า
ประเทศจีนได้เผาถ่านหินไปแล้วสี่พันล้านตันต่อปี</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Granskning Av 3 Anledningar Marijuana Borde Förbli Olagligt ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/sv/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 15:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/sv/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkription ﻿Runt om i världen blir marijuana avkriminaliserat eller till och med legaliserat
Men är detta verkligen en bra idé? I online-debatten blir de skadliga sidorna ofta nertonade.
Så låt oss ta en titt på de tre största argumenten mot en legalisering av marijuana.
♪ Intromusik ♪
Argument nummer 1: Under de senaste få årtiondena
har marijuanan modifierats för att bli mycket mer potent.
Idag är marijuana så potent att det faktiskt är en stark drog som kan orsaka psykoser.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Powody Dla Których Marihuana Powinna Pozostać Nielegalna Omówione ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/pl/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 15:39:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/pl/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkrypcja ﻿Na całym świecie posiadanie marihuany przestaje być postrzegane jako przestępstwo, a nawet staje się legalne.
Lecz czy to faktycznie dobry pomysł? Internetowe debaty na temat marihuany, często pomijają jej złe strony.
A więc, rzućmy okiem na 3 najmocniejsze argumenty używane przeciwko legalizacji marihuany.
Argument nr 1: W kilku ostatnich dekadach
marihuana została zmodyfikowana w taki sposób, by być znacznie silniejszą.
Dzisiejsza marihuana jest tak silna, że może wywoływać psychozę.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 grunner til at kjernekraft er fantastisk! 3/3 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/no/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 15:29:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/no/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripsjon ﻿Tre grunner hvorfor vi burde fortsette å bruke kjernekraft.
En: Kjernekraft redder liv
I 2013, en studie utført av NASA fant ut at kjernekraft har forhindret
rundt 1.8 millioner dødsfall.
Selv om du inkluderer dødstallene fra Chernobyl og Fukushima,
atomenergi rangerer sist i dødsfall per energienhet produsert.
Mens radioaktivt avfall er veldig giftig, er det vanligvis lagret et sted,
mens giftgasser fra fossilt brennstoff er pumpet ut i luften</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>1,000 km Kabel till Stjärnorna - Himlakroken ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/sv/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 15:25:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/sv/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkription ﻿Att ta sig till rymden är svårt.
Just nu, är det som att ta sig uppför ett berg på en enhjuling.
Med en ryggsäck full av sprängmedel.
Otroligt långsamt, du kan inte transportera mycket saker, och du kan dö.
En raket behöver uppnå en hastighet av ca 40,000 km/h för att undkomma jordens dragningskraft.
För att uppnå den hastigheten består raketer mestadels av bränsle med en liten yta för nyttolast i toppen.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Egoistyczny altruizm - samolubny argument za uczynieniem świata lepszym miejscem. ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/pl/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 15:23:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/pl/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkrypcja ﻿Do niedawna większość populacji Ziemi pracowała na farmach
i suma produkcji światowej ekonomii
składała się głównie z rolnictwa.
Ta wydajność była ograniczona przez stałą wielkość ziemi.
Całkowita wydajność ekonomiczna nie zmieniała się za bardzo z roku na rok.
Wielkość ciasta była stała; a świat pozostawał grą o sumie zerowej.
W takim pogrążonym w stagnacji świecie, jedynym sposobem by zyskać, ktoś inny musi stracić.
Jeśli weźmiesz większą część ciasta, ktoś inny dostanie mniejszą.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>1,000km Cablu către Stele - Cârligul de cer ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ro/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 15:19:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ro/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcriere ﻿A ajunge în spațiu este greu
În acest moment, este ca și cum ai urca pe un munte pe un monociclu
Cu un rucsac plin de explozivi
Incredibil de lent, nu poți transporta multe lucruri și ai putea muri
O rachetă trebuie să atingă o viteză de aproximativ 40.000 km pe oră pentru a scăpa de pe Pământ
Pentru a ajunge la această viteză rachetele sunt în mare parte containere pentru combustibil cu un vârf mic de sarcină utilă</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Marixuananın niyə qeyri-qanuni qalmasının 3 arqumenti nəzərdən keçirilir ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/az/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 15:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/az/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkriptlər ﻿Bütün dünyada marixuana dekriminallaşdırılır, hətta qanuniləşdirilir.
Amma bu, həqiqətən yaxşı bir fikirdirmi?
Onlayn debatda zərərli tərəflər çox vaxt kiçildilir.
Ona görə də, gəlin marixuananın qanuniləşdirilməsinə qarşı ən güclü üç arqumentə baxaq.
1-ci arqument:
Son bir neçə onillikdə marixuana daha güclü olmaq üçün hazırlanmışdır.
Bu gün marixuana o qədər güclüdür ki, əslində, psixoza səbəb ola biləcək qədər güclü bir dərmandır.
Marixuananın əsas aktiv tərkib hissəsi THC-dir və digər risk faktorlarından asılı olmayaraq THC-nin psixozla əlaqəli olduğuna dair güclü sübutlar var.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>ข้อโต้แย้งที่เห็นแก่ตัวเองในการทำให้โลกดีขึ้น - อัลตรูอิสติกอิสติก ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/th/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 15:13:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/th/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>วิดีโอ สรุป ﻿ตั้งแต่อดีต จนกระทั่งถึงช่วงก่อนหน้านี้ไม่นานนัก ประชากรส่วนใหญ่ของโลก เคยทำงานในฟาร์ม
และผลผลิตทั้งหมดของเศรษฐกิจโลก
มาจากผลผลิตทางเกษตรทั้งสิ้น
ผลผลิตเหล่านี้ เคยถูกจำกัดด้วยขนาดของพื้นที่ในการเพาะปลูก
ผลผลิตทั้งหมดในระบบเศรษฐกิจโลกจึงไม่มีการเปลี่ยนแปลงมากนักในแต่ละปี
ถ้าเปรียบกับพาย ขนาดของพายถูกกำหนดไว้แล้ว โลกนี้คือเกมที่ต้องมีคนแพ้และชนะ
ในโลกที่ค่อนข้างซบเซา วิธีเดียวที่จะมีความมั่งคั่งกว่าเดิม คือการที่คนอื่นๆ จะต้องจนลง
ถ้าคุณจะเอาพายชิ้นที่ใหญ่ขึ้น คนอื่นๆ จะได้พายขนาดเล็กลง
ถ้าคุณต้องการอาหารมากขึ้น คุณต้องเอาชนะ ปล้น และขโมย วิธีเหล่านี้เป็นกลยุทธที่ดีทีเดียว
ความสูญเสียของเพื่อนบ้านคือผลประโยชน์ของคุณ
นี่คือความเป็นจริงของสรรพสิ่ง ตั้งแต่หลายพันปีมาแล้ว
สังคมต่างรุกรานกันและกัน เพื่อที่จะแย่งพายชิ้นใหญ่ขึ้น
ความไม่เท่าเทียมทางเศรษฐศาสตร์ช่างรุนแรงนัก
บางคนมีพายชิ้นใหญ่เท่าที่ต้องการ ในขณะที่บางคนก็ต้องใช้ชีวิตกับเศษแป้ง
ต่อมา เมื่อมีการปฏิวัติอุตสาหกรรมเกิดขึ้น ทุกอย่างก็เปลี่ยนไป
เราพัฒนาเครื่องจักร ปรับปรุงพันธุ์พืชที่ดีขึ้น ผลิตปุ๋ยที่ดีกว่าเดิม
เกษตรกรรมก้าวหน้าดั่งจรวด แต่ไม่ได้ผลิตแค่อาหารที่มากขึ้น ทุกหน่วยอุตสาหกรรมทำให้ผลผลิตเหล่านั้นทะลักเลยต่างหาก
ตั้งแต่ ค.ศ. 1700 ถึง 1870 ผลผลิตจากเหล็กในอังกฤษ เพิ่มขึ้นถึง 137 เท่า
การปฏิวัติอุตสาหกรรม ทำให้การเพิ่มขึ้นของผลผลิตทางเศรษฐกิจอย่างที่ไม่สามารถจินตนาการได้
สิ่งนี้ได้บิดเบือนลักษณะธรรมชาติความเป็นจริงของสังคม
การเติบโตทางเศรษฐกิจ ได้เปลี่ยนโลกจากเกมที่ต้องมีคนแพ้และชนะ เป็นเกมที่สามารถมีคนชนะร่วมกันได้
เราได้ค้นพบวิธีที่จะสร้างพายชิ้นใหญ่กว่าเดิม แต่ไม่ใช่แค่ใหญ่ขึ้นนะ แต่พายสามารถขยายได้เองในทุกๆ ปี
คนมั่งมีก็สามารถรวยขึ้นได้อีกในเวลาเดียวกัน
การพัฒนาเช่นนี้กำลังแพร่กระจายและยังคงดำเนินต่อไปในทุกวันนี้
ยาฆ่าเชื้อที่ฆ่าแบคทีเรีย
โรงไฟฟ้าที่ผลิตพลังงาน
โทรศัพท์ที่เชื่อมต่อเราทุกคนด้วยกัน
เครื่องบินที่สามารถพาเราเที่ยวได้ในราคาไม่แพง
ตู้เย็นที่เก็บอาหาร
ความก้าวหน้าอย่างไม่หยุดยั้งในทุกๆ หน่วยเศรษฐกิจดูเหมือนจะเป็นเรื่องปกติสำหรับเราในทุกวันนี้</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>1.000km di cavo fino alle stelle - lo Skyhook ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/it/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 15:12:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/it/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>Video Trascrizione ﻿Arrivare nello spazio è difficile,
per adesso è come
scalare una montagna su un monociclo
con uno zaino pieno di esplosivi: è incredibilmente lento,
non si possono portare molte cose e si può morire.
Un razzo deve raggiungere una velocità
di circa 40000 km/h per lasciare la Terra.
Per arrivare a quella velocità
i razzi sono essenzialmente serbatoi di carburante
con una piccola quantità di carico utile
Questo non va bene se vuoi andare su un altro pianeta</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Kabel 1.000 km yang menuju ke bintang - Skyhook ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/id/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 15:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/id/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripsi ﻿Pergi ke luar angkasa adalah hal yang sulit.
Sekarang, terasa seperti mendaki gunung menggunakan sepeda roda satu
sambil membawa tas yang berisi bahan peledak.
Sangat lambat, kamu tidak bisa membawa banyak barang,
dan mungkin kamu akan mati.
Roket perlu mencapai kecepatan sekitar 40.000 km/jam untuk keluar dari Bumi.
Untuk mencapai kecepatan tersebut,
sebagian besar roket memiliki wadah untuk bahan bakar
dengan muatan kecil di ujungnya.
Hal ini tidak baik jika kamu ingin pergi ke planet-planet lain,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 grunde til hvorfor atomenergi er forfærdeligt! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/da/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 15:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/da/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>Video Transskription ﻿Der er tre grunde til hvorfor vi skal stoppe brugen af atomkraft
Første: Hastig vækst af atomvåben
Nuklear teknologi fik en voldig entré til verden
kun et år efter den første atomprøvesprængning i 1944,
blev to storbyer destrueret af blot to bomber.
Efter det, begyndte reaktor teknologi langsomt at udvikle sig
da efterspørgslen af elektricitet voksede,
men det er altid sammenlignet med atomvåbens teknologi.
Det er næsten umuligt at udvikle atomvåben</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>原子力エネルギーがひどい理由は3つあります！ ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ja/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 14:58:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ja/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>ビデオ 転写 ﻿原子力をやめるべき３つの理由 １. 核兵器の拡散 原子力技術は世界を緊張状態に置く 1944年実験に成功した翌年 ２つの爆弾で２つの都市が</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 anledningar till varför kärnkraft är bra! 3/3 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/sv/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 14:57:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/sv/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkription ﻿Tre anledningar till varför vi ska fortsätta använda kärnkraft
Ett: kärnkraft räddar liv
I 2013 visade en studie genomförd av NASA att kärnkraft har förhindrat -
– omkring 1.8 miljoner dödsfall
Även om du räknar med dödsfallen från Chernobyl och Fukushima –
– rankas kärnkraft sist i dödsfall per energienhet som produceras.
Även fast kärnavfall är väldigt farligt så är det förvarat någonstans –
– medans de farliga biprodukterna av fossila bränslen släpps ut i luften –</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Razões pelas quais a energia nuclear é incrível! 3/3 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/pt-br/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 14:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/pt-br/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>Vídeo Transcrição ﻿Três motivos pelos quais devemos continuar usando energia nuclear:
Energia nuclear salva vidas. Em 2013, um estudo conduzido pela NASA
descobriu que energia nuclear preveniu em torno de 1,8 milhões de mortes.
Mesmo se incluirmos as mortes dos casos de Chernobyl e Fukushima
energia nuclear fica em último no ranking
entre outras formas de energia produzidas. Apesar do lixo nuclear
ser realmente tóxico, eles realmente são armazenados em algum lugar,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 ragioni per cui l&#39;energia nucleare è terribile! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/it/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 14:50:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/it/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>Video Trascrizione ﻿Tre ragioni per cui dovremmo smettere di utilizzare l&amp;rsquo;energia nucleare.
Diffusione delle armi nucleari. La tecnologia nucleare è entrata violentemente nel palcoscenico mondiale.
Solo un anno dopo il primo test nucleare al mondo nel 1944
Due grandi città furono distrutte soltanto da due singole bombe.
Dopo ciò, la tecnologia dei reattori si è lentamente evoluta in un metodo per generare elettricità,
sebbene sia stata sempre strettamente connessa alla tecnologia delle armi nucleari.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>1,000公里的星际电缆 - 天空钩 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/zh-hans/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 14:50:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/zh-hans/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>视频 文字稿 ﻿进入太空是个艰难的活计 以现在的科技，这就像骑着独轮车登山 并且还背着极易爆炸的火药 这个过程非常耗时， 你无法运送过多物资， 死亡的机率</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>טיעון רוחני עצמי לשיפור העולם - אלטרואיזם אגואיסטי. ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/he/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 14:40:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/he/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>וידאו טְק֡ס֙ט ﻿עד לאחרונה, רוב אוכלוסיית העולם עבדה בחקלאות
וסך הייצור של כלכלת העולם
היה בעיקר התפוקה החקלאית הכוללת.
ותפוקה זו הייתה מוגבלת על ידי הגודל הקבוע של הקרקע.
התפוקה הכוללת של המשק לא השתנתה הרבה משנה לשנה.
גודל העוגה היה קבוע; העולם היה משחק סכום אפס.
בעולם לא מתפתח כזה, הדרך היחידה לקבל יותר היא אם מישהו אחר יקבל פחות.
אם אתה לוקח חתיכה גדולה יותר מהעוגה, החתיכה של מישהו אחר תקטן.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>1 000 km kábel ku hviezdam - Skyhook ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/sk/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 14:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/sk/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>Video Prepis ﻿Dostať sa do vesmíru je ťažké
V súčasnosti je to ako liezť na horu na jednokolke
s batohom plným výbušnín.
Neuveriteľne pomaly, nemôžete prenášať veľa vecí
a môžete zomrieť.
Raketa potrebuje dosiahnuť rýchlosť približne 4000 km/hod aby utiekla zemskej tiaži.
Aby túto rýchlosť dosiahli,
rakety sú najmä kontajnery pre palivo
s nákladom v malej špičke.
To je zlé, pokiaľ sa chcete dostať na inú planétu,
pretože potrebujete mnoho ťažkých vecí, ak chcete prežiť a možno sa dokonca aj vrátiť.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Egoistički altruizam - sebični argument za stvaranje boljeg svijeta. ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/hr/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 14:25:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/hr/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripcija ﻿Sve donedavno, velik dio svjetske populacije radio je na oranicama
i cjelokupni proizvod svjetskoga gospodarstva
bio je uglavnom jednak cjelokupnom poljoprivrednom proizvodu.
Taj proizvod je bio ograničen nepromjenjivom veličinom obradive zemlje.
Cjelokupni proizvod gospodarstva nije se primjetno mijenjao iz godine u godinu.
Veličina kolača bila je nepromjenjiva; svijet je bio igra nultoga zbroja.
U takvom zaostalome svijetu, jedini način poboljšanja vlastitoga stanja bio je pogoršanje nečijega tuđega.
Ako uzmete veći dio kolača, netko drugi će dobiti manji dio.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Эгоистический альтруизм - эгоистический аргумент в пользу улучшения мира. ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ru/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 14:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ru/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>Видео Транскрипт ﻿До недавнего времени, большая часть населения мира работала на фермах,
и общее производство в мировой экономике
зависело, по большей части, от с/х продукции.
И её производство было ограничено размерами участка земли.
Общее производство с годами не менялось сильно.
Размер пирога был фиксированным; мир был игрой с нулевой суммой.
В таком стагнирующем (не развивающемся) мире единственным способом улучшения жизни
было угнетение кого-то другого.
Если ты возьмёшь бОльший кусок пирога, кто-то другой получит меньше.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Argumenti, miks marihuaana peaks jääma ebaseaduslikuks, läbi vaadatud. ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/et/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 14:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/et/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkriptsioon ﻿Üle kogu maailma,
marihuaana dekriminaliseeritakse või isegi legaliseeritakse.
Aga on see tõesti hea mõte?
Veebidebatis
vaikitakse kahjulikud mõjud tihtilugu maha.
Seega vaatame kolme kõige mõjukamat argumenti
marihuaana legaliseerimise vastu.
Argument number 1:
Viimaste aastakümnetega
on marihuaanat töödeldud, et see oleks tugevama mõjuga.
Marihuaana on nüüdseks niivõrd kange,
et see on piisavalt tugev narkootikum, põhjustamaks psühhoosi.
Peamine aktiivne koostisosa marihuaanas on THC,
ning on kindlaid tõendeid, et THC on psühhoosi tekkega seotud</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>1,000km Cable to the Stars - The Skyhook ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ms/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 13:37:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ms/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripsi ﻿Mendapatkan ruang adalah sukar.
Sekarang, ia seperti naik ke atas gunung di atas kereta roda unicycle-
dengan ransel penuh bahan peledak.
Sangat perlahan, anda tidak boleh mengangkut banyak barangan, dan anda mungkin mati.
Roket perlu mencapai kelajuan kira-kira 40,000km sejam untuk melarikan diri dari Bumi.
Untuk mencapai kelajuan itu, roket kebanyakannya bekas untuk bahan bakar dengan hujung muatan kecil.
Ini tidak baik jika anda mahu pergi ke planet lain,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 λόγοι για τους οποίους η πυρηνική ενέργεια είναι εκπληκτική! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/el/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 13:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/el/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>Βίντεο Αποσπάσματα ﻿Τρεις λόγοι για τους οποίους θα πρέπει να συνεχίσουμε να χρησιμοποιούμε πυρηνική ενέργεια.
1: Η πυρηνική ενέργεια σώζει ζωές.
Το 2013, μια μελέτη που διεξήχθη από τη NASA βρήκε ότι η πυρηνική ενέργεια έχει εμποδίσει
περίπου 1,8 εκατομμύρια θανάτους.
Ακόμα κι αν κάποιος συμπεριλάβει τους θανάτους από το Τσερνομπίλ και την Φουκουσίμα,
Η πυρηνική ενέργεια κατατάσσεται τελευταία σε θανάτους ανά μονάδα παραγόμενης ενέργειας.
Ενώ τα πυρηνικά απόβλητα είναι πολύ τοξικά, συνήθως αποθηκεύονται κάπου,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>마리화나가 불법이어야 하는 세 가지 이유 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ko/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 13:34:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ko/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>비디오 대본 ﻿많은 나라에서 대마초가 비(非)범죄화 되거나 합법화되고 있습니다. 이게 정말 맞는 걸까요? 온라인 상의 논쟁에서는, 부정적 측면이 과소평가되기도</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Egoistický altruizmus - sebecký argument pre zlepšenie sveta. ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/sk/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 13:33:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/sk/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>Video Prepis ﻿Až donedávna značná väčšina populácie pracovala na farmách
a celková produkcia svetovej ekonomiky
bola väčšinovo poľnohospodárska.
A táto produkcia bola omedzená nemeniacou sa rozlohou pôdy.
Celková produkcia ekonomiky sa z roka na rok veľmi nemenila.
Veľkosť koláča sa nemenila; svet bola hra s nulovým súčtom.
V takomto stagnujúcom svete jedinou cestou ako si polepšiť je, že sa niekomu inému pohorší.
Ak si vezmeš väčší kus koláča, niekto iný dostane menší.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Dôvody, prečo je jadrová energia úžasná! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/sk/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 13:28:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/sk/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>Video Prepis ﻿Tri dôvody, prečo by sme mali naďalej používať atómovú energiu.
Po prvé: atómová energia zachraňuje životy.
V roku 2013 NASA vykonala štúdiu, podľa ktorej atómová energia zabránila
zhruba 1,8 miliónu úmrtí.
Aj keby že zhrniete počet obetí Černobyľu a Fukušimi,
tak atómová energia je posledná v počte úmrtí na jednotku vyprodukovanej energie.
Aj keď je atómový odpad veľmi toxický, väčšinou je niekde uskladnený,
zatiaľ čo toxické vedľajšie produkty fosílnych palív sú pumpované do vzduchu,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 powody, dlaczego energia jądrowa jest niesamowita! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/pl/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 13:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/pl/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkrypcja ﻿Trzy powody, dla których powinniśmy kontynuować używać energii nuklearnej.
Po pierwsze: Energia nuklearna ratuje życia.
W 2013, badania prowadzone przez NASA wykazało, że energia nuklearna zapobiegła
około 1.8 milionom śmierci.
Nawet jeżeli brać pod uwagę ofiary z Czarnobyla i Fukuszimy,
energia nuklearna jest ostatnia w śmierciach na wyprodukowaną energię.
Podczas gdy odpady są bardzo toksyczne, to zwykle są gdzieś przechowywane,
a toksyczne bioprodukty paliw kopalnych są wydalane do powietrza,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Три аргументи, чому слід переглянути нелегальний стан марихуани ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/uk/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 13:03:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/uk/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Відео Транскрипція ﻿У всьому світі
марихуану декриміналізують або й узаконюють.
Але чи справді це вірне рішення?
В інтернеті-суперечках
часто недооцінюють її шкоду.
Тож розглянемо три найпотужніші доводи
проти взаконення марихуани.
Довід №1:
За останні десятиліття
марихуану вдосконалили аби зробити більш сильнодіючою.
Нині марихуана настільки міцна,
що справді є сильним наркотиком, що спричиняє психоз.
Головна діюча складова марихуани – тетрагідроканабінол або ТГК.
Існують неспростовні докази, що ТГК пов&amp;rsquo;язаний із психозом,
незалежно від інших чинників ризику.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>1,000 km Cable to the Stars - El Skyhook ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/es-es/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 13:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/es-es/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcripción ﻿Ir al espacio es difícil.
Actualmente sería como escalar una montaña en un monociclo
con una mochila llena de explosivos.
Increíblemente lento,
no puedes llevar muchas cosas,
y quizás mueras.
Un cohete tiene que alcanzar una velocidad de alrededor 40,000km/h para escapar de la Tierra.
Para alcanzar esa velocidad,
los cohetes son principalmente contenedores de combustible
con una pequeña parte de carga en la punta.
Esto es malo si es que quieres llegar a otros planetas,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Lý do tại sao cần sa nên được đánh giá bất hợp pháp ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/vi/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 12:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/vi/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Video Bản trích ﻿Ở nhiều nơi trên thế giới, cần sa đang dần được hợp pháp hóa
Nhưng liệu đây có phải là 1 ý tưởng hay ? Trong các cuộc tranh luận online, những mặt hại của nó thường bị hạ thấp
Vậy chúng ta cùng xem xét ba lý do thuyết phục nhất chống lại việc hợp pháp hóa cần sa.
[Giới thiệu] Translator: 2527 Recyclebin ; Reviewer: Triệu Hoàng Anh, Bảo Đậu.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>1000 km kabel naar de sterren - The Skyhook ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/nl/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 12:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/nl/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcriptie ﻿In de ruimte komen is moeilijk,
momenteel is het als een berg beklimmen op een eenwieler,
met een rugzak vol explosieven.
Zeer traag, je kan niet veel spullen meenemen, en je kan doodgaan.
Een raket moet een snelheid halen van ongeveer 40.000 km/h
om los te komen van aarde.
Om die snelheid te behalen,
zijn raketten grotendeels containers voor brandstof
met een kleine hoeveelheid voor de voorstuwing.
Dit is slecht als je naar andere planeten wilt gaan,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A Selfish Argument for Making the World a Better Place – Egoistic Altruism ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 12:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Until recently, the vast majority of the world population worked on farms
and the total production of the world&amp;rsquo;s economy
was mostly the total agricultural output.
And this output was limited by the fixed size of the land.
The total output of the economy did not change a lot year by year.
The size of the pie was fixed; the world was a zero-sum game.
In such a stagnating world, the only way to get better off is if someone else gets worse off.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 iemesli, kāpēc kodolenerģija ir briesmīga! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/lv/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 12:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/lv/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripts ﻿Trīs iemesli, kādēļ mums vajadzētu beigt izmantot atomenerģiju.
Kodolieroču izplatība Kodoltehnoloģija veica vardarbīgu ieeju uz pasaules skatuves:
Tikai vienu gadu pēc pasaules pirmā kodolizmēģinājuma 1944. gadā,
Divas lielas pilsētas tika iznīcinātas tikai ar vienu vienīgu bumbu katrai.
Pēc tā, reaktoru tehnoloģija lēnām attīstījās
kā līdzeklis enerģijas ražošanai,
bet tā vienmēr ir bijusi cieši saistīta ar kodolieroču tehnoloģiju.
Ir gandrīz neiespējami izstrādāt kodolieročus
bez pieejas reaktoru tehnoloģijai.
Patiesībā, Kodolneizplatīšanas līgums kalpo par</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Hujahan Mengapa Dadah Ganja Perlu Dikekalkan Sebagai Haram: Ulasan ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ms/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 12:22:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ms/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripsi ﻿Di seluruh dunia,
ganja mula dibenarkan di sisi undang-undang.
Tapi adakah ini idea yang baik?
Berdasarkan perdebatan dalam talian
keburukannya sering dipandang remeh.
Jadi mari kita lihat tiga hujah yang paling kuat
menentang ganja dibenarkan di sisi undang-undang.
Hujah pertama:
Dalam beberapa dekad yang lalu,
Ganja telah diubah suai untuk menjadi dadah yang lebih kuat.
Hari ini, ganja ialah dadah yang sangat kuat
ganja merupakan dadah kuat yang boleh menyebabkan psikosis.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>宇宙まで届く1,000kmのケーブル - スカイフック ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ja/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 12:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ja/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>ビデオ 転写 ﻿宇宙へ行くのは難しい たとえるなら 一輪車で山を登るようなものだ しかも 大量の爆薬を背負いながら 速く走らないと 重さで転倒し 死んでしまう</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>حجة أنانية لجعل العالم مكانًا أفضل - الإيغوية الإحسانية. ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ar/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 12:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ar/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>فيديو نص ﻿حتى وقت قريب, الغالبية العظمى من
سكان العالم عملوا بالمزارع وكان مجمل الانتاج الاقتصادي للعالم
في الأغلب الانتاج الزراعي
و هذا الانتاج محدود بمساحة الأرض الثابتة
الانتاجية الاقتصادية لم تتغير كثيراً بمرور الاعوام
حجم الفطيرة كان ثابت
العالم كان لعبة محصلتها صفر
في مثل هذا العالم الراكد , الطريقة الوحيدة لتصبح افضل حالاً هي اذا اصبح شخص اخر اسوء حالاً
إذا أخذت قطعة أكبر من الفطيرة
قطعة شخص اخر تصبح أصغر</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 ok, amiért a nukleáris energia fantasztikus! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/hu/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 12:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/hu/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>Videó Tranzkript ﻿Három ok, hogy miért folytassuk a nukleáris energia használatát.
Első: az atomenergia életeket ment.
2013-ban, a NASA egy tanulmánya szerint, az atomenergia megakadályozta
mintegy 1,8 millió ember halálát.
Még ha beleszámoljuk a Csernobil és Fukusima által okozott halálokat,
az atomenergia utolsó helyen áll a termelt energia egységenkénti halálozás tekintetében.
Bár a nukleáris hulladék tényleg nagyon mérgező, általában valahol mégis tárolják,
ezzel szemben a fosszilis tüzelőanyagok mérgező melléktermékeit a levegőbe eresztik,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Sebab Mengapa Tenaga Nuklear Hebat! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ms/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 11:45:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ms/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripsi ﻿Terdapat 3 sebab mengapa kita perlu meneruskan penggunaan tenaga nuklear
Pertama : Tenaga nuklear menyelamatkan nyawa
Pada 2013, sebuah kajian yang dilakukan NASA menemui bahawa tenaga nuklear mencegah
kira-kira 1.8 juta kematian
Jika anda memasukkan angka kematian daripada tragedi Chernobyl dan Fukushima
tenaga nuklear berada di tempat terakhir untuk kematian per unit tenaga dihasilkan
Sisa nuklear amat bertoksik dan disimpan di sesetengah tempat
sementara itu, hasil sampingan bahan api fosil dipam ke udara</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Důvody, proč je jaderná energie hrozná! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/cs/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 11:36:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/cs/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripce ﻿Tři důvody, proč bychom měly přestat používat nukleární energii
1: Jaderné zbrojení
Nukleární technologie způsobila násilný vstup do nové éry
Pouze rok po prvním testu atomové bomby v roce 1944
Dvě velká města byla zničena pouze dvěma bombami
Poté technologie reaktorů se pomalu vyvíjela v zájmu generovat
elektřinu avšak byla stále silně
propojena s atomovými zbraněmi.
Je téměř nemožné vyrobit atomovou bombu bez přístupu k
jadernému reaktoru
Dohody o nešíření zbraní v podstatě slouží k šíření</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Alasan Mengapa Energi Nuklir Menakjubkan! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/id/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 11:27:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/id/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripsi ﻿Tiga alasan mengapa kita harus terus menggunakan energi nuklir.
Satu: energi nuklir menyelamatkan nyawa.
Pada tahun 2013, sebuah studi yang dilakukan oleh NASA menemukan bahwa energi nuklir telah mencegah
sekitar 1,8 juta kematian.
Bahkan jika Anda termasuk korban meninggal dari Chernobyl dan Fukushima,
energi nuklir memiliki peringkat terakhir dalam kematian per satuan energi yang dihasilkan.
Sementara limbah nuklir benar-benar beracun, itu biasanya disimpan di suatu tempat,
sedangkan produk sampingan beracun dari bahan bakar fosil dipompa ke udara</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Pourquoi la Marijuana devrait rester illégale - Analyse de 3 arguments ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/fr/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 11:12:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/fr/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Vidéo Transcription ﻿Partout dans le monde, la marijuana devient dépénalisée ou même deviens légale.
Mais, est-ce une bonne idée ? Les débats sur internet minimisent souvent les côtés nocif.
Donc, regardons les trois plus grands arguments contre la légalisation de la marijuana.
Premier argument : Le cannabis est une drogue dure. Dans les dernières décénies,
La marijuana a été modifiée pour devenir plus puissante.
De nos jours, la marijuana est tellement puissante qu&amp;rsquo;elle est une drogue dure qui peut engendrer des psychoses.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 raisons pour lesquelles l&#39;énergie nucléaire est géniale ! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/fr/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 11:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/fr/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>Vidéo Transcription ﻿Trois raisons pour lesquelles on devrait continuer à utiliser l&amp;rsquo;énergie nucléaire.
Premièrement: l&amp;rsquo;énergie nucléaire sauve des vies.
En 2013, une étude menée par la NASA a montré que l&amp;rsquo;énergie nucléaire a évité
la mort d&amp;rsquo;environ 1.8 million de personnes.
Même en incluant le nombre de victimes de Chernobyl et Fukushima,
l&amp;rsquo;énergie nucléaire se classe dernière en mort par unité d&amp;rsquo;énergie produite.
Bien que les déchets nucléaires soient toxiques, ils sont généralement stockés quelque part,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 أسباب تجعل الطاقة النووية سيئة! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ar/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 10:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ar/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>فيديو نص ﻿ثلاثة أسباب توضح لم علينا أن نتوقف عن إستخدام الطاقة النووية
أولاً: إنتشار الأسلحة النووية.
التكنولوجيا النووية دخلت بشكل عنيف على الساحة العالمية
فبعد عام واحد فقط من أول تجربة تفجير نووي في العالم عام 1944,
تم تدمير مدينتين كبيرتين بواسطة قنبلتين فقط.
بعد ذلك, تطورت تكنولوجيا المفاعلات ببطئ
كوسيلة لتوليد الطاقة الكهربائية,
لكنها كانت دائمًا مرتبطة ارتباطًا وثيقًا مع تكنولوجيا الأسلحة النووية.
من المستحيل تقريبا تطوير سلاح نووي</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Arguments Why Marijuana Should Stay Illegal Reviewed ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 10:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿All around the world,
marijuana is being decriminalized, or even made legal.
But is this really a good idea?
In the online debate,
the harmful sides are often downplayed.
So let&amp;rsquo;s look at the three most powerful arguments
against legalizing marijuana.
[Intro - Kurzgesagt]
Argument number 1:
In the last few decades,
marijuana has been engineered to become much more potent.
Today, marijuana is so potent,
that it&amp;rsquo;s actually a strong drug that may cause psychosis.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Un argumento egoísta para hacer del mundo un lugar mejor - Altruismo Egoísta ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/es-419/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 10:54:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/es-419/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcripción ﻿No tanto tiempo atrás, la gran mayoría de la población mundial trabajaba en granjas
y la total producción econónica mundial
era principalmente la totalidad de la producción agrícola
Y esta producción estaba limitada por el tamaño fijo del terreno
La producción total de la economía no cambió mucho año tras año
El tamaño del pastel estaba fijado; el mundo era un juego de cero suma
En este mundo estancado, la única manera de estar mejor era si alguien se empeoraba</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Kablla 1000km për në Galaksi - Kabllat Qiellorë ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/sq/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 10:51:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/sq/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripte ﻿Të shkosh në hapësirë është e vështirë.
Në këtë moment, është si të ngjitesh në bjeshkë me bicikletë njërrotëshe.
Me një çantë plot eksplozivë.
Shumë ngadalë, nuk mund të transportosh shumë gjëra, dhe mund edhe të vdisni.
Një raketë duhet të arrijë shpejtësi rreth 40.000 km/h për tu larguar nga Toka.
Për ta arritur atë shpejtësi, raketat janë kryesisht kontenierë me karburant dhe një ngarkesë fare të vogël.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Razões Pelas Quais a Energia Nuclear é Terrível! 2/3 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/pt-br/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 10:41:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/pt-br/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>Vídeo Transcrição ﻿Três razões pelas quais nós deveríamos parar de usar energia nuclear
Um: proliferação de armamentos nucleares
A tecnologia nuclear entrou violentamente no mundo:
apenas um ano após os primeiros testes de explosões nucleares em 1944,
duas grandes cidades foram destruídas por apenas duas dessas bombas.
Após isso, a tecnologia dos reatores lentamente se aprimorou
como um meio de geração de eletricidade
mas ela sempre esteve intimamente conectada com as tecnologias nucleares para fins militares.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Egoistični altruizem - sebičen argument za izboljšanje sveta. ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/sl/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 10:22:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/sl/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>Video Prepis ﻿Do nedavnega, je velika večina svetovne populacije delala na kmetijah
in skupna proizvodnja svetovnega gospodarstva
bila končni kmetijski donos.
In ta donos je bil omejen na nespremenljivo velikost zemlje.
Končni donos gospodarstva se skozi leta ni dosti spremenil.
Velikost pite je bila stalna; svet je bil igra z ničelno vsoto.
V takšnem stagniranem svetu je edini način za lastno izboljšanje, tuje poslabšanje.
Če ti dobiš večji del pite, nekdo drug dobi manjšega.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3เหตุผลที่พลังงานนิวเคลียร์เป็นสิ่งที่แย่! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/th/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 10:17:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/th/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>วิดีโอ สรุป ﻿นี่คือสามเหตุผลว่าทำไมเราควรหยุดใช้พลังงานนิวเคลียร์
ข้อหนึ่ง: การแพร่ขยายของอาวุธนิวเคลียร์
เทคโนโลยีทางด้านนิวเคลียร์ เปิดประตูความขัดแย้งบนเวทีโลก
เพียงหนึ่งปีหลังจากการทดลองใช้ระเบิดนิวเคลียร์ครั้งแรก ในปี ค.ศ.1994
เมืองใหญ่สองเมืองถูกทำลายโดยระเบิดเพียงสองลูกเท่านั้น
หลังจากนั้นเทคโนโลยีปฏิกรณ์นิวเคลียร์พัฒนาได้ช้า
ในวัตถุประสงค์ด้านการผลิตพลังงาน
แต่ในกรณีของอาวุธนิวเคลียร์กลับตรงกันข้าม
มันจะเป็นไปไม่ได้เลยที่จะพัฒนาอาวุธนิวเคลียร์
หากปราศจากการเข้าถึงเทคโลยีปฏิกรณ์นิวเคลียร์
ในสนธิสัญญาไม่แพร่ขยายอาวุธนิวเคลียร์ ที่มีวัตถุประสงค์
เพื่อการเผยแพร่เทคโนโลยีปฏิกรณ์นิวเคลียร์ โดยไม่แพร่ขยายอาวุธนิวเคลียร์
มีความสำเร็จค่อนข้างจำกัด
ใน 40 ปีที่ผ่านมา ห้าชาติได้พัฒนาอาวุธนิวเคลียร์ของตนเอง
ด้วยเทคโนโลยีปฏิกรณ์นิวเคลียร์
ความจริงคือ การแยกแยะ โครงการอาวุธนิวเคลียร์ลับ
จาก การใช้พลังงานนิวเคลียร์อย่างสันติ นั้นยากมาก
ในปี 1970 ผู้นำด้านนิวเคลียร์ได้ขายเทคโลยีนิวเคลียร์สันติ
ให้แก่ประเทศอื่น ซึ่งพัฒนาอาวุธนิวเคลียร์เป็นเวลาต่อมา
ทางไปสู่อาวุธนิวเคลียร์นั้น ถูกปูทางด้วยการใช้นิวเคลียร์อย่างสันติอยู่เสมอ
ข้อสอง: กากนิวเคลียร์และมลพิษ
เชื้อเพลิงนิวเคลียร์ที่ถูกใช้แล้วไม่เพียงแต่มีกัมตภาพรังสีเท่านั้น แต่หาก
มีเคมีสสารที่มีพิษมาก เช่นพลูโตเนียม
ซึ่งใช้ระยะเวลาหลายพันปีถึงจะสูญเสียความอันตราย
และยังมีกระบวนการที่เรียกว่า การนำกลับมาใช้ใหม่ซึ่งคือ
การสกัดพลูโตเนียม จากกากนิวเคลียร์
มีจุดประสงค์สองอย่าง
คือเอาไปทำสร้างอาวุธนิวเคลียร์ หรือ นำกลับมาใช้เป็นเชื้อเพลิงใหม่
แต่การนำกลับมาใช้เป็นเชื้อเพลิงใหม่นั้นแทบนับนิ้วได้
เพราะว่าเราไม่มีเตาปฏิกรณ์สำหรับการนำมาใช้ใหม่
กากนิวเคลียร์ เพียงหยิบมือก็สามารถฆ่าคุณได้; ไม่กี่โล สามารถเอาไปทำระเบิดปรมาณู
แม้กระทั่งประเทศเยอรมณีก็อยู่หลายตันเลยทีเดียว
แค่ล้อเล่นน่า หลายสิบปีที่แล้วการนำมาใช้ใหม่เป็นความคิดที่ดี
อ้าว แล้วกากนิวเคลียร์จะไปอยู่ไหนหละ?
หลังจากทิ้งกากนิวเคลียร์ลงมหาสมุทรได้ถูกห้าม เราจึงทำการฝังมัน
แต่เราไม่สามารถหาสถานที่ ที่ มัน</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Ein selbstsüchtiges Argument, die Welt zu einem besseren Ort zu machen - egoistischer Altruismus ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/de/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 10:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/de/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkript ﻿Bis vor kurzem hat ein Großteil der Weltbevölkerung in der Landwirtschaft gearbeitet
Und die gesamte Produktion der Weltökonomie war zum Großteil die Landwirtschaftsproduktion
Und diese Produktion wurde limitiert von der Größe des Landes
Die gesamte Produktion der Ökonomie hat sich in den Jahren nicht verändert
Die größe des Kuchen wurde bearbeitet
Die Welt war ein Nullsummenspiel
In so einer stagnierenden Welt
Ist der einzige weg um besser dran zu sein, dass jemand schlechter dran ist</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 காரணங்கள் நியூகிள் ஆற்றல் அற்புதம்! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ta/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 10:09:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ta/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>வீடியோ மொழி ﻿en? mundru karanangalukkaaga anushakti ubayogikkapadavendum?
ஒன்று: அணு ஆற்றல் உயிர்களை காப்பாற்றுகிறது.
2013 ஆம் ஆண்டில், நாசா நடத்திய ஒரு ஆய்வில் அணு ஆற்றல் தடுத்தது என்று கண்டறியப்பட்டது- ,uyirallpugalai
1.8 மில்லியன் மரணங்கள்.
நீங்கள் செர்னோபில் மற்றும் புகுஷிமா இருந்து உயிரிழப்புகளை அடங்கும் கூட,
அணு ஆற்றல் உற்பத்தி ஆற்றல் அலகிலும் மரணம் கடைசி இடத்தில் உள்ளது
அணு கழிவு உண்மையில் நச்சு என்றாலும் கூட, அது வழக்கமாக எங்காவது சேமிக்கப்படும்,
படிம எரிபொருட்களை நச்சு பக்கவிளைவுகள் காற்றில் உந்தப்பட்ட போது
நாங்கள் ஒவ்வொரு நாளும் மூச்சு
எனவே, வெறும் மூலம் படிம எரிபொருட்களை அளவை குறைத்து எரித்தனர், புற்றுநோய் எண்ணற்ற வழக்குகள்</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 grunner til hvorfor cannabis bør forbli ulovlig ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/no/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 10:04:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/no/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripsjon ﻿Over hele verden blir marihuana avkriminalisert eller t.o.m legalisert.
Men er dette virkelig en god idé? I diskusjoner på nettet blir de negative sidene ofte avfeiet.
La oss se på de tre viktigste argumentene mot å legelisere marihuana.
KURZGESAGT
I et nøtteskall - Argument 1: I løpet av de siste tiårene
har marihuana blitt kraftigere gjennom avling.
I dag er det kraftig nok til å kunne forårsake psykose.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>一個自私的論點，為了讓世界變得更好 - 利己主義的利他主義。 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/zh-hant/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 10:02:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/zh-hant/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>影片 文字稿 ﻿在不久之前，主要的世界人口參與農事生產 並且世上的經濟產出等於 近乎等於農業的產量 並且農業的產量受到土地面積限制 因此經濟產出並不會因</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>1.000 km de Cabo para as Estrelas - O Skyhook ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/pt-br/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 09:53:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/pt-br/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>Vídeo Transcrição ﻿Chegar no espaço é difícil
No momento, é como escalar uma montanha em um monociclo
com uma mochila cheia de explosivos
Incrivelmente devagar, você não pode transportar muita coisa, e ainda pode morrer
Um foguete precisa atingir uma velocidade de aproximadamente 40,000km por hora para escapar da Terra
Para atingir tal velocidade, foguetes são predominantemente recipientes para combustível com uma pequena ponta de carga
Isso é ruim se você quer ir para outro planeta</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Un argomento egoistico per rendere il mondo un posto migliore - Altruismo egoistico. ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/it/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 09:43:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/it/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>Video Trascrizione ﻿Fino a poco tempo fa, la stragrande maggioranza della popolazione mondiale lavorava nelle fattorie
e la produzione totale dell&amp;rsquo;economia mondiale
era per lo più la produzione agricola totale.
E questa produzione era limitata dalla dimensione stessa del terreno.
La produzione totale dell&amp;rsquo;economia non cambiava molto di anno in anno.
La dimensione della torta era fissa; il mondo era un gioco a somma zero.
In un mondo così stagnante, l&amp;rsquo;unico modo per stare meglio è se qualcun altro stava peggio.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 കാരണങ്ങൾ നൂക്ലിയർ എനർജി അത്ഭുതകരമാണ്! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ml/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 09:41:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ml/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>വീഡിയോ അപൂർണ്ണം ﻿എന്‍തു കൊന്‍ടു ആണവ ഇന്‍ധന ഉപയോഗ൦ നിര്‍ത്തണ൦ എന്നതിനു മൂന്ന് കാരണങ്ങള്‍ ഉണ്‍ട്.
ഒന്ന് - ആണവ ആയുധ പ്രചാരമാണ്
ആണവ സാങ്കേതികവിദ്യ അക്രമം ഉണ്ടാക്കി ലോകം നിയമനിർമാണസഭകളിൽ പ്രവേശന
ലോകത്തിലെ ശേഷം വെറും ഒരു വർഷം ഒന്നാം എന്നേക്കും ആണവപരീക്ഷണം സ്ഫോടനം
1944
രണ്ടു വലിയ നഗരം നശിപ്പിക്കപ്പെട്ടു രണ്ട് ബോംബുകൾ
പതിയെ ശേഷം, റിയാക്ടർ സാങ്കേതികവിദ്യ നേടിത്തരുന്ന മാർഗ്ഗമായി ഉടലെടുത്തിട്ടുണ്ട്
വൈദ്യുതി പക്ഷേ അത് എല്ലായ്പോഴും നാളായി ആണവ ഉപയോഗിച്ച് പരിഗ്രഹിച്ചില്ല ബന്ധപ്പെട്ടു
ആയുധങ്ങൾ സാങ്കേതികവിദ്യ
വികസിപ്പിക്കാൻ ഏതാണ്ട് അസാധ്യമാണ് ആണവായുധ റിയാക്ടറിൽ ആക്സസ്സ് ഇല്ലാതെ
സാങ്കേതിക
ആണവ നോൺ ആണവനിർവ്യാപന വാസ്തവത്തിൽ കരാറിൽ പരത്തുന്ന ഉദ്ദേശം</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Nükleer Enerjiyi Korkunç Kılan 3 Neden! 2/3 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/tr/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 09:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/tr/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkript ﻿Nükleer enerjiyi kullanmayı bırakmak için üç sebep.
Bir: nükleer silahların yaygınlaşması
Nükleer teknoloji dünya sahnesine şiddetli
bir giriş yaptı: 1944&amp;rsquo;te
Dünyanın ilk nükleer test
patlamasının ardından iki büyük şehir
sadece iki bomba ile yok edildi.
Bundan sonra, reaktör teknolojisi yavaşça
elektrik üretimi için kullanlmaya başlandı
ama hep nükleer silah teknolojisiyle içten
içe bağlantılıydı. Nükleer teknolojiye
erişmeden nükleer silah yapmak imkansızdı.
Silahların yaygınlaşmasını engellemeyi
amaçlayan bir anlaşma olan
Nükleer Silahların Yaygınlaşmasını</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>세계를 더 나은 곳으로 만드는 이기적인 주장: 이기적 이타주의. ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ko/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 09:38:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ko/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>비디오 대본 ﻿최근까지 세계 인구의 대다수가 농장에서 일했으며, 세계 경제의 총생산은 대부분 농업 생산량이었습니다. 이 산출량은 땅의 크기에 의해 제한되었습니다</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Егоистичният алтруизъм е една себична аргументация за направата на света по-добро място. ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/bg/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 09:29:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/bg/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>Видео Транскрипция ﻿Съвсем до скоро, по-голямата част от световното население е работело на нивата
и общият продукт на световната икономика
е бил най-вече резултат на селско стопанство.
Този резултат е бил ограничен от фиксираната площ на наличната земя.
Общият икономически продукт не се е променял особено през годините.
Размерът на баницата е бил фиксиран, а светът е бил игра с опрделен край.
В такъв свят на стагнация, единственият начин да забогатееш е чрез обедняването на друг.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Một lập luận ích kỷ cho việc làm cho thế giới trở nên tốt đẹp hơn - Lòng vị tha ích kỷ. ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/vi/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 09:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/vi/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>Video Bản trích ﻿Cho đến gần đây, hầu hết dân số trên thế giới đều lao động trong nông trại
và tổng sản phẩm của nền kinh tế toàn cầu
phần lớn đều là tổng sản lượng nông nghiệp
Và sản lượng này thì bị hạn chế bởi diện tích cố định của đất đai
Tổng sản lượng của nền kinh tế hồi xưa thường không đổi sau nhiều năm</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Argumentos Por Que a Maconha Deve Permanecer Ilegal Avaliados ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/pt-br/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 09:07:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/pt-br/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Vídeo Transcrição ﻿Por todo o mundo, a maconha está sendo descriminalizada
e até mesmo legalizada.
Mas essa é mesmo uma boa ideia?
No debate online, os efeitos negativos são geralmente minimizados.
Então vamos dar uma olhada nos três argumentos mais poderosos contra a legalização da maconha.
♪ Intro ♪ Kurzgesagt
Argumento nº1: A maconha é uma droga forte.
Nas últimas décadas, a maconha tem sido modificada para se tornar muito mais potente.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 motive pentru care energia nucleară este teribilă! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ro/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 08:57:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ro/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcriere ﻿Trei motive pentru care ar trebui să nu mai folosim energia nucleară.
Unu: Proliferarea armamentului nuclear.
Tehnologia nucleară și-a făcut debutul violent pe scena mondială.
La numai un an după primul test nuclear din lume din 1944,
două mari orașe au fost distruse de doar două bombe.
Dupa aceea, tehnologia reactoarelor a început încet să se dezvolte
ca o metodă de a genera electricitate,
dar a fost mereu strâns legată de tehnologia armelor nucleare.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>¡3 Razones por las que la energía nuclear es terrible! 2/3 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/es-419/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 08:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/es-419/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcripción ﻿tres razones por las que debemos dejar de usar la energía nuclear
uno : la proliferación de armas nucleares.
tecnología nuclear hizo una entrada violenta en el escenario mundial :
sólo un año después de la primera explosión de ensayo nunca nuclear del mundo en 1944 ,
dos grandes ciudades fueron destruidas por sólo dos bombas individuales.
después de eso, la tecnología de reactores evolucionó lentamente
como un medio de generación de electricidad,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Un Argument Égoïste en faveur d&#39;un Monde Meilleur - l&#39;Altruisme Égoïste ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/fr/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 08:33:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/fr/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>Vidéo Transcription ﻿Jusqu&amp;rsquo;à récemment, la grande majorité de la population mondiale travaillait dans les fermes.
et la production totale
était surtout la production agricole.
Et cette production était limitée par la taille fixe des terres.
La production totale
ne changeait pas beaucoup d&amp;rsquo;année en année.
La taille du gâteau était fixe,
Le monde était un jeu à somme nulle.
Dans un monde si stagnant, la seule façon de s&amp;rsquo;en sortir mieux</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Egoistisk altruism - ett själviskt argument för att göra världen till en bättre plats. ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/sv/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 08:22:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/sv/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkription ﻿Tills för inte så länge sen, jobbade majoriteten av världens befolkning på gårdar
och den totala produktionen av världens ekonomi
var mestadels den totala jordbruksproduktionen.
Och produktionen var begränsad av den fasta landytan.
Den totala ekonomins totala produktion ändrades inte mycket år för år.
Storleken på &amp;ldquo;kakan&amp;rdquo; var konstant; världen var ett nollsummespel.
I en värld som förändras så pass långsamt, var det enda sättet att få det bättre&amp;hellip;</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Ένα εγωιστικό επιχείρημα για το να κάνουμε τον κόσμο ένα καλύτερο μέρος - εγωιστική αλτρουιστικότητα. ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/el/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 08:21:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/el/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>Βίντεο Αποσπάσματα ﻿Μέχρι πρόσφατα, οι περισσότεροι άνθρωποι παγκοσμίως δούλευαν σε φάρμες&amp;hellip;
&amp;hellip;και η συνολική παραγωγή της παγκόσμιας οικονομίας&amp;hellip;
&amp;hellip;ήταν, κυρίως, το σύνολο των αγροτικών προϊόντων.
Και αυτά τα προϊόντα περιορίζονταν απ&amp;rsquo; το σταθερό μέγεθος της γης.
Η συνολική απόδοση της οικονομίας δεν άλλαζε και πολύ χρόνο με το χρόνο.
Το μέγεθος της πίτας ήταν σταθερό. Ο κόσμος ήταν ένα Παιχνίδι Μηδενικού Αθροίσματος.
Σ&amp;rsquo; έναν τέτοιο τελματώδη κόσμο, ο μόνος τρόπος να βελτιωθείς είναι αν κάποιος άλλος χειροτερεύσει.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 λόγοι για τους οποίους η πυρηνική ενέργεια είναι φρικτή! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/el/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 08:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/el/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>Βίντεο Αποσπάσματα ﻿Τρεις λόγοι που δεν πρέπει να χρησιμοποιούμε πια πυρηνική ενέργεια
ΕΠΕΚΤΑΣΗ ΠΥΡΗΝΙΚΩΝ ΟΠΛΩΝ Η πυρηνική τεχνολογία εισήχθη βίαια στο παγκόσμιο προσκήνιο
Μόλις μια χρονιά μετά την πρώτη πυρηνική δοκιμή το 1944
Δυο μεγάλες πόλεις καταστράφηκαν από δύο βόμβες,
Έπειτα, άρχισαν να αναπτύσσονται σιγά σιγά οι πυρηνικοί αντιδραστήρες
ως μέσο παραγωγής ηλεκτρισμού
ωστόσο πάντα συνδεόταν με την παραγωγή πυρηνικών όπλων
Είναι σχεδόν αδύνατο να φτιάξεις πυρηνικά όπλα
χωρίς πρόσβαση σε αντιδραστήρες</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Razloga zašto je nuklearna energija sjajna! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/hr/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 08:09:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/hr/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripcija ﻿Tri razloga zašto bismo trebali nastaviti koristiti nuklearnu energiju
Prvi: nuklearna energija spašava živote
2013., u istraživanju koje je provela NASA pronađeno je da je nuklearna energija spriječila
oko 1.8 milijuna smrti
Čak i ako se uključe žrtve iz Černobila i Fukušime
nuklearna energija se nalazi na posljednjem mjestu smrti po proizvedenoj energetskoj jedinici
iako je nuklearni otpad jako otrovan, obično je negdje pohranjen
dok su otrovni nusprodukti fosilnih goriva odbacivani u zrak</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>৩ কারণ যেহেতু নিউক্লিয়ার শক্তি অসাধারণ! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/bn/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 08:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/bn/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>ভিডিও ট্রান্সক্রিপ্ট ﻿তিন কারণে আমরা পারমাণবিক শক্তি ব্যবহার চালিয়ে যাওয়া উচিত.
এক: পারমাণবিক শক্তি মানুষের জীবন বাচায়.
2013 সালে নাসা দ্বারা পরিচালিত একটি গবেষণায় দেখা গেছে যে, পারমাণবিক শক্তি প্রতিহত করেছে
প্রায় 1.8 মিলিয়ন মানুষের মৃত্যু.
এমনকি আপনি যদি চেরনোবিল ও ফুকুশিমার থেকে মৃত্যুর টোল অন্তর্ভুক্ত,
পারমাণবিক শক্তি প্রতি শক্তি ইউনিট উত্পাদিত মৃত্যুতে গত নিম্ন স্তরে গণ্য হবে.
যদিও পারমাণবিক বর্জ্য সত্যিই বিষাক্ত, এটা সাধারণত কোথাও সঞ্চিত,
জীবাশ্ম জ্বালানির বিষাক্ত উপজাত বায়ু প্রবেশ করানো হয় যখন</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 причины, почему ядерная энергия потрясающая! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ru/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 07:59:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ru/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>Видео Транскрипт ﻿Три причины продолжать использовать ядерную энергию.
Во-первых, ядерная энергия спасает жизни.
Исследование, проведённое NASA в 2013 году, показало, что
ядерная энергия помогла предотвратить около 1,8 миллиона смертей.
Даже если учесть смерти в Чернобыле и Фукусиме,
ядерная энергия на последнем месте по смертям на единицу произведённой энергии.
Хоть ядерные отходы и токсичны, они обычно где-то хранятся,
в то время как побочные продукты ископаемого топлива выбрасываются
в воздух, которым мы дышим.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 lý do tại sao năng lượng hạt nhân thật tuyệt vời 3/3 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/vi/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 07:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/vi/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>Video Bản trích ﻿3 lí do chúng ta nên tiếp tục sử dụng năng lượng hạt nhân
Thứ nhất: Năng lượng hạt nhân bảo tồn tính mạng
Trong năm 2013, một nghiên cứu được tiến hành bởi NASA thống kê rằng năng lượng hạt nhân đã giảm thiểu
khoảng 1,8 triệu người chết.*
Thậm chí nếu bạn bao gồm số người chết từ thảm họa hạt nhân Chernobyl và Fukushima,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Tysiąckilometrowa lina do gwiazd - Skyhook ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/pl/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 07:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/pl/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkrypcja ﻿Polecieć do kosmosu jest trudno.
Można to porównać do wjeżdżania na monocyklu pod górę z plecakiem pełnym materiałów wybuchowych.
Nie możesz wziąć ze sobą dużo rzeczy i możesz umrzeć.
Rakieta, żeby wylecieć z Ziemi, musi osiągnąć prędkość 40000km/h.
Aby osiągnąć tę prędkość, rakiety większość swojego miejsca poświęcają na paliwo zostawiając niewielkią przestrzeń w kabinie
To złe rozwiązanie jeśli chcesz dolecieć do innych planet,
ponieważ potrzebujesz dużo ciężkich rzeczy jeśi chcesz przeżyć</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>一个自私的论点是让世界变得更好 - 利己主义的利他主义。 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/zh-hans/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 07:14:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/zh-hans/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>视频 文字稿 ﻿现在世界上绝大多数的人口都在农场工作 世界经济的总产量 主要是农业总产量 而农业产量受到土地规模的限制 经济总产量多年来并没有太大变化 “</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3つの理由：原子力エネルギーは素晴らしい！ ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ja/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 07:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ja/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>ビデオ 転写 ﻿原子力を使うべき３つの理由 １. 原子力は命を守る ＮＡＳＡの最近の研究によれば 原子力は180万人もの命を守った チェルノブイリと福島を</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A marihuána tiltása melletti 3 gyakori érvről ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/hu/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 07:11:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/hu/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Videó Tranzkript ﻿A marihuánát egyre több helyen dekriminalizálják vagy teszik legálissá.
De biztos hogy ez jó ötlet?
Az online vitákban a káros hatásokat gyakran alábecsülik.
Vessünk tehát egy pillantást a marihuána legalizálása ellen felhozott 3 legerőteljesebb érvre.
Első érv: A kannabisz egy erős drog
Az utóbbi évtizedekben a marihuánát sokkal erősebbé tették
Manapság a marihuána olyan hatásos, hogy egy erős droggá vált, ami pszichózist okozhat.
A marihuána fő hatóanyaga a THC, és erős bizonyítékok utalnak arra, hogy kapcsolódik a pszichózishoz,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Un câble de 1,000 km jusqu’aux étoiles - Le Skyhook ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/fr/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 07:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/fr/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>Vidéo Transcription ﻿Se rendre dans l&amp;rsquo;espace est difficile.
Actuellement, c&amp;rsquo;est comme grimper une montagne sur un monocycle
munis d&amp;rsquo;un sac à dos rempli d&amp;rsquo;explosifs.
Incroyablement lent, vous ne pouvez pas transporter grand chose et vous risquez de mourir.
Une fusée a besoin d&amp;rsquo;atteindre une vitesse d&amp;rsquo;environ 40.000 km/h pour s&amp;rsquo;échapper de la Terre.
Pour atteindre cette vitesse, les fusées sont pour la plupart des réservoirs de carburant
avec un tout petit peu de cargaison.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 iemesli, kāpēc kodolenerģija ir lieliska! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/lv/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 06:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/lv/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripts ﻿Trīs iemesli kādēļ mums vajadzētu turpināt izmantot atomenerģiju.
Atomenerģija glābj dzīvības
gadā NASA veiktais pētījums ir pierādījis, ka atomenerģija ir novērsusi
aptuveni 1,8 miljonus nāvju.
Pat, ja tiek ieskaitītas cilvēku dzīvības Černobiļā un Fukušimā.
Atomenerģija ieņem pēdējo vietu sacensībā &amp;ldquo;nāves pret saražotajām enerģijas vienībām&amp;rdquo;.
Kaut arī atomatkritumi ir ļoti toksiski, tie parasti tiek kaut kur glabāti.
Kamēr fosilā kurināmā toksiskie blakusprodukti tiek izpumpēti gaisā,
kuru mēs elpojam katru dienu.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Прегледани 3 аргументи зошто марихуаната треба да остане нелегална ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/mk/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 06:42:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/mk/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Видео Транскрипт ﻿Во целиот свет марихуаната се декриминализира или станува легална,
но дали е ова добра идеја?
Во онлајн дебата, штетните сајтови се често потценувани,
така да, ајде да погледнеме во трите најзастапени аргументи против легализација на марихуаната.
Аргумент #1: Канабисот е силна дрога
Во последните неколку децении,
марихуаната е инженирана да стане монгу повеќе потентна.
Денеска марихуаната е многу потентна,
што е всушност силна дрога што можеби придизвикува психоза</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Esrarın Yasadışı Kalması Gerektiğine Dair 3 İddianın İncelemesi ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/tr/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 06:38:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/tr/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkript ﻿Dünyanın her tarafında esrar yasal hale getiriliyor
Ama bu gerçekten iyi bir fikir mi? İnternette ki tartışmalarda zararlı diyenlerin sayısı yeterince göz önüne alınmıyor mu?
Bu yüzden esrarı yasallaştırmaya karşı en güçlü üç argümana bakalım.
Intro - Kurzgesagt
Argüman 1: Son on yılda esrar git gide daha güçlü hale geliyor
Şimdiki esrar o kadar güçlü ki artık psikoz (ruh hastalıkları) oluşturuyor
Esrarın ana etken maddesi THC&amp;rsquo;dir ve diğer risk faktörlerinden bağımsız olarak THC&amp;rsquo;nin ruh hastalıklarına sebep olduğuna dair güçlü kanıtlar vardır.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 argumenttia marihuanan laittomuuden puolesta läpikäytynä ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/fi/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 06:24:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/fi/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkriptio ﻿Ympäri maailmaa
marihuanaa ollaan dekriminalisoimassa tai jopa laillistamassa.
Mutta onko tämä kuitenkaan hyvä idea?
Nettiväittelyissä
huonoja puolia usein vähätellään.
Käydään siis läpi kolme vahvinta argumenttia
marihuanan laillistamista vastaan.
Väite numero 1:
Viime vuosikymmeninä
marihuanasta on jalostettu paljon vahvempaa.
Nykyään marihuana on niin väkevää,
että se on tosiasiassa kova huume, joka saattaa aiheuttaa psykoosin.
Marihuanan keskeisin vaikuttava ainesosa on THC,
ja on olemassa vahvaa näyttöä siitä, että THC:n ja psykoosin välillä on yhteys</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Anledningar Varför Kärnkraft Är Fruktansvärt 2/3 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/sv/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 06:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/sv/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkription ﻿Tre anledningar till varför vi borde sluta använda kärnkraft.
Ett: kärnvapensspridning
Kärnteknik gjorde en våldsam entré på världsscenen:
Bara ett år efter världens första kärnvapenstest i 1944,
blev två storstäder förstörda av bara två enstaka bomber.
Efter det, utvecklades reaktorteknik sakta
som ett sätt att generera elektricitet,
men det har alltid förknippats med dess nära relation till kärnvapensteknologi.
Det är nästintill omöjligt att skapa kärnvapen
utan tillgång till reaktorteknologi.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Аргументы, чаму марихуана павінна застацца незаконнай: аналіз ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/be/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 06:13:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/be/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Відэа Транскрыпцыя ﻿Па ўсім свеце,
марыхуана дыкрыміналізуецца, ці нават апыняецца легальнай.
Але ці гэта сапраўды добрая ідэя?
У гэтым анлайн дэбаты
шкодныя бакі часта згладжваюцца.
Такім чынам, давайце паглядзім на тры самых моцных аргументаў
супраць легалізацыі марыхуаны.
[Intro - Kurzgesagt]
Аргумент нумар 1:
У апошнія некалькі дзесяцігоддзяў,
Марыхуана была мадыфікавана каб стаць значна больш моцнай.
Сёння, марыхуана з&amp;rsquo;яўляецца настолькі моцнай,
што на самой справе гэта моцны наркотык, які можа выклікаць псіхоз.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Lý do tại sao năng lượng hạt nhân là tồi tệ! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/vi/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 06:05:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/vi/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>Video Bản trích ﻿Ba lý do tại sao chúng ta nên ngừng sử dụng năng lượng hạt nhân.
Một: phổ biến vũ khí hạt nhân.
Công nghệ hạt nhân đã khiến bạo lực lan tràn ở mức độ toàn thế giới:
chỉ một năm sau cuộc thử nghiệm nổ hạt nhân đầu tiên vào năm 1944,
hai thành phố lớn đã bị phá hủy bởi chỉ hai quả bom.
Sau đó, công nghệ lò phản ứng chậm rãi phát triển</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Argumentos Porque a Maconha Deve Permanecer Ilegal Avaliados ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/pt-pt/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 06:04:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/pt-pt/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Vídeo Transcrição ﻿Por todo o mundo a maconha vem sendo descriminalizada ou até mesmo sendo legalizada
Mas isso realmente é uma boa ideia?
No debate online, os aspectos danosos são frequentemente subestimados
Então vamos ver o três argumentos mais fortes contra a legalização da maconha
Argumento número um:
Nas últimas décadas a maconha vem sendo geneticamente modificada para se tornar mais potente
Hoje, a maconha é tão potente que é uma droga pesada que pode causar psicose</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 důvody, proč nelegalizovat marihuanu ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/cs/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 05:58:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/cs/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripce ﻿Po celém světě se marihuana dekriminalizuje nebo dokonce legalizuje
Ale je to dobrý nápad? V online debatách jsou špatné stránky marihuany bagatelizované.
Pojďme se podívat na 3 nejsilnější argumenty proti legalizaci marihuany.
INTRO
Argument 1: MARIHUANA JE TVRDÁ DROGA
V posledních desetiletích
se marihuana stávala čím dál silnější.
Dnes je tak silná, že může způsobit psychózu.
Hlavní aktivní složkou je THC a jsou silné důkazy o tom, že THC je spojeno s psychózou</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 причини, поради които ядрената енергия е ужасна! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/bg/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 05:58:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/bg/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>Видео Транскрипция ﻿Има три причини да спрем да използваме ядрена енергия.
Първо: разпространението на ядрените оръжия.
Ядрената технология бързо навлиза на световната сцена
само една година след първия тест на ядрено оръжие през 1944 г.
Два големи града са унищожени само с две бомби.
След това реакторната технология бавно еволюира към
производство на електричество,
но винаги е била тясно свързана с технологията на атомните оръжия.
Почти невъзможно е да се разработват ядрени оръжия без използване на реакторната технология.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Alasan Mengapa Tenaga Nuklear Adalah Teruk! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ms/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 05:57:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ms/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripsi ﻿Terdapat tiga sebab mengapa kita perlu berhenti menggunakan tenaga nuklear
Pertama : Percambahan senjata nuklear
Teknologi nuklear adalah sangat berbahaya untuk dunia
setahun selepas ujian letupan nuklear pertama dunia pada 1944
dua bandar besar telah dimusnahkan oleh 2 buah bom
Selepas itu, teknologi reaktor berevolusi dengan perlahan
hanya untuk menjana tenaga elektrik
tetapi ia selalu dikaitkan dengan teknologi senjata nuklear
Hampir mustahil untuk membangunkan senjata nuklear
tanpa mengakses kepada teknologi reaktor</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Dünyayı Daha İyi Bir Yer Yapmayı Amaçlayan Bencilce Argüman - Bencil Özgecilik ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/tr/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 05:49:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/tr/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkript ﻿Yakın zamana kadar, dünya nüfusunun büyük bir çoğunluğu çiftliklerde çalışıyordu
ve dünya ekonomisinin toplam üretimi
çoğunlukla toplam tarımsal üretimdi.
Bu verim toprağın sabit boyutuyla sınırlanmıştı
Ekonominin toplam üretimi yıldan yıla
çok değişmedi.
Turtanın boyutu sabitti;
dünya bir sıfır toplamlı oyundu.
Böylesine durgun bir dünyada,
kazanç sağlamanın tek yolu bir başkasının kaybetmesiydi.
Eğer turtadan büyük bir parça alırsanız,
bir başkası daha az alır.
Eğer daha fazla yemek istiyorsanız, o zaman</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>1000км трос до зірок - Небесний гак ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/uk/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 05:06:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/uk/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>Відео Транскрипція ﻿Дістатися космосу важко.
Зараз це як зійти на гору на одноколісному велосипеді
з рюкзаком, заповненим вибухівкою.
Неймовірно повільно, без можливості транспортувати велику кількість речей і з можливістю померти.
Ракеті потрібно досягнути швидкості в 40,000 км/год щоб покинути Землю.
Щоб досягнути цієї швидкості, ракети це здебільшого контейнери з паливом і крихітною верхівкою з корисним вантажем.
Це погано, якщо ви хочете відправитись до інших планет,
тому, що потрібно багато важких речей, якщо ви хочете вижити і можливо колись повернутися назад.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>1000 km-es kábel a csillagokig - A Skyhook ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/hu/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 05:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/hu/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>Videó Tranzkript ﻿Az űrbe feljutni nehéz.
Jelenleg ez olyan, mint egykerekűzve feljutni egy hegyre,
egy hátizsáknyi robbanóanyaggal.
Hihtetlenül lassú, csak kis szállítmány lehetséges, és meghalhatsz közben.
Egy rakétának kb. 40 000 km/h sebességet kell elérnie, hogy kijusson az űrbe.
Ezért a rakéták lényegében üzemanyagtankok egy apró rakománnyal.
Ez nem jó, ha más bolygókra szeretnénk eljutni,
mert nagyon sok nehéz dologra van szükség a túléléshez, és esetleg&amp;hellip;
a hazatéréshez.
Van-e mód az űrbe utazásra kevesebb üzemanyaggal, és nagyobb rakománnyal?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Καλώδιο 1,000χλμ στα αστέρια - Το Skyhook ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/el/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 05:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/el/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>Βίντεο Αποσπάσματα ﻿Το να φτάσεις στο διάστημα είναι δύσκολο.
Αυτή τη στιγμή, είναι σαν να ανεβαίνεις σε ένα βουνό σε ένα μονόκυκλο -
με ένα σακίδιο γεμάτο από εκρηκτικά.
Απίστευτα αργή, δεν μπορείτε να μεταφέρετε πολλά πράγματα και ίσως πεθάνετε.
Ένας πύραυλος πρέπει να φτάσει σε μια ταχύτητα περίπου 40.000 χιλιομέτρων την ώρα για να ξεφύγει από τη Γη.
Για να φτάσουν αυτήν την ταχύτητα, οι πύραυλοι είναι ως επί το πλείστον δοχεία για καύσιμα με ένα μικροσκοπικό άκρο ωφέλιμου φορτίου.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Egoisma argumento por plibonigi la mondon - egoisma altruismo. ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/eo/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 04:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/eo/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>Video Transskribo ﻿Ĝis antaŭnelonge, la granda plejmulto da homoj en la mondo laboris en kamparoj
kaj la tuta produkto de la tutmonda ekonomio
estis plejparte la sumo de agrikultura produktado.
Kaj tiu produktado estis limigita de la konstanta grandeco de tero.
La tuta produkto de la ekonomio ne ŝanĝiĝis multe inter jaroj.
La grandeco de la kuko estis konstanta; la mondo estis &amp;ldquo;nul-suma ludo&amp;rdquo;.
En tia senprogresa mondo, la ununura maniero por pliboniĝi estas malplibonigi iun alian.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>1.000 km Ulduzlara Kabel - Skyhook ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/az/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 04:39:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/az/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkriptlər ﻿Fəzaya getmək çətindir.
Hal-hazırda bu, partlayıcılarla dolu kürək çantası ilə tək təkərli velosipedlə dağa çıxmaq kimi bir şeydir.
Hər şey inanılmaz dərəcədə yavaşdır, özünüzlə çox şey apara bilməzsiniz və ölə bilərsiniz.
Bir raketin Yerdən çıxması üçün saatda təxminən 40.000 km sürətə çatması lazımdır.
Bu sürətə çatmaq üçün raketlər əsasən yanacaq daşayan konteynerlər olub, özləri ilə çox az yük daşıya bilərlər.
Əgər başqa planetlərə getmək istəyirsinizsə, bu pisdir, çünki sağ qalmaq və bəlkə də geri qayıtmaq üçün sizə çoxlu ağır əşyalar lazımdır.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Egoistický altruismus - sobecký argument pro zlepšení světa. ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/cs/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 04:28:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/cs/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripce ﻿Ještě nedávno pracovala většina světové populace na farmách
a celkovou produkci světové ekonomiky
tvořila z většiny celková zemědělská produkce.
A tato produkce byla limitována pevnou velikostí obdělávané země.
Celková produkce ekonomiky se rok od roku příliš neměnila.
Velikost koláče byla pevná - svět byl hra s nulovým součtem.
V takto stagnujícím světě je jedinou cestou k tomu, mít se líp, zhoršit situace druhého.
Pokud dostanete větší kus koláče, někdo jiný musí dostat menší.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Et selvsentrert argument for å gjøre verden til et bedre sted - Egoistisk Altruisme ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/no/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 04:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/no/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripsjon ﻿Inntil nylig jobbet det store flertallet av verdensbefolkningen på gårder
og den totale produksjonen av verdens økonomi
var for det meste den totale landbruksproduksjonen.
Og denne produksjonen var begrenset p.g.a landets gitte størrelse.
Den totale produksjonen endret seg ikke mye fra år etter år.
Størrelsen på kaken var allerede bestemt: Verden var et &amp;ldquo;nullsum spill&amp;rdquo;.
I en slik stagnerende verden er den eneste måten å bli bedre på er hvis noen andre får det verre.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 razloga zašto je nuklearna energija užasna! 2/3 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/hr/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 04:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/hr/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripcija ﻿Tri razloga zašto bismo trebali prestati koristiti nuklearnu energiju.
Prva: Naglo širenje nuklearnog oružja
Nuklearna energija je napravila silovit ulazak na svjetsku scenu
samo jednu godinu nakon prve svjetske testne nuklearne eksplozije 1944.
dva velika grada su uništena sa samo dvije bombe!
Nakon toga, tehnologija reaktora se sporo razvijala
kao sredstvo proizvodnje električne energije
ali je uvijek bila usko poveza sa tehnologijom nuklearnog oružja.
Skoro je nemoguće razviti nuklearno oružje</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 grunner til at kjernekraft er forferdelig! 2/3 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/no/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 04:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/no/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripsjon ﻿Tre grunner til at vi bør slutte å bruke atomenergi
En: Spredning av kjernefysiske våpen.
Kjernefysisk teknologi gjorde en voldelig inngang på verdensscenen :
bare ett år etter verdens aller første atomprøvesprengning i 1944,
ble to store byer ødelagt av bare to enkle bomber.
Etter dette, utviklet reaktorteknologi seg sakte
som en metode for å generere elektrisitet,
men det har alltid vært nært koblet til atomvåpen-teknologi.
Det er nesten umulig å utvikle atomvåpen</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3個原因解釋為何核能是可怕的！ ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/zh-hant/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 04:04:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/zh-hant/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>影片 文字稿 ﻿3個&amp;quot;為什麼我們要停止使用核能&amp;quot;的理由 核子武器擴散 核能技術以一種暴力式的方式登上世界舞台。 在1944年世界第</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Érv a Nukleáris Energia Ellen! 2/3 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/hu/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 03:53:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/hu/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>Videó Tranzkript ﻿Három ok, hogy miért ne használjunk többé atomenergiát.
Az első: az atomfegyverek elterjedése.
A nukleáris technológia drámaian robbant be világunkba:
Csupán egyetlen évvel a világ első kísérleti atomrobbantása után 1944-ben,
két nagyvárost pusztított el mindössze két bomba.
Ezután alakult ki lassan a reaktor technológia,
hogy elektromos energiát generáljon,
de mindig is szorosan összefűződött az atomfegyver technológiával.
Szinte lehetetlen atomfegyvereket fejleszteni
a reaktor technológia nélkül.
Az atomsorompó szerződésnek az a konkrét célja,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Arsye pse energjia e nuklearit eshte e mire! 3/3 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/sq/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 03:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/sq/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripte ﻿Tri arsye pse duhet të vazhdojmë përdorimin e energjisë bërthamore.
Një: energjia bërthamore shpëton jetën.
Në vitin 2013, një studim i kryer nga NASA gjetur se energjia bërthamore ka penguar
rreth 1.8 milionë vdekje.
Edhe në qoftë se ju të përfshijë shkallës së vdekjeve nga Çernobilit dhe Fukushima,
energjia bërthamore renditet e fundit në vdekje për Njësia e energjisë e prodhuar.
Ndërsa mbetjet bërthamore është me të vërtetë toksike, është e ruajtur zakonisht diku,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 कारण न्यूक्लियर ऊर्जा खराब आहे! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/mr/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 03:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/mr/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>व्हिडिओ ट्रान्स्क्रिप्ट ﻿आपण अण्विक ऊर्जेचा वापर थांबवण्याची तीन कारणे.
अण्विक अस्त्रांची वेगवान वाढ. जगातील सर्वात पहिल्या वहिल्या अण्विक चाचणीचा भडका उडाल्यानंतर
केवळ एका वर्षानंतर, 1944 साली
प्रत्येकी एक या प्रमाणे दोन अणूबॉम्बनी दोन मोठ्या शहरांचा नाश केला
आणि लगेचच अण्विक तंत्रज्ञानाने जगाच्या मंचावर हिंसक प्रवेश केला.
त्यानंतर अणूभट्टी तंत्रज्ञान वीज निर्मितीचे साधन म्हणून उत्क्रांत झाले.
परंतु ते नेहमीच अण्विक अस्त्र तंत्रज्ञानाशी
फार जवळून जोडले गेले आहे.
भट्टी तंत्रज्ञान उपलब्ध असल्याखेरीज</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 syytä, miksi ydinenergia on kauheaa! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/fi/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 03:22:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/fi/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkriptio ﻿Kolme syytä, miksi meidän pitäisi hylätä ydinvoima.
Ydinaseiden runsastuminen Ydintekniikka saapui maailmaan väkivaltaisesti:
vain vuosi ensimmäisen, vuoden 1944 ydinkokeen jälkeen,
kaksi suurta kaupunkia tuhottiin vain kahden pommin avulla.
Sitemmin reaktoritekniikka on kehittynyt hitaasti
energian tuotannon keinona,
mutta sillä on aina ollut intiimi suhde ydinasetekniikkaan.
On lähes mahdotonta tuottaa ydinaseita
ilman reaktoritekniikan hallitsemista.
Itse asiassa Ydinsulkusopimus auttaa
ydintekniikan levittämisessä kuitenkaan levittämättä ydinaseita
vaisulla menestyksellä.
40 vuoden ajassa viisi valtiota on kehittänyt omat aseensa</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>دلایل بد بودن انرزی هسته ای ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/fa/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 03:11:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/fa/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>ویدئو متن ﻿سه دلیل که چرا ما باید استفاده از انرژی هسته ای را متوقف کنیم.
اول: گسترش سلاح های هسته ای.
فناوری هسته ای باعث خشونت در صحنه جهانی خواهد شد.
فقط یکسال بعد از اولین تست انفجار اتمی در جهان در سال 1944
دو شهر بزرگ تنها به وسیله ی دو بمب نابود شدند
بعد از آن فناوری راکتور ها به آرامی گسترش یافته
به عنوان وسیله تولید برق.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Reasons Why Nuclear Energy Is Awesome! 3/3 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 02:58:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Three reasons why we should continue using nuclear energy.
One: nuclear energy saves lives.
In 2013, a study conducted by NASA found that nuclear energy has prevented
around 1.8 million deaths.
Even if you include the death tolls from Chernobyl and Fukushima,
nuclear energy ranks last in death per energy unit produced.
While nuclear waste is really toxic, it’s usually stored somewhere,
while the toxic byproducts of fossil fuels are pumped into the air</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Um Argumento Egoísta para Fazer do Mundo um Lugar Melhor - Altruísmo Egoísta ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/pt-br/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 02:50:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/pt-br/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>Vídeo Transcrição ﻿Até recentemente, a grande maioria da população mundial trabalhava em fazendas
E a produção total da economia mundial era em sua maioria o total produzido pela agro-pecuária
E essa produção era ditada pela extensão de terra
O montante total da economia não alterava tanto com o passar dos anos
O tamanho do bolo era fixo. O mundo era uma equação terminada em zero
Em um mundo tão estagnado, a única maneira de alguém se dar bem, é se alguém se der mal</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Аргумента Срещу Легализацията на Марихуана - Разгледани ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/bg/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 02:48:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/bg/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Видео Транскрипция ﻿По целия свят
марихуаната бива декриминализирана или дори легализирана.
Но добра идея ли е това наистина?
В онлайн дебата
негативните аспекти често биват омаловажавани.
Затова нека разгледаме трите най-силни аргумента срещу легализирането на марихуаната.
Интро
Аргумент номер едно
В последните няколко десетилетия,
марихуаната е модифицирана, за да стане много по-потентна.
Днес, марихуаната е толкова потентна,
че всъщност е силен наркотик, който може да предизвика психоза.
Главната активна съставка е THC,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>1000km Kabel Til Stjernene - Himmelkroken (Romtjore) ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/no/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 02:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/no/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripsjon ﻿Å dra ut i verdensrommet er vanskelig.
Akkurat nå er det som å gå opp et fjell
på en enhjulsykkel med en ryggsekk full av eksplosiver.
Det går nokså sakte, man kan ikke bringe med seg mye utstyr og man kan dø.
En rakett må nå en hastighet på omtrent
40 000 km/t for å forlate Jorden.
For å oppnå den hastigheten er raketter rett og slett
drivstoffbeholdere med veldig lite baggasje.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 סיבות למה אנרגיה גרעינית זו נורא! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/he/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 02:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/he/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>וידאו טְק֡ס֙ט ﻿3 סיבות שבגללן צריך
להפסיק להשתמש באנרגיה גרעינית:
הפצת נשק גרעיני האנרגיה הגרעינית התחילה את דרכה באלימות:
כעבור שנה אחת בלבד משנת 1944, שבה התרחש הניסוי הגרעיני הראשון אי פעם,
שתי ערי ענק הושמדו על ידי שתי פצצות בלבד.
לאחר מכן, טכנולוגיית הכורים הגרעיניים התפתחה באיטיות
כאמצעי להפקת חשמל,
אבל היא נשארה מקושרת לטכנולוגיית הנשקים הגרעיניים.
כמעט בלתי אפשרי להפיק נשק גרעיני
ללא גישה לטכנולוגיית כורים גרעיניים.
למעשה, האמנה למניעת הפצת הנשק הגרעיני ממלאת את מטרתה,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 اسباب لماذا يجب ان تبقى ال مارجوانا غير قانونيه ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ar/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 02:28:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ar/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>فيديو نص ﻿في جميع أنحاء العالم
يتم عدم تجريم الماريجوانا ، أو تُشرع لجعلها قانونية
لكن هل هذه حقاً فكرة جيدة؟
في النقاش عبر شبكة الإنترنت
غالباً ما يتم التقليل من أهمية الجوانب الضارة
لذلك دعونا ننظر إلى الحجج الثلاث الأقوى
ضد تشريع الماريجوانا
مقدمـــــة
الحجة الأولى
في العقود القليلة الماضية
صُممت الماريجوانا لتصبح أكثر فعالية
اليوم ، الماريجوانا فعّالة للغاية
في الواقع إنه مُخدرٌ قوي قد يسبب الذهان
العنصر النشط الرئيسي للماريجوانا هو رباعي هيدرو كانابينول</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 कारण न्यूक्लियर ऊर्जेचं अद्याप आहे! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/mr/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 02:24:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/mr/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>व्हिडिओ ट्रान्स्क्रिप्ट ﻿आपण अणूऊर्जेचा वापर का सुरू ठेवला पाहिजे याची तीन कारणे.
अणूऊर्जा जीवरक्षक आहे. नासा या संस्थेने 1913 साली केलेल्या अभ्यासानुसार अणूऊर्जेमुळे
साधारणपणे 1.8 दशलक्ष मृत्यू रोखलेले आहेत.
जरी तुम्ही चेर्नोबिल आणि फुकुशिमा येथल्या मृत्यूंचा समावेश केला तरीही
निर्माण झालेल्या ऊर्जेच्या प्रत्येक एककागणिक झालेल्या मृत्यूंत अणूऊर्जेचा क्रमांक शेवटचा आहे.
अणूकचरा हा खरोखरच विषारी असला तरीही तो कोठेतरी साठवला जातो.
याउलट जैवइंधनांची विषारी सहउत्पादिते पंपाने
आपण दर दिवशी श्वासाद्वारे घेत असलेल्या हवेत सोडली जातात.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>दुनिया को बेहतर स्थान बनाने के लिए एक स्वार्थी तर्क - स्वार्थी दूसरों का उपकार करने का सिद्धान्त ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/hi/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 02:22:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/hi/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>वीडियो ट्रांसक्रिप्ट ﻿हाल ही में, दुनिया की विशाल आबादी खेतों पर काम करती है
और दुनिया की अर्थव्यवस्था का कुल उत्पादन
ज्यादातर कृषि उत्पादन था।
और यह उत्पादन भूमि के निश्चित आकार से सीमित था।
अर्थव्यवस्था का कुल उत्पादन वर्ष दर साल बहुत ज्यादा नहीं बदला।
पाई का आकार तय किया गया था; दुनिया शून्य राशि वाला गेम था।
ऐसी स्थिर दुनिया में, बेहतर होने का एकमात्र तरीका यह है कि अगर कोई और खराब हो जाता है।</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 разлога зашто би марихуана требалa да остане незаконитa ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/sr-cyrl/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 02:22:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/sr-cyrl/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Видео Транскрипт ﻿Широм света марихуана се декриминализује или чак легализује.
Али да ли је ово заиста добра идеја? У онлајн дискусији често се умањују лоше стране.
Дакле, погледајмо три најснажнија аргумента против легализације марихуане.
Intro - Kurzgesagt Caption Review: Doga Poyraz Tahan
Аргумент 1: У последњих неколико деценија
Марихуана је узгојена да постане много снажнија
Данас је марихуана толико моћна да заправо представља снажан наркотик који може изазвати психозу.
Главни активни састојак марихуане је ТХЦ и постоје снажни докази да је ТХЦ повезан са психозом</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>כבל של 1000 ק&#39;מ לכוכבים - וו החלל ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/he/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 02:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/he/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>וידאו טְק֡ס֙ט ﻿להגיע לחלל זה קשה.
כיום, זה כמו לדווש על הר עם חד אופן, עם תיק מלא בחומרי נפץ.
איטי להפליא, אינך יכול להעביר הרבה דברים, ואתה עלול למות.
רקטה צריכה להגיע למהירות של 40,000 קילומטר לשעה, כדי להמלט מכוח המשיכה של כדור הארץ.
כדי להגיע למהירות זו, הרקטות צריכות להכיל בעיקר דלק, וקצה קטן של מטען.
זה רע אם אתה רוצה להגיע לכוכב לכת אחר, כי אתה זקוק להרבה דברים כבדים</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>世界をより良い場所にするための利己主義 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ja/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 02:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ja/post/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>ビデオ 転写 ﻿ごく最近まで、大部分の人は 農業に従事していて 世界経済の総生産は ほぼ農業の総生産に等しく この生産量は、土地の面積に よって制約されて</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Разлога зашто је нуклеарна енергија сјајна! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/sr-cyrl/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 02:10:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/sr-cyrl/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>Видео Транскрипт ﻿Tri razloga zašto treba da nastavimo sa korišćenjem nuklearne energije.
Prvi: nuklearna energija spasava živote.
studija koju je sprovela NASA pronašla je da je nuklearna energija sprečila oko 1,8 miliona smrtnih slučajeva.
Čak iako uračunamo žrtve iz Černobila i Fukušime
nuklearna energija je na zadnjem mestu po broju smrtnih slučajeva po jedinici proizvedene energije.
Dok je nuklearni otpad veoma toksičan, obično se negde skladišti,
a toksični nusproizvodi fosilnih goriva se otpuštaju direktno u vazduh</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Raons per les quals l&#39;energia nuclear és terrible! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ca/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 02:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ca/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcripció ﻿3 raons per les quals hauriem de deixar de fer servir l&amp;rsquo;energia nuclear.
La proliferació de les armes nuclears La tecnologia nuclear va fer una forta entrada a l&amp;rsquo;escena mundial
només un any després de la primera prova nuclear del món
el 1944.
Dues grans ciutats van quedar destruïdes per només dues bombes.
Després d&amp;rsquo;això, la tecnologia dels reactors nuclears ha evolucionat lentament fins a ser un mitjà</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Nükleer Enerjiyi Mükemmel Kılan 3 Neden! 3/3 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/tr/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 01:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/tr/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkript ﻿Nükleer enerji kullanmaya devam etmemiz için 3 sebep:
1.Nükleer enerji hayat kurtarır.
2013&amp;rsquo;te,NASA tarafından yapılan bir araştırmada
nükleer enerjinin 1.8 milyon ölümü önlediği keşfedildi.
Çernobil ve Fukushima&amp;rsquo;daki ölümleri saysanız bile
nükleer enerji,üretilen enerji ünitesi başına
ölüm sırasında sonuncudur.Nükleer atık zehirli olsa da
fosil yakıtların zehirli yan ürünleri
her gün soluduğumuz havaya pompalanırken
genellikle bir yerlerde saklanır.
Yani,yalnızca yakılan fosil yakıt miktarını düşürererek
sayısız kanser ya da akciğer rahatsızlığı ve kömür madeni</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Разлога зашто је нуклеарна енергија ужасна! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/sr-cyrl/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 01:43:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/sr-cyrl/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>Видео Транскрипт ﻿Три разлога зашто бисмо требали да престанемо да користимо нуклеарну енергију.
Први: раст и развој нуклеарног оружја.
Нуклеарна технологија је насилно ушла на светску бину:
само једну годину после првог икад нуклеарног теста експлозије 1944,
два велика града су униште са само две бомбе.
Након тога, технологија реактора се полако развила
за потребе скупљања електрицитета,
али је одувек била интимно повезана са технологијом нуклеарних оружја.
Скоро је немогуће да се развије нуклеарно оружје</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Argumentos por los que la marihuana debería seguir siendo ilegal revisados ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/es-419/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 01:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/es-419/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcripción ﻿Al rededor del mundo la marihuana está siendo despenalizada o incluso legalizada
Pero, ¿es realmente una buena idea?
En la discusión en linea, los sitios dañinos a menudo lo minimizan
Así que revisemos los 3 argumentos más fuertes en contra de legalizar la marihuana
Argumento número uno: en las últimas décadas
la marihhuana ha sido diseñada para volverse mucho más potente
Hoy, la marihuana es tan potente que de hecho es una droga fuerte que podría causar psicosis.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3つの理由：なぜマリファナは違法のままであるべきかを検討しました。 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ja/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 01:11:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ja/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>ビデオ 転写 ﻿世界のいたるところで マリファナは非犯罪化されているか、合法なものになりつつある しかし、これは本当にいいアイディアなのだろうか オン</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3가지 이유로 핵 에너지는 끔찍합니다! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ko/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 01:03:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ko/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>비디오 대본 ﻿왜 우리가 핵에너지 사용을 그만둬야 하는지 3가지 이유를 들 수 있습니다. 첫째, 핵무기의 확산성. 핵기술은 전 세계가 폭력적이게 되는 계기를 제공했습</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>원자력이 멋진 세 가지 이유! 3/3 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ko/post/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 01:02:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ko/post/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>비디오 대본 ﻿왜 우리가 계속 핵 에너지를 이용하는지 세가지 이유:) 첫째, 핵 에너지가 생명을 구한다. 2013년에 나사에서 실행된 연구에서 핵 에너지가 약 180</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Тысячекилометровый трос до звёзд - Орбитальный гарпун ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ru/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 00:51:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ru/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>Видео Транскрипт ﻿Попасть в космос трудно
В наше время это все равно, что подняться на гору на одноколесном велосипеде
с рюкзаком полным взрывчатки
Невероятно медленно, вы не можете взять с собой много вещей
И вы можете умереть
Ракета должна достичь скорости примерно 40 000 км/ч
для того, чтобы покинуть Землю
Чтобы достичь такой скорости
ракеты строят во многом как емкости для топлива
с небольшим количеством груза.
Это плохо для тех, кто хочет полететь на другую планету,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>तारों के लिए 1,000 किमी केबल - स्काईहूक ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/hi/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 00:44:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/hi/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>वीडियो ट्रांसक्रिप्ट ﻿अंतरिक्ष में जाना कठिन है।
अभी, यह विस्फोटकों से भरे बैकपैक के साथ साइकिल से पर्वत पर चढ़ने जैसा है।
अभी, यह विस्फोटकों से भरे बैकपैक के साथ साइकिल से पर्वत पर चढ़ने जैसा है।
अविश्वसनीय रूप से धीमी गति से, आप बहुत सारे सामान का परिवहन नहीं कर सकते, और आप मर भी सकते हैं।
एक रॉकेट को पृथ्वी से भागने के लिए लगभग 40,000 किमी प्रति घंटे के वेग तक पहुंचने की आवश्यकता है।</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Evaluatie Van Drie Redenen Waarom Cannabis Illegaal Moet Blijven ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/nl/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 00:41:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/nl/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcriptie ﻿Op de hele wereld wordt cannabis gedecriminaliseerd of zelfs gelegaliseerd.
Maar is dat wel een goed idee?
Op het internet worden de schadelijke kanten vaak geminimaliseerd.
Laten we dus de drie beste argumenten bekijken
om cannabis niet te legaliseren.
Argument 1: cannabis in een harddrug.
In de jongste decennia is cannabis zo gekweekt om veel sterker te worden.
Cannabis is vandaag zo sterk
dat het een harddrug is die tot psychose kan leiden.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3个理由为什么大麻应该继续非法化审查 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/zh-hans/post/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 00:35:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/zh-hans/post/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>视频 文字稿 ﻿在全世界中 大麻正在被除罪化甚至合法化。 但是这真的是一个好主意吗？ 在网络上的争论中， （大麻合法化）有害的一面常常不被重视。 所以让我</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Alasan Mengapa Energi Nuklir Sangat Buruk! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/id/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 00:25:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/id/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripsi ﻿3 Alasan Kenapa kita harus berhenti menggunakan energi nuklir
pertama Senjata nuklir berkembang pesat
teknologi nuklir membuat pintu masuk kekerasan kedalam dunia
Hanya dalam 1 tahun setelah test nuklir pertama di dunia pada tahun 1944
2 kota besar telah dihancurkan oleh 2 bom tunggal
setelah itu , teknologi reaktor perlahan berkembang
yang berfungsi untuk menghasilkan tenaga listrik
tapi itu selalu dihubungkan dengan teknologi senjata nuklir
Hal ini hampir mustahil untuk mengembangkan senjata nuklir</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Dôvody, prečo je jadrová energia hrozná! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/sk/post/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 00:24:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/sk/post/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>Video Prepis ﻿Tri dôvody, prečo by sme mali prestať používať jadrovú energiu.
Šírenie jadrových zbraní Jadrová technológia spôsobila násilný vstup na svetovej scéne.
Len rok po prvom výbuchu jadrového testu na svete v 1944
boli zničené dve veľké mestá dvoma samostatnými bombami.
Na to sa technológia reaktorov pomaly vyvinula ako prostriedok generovania
elektriny, ale vždy bola úzko spojená s technológiou jadrových zbraní.
Je takmer nemožné rozvíjať jadrové zbrane bez prístupu k technológii reaktorov.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Un Cable de 1,000 km a las Estrellas - El Gancho Aéreo ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/es-419/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 00:11:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/es-419/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcripción ﻿Ir al espacio es difícil.
En este momento es como escalar una montaña en un monociclo
con una mochila llena de explosivos.
Increíblemente lento,
no puedes llevar muchas cosas,
y quizás mueras.
Un cohete tiene que alcanzar una velocidad de alrededor 40,000 Kilómetros por hora para escapar de la Tierra.
Para alcanzar esa velocidad,
los cohetes son principalmente contenedores de combustible
con una pequeña parte de carga en la punta.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>1000 км кабел до звездите - небесното куче ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/bg/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 00:09:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/bg/post/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>Видео Транскрипция ﻿Стигането до космоса е трудно.
В сегашния момент е все едно да се качвате на планина с колело с една гума &amp;hellip;
с раница, пълна с експлозиви.
Невероятно бавно, не можете да транспортирате много неща, а може и да умрете.
На една ракета и е нужна скорост около 40 000 км в час, за да избяга от Земята.
За да стигнат до тази скорост, ракетите са основно контейнери с гориво с мъничък товар</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Sejarah Baru untuk Kemanusiaan - Era Manusia ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ms/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 23:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ms/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripsi ﻿Manusia telah wujud sejak berjuta-juta tahun, sebagai sebahagian daripada alam .
Kemudian, sesuatu berubah. Dalam masa yang amat singkat
kita mengubah planet ini dan merekanya untuk memenuhi keperluan kita.
Setakat yang kita tahu, kita makhluk pertama yang bangunkan dan mengambil alih sebuah planet.
Peralihan dari memburu dan mengumpul, ke pertanian dan bangunan, begitu cepat hingga kebanyakan cara kita berfikir tentang dunia tiada guna lagi.
Salah satu idea kita yang paling kolot ialah kalendar yang paling biasa digunakan di dunia menegaskan bahawa kita hidup pada tahun 2016.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Nova zgodovina za človeštvo - Človeška doba ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/sl/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 23:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/sl/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Prepis ﻿Ljudje so obstajali na milijone let, kot del narave.
Ampak potem se je nekaj spremenilo. In v neverjetno kratkem času
smo spremenili planet, da ustreza našim potrebam.
Kolikor vemo, smo prva bitja, ki so se prebudila in popolnoma prevzela planet.
Prehod od lova in nabiranja do kmetovanja in gradnje, je bil tako osupljivo hiter,
da veliko naših načinov razmišljanja o svetu ni več uporabnih.
Ena od naših najbolj zastarelih idej je,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Az emberi történelem új korszaka - Az Emberi Korszak ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/hu/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 21:58:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/hu/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Videó Tranzkript ﻿Az emberek több millió évig a természet részeként éltek.
De aztán valami megváltozott és hihetetlenül rövid idő alatt
a szükségleteink szerint alakítottuk át a bolygót.
Jelenlegi tudásunk szerint mi vagyunk az első élőlények, amik teljesen irányításuk alá vettek egy bolygót.
A vadászatról és gyűjtögetésről a termelésre és építkezésre való átállás olyan hihetetlen gyors volt,
hogy a világgal kapcsolatos számos felfogásunk mára teljesen idejétmúlttá vált.
Az egyik legelavultabb ezek közül az, hogy a legelterjedtebb naptár alapján</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Una Nueva Historia para la Humanidad - La Era Humana ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/es-es/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 20:45:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/es-es/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcripción ﻿Los humanos hemos existido en la naturaleza durante millones de años.
Pero un día algo cambió y en un periodo de tiempo increíblemente corto
terraformamos este planeta y lo diseñamos para adaptarlo a nuestras necesidades.
Que sepamos, somos la primera especie en despertar y controlar por completo un planeta.
Pasamos tan rápidamente de cazar y recolectar a sembrar y construir
que muchas de nuestras formas de ver el mundo ya no son útiles.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>O nouă istorie pentru umanitate - Era umană. ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ro/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 18:09:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ro/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcriere ﻿Oamenii au existat timp de milioane de ani ca parte din natură.
Dar apoi, ceva s-a schimbat. într-un timp incredibil de scurt
am tansformat aceasta planetă și am modificat-o după nevoile noastre.
Din câte știm, suntem primele ființe care au preluat complet controlul asupra unei planete.
Tranziția de la vânat și cules, la agricultură și construcții, a fost atât de rapidă încât multe din modurile noastre de gândire asupra lumii nu mai sunt folositoare.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>人類の新しい歴史 - 人類時代 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ja/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 17:46:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ja/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>ビデオ 転写 ﻿人は数百万年間 自然の中にいた しかしある時変化が起き 驚くべき早さで 人は地球を便利に改造していった 目覚めた最初の存在は 瞬く間に惑星を</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Nauja žmonijos istorija - Žmogaus era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/lt/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 17:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/lt/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripcija ﻿Žmonės, kaip gamtos dalis, egzistavo milijonus metų.
Bet tada kai kas pasikeitė. Ir per neįtikėtinai trumpą laiko tarpą.
Mes pakeitėme šią planetą ir pritaikėme ją savo reikmėms.
Kiek žinome, mes esame pirmosios būtybės įgavusios sąmonę ir visiškai perėmusios planetą į savo rankas.
Perėjimas nuo medžioklės ir maisto rinkimo iki ūkininkystės bei statybos buvo toks beprotiškai greitas, jog didelė dalis to, kaip mes suvokėme pasaulį, neteko prasmės.
Tai, jog dauguma plačiausiai naudojamų kalendorių teigia, jog mes gyvename 2016-taisiais metais, yra viena iš labiausiai atgyvenusių mūsų idėjų.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Nova povijest za čovječanstvo - Era čovjeka ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/hr/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 16:55:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/hr/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripcija ﻿Ljudi su postojali milijunima godina, kao dio prirode.
Ali onda, nešto se promijenilo. I u nevjerojatno kratkom vremenu
oblikovali smo ovaj planet i dizajnirali ga kako bi odgovarao našim potrebama.
Koliko nam je poznato, mi smo prva bića koja su se probudila i i potpuno preuzeli planet.
Prijelaz iz lova i sakupljanja, na uzgoj i građenje, bio je tako zapanjujuće brz da mnogi od naših načina razmišljanja o svijetu više nisu korisni.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Uma Nova História para a Humanidade - A Era Humana ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/pt-br/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 16:43:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/pt-br/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Vídeo Transcrição ﻿Os humanos existem há milhões de anos como parte da natureza,
mas então, algo mudou,
e em uma quantidade incrivelmente pequena de tempo nós terraformamos este planeta
e fizemos com que atendesse às nossas necessidades.
Até onde sabemos, somos os primeiros seres a acordar e tomar completamente um planeta.
A transição de caçar e coletar para plantar e construir foi tão impressionantemente rápida&amp;hellip;
&amp;hellip;que muitas de nossas maneiras de pensar no mundo não são mais úteis.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>मानवता के लिए एक नया इतिहास - मानव युग ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/hi/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 16:36:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/hi/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>वीडियो ट्रांसक्रिप्ट ﻿कड़ोरों वर्षों से मानवजाती प्रकॄति का अंश रहा है।
मगर तब, अचानक, बहुत कम समय में, कुछ बदलने लगा।
हमने अपने ज़रूतों को पूरा करने के लिए इस ग्रह को भूपरिवर्तित कर लिया।
हमारे ज्ञान के सीमा में हम वह पहले प्राणी हैं जिनहोंने जागरुकता से संपूर्ण ग्रह पर काबू कर लिया।
शिकार और फल इकट्ठा करने से लेकर कॄषी और निर्माण तक का परिवर्तन इतना जलदी हुआ कि हमारे सोचने के कई भाव-तरीके आज के युग मैं अर्थहीन बन गए हैं।</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Uma Nova História para a Humanidade - A Era Humana ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/pt-pt/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 16:12:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/pt-pt/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Vídeo Transcrição ﻿Os humanos existem por milhões de anos como parte da natureza,
mas então, algo mudou,
e em uma quantidade incrivelmente pequena de tempo nós terraformamos este planeta
e o desenhamos para que atendesse às nossas necessidades.
Até onde sabemos, somos os primeiros seres a acordar e tomar completamente um planeta.
A transição de caçar e coletar para plantar e construir foi tão impressionantemente rápida&amp;hellip;
&amp;hellip;que muitas de nossas maneiras de pensar no mundo não são mais úteis.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Una Nueva Historia para la Humanidad - La Era Humana ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/es-419/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 15:22:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/es-419/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcripción ﻿Los humanos han existido por millones de años
como parte de la naturaleza
Pero luego algo cambió
Y en muy poco tiempo nosotros terraformamos este planeta
y lo diseñamos para satisfacer nuestras necesidades
hasta donde sabemos, somos los primeros seres en
despertarnos y tomar el control del planeta.
La transición de cazar y recolectar
a cultivar y construir, fue tan increíblemente rápida
que muchas de las maneras de pensar sobre el mundo ya no son útiles.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Ihmiskunnan uusi historia - Ihmisen aikakausi ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/fi/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 15:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/fi/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkriptio ﻿Ihmiset ovat olleet olemassa osana luontoa miljoonien vuosien ajan.
Mutta sitten jokin muuttui ja hämmästyttävän lyhyessä ajassa
me muokkasimme tämän planeetan
ja suunnittelimme sen vastamaan tarpeitamme.
Omien tietojemme mukaan olemme ensimmäisen laji koskaan, joka on kyennyt ottamaan koko planeetan haltuunsa.
Muutos metsästäjä-keräilijäkulttuurista maanviljelyyn ja rakentamiseen oli niin nopea, että monet ajattelutapamme maailmasta eivät ole enään käyttökelpoisia.
Yksi jälkeenjääneimmistä ideoistamme on se, että käytetyin kalenteri maailmassa väittää, että elämme vuotta 2016.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>人类的新历史——人类时代 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/zh-hans/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 15:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/zh-hans/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>视频 文字稿 ﻿人类作为大自然的一部分已经存在了数百万年。 然而，在很短暂的一段时间内，一些东西改变了 我们改变了这个星球， 并根据我们的需要来设计。</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>En Ny Historie for Menneskeheten - Den Menneskelige Æra ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/no/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 14:37:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/no/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripsjon ﻿Mennesket har eksistert i millioner av år som en del av naturen.
Men så skjedde det noe. I løpet av utrolig kort tid
terraformet vi planeten, og tilpasset den etter våte egne behov.
Så vidt vi vet, er vi den første arten som noen gang har fullstendig tatt over en planet.
Overgangen fra å være jegere og samlere, til å være bønder og byggmestere, skjedde så utrolig fort at mange av måtene vi fortsatt tenker på, ikke lenger er nyttige.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Новая история человечества - Эра Человека ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ru/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 14:35:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ru/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Видео Транскрипт ﻿Люди миллионы лет существовали, как часть природы
Но затем кое-что изменилось
И за невероятно короткий промежуток времени мы изменили эту планету, для удовлетворения наших потребностей
Насколько мы знаем, мы &amp;ndash; первые существа, которые пробудились и полностью взяли контроль над планетой.
Переход от охоты и собирательства к земледелию и строительству был столь молниеносным,
что многие наши способы мышления о мире, более неприменимы.
Одна из наших наиболее устаревших идей &amp;ndash;</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>人類的新歷史 - 人類時代 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/zh-hant/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 14:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/zh-hant/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>影片 文字稿 ﻿人類與大自然已經共處了數百萬年之久 但在極短的時間內，某些事發生了 人類改變了這顆星球，以符合我們的需求 就我們所知，人類是第一個覺醒</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>היסטוריה חדשה עבור האנושות - עידן האדם ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/he/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 13:28:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/he/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>וידאו טְק֡ס֙ט ﻿בני אדם היו קיימים במשך מיליוני שנים, כחלק מהטבע.
אבל אז, משהו השתנה, ובפרק זמן קצר ביותר
שינינו את העולם הזה והתאמנו אותו לצרכינו.
ככל שאנחנו יודעים, אנחנו היצורים הראשונים שקמו ולגמרי השתלטו על כוכב לכת.
המעבר מציד ואיסוף לחקלאות ובנייה, היה מהיר כל כך באופן עוצר נשימה שרוב הדרכים בהן חשבנו על העולם הן כבר לא מועילות.
אחד הרעיונות הכי מיושנים שלנו הוא שלוח השנה עם השימוש הכי נפוץ בעולם מתעקש שאנחנו חיים בשנת 2016.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Una nova història per a la humanitat - L&#39;era humana ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ca/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 12:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ca/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcripció ﻿Els humans hem existit a la natura durant milions d&amp;rsquo;anys.
Però un dia alguna cosa va canviar i en un període de temps increïblement curt
vam transformar el planeta i el vam dissenyar per adaptar-lo a les nostres necessitats.
Que sapiguem, som la primera espècie a despertar i controlar per complet un planeta.
Vam passar tan ràpidament de caçar i recol·lectar a sembrar i construir
que moltes de les nostres formes de veure el món ja no són útils.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>تاريخ جديد للبشرية - العصر البشرى ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ar/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 12:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ar/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>فيديو نص ﻿تواجد البشر كجزء من الطبيعة لملايين من السنين.
ولكن , حدث تغيير في وقت قصير بشكل مذهل.
لقد اخضعنا الكوكب وصممناه ليكون مناسبًا لاحتياجاتنا.
وبقدر ما نعرف , نحن اول كائنات تستعمر وتسود كوكبًا.
وكان الانتقال من الصيد والحصاد الى البناء والزراعه سريعًا جدًا مما جعل بعض افكارنا عن العالم لا قيمه لها.
واحدة من اكثر الافكار التى عفا عليها الزمن أن التقويم الاكثر استخدامًا يُصر أننا نعيش في العام 2016.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>İnsanlık İçin Yeni Bir Tarih - İnsanlık Çağı ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/tr/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 11:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/tr/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkript ﻿İnsanlar doğanın bir parçası olarak, milyonlarca yıldır var olmuştur.
Ama sonra bir şeyler değişti
ve inanılmaz derecede kısa bir sürede bu gezegeni şekillendirip ihtiyaçlarımıza uyacak şekilde tasarladık.
bildiğimiz kadarıyla gözü açılıp bir gezegeni fetheden ilk varlıklarız
avlanma ve toplamadan tarıma ve inşaya geçiş o kadar nefes kesici bir hızdaydı ki Dünya hakkında düşündüğümüz bir çok yol artık kullanılabilir değil
hükmü kalmamış fikirlerimizden biri çoğunlukla kullanılan takvim 2016&amp;rsquo;da yaşadığımıza ayak direr</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Yeni bir insanlık tarihi - İnsan Çağı ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/is/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 10:27:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/is/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Myndband Handrit ﻿Menn hafa fyrirfunndist í milljónir ára sem hluti náttúrunnar.
En síðan breytist eitthvað, og á ótrúlega stuttum tíma
mótuðum við þessa plánetu og hönnuðum hana til þess að hæfa þörfum okkar.
Að því er við vitum best, erum við fyrstu verunar til að vakna og algjörlega taka yfir plánetu.
Umbreytingin frá að veiða og safna í að rækta og byggja var svo undralega hröð,
að margir hugsunarháttar okkar um heimin eru ekki lengur gagnlegir.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Nova Historio por la Homaĵo - La Homa Epoko ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/eo/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 09:57:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/eo/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transskribo ﻿Homo ekzistas dum milionoj da jaroj, kiel parto de naturo.
Sed tiam, io ŝanĝiĝis. Kaj dum ege mallonga kvanto de tempo,
ni teroformigis ĉi tiun planedon kaj desegnis ĝin por taŭgi niajn bezonojn.
Laŭ nia scio, ni estas la unuaj estaĵoj vekiĝi kaj tute transpreni planedon.
La transiĝo de ĉasado kaj kolektado, al farmado kaj konstruado, estis tiom senspirige rapida, ke multe da niaj manieroj de pensi pri la mondo ne plu estas utilaj.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Inimajandus uus ajalugu - Inimajastu ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/et/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 09:37:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/et/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkriptsioon ﻿Inimesed on olnud looduse osa miljoneid aastaid.
Aga siis muutus midagi ja uskumatult lühikese ajaga
kujundasime selle planeedi ümber
ja kohandasime selle oma vajadustega.
Meile teadaolevalt oleme esimesed ärganud ja planeedi täielikult üle võtnud olendid.
Üleminek küttimiselt ja koriluselt põllundusele ja ehitamisele
oli nii hingematvalt kiire, et paljude meie arusaamadega maailma asjadest ei ole enam midagi peale hakata.
Üks meie kõige aegunumatest ideedest seisneb selles, et meie kõige enamkasutatavam kalender</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Нова історія для людства - Ера людини ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/uk/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 09:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/uk/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Відео Транскрипція ﻿Мільйони років люди існували як частина природи.
Але потім щось змінилося. І за неймовірно короткий проміжок часу
Ми змінили лице цієї планети та пристосували її до наших потреб.
Наскільки нам відомо, ми є першими створіннями, які пробудилися та повністю заволоділи планетою.
Перехід від мисливства й збирання до землеробства та будівництва був настільки вражаюче швидким, що ми більше не можемо покладатись на наші уявлення про світ.
Одне з найбільш застарілих уявлень у тому, що за найрозповсюдженішим календарем світу ми нібито живемо у 2016 році.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>En ny historie for menneskeheden - Menneskeæraen ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/da/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 08:54:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/da/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transskription ﻿Mennesker har eksisteret i millioner af år som en del af naturen.
Men så ændrede noget sig. Og i et utroligt kort tidsrum,
terraformerede vi denne planet, og designede den til at passe til vores behov. Så vidt vi ved, er vi de første skabninger til at vågne og helt overtage en planet.
Overgangen fra jagt og samling til landbrug og byggeri var så ubeskrivelig hurtig,
at mange af de måder, vi ser verden på, ikke længere er nyttige.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Nowa Historia Dla Ludzkości - Era Człowieka ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/pl/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 08:44:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/pl/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkrypcja ﻿Ludzie istnieli przez miliony lat jako część przyrody
lecz wtedy coś się zmieniło i w niezwykle krótkim okresie czasu
zmieniliśmy tę planetę i dostosowaliśmy ją do naszych potrzeb.
Z tego co nam wiadomo, jesteśmy jedynymi istotami, które &amp;ldquo;przebudziły się&amp;rdquo; i całkowicie zdominowały swoją planetę.
Przejście z łowiectwa i zbieractwa do rolnictwa i budownictwa nadeszło tak szybko,
że wiele sposobów myślenia o tym świecie okazuje się nieprzydatne
Jednym z naszych najmniej aktualnych pomysłów jest fakt, że według najczęściej używanego kalendarza żyjemy w roku 2016.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>En ny historia för mänskligheten - Människans era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/sv/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 08:36:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/sv/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkription ﻿Människor har funnits i miljontals år
som en del av naturen.
Men plötsligt ändrades något
och på väldigt kort tid terraformade vi planeten
och utformade den för att passa våra behov.
Så vitt vi vet är vi de första varelserna som totalt har tagit över en planet.
Övergången från jägare-samlare till jordbruk och byggande
var så otroligt snabb att många av våra tankesätt inte längre är användbara.
En av våra mest utdaterade idéer är att den mest använda kalendern idag insisterar att vi lever i år 2016.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Een nieuwe geschiedenis voor de mensheid - Het tijdperk van de Mens ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/nl/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 08:19:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/nl/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcriptie ﻿De mensheid bestaat al voor miljoenen jaren als een onderdeel van de natuur.
Maar toen veranderde iets. En in een heel erg korte tijd,
hebben we deze planeet geterraformeerd en ontworpen om onze benodigdheden te voldoen.
Voor hoever wij weten zijn wij het eerste ras die compleet zijn eigen planeet heeft overgenomen.
De verandering van jagen en bijeenkomen naar landbouw en bouwen, was zo adembenemend snel dat veel van onze manieren om over de wereld te denken niet langer van toepassing waren.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>ประวัติศาสตร์ใหม่สำหรับมนุษย์ชาติ - ศักราชมนุษย์ ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/th/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 06:43:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/th/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>วิดีโอ สรุป ﻿มนุษย์มีชีวิตอยู่มานานนับล้านปี เป็นส่วนหนึ่งของธรรมชาติ
แต่แล้วเกิดการเปลี่ยนแปลง และในเวลาที่สั้นอย่างไม่น่าเชื่อ
เราปรับโลกใบนี้และออกแบบ เพื่อให้พอดีกับความต้องการของเรา
เท่าที่เรารู้ เรากำลังเป็นพวกแรกที่ตื่นรู้ และครองโลกอย่างสมบูรณ์
การเปลี่ยนแปลงจากการล่าสัตว์ และเกิดชุมชนเพื่อการเกษตรและสร้างบ้าน ก็เป็นไปอย่างรวดเร็ว
จนหลายอย่างที่เคยคิดเอาไว้เกี่ยวกับโลกนี้ ใช้ไม่ได้แล้ว
หนึ่งในความคิดที่ล้าสมัยที่สุดของเราคือ ปฏิทินที่ใช้มากที่สุดในโลกยืนยันว่าเรามีชีวิตอยู่ในปี 2016
มุมมองนี้บิดเบือนประวัติศาสตร์ของเราเอง และทำให้มันยากที่จะเข้าใจว่าเราเป็นใคร
และที่เรามาได้ไกลแค่ไหน ในเวลาที่สั้นอย่างไม่น่าเชื่อ
บางทีมันอาจจะถึงเวลาที่จะเลือกปีที่ 0 สำหรับมนุษยชาติ
ปี 0 ที่แท้จริงหมายถึงเราเป็นสายพันธุ์และรวมถึงทุกวัฒนธรรม
ปี 0 คือจุดที่เราเริ่มสร้างโลกใหม่ของเราทับโลกใบเก่า
12,000 ปีที่ผ่านมา มนุษย์หลายร้อยมารวมกัน อยู่ในภูเขาทางตอนใต้ของอนาโตเลีย
พวกเขาล่าสัตว์และเก็บของป่า ไม่มีความรู้ การเกษตรหรือการใช้โลหะ
ทั้งหมดที่พวกเขามีอยู่ คือ เครื่องมือที่ทำจากหินและไม้
แต่พวกเขาสร้างความเป็นมนุษย์อย่างแรก โครงการก่อสร้างขนาดใหญ่
7,000 ปีก่อนที่ปิรามิดที่ถูกสร้างขึ้นในอียิปต์
วงของเสาหินขนาดใหญ่ที่บรรพบุรุษของเราสร้างขึ้น กินเนื้อที่กว่า 300 เมตร
แต่ละอัน สูงถึง 6 เมตร และน้ำหนัก 40 ตัน
การตกแต่งด้วยศิลปะรูปสัญลักษณ์ และแกะสลักหินรูปสัตว์และสัตว์ในตำนาน
เราคิดไม่ออกว่า พวกเขาสามารถที่จะทำเช่นนี้
มันอาจจะเป็นโครงการขนาดใหญ่สำหรับยุคหิน ซึ่งต้องใช้ระดับงานแบบองค์กร เราไม่อาจรู้ได้
ว่ามนุษย์เริ่มแรกมีความสามารถนี้ จนเรามาพบสถานที่นี้
ดังนั้น ทำไมพวกเขาสร้างมัน?
ทฤษฎีที่นิยมมากที่สุด คือ นี้เป็นวัดแรกของมนุษยชาติที่อุทิศแด่พระเจ้าที่ถูกลืมมานาน</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Нова историја за човечанство - Ера човека ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/sr-cyrl/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 06:42:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/sr-cyrl/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Видео Транскрипт ﻿Људи постоје, као део природе, милионима година.
Али се онда нешто променило. И за невероватно кратко време
смо тераформитрали планету и дизајнирали је да одговара нашим потребама.
Колико знамо, ми смо прва бића која су пробудила и комплетно освојила планету.
Транзиција од лова и сакупљања до земљорадње и изградње је била толико брза,
да многи од наших погледа на свет више нам нису корисни
Једна од наших најзастарелијих идеја је та да, најчешће коришћени календар на планети</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>İnsanlıq Üçün Yeni Tarix - İnsanlıq Erası ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/az/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 05:42:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/az/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkriptlər ﻿İnsanlar təbiətin bir hissəsi olaraq milyonlarla ildir yaşayırlar.
Amma bəzi şeylər dəyişib.
və inanılmaz dərəcədə qısa bir müddətdə
planeti dəyişib, ehtiyaclarımızı ödəməsi üçün dizayn etmişik.
Bildiyimiz kimi, oyanaraq planeti ələ keçirən ilk canlılarıq.
Ovçuluq və yığıçılıqdan əkinçilik və quruculuğa keçid o qədər tez oldu ki,
bir çoxumuzun dünya haqda düşüncələri artıq yararlı deyil.
Ən köhnəlmiş fikirlərimizdən biri
ən çox istifadə olunan təqvimə görə 2016-cı ildə yaşamağımızdır.
Bu tariximiz haqda olan düşüncələrimizi təhrif edib, bizim irq olaraq kim olduğumuzu və</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Нова история за човечеството - Ерата на Човека ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/bg/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 05:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/bg/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Видео Транскрипция ﻿Хората са съществували милиони години като част от природата.
Но нещо се е променило. И за невероятно кратък период
сме изменили планетата, така че да подхожда на нуждите ни.
Доколкото знаем, сме първите същества, завладели напълно цяла планета.
Преминали сме от лов и събирачество към земеделие и строителство толкова бързо, че много от идеите ни за света вече не са полезни.
Една от най-остарелите ни идеи, е че най-широко разпространения календар в света гласи, че живеем в 2016-та година.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>인류를 위한 새 역사 - 인류대 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ko/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 04:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ko/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>비디오 대본 ﻿인류는 수 백만년 동안 자연의 일부로서 존재해 왔습니다. 하지만 그 이후, 무언가가 변했습니다. 믿기지 않을 만큼 짧은 시간동안 우리는 이 행성을 변화시</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Une Nouvelle Histoire pour l&#39;Humanité – L&#39;Ère Humaine ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/fr/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 03:57:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/fr/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Vidéo Transcription ﻿Les humains ont existé dans la nature durant des millions d&amp;rsquo;années.
Mais ensuite, quelque chose a changé.
Et dans un laps de temps incroyablement court,
nous avons terraformé cette planète et l&amp;rsquo;avons modifiée pour répondre à nos besoins.
Pour autant que nous sachions, nous sommes les seuls êtres à nous réveiller et prendre le contrôle d&amp;rsquo;une planète entière.
La transition de chasse et cueillette à agriculture et construction fut si incroyablement rapide</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Sejarah Baru untuk Kemanusiaan - Era Manusia ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/id/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 03:34:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/id/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripsi ﻿Manusia telah ada selama jutaan tahun, sebagai bagian dari alam.
Tapi kemudian, sesuatu berubah. Dan dalam jumlah yang sangat singkat,
&amp;hellip;kita mengubah planet ini dan dirancang agar sesuai dengan kebutuhan kita.
Sejauh yang kita tahu, kita adalah makhluk pertama untuk membangkitkan dan benar-benar mengambil alih planet.
Peralihan dari berburu dan mengumpulkan, menuju pertanian dan membangun, begitu cepat, sehingga banyak dari cara kita berpikir tentang dunia yang tidak lagi berguna.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Một Lịch sử Mới cho Nhân Loại - Thời đại Nhân Loại ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/vi/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 03:18:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/vi/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Bản trích ﻿Loài người đã tồn tại hàng triệu năm như là một phần của tự nhiên.
Nhưng bỗng dưng có thứ gì đó đã thay đổi, và nó chỉ xảy ra trong chớp nhoáng.
Chúng ta đã khai phá hành tinh này và thiết kế lại nó để đáp ứng những nhu cầu của chúng ta.
Cho tới hiện tại, chúng ta là sinh vật duy nhất thức tỉnh và chiếm lấy hoàn toàn hành tinh này.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 03:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Humans have existed for millions of years, as part of nature.
But then, something changed. And in an incredibly short amount of time..
..We terraformed this planet and designed it to fit our needs.
As far as we know, we&amp;rsquo;re the first beings to awaken and completely take over a planet.
The transition from hunting and gathering to farming and building, was so breathtakingly fast,
that many of our ways of thinking about the world are no longer useful.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Ein neues Zeitalter der Menschheit – Die menschliche Ära ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/de/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 03:04:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/de/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkript ﻿Menschen existieren jetzt seit Millionen von Jahren, als ein Teil der Natur, &amp;hellip;
&amp;hellip; doch dann hat sich etwas geändert &amp;hellip;
&amp;hellip; und in einer unglaublich kurzen Zeit haben wir diesen Planeten umgebaut, sodass er unseren Bedürfnissen entspricht.
Soweit wir wissen, sind wir die ersten Wesen, die einen Planeten komplett übernommen haben.
Der Übergang vom Jagen und Sammeln zur Landwirtschaft und Baukunst &amp;hellip;
&amp;hellip; war so unglaublich schnell, dass viele Wege über unsere Welt zu denken nicht länger von Nutzen sind.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Isang Bagong Kasaysayan para sa Sangkatauhan - Ang Panahon ng Tao ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/tl/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 02:37:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/tl/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripsyong ﻿Ang mga tao ay nagsimula noong milyong taong nagdaraan, bilang parte ng kapaligiran.
Pero noong panahon na iyon, may nag-iba. At sa isang sobrang madaling panahon&amp;hellip;
..binago natin ang mundong ito at dinisenyo ito upang magkasya ang aming mga pangangailangan.
Bilang malayo bilang alam namin, tayo ay ang unang nilalang na at ganap na kumuha ng higit sa isang planeta.
Ang paglipat mula sa pangangaso at pagtitipon sa pagsasaka at gusali, ay saksakan ng bilis,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Nová historie pro lidstvo - Éra lidstva ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/cs/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 01:27:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/cs/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripce ﻿Lidé existovali miliony let jako část přírody.
Ale pak se něco změnilo.
A ve velmi krátkém čase jsme planetu přeměnili tak, aby vyhovovala našim potřebám.
Pokud víme, jsme první bytosti, které probudily a úplně ovládly planetu.
Přechod od lovu a sběru k zemědělství a stavebnictví byl tak dechberoucí a rychlý,
že mnohé způsoby, kterými přemýšlíme o světě, už dnes nejsou užitečné.
Jedním z našich nejvíce zastaralých nápadů je, že nejpoužívanější kalendář světa tvrdí, že žijeme v roce&amp;hellip;</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Una Nuova Storia per l&#39;Umanità – L&#39;Era Umana – Il Primo Calendario 12.017 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/it/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 01:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/it/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Trascrizione ﻿L&amp;rsquo;uomo è esistito per milioni di anni, come parte della natura,
ma poi, qualcosa è cambiato
e in un tempo incredibilmente breve, abbiamo terraformato questo pianeta
e l&amp;rsquo;abbiamo progettato per soddisfare le nostre esigenze.
Per quanto ne sappiamo, siamo i primi esseri ad esserci risvegliati e ad aver preso il controllo completo di un pianeta.
Il passaggio da caccia e raccolta ad agricoltura e costruzioni, è stato così sorprendentemente veloce</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>মানবতার জন্য একটি নতুন ইতিহাস - মানব যুগ। ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/bn/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 00:19:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/bn/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>ভিডিও ট্রান্সক্রিপ্ট ﻿মানুষ প্রকৃতির অংশ হিসাবে, কোটি কোটি বছর ধরে টিকে আছে.
কিন্তু তারপর, কিছু পরিবর্তন. এবং সময় একটি অবিশ্বাস্যভাবে স্বল্প পরিমাণ
আমরা এই গ্রহের terraformed এবং আমাদের চাহিদা মাপসই এটা পরিকল্পিত.
যতদুর আমরা জানি, আমরা প্রথম মানুষ জাগ্রত এবং সম্পূর্ণরূপে একটি গ্রহের উপর নিতে যাচ্ছেন
ট্রানজিশন শিকার ও জমায়েত থেকে, চাষাবাদ এবং ভবন, তাই breathtakingly দ্রুত যে বিশ্বের সম্পরকে আমাদের উপায়ে অনেক লোক আর দরকারী ছিল.
আমাদের সবচেয়ে সেকেলে ধারণা এক বিশ্বের মধ্যে সবচেয়ে বেশি ব্যবহৃত ক্যালেন্ডারের যে জোরাজুরি যে আমরা 2016 বছরের মধ্যে বাস</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Nová história pre ľudstvo - Ľudská éra. ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/sk/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 00:08:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/sk/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Prepis ﻿Ľudia existujú už milióny rokov
ako súčasť prírody.
Ale potom sa niečo zmenilo
a v neuveriteľne krátkom čase
sme premenili túto planétu
a nadizajnovali ju aby odpovedala našim potrebám.
Zatiaľ podľa toho čo vieme sme prvé bytosti ktoré sa prebudili a úplne osídlili planétu
Zmena od lovu a zberu k farmárčeniu a stavaniu bola tak neuveriteľne rýchla, že
veľa našich myšlienok o svete sú už nepoužiteľné
Jedna z našich najzastaralejších myšlienok</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Μία Καινούρια Ιστορία για την Ανθρωπότητα - Η Εποχή των Ανθρώπων ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/el/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 00:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/el/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Βίντεο Αποσπάσματα ﻿Οἱ ἄνθρωποι ὑπάρχουν ἐδῶ καὶ ἐκατομμύρια ἔτη, ὡς μέρος τῆς φύσεως.
Ἀλλὰ μετά, κάτι ἄλλαξε. Καὶ σὲ ἕνα πολὺ μικρὸ χρονικὸ διάστημα,
γαιοποιήσαμε αὐτὸν τὸν πλανήτη καὶ τὸν σχεδιάσαμε σύμφωνα μὲ τὶς ἀνάγκες μὰς.
Ἀπὸ ὅσο γνωρίζουμε, εἴμαστε τὸ πρῶτο εἴδος ποὺ ἀφυπνίστηκε καὶ κατέλαβε ἐντελῶς ἕναν πλανήτη.
Ἡ μετάβαση ἀπὸ τὸ κυνῆγι καὶ τὴν συλλογὴ τροφῆς, στὴν γεωργία καὶ τὴν δόμηση, ἦταν τόσο τρομακτικὰ
γρήγορη, ὥστε ὁ τρόπος ποὺ σκεπτόμαστε γιὰ κάποια πράγματα δὲν εἶναι πλέον χρήσιμος.</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
