<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Conversations on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/conversations/</link><description>Recent content in Conversations on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/conversations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Best of 2023 - Dean Laws | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380001/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dean Laws was in his 50s when doctors told him he had Parkinson's disease. For a time, he was devastated. Then he formed a running crew with his friends called 'The Dean Team', and made a plan to run the Sydney Marathon
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2023 - Karin Bäumler | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Some years ago, Karin Bäumler found herself in a fight for her life after being diagnosed with ovarian cancer. In the thick of it all, making music was a refuge
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2023 - Amar Singh | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amar Singh's sense of belonging to Australia has only grown since he leant into his Sikh faith, growing out his beard and his hair, wearing a turban and committing himself to the service of his entire community
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2023 - Danny Estrin | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Voyager frontman Danny Estrin on his unconventional path from heavy metal to law and the Eurovision grand final Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2023 - Deb Wallace | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former top Detective Deb Wallace with ingenious and surprising stories from her working life smashing criminal gangs in Sydney
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sandy Mackinnon's never-ending adventures aboard Jack de Crow | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380006/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380006/</guid><description>Podcast Description For 25 years Sandy wondered what became of the little yellow dinghy he left in Romania, after a months-long voyage from the UK. Could it still be waiting for him the marshes of the Danube Delta, ready for another adventure?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Melissa Lucashenko and the story of Edenglassie | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Melissa Lucashenko was a motorcycle detailer, a house painter, a prison advocate, and a game show contestant before finding her way as a writer
Transcript</description></item><item><title>William McInnes and his favourite Australianisms | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380008/</guid><description>Podcast Description The actor and author thinks that nowhere in the world is the English language more poetic, colourful and persuasive than here in Australia
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Piecrust promises and broken hearts | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alecia Simmonds with tales from a time in Australia's legal history when the jilted and broken-hearted could sue for redress in the courts Transcript</description></item><item><title>The truth about Pax Romana | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Holland on the glories, bloodshed and barbarianism of the golden days of the Roman Empire
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lee Miller: surrealist photographer, war correspondent, and gourmet chef | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380011/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Antony Penrose grew up knowing little about his remarkable mother Lee Miller, who had studied with Man Ray in Paris, and become a model, a photographer, and a war correspondent. But then an unexpected find in the family attic changed everything
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lucy's button shop | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lucy Godoroja deals in the business of buttons, and the stories each button carries with it from Bohemia, or Milan to her shop in Sydney, and then into the hands of passers-by
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hayley's morbid curiosity | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380013/</guid><description>Podcast Description British-Australian journalist Hayley Campbell uncovers the secret society of the western world's death industry, run by people who have made death their life's work. CW: contains discussions of death and descriptions of dead bodies
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Pentridge Prison, Australia's bluestone hell | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Writer and journalist James Phelps takes you inside the bluestone walls and medieval-looking turrets of Australia's most infamous jail
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jon Owen's radical love | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jon Owen on how he chose a life of 'intentional downward mobility' to help addicts, sex workers, and the homeless, from Calcutta to Mount Druitt to the Wayside Chapel
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Catherine Martin: making Elvis and loving Baz | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380016/</guid><description>Podcast Description How a fashion-loving misfit from Sydney took over Hollywood with husband Baz Luhrmann, winning more Oscars than any other Australian (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The ladder out of depression with psychiatrist Ian Hickie | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Professor Ian Hickie has spent decades trying to understand clinical depression. Where does it come from? What role do genes play? And most importantly – what works to release its chokehold?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Prepared for anything | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brendan Watson took his Scouts promise very seriously as a young boy. He's leaned in to his pledge in some very unexpected ways, from Moscow to Mongolia and through temporary blindness back home again
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The rise of the Super Bilby | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ecologist Katherine Moseby is helping Australia's bilbies, quolls, and stick-nest rats evolve to become tougher, faster and stronger, so they can survive the looming threat of more than 2 million feral cats (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mick and Juana: a love story | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mick O'Regan met his feisty, brilliant wife Jo for the first time on a work brigade in Nicaragua. They fell in love and had a beautiful baby boy. Then quite unexpectedly, when Jo was in her 50s, Mick became her carer
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Wily cockatoos, bin chickens and spangled drongos | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380021/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Darryl Jones on the dramatic lives of Australia's city-dwelling native birds Transcript</description></item><item><title>How David got his sea legs | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380022/</guid><description>Podcast Description When David Hannan was a young man, he fled university and took a detour to the wild coral coast of WA where he became a lobster fisherman, before earning an Emmy for his underwater cinematography
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kylie Moore-Gilbert's freedom fight | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kylie Moore-Gilbert spent two years inside the Iranian prison system, secretly communicating with fellow women prisoners while she waited for news from Australia
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Richard Flanagan's chain of events | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380024/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Richard Flanagan was forever changed as a young man, when he was trapped for hours and almost drowned in an isolated stretch of river on Tasmania's wild west coast
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ariadne and the Minotaur | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Writer Kate Forsyth on how revisiting the story of a mythic Minotaur lurking in a labyrinth in Crete helped her realise that we all need monsters (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Running from the FBI: life in The Weather Underground | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380026/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Zayd Dohrn’s parents were militant left-wing revolutionaries, and he was born while they were living underground, fugitives from the FBI (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Killer sponges of the vasty deep | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr Merrick Ekins is Australia's leading expert in carnivorous sea sponges. Some sponges are secret killers, others are made up of glass and imprison tiny shrimp-like lovers for eternity, and others make love to themselves to reproduce
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bruce Englefield's devilish charm | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380028/</guid><description>Podcast Description On a whim, Bruce Englefield bought a wildlife park in Tasmania and moved from across the other side of the world to make life better for Tasmanian Devils
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sandi Toksvig and the school of life | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380029/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380029/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Danish-British author and comedian on her father's laissez faire attitude to school, and how this opened her mind and brought her to NASA's mission control room for the moon landing of 1969
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Stephen sang himself to life | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380030/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380030/</guid><description>Podcast Description From homeless teen to operatic stardom: how a job at the David Jones food hall changed the trajectory of Stephen Smith's life
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Shanelle Dawson: the daughter's story | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380031/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380031/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2018, Shanelle Dawson's family were the subject of a hit true crime podcast which helped convict her father Chris Dawson of her mother's murder. Now she's reclaiming her own story and the story of her mother Lynette Transcript</description></item><item><title>Pip Williams: from dyslexia to the Dictionary of Lost Words | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380032/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pip Williams was diagnosed with dyslexia as a teenager. She grew up to write a novel inspired by the history of the Oxford Dictionary, which soon became an international bestseller
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Penny Moodie's compulsive and compelling life | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380033/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Penny grew up consumed by catastrophic thoughts and developed habits to try to ward off impending doom. It turned out she had been living with obsessive compulsive disorder for 30 years
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The hunt for deep sea bioluminescence (and a giant squid) | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380034/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marine biologist Dr Edith Widder was inside a submersible searching for bioluminescence in the ocean depths when she saw a giant squid as big as a two story house (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The speech collector | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380035/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tony Wilson was always drawn to the world's great speeches. Then, without warning, he was called on to make the most difficult speech of his life (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Champion surfer Jodie Cooper on the breaks that made her | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380036/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380036/</guid><description>Podcast Description How Jodie went from skateboarding in her home town of Albany to become a world surfing champion, frothing all the way
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Penny's odyssey to Greece and family | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380037/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380037/</guid><description>Podcast Description An unexpected DNA test result sent Penny Mackieson on a mission across the other side of the world, to find her real natural mother, and discover her identity
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The caving time lord | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380038/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr Kira Westaway is a geochronologist who places modern and ancient humans in context by dating things found in caves. For Kira, how we understand ourselves now is tied up in the past (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The lucky accident of Sydney's Opera House | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380039/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Helen Pitt on how the luminous shells of the Sydney Opera House nearly didn't get off the drawing board
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lovemore's left hook | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380040/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380040/</guid><description>Podcast Description A chance encounter led Lovemore Ndou into his local boxing gym, and a lucky left hook became his ticket out of apartheid South Africa
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Silverchair's drummer grows up | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380041/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ben Gillies was a 15 year old drummer when Silverchair became a global sensation. After almost two decades of being a rock star, the band broke up, and Ben began to face his own demons
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The psychopaths among us | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380042/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lawyer and author David Gillespie has been on a mission to understanding psychopaths after realising he might have worked with one
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The chef who changed the world | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josh Niland on his mission to cook with fish eyes, fish liver, and fish sperm to help revolutionise how we cook and eat fish
Transcript</description></item><item><title>David Marr's reckoning with his family's brutal past | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380044/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380044/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Marr with the story of his great-great-grandfather Reg Uhr, who led murderous expeditions with the Native Police during Queensland’s frontier wars CW: mentions the names of Aboriginal people who have died
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ancestors like aliens: clues from the Cambrian explosion | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380045/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Diego Garcia-Bellido is a palaeontologist who specialises in soft-bodied fossils from hundreds of millions of years ago. These perfectly preserved eyes, guts and nervous systems provide a window into the beginning of our own family tree, and into life on Mars.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Robyn Davidson, wandering spirit | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380046/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Robyn Davidson on her adventures high in the Himalayas, her love affair with an Indian prince, and her late in life reckoning with her own story (CW: mentions suicide)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jessica Cottis — inside the colour of sound | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380047/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jessica is an orchestral conductor, organ virtuoso and also a synesthete who 'sees' colour in her mind's eye (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Silk, sex, secrets and spiders | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380048/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380048/</guid><description>Podcast Description James O'Hanlon digs deep into the secret world of spiders; complex and tiny lives most of us are either unaware or afraid of
Transcript</description></item><item><title>From Antioch to Syracuse and Tyre | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380049/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Historian Katherine Pangonis with stories from five cities of the ancient world, from their splendour in antiquity to their comparatively modest twilight
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Confessions of a drama kid | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380050/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor and writer Brendan Cowell with tender and funny tales from his boyhood as a child actor and a budding playwright (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Suzie Miller: finder of ways | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380051/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Suzie Miller with stories from her free range St Kilda childhood, her drama-filled life as a lawyer, and the inspiration behind her play Prima Facie
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Meaghan's connections to family, town and country | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380052/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Meaghan Katrak Harris with stories from her life as a teenage mother and raising a multicultural family, and her working life as a social worker and an academic
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Xanthe Mallett on skeletons, forensics, crime and body farms | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380053/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Forensic scientist Dr Xanthe Mallett on her work analysing skeletal remains, investigating cases of wrongful conviction and studying the decomposition of the human body (CW: contains references to death and crime) Transcript</description></item><item><title>Seeing the world through a dog's eyes | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380054/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dog behaviourist Laura Vissaritis uses science and psychology to better understand what our dogs really are telling us
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dynasties and dynamism | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380055/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nicholas Jose was living in China in 1989, when the military was sent in to violently quell pro-democracy rallies in Tiananmen Square. He left Beijing the next day and returned to a changed city
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sam Neill's menagerie | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380056/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Neill is a winemaker, a cancer survivor and a father. He's also an actor, who's made more than 100 films
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Smuggled to Antarctica | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380057/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rachael Mead with the true story of Nel Law, who stowed away on a Danish ship in 1961 to become the first Australian woman to set foot on Antarctica Transcript</description></item><item><title>The echidna argument | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380058/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Strategic analyst Sam Roggeveen says Australia needs to think more like an echidna when it comes to defence Transcript</description></item><item><title>Living to 120 and beyond | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380059/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr David Sinclair is a longevity expert who believes ageing is a treatable disease (R) Transcript</description></item><item><title>What happens to us while we're under anaesthesia? | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380060/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kate Cole-Adams has discovered what happens to us while we dwell in the chemical oblivion of general anaesthetic (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chadden's planet Earth | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380061/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chadden Hunter was in his twenties when he found himself sitting around a campfire in the Ethiopian highlands, talking about his PhD thesis with Sir David Attenborough. The meeting changed his life Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bronwyn's books | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380062/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380062/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Bronwyn Sheehan's daughter befriended a little girl in year four, her eyes were opened up to the realities of life for children in care, and their carers
Transcript</description></item><item><title>George Megalogenis on the stats that tell the Australian story | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380063/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380063/</guid><description>Podcast Description From the 1944 wartime referendum, to the 1999 vote on whether to become a republic, referenda always tell us things about Australia that aren't revealed in a normal federal election
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Peter's long goodbye | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380064/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Broadcaster Peter Goers was in his twenties when his parents died suddenly, in a plane crash outside New Orleans. Decades later, he's beginning to make sense of the loss
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Stories of starting over: Susan Johnson | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380065/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Writer Susan Johnson began an unexpected adventure when she moved to the Greek island of Kythera with her 85-year old mother Barbara (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Stories of starting over: Kim Crotty | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380066/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380066/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Kim Crotty was locked up in Dartmoor prison for growing marijuana, his two young sons were bereft. After he began writing bedtime stories for his boys from his cell, a new chapter opened up for him after he was released from jail (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Stories of starting over: Anne Howell | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380067/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380067/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a serious brain operation, Anne Howell woke up in hospital with retrograde amnesia, thinking she was nine years old. With no real understanding of who she was or who she could trust, she set about rediscovering her identity (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Stories of starting over: Charles Lomu | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380068/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380068/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Tongan-Australian man on being privileged to see love in action in his grandparents, how a spiral into grief and anger led him to periodic detention, and how cutting hair today helps him steer young men away from a dark path (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Stories of starting over: DJ Hookie | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380069/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Nash was 19 when his limbs were amputated due to meningococcal septicaemia. After he began to navigate life with hooks for arms, he built a new life as a DJ (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Maggie Mackellar on farming, motherhood, and catching sheep | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380070/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Maggie Mackellar with stories from her life on a Merino wool farm on the east coast of Tasmania, and all of life and death that surrounds her through the cycle of lambing seasons
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Big Pineapple, The Big Merino, The Big Gumboot: how big things captured Australia | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380071/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr Amy Clarke on the history of Big Things and our enduring fondness for kitsch and curious creations
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Crispian Chan on Perth's forgotten terror | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380072/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Crispian Chan grew up in the shadow of a campaign of terror in Perth that engulfed his family restaurant and haunted him for years Transcript</description></item><item><title>Geraldine Brooks and the world in words | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380073/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380073/</guid><description>Podcast Description The historical novelist has seen enough action to last a lifetime from her days as a Middle East correspondent, and it was her mother's imaginative influence that led her to turn her fascination with history into new interpretations (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Craig Hamilton's three lives | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380074/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Coalminer turned broadcaster Craig Hamilton was in his 30s when he had a psychotic episode on Broadmeadows train station. In the aftermath, his life was completely changed (CW: mentions suicide)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Robert Waldinger's good life | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380075/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr Robert Waldinger on what it takes to live a happy life Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bertie Blackman's bohemian childhood | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380076/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bertie Blackman on her unconventional childhood with her father the artist Charles Blackman
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Julie became Matilda #1 | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380077/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380077/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1979, Julie Dolan was named as the inaugural captain of the Matildas. Ever since, she's helped build the juggernaut from the ground up
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kim and the Constitution | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380078/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kim Rubenstein on the inner workings and history of the Australian constitution
Transcript</description></item><item><title>John Gaden's golden run | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380079/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380079/</guid><description>Podcast Description John Gaden on turning his back on law and landing on the stage
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Remembering Michael Parkinson | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380080/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Broadcaster Michael Parkinson with the life story of his late father John William - Yorkshireman, miner, humourist and fast bowler (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Maddy, the shipwreck mermaid | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380081/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr Maddy McAllister's job as a marine archaeologist involves diving into the deep to uncover the artefacts and human stories sunk in shipwrecks (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The invisible Mrs Orwell | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380082/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anna Funder on unearthing the story of the talented and determined Eileen O'Shaughnessy, George Orwell's first wife
Transcript</description></item><item><title>From the meatworks to mending men's souls | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380083/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 13:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380083/</guid><description>Podcast Description After arriving in Australia from Yugoslavia as a boy, Peter Stojanovic began working at a Melbourne meatworks. Decades on, he's now a counsellor helping violent men change their behaviour
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jana Pittman's turning point | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380084/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jana Pittman became one of Australia's most famous athletes as a young woman. Then at age 30, she found herself at a painful crossroads
Transcript</description></item><item><title>David the Seahorse saviour | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380085/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380085/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Harasti with the story of how he opened a chain of underwater seahorse hotels to save an endangered species
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Heart in Two Places | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380086/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 11:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sarah Donnelley on her life working at Wilcannia Central School, on Barkandji Country 950 kilometres west of Sydney (R) Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr Freakman, hippie psychiatrist | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380087/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 13:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Psychiatrist Dr Harry Freeman on the memorable patients, LSD, and medical epiphanies from his 50 years in psychiatry Transcript</description></item><item><title>The sculptor's son | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380088/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hung Le and his family made a terrifying escape from Saigon in 1975, carrying one suitcase, a box of biscuits and some seasick pills. Decades after they fled, Hung returned to Vietnam to honour his late father's wishes (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Brendan Watkins claimed his birthright | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380089/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brendan Watkins on his search to find the truth about his birth parents and the failings of the Catholic church his discoveries unveiled
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mark Brandi on compassion, chance and reinvention | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380090/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Author Mark Brandi is a keen observer of people, a skill he honed growing up in a pub in country Victoria, where the family’s Italian heritage was the source of scrutiny
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Danny Estrin's Eurovision glory | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380091/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Voyager frontman Danny Estrin on his unconventional path from heavy metal to law and the Eurovision grand final Transcript</description></item><item><title>Oliver Twist, the storyteller | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380092/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rwandan-born comedian and playwright Oliver Twist on his years as a refugee and how his life as a storyteller began
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The leadership and gentleness of Alex Blackwell | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380093/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380093/</guid><description>Podcast Description The former captain of the Australian Women's cricket team shares what she's learned along the way, and how cricket has helped her in genetic counselling, her next career (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>On the trail of the mega-shark | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380094/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380094/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Tim Flannery was a boy he found a palm-sized fossilised tooth of a prehistoric shark.The find changed the course of his life
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Toby Walsh: the power and perils of Chat GPT | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380095/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Professor Toby Walsh on the rise of generative AI chatbots and their potential to overtake human intelligence
Transcript</description></item><item><title>John's wild dogs | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380096/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380096/</guid><description>Podcast Description They have strange coats that look like they're painted on, and while their big Mickey Mouse ears are cute, their domestic dog-like looks aren't particularly exotic. But Africa's painted dogs are unlike any other carnivores on the planet
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Martin Flanagan on exchanging shame for grace | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380097/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 13:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380097/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1966, Martin was 10 years old when he was sent to a Catholic Boarding school in North-West Tasmania. Decades later, he began his own reckoning with what had happened at the school (CW: discusses sexual abuse)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Healing the grieving heart | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wendy Liu has spent many years right up close to death. As a forensic counsellor she worked with families who had lost someone to an accident or violence, and as a grief counsellor she supports people surviving all kinds of losses. Wendy says her work brings her a keener appreciation of life
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Maggie Beer: from Bankstown to the Barossa | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380099/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Maggie Beer started her working life at the age of 14 in a chenille bedspread factory. Two decades later, in a pheasant farm in the Barossa Valley, she found her dream job
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Ben's brain changed | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380100/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380100/</guid><description>Podcast Description An unexpected stroke temporarily robbed Ben Mckelvey of his ability to speak, write and understand words. Eventually, Ben re-learnt the art of language, but his brain, his identity and how he connected to others had changed forever
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The army town, the lodger, and a succulent Chinese meal | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380101/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Writer Mark Dapin’s childhood was disrupted at the age of 10, when his mum fell in love with the lodger. He was then raised in an army town called Aldershot in the UK, which began his fascination with stories of crime and warfare
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Anna McGahan and God | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380102/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anna McGahan was playing a sex worker on Australia's biggest television show when she found God, renounced nudity on screen and tried to become the perfect Christian woman
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The story of the human voice | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380103/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380103/</guid><description>Podcast Description John Colapinto was singing a Beatles song in front of Bette Midler when he injured his vocal cords. The experience set him on the path to studying the human voice
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The wild boy who became a parenting expert | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380104/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Professor Mark Dadds has helped hundreds of troubled kids from his clinic at the University of Sydney. He feels an extra connection to them, as he was once a wild and rebellious boy himself
Transcript</description></item><item><title>From Boudicca to the Night Witches: a history of women at war | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380105/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sarah Percy with a new history of the world's frontline women soldiers
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Marcia Hines the American Queen of Australian Pop | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380106/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marcia Hines arrived in Australia just 16 years old, and unknowingly pregnant. She planned to stay for six months, but 50 years later, she still calls Australia home
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Bookbinder's Luck | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380107/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 12:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dominic Riley on how a a chance encounter with a bookbinding monk named Brother Bede changed the course of his life
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The power and determination of Nas Campanella | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380108/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nas Campanella grew up in a big Italian-Australian family, and she was six months old when she lost her sight. Nas then grew up to become one of Australia's most well-known TV and radio journalists Transcript</description></item><item><title>Frank’s years of living dangerously | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380109/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Frank Palmos arrived in Indonesia as a green journalist looking to make his mark. He walked straight into a pivotal moment in the nation's history, which would culminate in 'The Year of Living Dangerously'
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jessica's life in two worlds | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380110/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jessica Kirkness on her luminous childhood with her grandparents Melvyn and Phyllis, who were both profoundly deaf
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Stories from Gudanji Country | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380111/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Debra Dank walks and talks differently when she's at home on Gudanji country, because she comes with this place (R) Transcript</description></item><item><title>The tin hut that's still standing | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380112/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr John Paterson grew up in a tin hut in rural Darwin. He helped hold it down during Cyclone Tracy and has taken care of it so it still stands today. John learnt many lessons in that tin hut, which have followed him through life
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nova Peris shines bright | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380113/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nova is a woman of many firsts — an Olympic gold medallist and Northern Territory Senator. She continues to strive for excellence while showing up for mob (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Leanne's passion for justice | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380114/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Leanne Liddle was just 18 years old when she became a policewoman, but after a brutal attack during a routine traffic stop left her unable to serve, she decided to fight for justice in a different way
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jimmy Little's daughter tells her dad's story | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380115/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Frances Peters-Little speaks about writing the story of her dad Jimmy's extraordinary career in music, and how he never lost his connection to his country.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mama Piku | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380116/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380116/</guid><description>Podcast Description For more than a decade now, Yolarnie Amepou has been navigating tribal conflicts along the Kikori River to help protect her beloved pig-nosed turtle. To everyone in this part of Papua New Guinea, she's known as "turtle lady"
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sorcery and salvation in Papua New Guinea | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380117/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ruth Kissam was absent-mindedly perusing a noticeboard at a hospital in Papua New Guinea when she came across a flyer from the local morgue. That notice opened the door for Ruth into the world of sorcery and the plight of women accused of witchcraft
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The mythical legends of Dravuni Island | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380118/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380118/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Kaliopate Tavola retired from Fijian politics, he turned his attention to recording the fantastic stories of creation from his home island of Dravuni - tales of warlords, giant sea serpents and boats that could grow tall like a tree
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The whistling frogs of Fiji's forests | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380119/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nunia Thomas-Moko grew up afraid of the reptilian creatures that lurked in Fiji's stunning forests. Ironically, she has become the country's leading expert in rare frogs and crested iguanas. She had to put on a brave face to catch them first
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Meet the Queen of Vude | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380120/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380120/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Laisa Vulakoro was six years old she learnt the English words "famous" and "star". She would point to the night's sky on her tiny island, and tell its 300 residents that's where she was going
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Michael Trant on writing a farmer’s way | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380121/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Author Michael Trant combines his love of the land with his passion for storytelling — writing his books while ploughing the paddock in a tractor
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The broken-hearted cure | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380122/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380122/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a devastating divorce, Charlotte Ree began cooking her way out of heartbreak
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sarah Davis: Paddling the Nile and beyond | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380123/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sarah Davis on her journey from corporate risk management to the paddle-powered adventures in shark-infested waters
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The flying vet | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380124/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Campbell Costello has one of the world's largest and most exciting consulting rooms in the world, for his job as a vet in outback Queensland (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Fergus, prison visitor | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380125/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fergus Hynes found his true calling in retirement: listening to prisoners and helping them with their problems Transcript</description></item><item><title>Doctor Sonia, Outback GP | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380126/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380126/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Sonia Henry signed up to work as a GP in a remote mining town in the Pilbara, the experience changed almost everything she believed about Australia.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Shirley's secret and a silver angel: the story of Heather Mitchell | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380127/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Heather Mitchell on the family secrets and the fortune teller's prophecy which shaped her life (CW: mentions suicide and cancer)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>An unexpected life in Murderball | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380128/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cameron Carr was a rising star in Rugby League when a shocking accident changed everything. A few years later he found a new path, in a sport known as 'Murderball'
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Finding a dad, zoology and a life-threatening illness | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380129/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ben Bravery tells the story of his childhood in Logan, Queensland, how he went from a career at KFC to studying male satin bowerbirds and why being a patient led him to study medicine (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Fat Girl Dancing: Kris Kneen | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380130/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380130/</guid><description>Podcast Description How Kris Kneen learned to look unblinkingly at their fat body, and find a new courage to be in the world
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Muzafar Ali: from Afghanistan to Adelaide | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380131/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Muzafar Ali is a football-loving photographer from Afghanistan, now living in Australia. When he discovered the long history of Afghan cameleers in the outback, he set off, with his camera, to find out more
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Life as a prison philosopher | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380132/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andy West on how his family story led him a life teaching philosophy inside some of Britain's toughest jails
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Charmian, the violin and the zipper man | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380133/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Australian violinist Charmian Gadd was a wild musical prodigy from the Central Coast when a zipper-inventing musician changed the course of her life (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>William Sitwell: a history of the restaurant | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380134/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Food critic William Sitwell with stories of eating out in history, from the wine taverns of ancient Pompeii to today's molecular gastronomy
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sean Fong dominating life on the jiu-jitsu mat | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380135/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sean Fong is a para world champion in jiu-jitsu. The 'gentle' martial art has allowed Sean to shatter any illusions that society might have about people with physical differences.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Asma Khan and the Darjeeling Express | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380136/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chef Asma Khan uses cooking to connect with her family. After moving from Kolkata to England, she longed to return home to learn her mother's recipes. She did that, and brought them back to London, opening a restaurant called Darjeeling Express
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mandy Nolan: embracing the 'weird freaky girl' | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380137/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mandy Nolan didn't fit in as a child, in the country town where she grew up. But later in life, her differences became her superpower (CW: discusses domestic violence and addiction)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Deb Wallace became the gangbuster | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380138/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380138/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former Detective Deb Wallace with stories from her working life in the NSW Police, where she was tasked with breaking up criminal gangs
Transcript</description></item><item><title>David Rankin: Gymea, Art and Lily | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380139/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Artist David Rankin grew up as the son of a bootmaker in suburban Sydney. He became an outback teacher, then a a painter, before meeting the great love of his life, the writer Lily Brett
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lessons from slime mould — a brainless blob | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380140/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tanya Latty is an insect scientist with a quirky taste in pets, and a keen eye for detail. But it's the lessons from her brainless pet slime mould that she's most fascinated about
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Don Walker: the quiet bloke in Cold Chisel | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380141/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Don Walker has written some of Australia's greatest songs, and they keep coming. But rock and roll's resident 'quiet bloke' could have led a very different life
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Letting the tiger out of the cage | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380142/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adventurers and extreme athletes, who jump off bridges and walk across deserts, have a reputation for being fearless daredevils who take unnecessary risks. But sport psychologist Dr Eric Brymer says feeling fear is vital to the mind of the adventurer
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lessons from the Kingdom of Sargon | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380143/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Historian Peter Frankopan on how the earth's climate has shaped human history
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bo Seo on good arguments | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380144/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380144/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two-time World Debating champion Bo Seo on how love and listening can improve how we disagree Transcript</description></item><item><title>The wild ride of Di's life | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380145/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380145/</guid><description>Podcast Description The bull rider and horsewoman has lived a life full of danger and drama, at the rodeo and outside it. Di's incredible experiences have taught her to lean into fear, rather than avoid it
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The curious history of sweating it out | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380146/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380146/</guid><description>Podcast Description From the naked athletes of Ancient Greece to the Jane Fonda revolution of the last century, sport and exercise have had a surprising hold on humans
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hijacks, heists, and a sinking boat | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380147/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380147/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a young woman craving adventure, Marele Day hitchhiked on a catamaran sailing across the Indian Ocean. After befriending the French skipper, Marele discovered years later that he was a fugitive on the run.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Being Sharon Stone's stunt double | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380148/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ky Furneaux spent 16 years in Hollywood as a professional stunt performer, falling, fighting and breaking glass on cue. She has managed to make her next life even more extreme — surviving in the wild, sometimes with just a knife, often naked (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Love and Loss, in Watsonia | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380149/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Damian Callinan with the grand love story of his parents Adrian and Kathleen, who met in 1946 at a football match. They were together for 62 years before a terrible accident changed everything (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The art of English, according to Benjamin Dreyer | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380150/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Benjamin Dreyer has strong ideas about the English language, and how to transform books into the best possible versions of themselves. But he's not a member of the grammar police
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Theologian Pádraig Ó Tuama on making peace and living in poetry | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380151/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pádraig Ó Tuama survived conversion therapy and exorcism as a young gay man in a church in Ireland, then became a leading peace negotiator and a poet
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cows on a plane | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380152/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Paul McVerry is an experienced cattleman and a stud breeder, who had a vision to fly a gift of cattle to India with the help of Dan Murphy
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jenny Graves — the curious case of sex cells | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380153/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380153/</guid><description>Podcast Description For Jenny Graves, the genetic history of Australia's unique wildlife holds a key to the future of human evolution.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Benjamin's epic flight | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380154/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Benjamin is an adventure paraglider and documentary maker. One day, while paragliding in central Mexico, he was forced to make a sudden landing in an isolated valley.
There he encountered a vast swarm of millions of monarch butterflies, carpeting the forest floor and tree trunks.
This experience led him to replicate the Herculean migration of this seemingly common butterfly.
He launched his own flight along the thermal air currents which carried him all the way from Mexico to Canada.</description></item><item><title>Raising the Kanneh-Masons | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380155/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kadiatu Kanneh-Mason on what it takes to keep up with her seven children — all of them gifted classical musicians (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Paul Kennedy on finding his way | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380156/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380156/</guid><description>Podcast Description The ABC Sports presenter describes his life at 17, a year dominated by football, girls, beer, and a serial killer stalking his neighbourhood (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Toni Jordan's lucky life | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380157/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380157/</guid><description>Podcast Description Toni Jordan grew up working in a TAB and going to the greyhound races. Then she grew up to become a best-selling novelist
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Crossing the continent | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380158/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380158/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sophie Matterson fell in love with camels at first sniff. After working with them for years, she hatched a plan to walk across the vast Australian continent with five humped companions - Jude, Delilah, Charlie, Clayton and Mac
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dean Laws: running for his life | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380159/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dean Laws was in his 50s when doctors told him he had Parkinson's disease. For a time, he was devastated. Then he formed a running crew with his friends called 'The Dean Team', and made a plan to run the Sydney Marathon
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Remembering Barry Humphries | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380160/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380160/</guid><description>Podcast Description Barry Humphries was a legend of the screen and stage, but throughout his career, he remained astonished at the success of Dame Edna and her enduring appeal
Transcript</description></item><item><title>My father, Karratha, and me | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380161/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380161/</guid><description>Podcast Description Annette Trevitt with a tale of real estate, family and complicated grief set in the Pilbara mining town of Karratha
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Teddy Tahu Rhodes and the letter that changed his life | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380162/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380162/</guid><description>Podcast Description He's one of the world's most acclaimed opera stars, but Teddy Tahu Rhodes did everything he could, for a very long time, to avoid his destiny on stage (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Om's journey home | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380163/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Om Dhungel grew up in Bhutan, where his people became the target of a brutal ethnic cleansing campaign. Overnight Om became a refugee, eventually rebuilding his life and family in his beloved new home of Blacktown
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jackie Huggins: my father Jack | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380164/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380164/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jackie Huggins with the story of her father Jack, who was a surf lifesaver, a rugby league player, a soldier taken prisoner in the Fall of Singapore, and the first Indigenous Australian to work in the post office (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Surviving Sandakan | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380165/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Only six men, out of thousands, survived the horrors of the infamous Sandakan POW camp. Bill Sticpewich was one of them
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A sister's love | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380166/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380166/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Bronwen Edward's big brother Mark took his own life, she decided to channel her grief into something much bigger than herself
Transcript</description></item><item><title>On the wing | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380167/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Zoologist Milly Formby serendipitously became passionate about shorebirds while working as a tapestry weaver. She decided to learn how to fly, build her own plane and follow their path around Australia
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A work of the heart | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380168/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380168/</guid><description>Podcast Description High school English teacher, Brendan James Murray with funny, heartbreaking, inspirational and strange tales from his working life (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Danijel's life between borders | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380169/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Danijel Malbasa grew up in an ethnically-mixed family in the former Yugoslavia. When the country was on the precipice of war, the Malbasa family was metaphorically and literally torn apart
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The secrets and generosity of the dead | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380170/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Journalist Jackie Dent explores the the world of anatomists and dissectors, the people who open up human cadavers to uncover their secrets
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Maggie Dent - Raising Strong Girls | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380171/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380171/</guid><description>Podcast Description Parenting expert Maggie Dent on on how parents can raise confident and well-adjusted girls
Transcript</description></item><item><title>To Kythera, with my mother | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380172/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Writer Susan Johnson was in her 60s when she decided to make a new life on the Greek Island of Kythera, with her 85-year old mother Barbara along for the adventure Transcript</description></item><item><title>Matt Hall's life at supersonic speed | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380173/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380173/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matt Hall made his first solo flight at 15 years old and has been addicted to life in the air ever since. He became a top gun fighter pilot and after serving for more than 20 years, he still hasn't come down to earth
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Family folklore: spies, secrets and suffering | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380174/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380174/</guid><description>Podcast Description Phil Kafcaloudes grew up hearing stories about his legendary grandmother, who became a spy for the British in World War Two. It was even said she killed a man to protect her secret
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kate Forsyth on the intrepid and curious Charlotte Waring Atkinson | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380175/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380175/</guid><description>Podcast Description Charlotte was Australia's first children's author. She came to the colony of NSW from London in 1826, and now her trailblazing, tragic and dramatic life story has been written by her descendants, Kate Forsyth and Belinda Murrell (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What the world can learn from Charlie Brown | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380176/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380176/</guid><description>Podcast Description From Charlie Brown to Franz Kafka, psychoanalyst Josh Cohen explores why being a loser can be a good thing
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Billy Bragg — the boy from Barking | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380177/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380177/</guid><description>Podcast Description Billy Bragg grew up in working-class Barking, east of London.The expected path was to go from school to the local car factory, but Billy had his sights set further. After discovering punk as a teenager, Billy found a way to make his voice heard and even a brief stint in the army couldn’t keep him away from a life in music.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Gillian Bell — life and cake | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380178/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380178/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gillian has the best job in the world — travelling overseas to bake sumptuous and heartfelt wedding cakes, using foraged and fresh produce to tell a couple's story through taste, texture and fragrance. Cake has been a staple in Gillian's life, through immigration, adventure and loss (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>George Williams – the whacky world of micronations | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380179/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Micronations are home to fascinating, often eccentric characters who construct their self-declared countries in their own image, with pomp, pageantry and passports to boot.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Growing up in a country pub | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380180/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Beck had a wild, lively and at times devastating childhood, growing up in Bendigo's old Crown Hotel
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Becoming a cowboy | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380181/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Roland Breckwoldt fell in love with the idea of being a cowboy as a child, so at 15 he railed against his strict German father's wishes, left home and found himself in the majesty of the Queensland outback
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How memory works | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380182/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380182/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over her many decades as a practising psychiatrist, Veronica O'Keane developed a fascination for our memory, how it functions in the brain, and the role it has in shaping our identity
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The alluring aliens of our forests | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380183/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380183/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fungi have given us many gifts, from penicillin to food, but they can also be quite scary. Dr Alison Pouliot spends her time trying to explain these strange alien-like things
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Keenan's courage | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380184/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380184/</guid><description>Podcast Description Justice advocate Keenan Mundine broke the cycle of crime and incarceration in his own life after a chance meeting at a birthday party (CW: mentions suicide, references to drug use. Strong language. Discretion advised) (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Saul Griffith's electrifying mission | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380185/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380185/</guid><description>Podcast Description Saul Griffith believes that the key to solving the climate crisis is to electrify everything, starting with our homes. The inventor, engineer and entrepreneur is spearheading this mission in his own postcode with Electrify 2515, which aims to have all household machines powered by renewable energy
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A daughter's unswerving love — Sarah Holland-Batt and her father | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380186/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380186/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sarah Holland-Batt's dad Tony was a loving father, her intellectual mentor and her friend. At 18, she became one of his carers. Later she battled an aged care system which let him down in the worst way possible (R) Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lee Berger &amp; the Cave of Lost Hominids | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380187/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380187/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lee Berger, the National Geographic Explorer in Residence and real-life Indiana Jones, has found remarkable things underground. His discoveries are revolutionising what we understand about our own origins
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rockstar animals and the Orthodox Church | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380188/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380188/</guid><description>Podcast Description John Simons is fascinated by the lives of animals which have become stars. From a famous hippo at London Zoo, to a wombat owned by a Pre-Raphaelite painter in England, these are the rock stars of the animal world
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Briana, Max and Freddy: love, trains and mouth music | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380189/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380189/</guid><description>Podcast Description Briana Blackett was a journalist working in Qatar when she realised her baby son Max wasn't responding to his name. When Max was diagnosed with autism, and in time her second son Freddy was too, she left Doha to begin an entirely different life (R) Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Vietnam vet and the Arnhem Land community | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380190/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380190/</guid><description>Podcast Description Neville White was trying to heal from the trauma of the Vietnam War when he travelled out to a remote community in Arnhem Land called Donydji. Their stories became increasingly intertwined as he spent more and more time there
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Great Fire of Salonika | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380191/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380191/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gail Jones grew up in an old quarantine station, wondering about the soldiers who stayed there on their way home from WWI. Her new novel imagines life on the eastern front in 1917
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Alex and the tree-climbing lions | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380192/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380192/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex Braczkowski is a big cat exert and National Geographic explorer. For years he's been following a rare group of tree-climbing lions, including the charismatic, enigmatic, three-legged Jacob
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Louise Kennedy on Belfast, bombs and a disastrous pav | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380193/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380193/</guid><description>Podcast Description Writer Louise Kennedy spent her early childhood just outside of Belfast. It was the height of The Troubles and violence was ever-present. After that violence came too close to home, Louise’s family moved to the Republic of Ireland. After 3 decades working as a chef, a chance invitation to a writer's group lead to an unexpected new career.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Peter Garrett: rock and roll changemaker | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380194/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380194/</guid><description>Podcast Description Midnight Oil frontman Peter Garrett on his life in music, environmental action, and politics, and the end of The Oils. Transcript</description></item><item><title>Amar Singh's love for faith, family and country | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380195/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380195/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amar Singh's sense of belonging to Australia has only grown since he leant into his Sikh faith, growing out his beard and his hair, wearing a turban and committing himself to the service of his entire community
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Judith Heumann - disability warrior | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380196/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380196/</guid><description>Podcast Description One of the most influential disability rights activists in history tells her story of her fight for the right to receive an education, have a job, and just be human (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Putting lipstick on a great white shark | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380197/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380197/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rodney Fox was torn apart by a great white shark and it took 462 stitches to put him back together again. He was then instrumental in filming Jaws, the most terrifying shark film of all time. But over time, this salty seadog has become the apex predator's fiercest protector (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Esther Freud's unconventional family | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380198/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380198/</guid><description>Podcast Description Esther Freud has many famous men in her family, including psychoanalyst Sigmund Freud. But it is her mother's story which has left the greatest mark on the writer
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Fintan O'Toole: the evolution of modern Ireland | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380199/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380199/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fintan O’Toole grew up in an Ireland undergoing great change but before the country could move forward, it would have to deal with its sometimes dark past.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is there a cheating gene? | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380200/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380200/</guid><description>Podcast Description Once journalist and author Kate Legge recovered from the news her husband of 30 years was cheating on her, she uncovered four generations of infidelity through his family
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The fastest woman in the sky | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380201/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380201/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jess Johnston found skydiving after a tough few years, and while it might sound like a contradiction, plummeting towards the earth at 400 km/h saved her life
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Richie Ramone and the record shop | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380202/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380202/</guid><description>Podcast Description No, he's not 'that' Richie Ramone, but this Richie Ramone's passion for punk is just as fierce (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The 700-room nightmare | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380203/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380203/</guid><description>Podcast Description For a thousand years, Colditz Castle has existed in some form, perched on the edge of a cliff in eastern Germany. From a royal hunting lodge, to a madhouse, and then most famously as an inescapable prisoner of war camp during World War II
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The poker-playing cardiologist | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380204/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380204/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a child, before she escaped communist Hungary, Bo Remenyi had no ambitions. But when she got to Australia all of that changed. She's gone from cruising the casino floor as a high-stakes professional poker player, to saving the lives of children in remote Australia (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The forgotten children of the Empire | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380205/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380205/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Margaret Humphreys received a letter from Australia, she had no idea it would unearth a huge, heartless scheme that forcibly removed children from their homeland and sent them alone, isolated and confused to the other side of the world
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ben and the birth of Miss Ellaneous | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380206/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380206/</guid><description>Podcast Description Darwin's Ben Graetz on becoming one of Australia's best-known Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander Drag Queens (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>My mother, South Africa and me | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380207/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380207/</guid><description>Podcast Description Franceska Jordan with the story of her remarkable mother Isabella — a South African trade unionist and anti-apartheid activist who inspired her daughter to carry on her community work
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Judy's fight for Victoria's first safe injecting facility | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380208/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380208/</guid><description>Podcast Description Growing up in Wangaratta, Judy Ryan learned we all have a responsibility to look after each other. When she moved to inner-city Melbourne that meant caring for the injecting drug users dying in her neighbourhood
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mark and the rainbow connection | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380209/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380209/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mark Trevorrow on how the music of composers Anthony Newley and Paul Williams influenced the course of his life and began the evolution of his alter ego, Bob Downe (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mammal mania | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380210/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380210/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kris Helgen loves mammals and he's ventured to some dangerous, isolated places to find them. In fact, Kris has helped name and discover more than 100 magnificent mammals
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The vivacious Umberto Clerici | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380211/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380211/</guid><description>Podcast Description The new chief conductor of the Queensland Symphony Orchestra, on the chair of spikes that accompanied his early musical career, and why he doesn't tone down his Italianness in Australia
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Love and music | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380212/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380212/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two years ago, Karin Bäumler found herself in the fight for her life after being diagnosed with ovarian cancer. In the thick of it all, making music with her husband Robert Forster became her refuge
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Run-away memories: Anne's story of retrograde amnesia | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380213/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380213/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a serious brain operation, Anne Howell woke up in hospital with retrograde amnesia, thinking she was nine years old. With no real understanding of who she was or who she could trust, she set about rediscovering her identity
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The case of the unknown sailor | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380214/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380214/</guid><description>Podcast Description DNA expert Dr Jeremy Austin on his 14-year quest to help solve one of Australia's enduring military mysteries: the identity of the 'unknown sailor' (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The mystery of the travelling Taranaki panels | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380215/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380215/</guid><description>Podcast Description Taranaki descendent Rachel Buchanan with the story of priceless Maori artwork and their role in the ransom of a child, kidnapped by Italian gangsters
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nance, Ruby &amp; Nell: the women who changed Australian cricket | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380216/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380216/</guid><description>Podcast Description How women cricket players saved the "gentleman's" game and repaired diplomatic relations between England and Australia
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Teen mum Melissa Redsell proved everyone wrong | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380217/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380217/</guid><description>Podcast Description Melissa Redsell was 16 and in her last year of school when she found out she was pregnant. Although many people told her she'd 'ruined her life' she went on to prove everyone wrong
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bronnie and the jaws of life | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380218/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380218/</guid><description>Podcast Description Firie Bronnie Mackintosh is built from tough stuff - she attends emergencies to cut people out of crushed cars and rescue them from burning buildings. Her strength was forged in Rotorua, New Zealand, where she experienced a violent undercurrent and the first frothy coffees, introduced by her parents
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The boy with op shop fever | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380219/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380219/</guid><description>Podcast Description Writer Tony Birch with tales of his Fitzroy childhood including his grandmother Alma's 'op shop fever', his love for pine cones and blankets, and the macabre holiday he lived through when he was 5 years old (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Australia speaks to the world (and spies) | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380220/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380220/</guid><description>Podcast Description Listened to around the world by locals, spies and military officials, Radio Australia has long been rated by its hundreds of thousands of global listeners as more informative than the BBC World Service. So why don't we know anything about it?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr Koppe's new life | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380221/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380221/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hilton Koppe on how his life as a soccer-obsessed country GP changed forever when he became a patient himself
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deborah's fight for her wings | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380222/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380222/</guid><description>Podcast Description Deborah Lawrie had her first flying lesson at 16, then became a flying instructor herself. But when she applied for a job as a pilot, she found herself in the fight of her life (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Where the Music Began — a story collection | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380223/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380223/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vic Simms, Jen Cloher, Vika and Linda Bull, Rob Hirst, Elena Kats-Chernin, William Barton with stories from their formative years
Transcript</description></item><item><title>John Grisham: lawyering, writing and innocence | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380224/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380224/</guid><description>Podcast Description Novelist John Grisham with his life story; from his work as a trial lawyer, to writing, and how he became involved in a movement using DNA testing to exonerate the innocent (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Danielle, Jimmy the pig, and the inferno | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380225/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380225/</guid><description>Podcast Description Academic Danielle Celemajer on how the Black Summer bushfires brought she and her rescue pig Jimmy into a terrible proximity with the inferno, changing both of their lives forever
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Aunty Val became the 'Afar Angel' | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380226/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380226/</guid><description>Podcast Description Valerie Browning moved to the northern deserts of Ethiopia as a naive young nurse in 1973. A chance meeting on the streets of neighbouring Djibouti changed her life, and women's health in the region
Transcript</description></item><item><title>From Croatia to the Canefields: a love story | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380227/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380227/</guid><description>Podcast Description Debra Gavranich with the story of her mother Marija, who left her tiny Croatian island to make a life with a man she’d never met, in Far North Queensland's Cassowary Valley (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The ghosts of Babylonia | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380228/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380228/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr Irving Finkel on the ghosts who joined the ancient Assyrians and Babylonians in their day to day lives (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tim Ferguson: breaking barriers and taking names | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380229/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 13:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380229/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tim Ferguson was in the midst of a high-flying comedy career when he started experiencing 'whacky symptoms'. In his early 30s, doctors told him he had Multiple Sclerosis
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A song connection: Genevieve and the Tiwi strong women | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380230/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380230/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Dr Genevieve Campbell heard the intoxicating music of Tiwi song women, it made her hair stand on end. Immediately she knew she needed to meet the women, and these relationships have changed her ideas of what music is
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dave Gleeson needs a damn good lie down | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380231/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380231/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dave Gleeson is known for his blistering performances in The Screaming Jets and The Angels, but he grew up singing at Mass in Cardiff, with a mum who opened their home to hundreds of foster children
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The last keeper of Boston Light | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380232/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380232/</guid><description>Podcast Description One of America's oldest lighthouses was built in 1716 and survived the Revolutionary War. Its first two keepers met dismal ends, but Sally Snowman was always enamoured by it. She is the first woman to care for the lighthouse, and now she will be the last (R)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cynthia's Swans | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380233/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380233/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Cynthia Banham survived the unthinkable, she had to reinvent herself, with the support of her family, and the kindness of the Sydney Swans AFL team
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Edita’s 600 days of longing | Conversations</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2695380234/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2695380234/</guid><description>Podcast Description Edita Mujkic fled the Bosnian War in Sarajevo with her two children, 50 American dollars in her pocket and no real plan. It took her almost two years to get her husband Goran out of the deadly siege situation, all the way from the Lake District in England
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>