<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/neds-declassified-podcast-survival-guide/</link><description>Recent content in Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/neds-declassified-podcast-survival-guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ned's Stars' All-Time Favorite Ned's Declassified Episode | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070045/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get your wishes ready Ned Heads, because this week we’re breaking down “Daydreaming.” As Ned drifts off in Mr. Sweeny’s class, chaos erupts in his daydream that can only be solved with the help of Nickelodeon’s best animated duo, the Fairly OddParents! The gang shares exclusive behind the scenes moments from this episode, including what it was like working with animated characters. They also open up about how this special crossover episode helped them finally feel included in the Nickelodeon family.</description></item><item><title>Actor Chris Zylka On Hollywood And Dating Paris Hilton | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070044/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Ned’s Pod, the gang is joined by special guest (and one of Lindsey’s all-time favorite people) Chris Zylka! Chris is an actor best known for his roles in Shark Night, The Amazing Spider-Man, and The Leftovers. Chris and the gang talk about his longtime friendship with Lindsey, his experience on Zeke and Luther with Daniel, and why he decided to leave Hollywood. Chris also opens up about the hardships of public relationships and his breakup with Paris Hilton.</description></item><item><title>Ned's Stars Brutal Honesty On Friendship | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070043/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Ned’s Pod, we’re rewatching “Best Friends.” The crew not only breaks down Ned, Cookie, and Moze’s friendships, but they get real about their own. They talk about their oldest friendships, getting through hard times in life together, and what it takes to be a good friend. Lindsey also opens up about how relationships have changed since her sobriety.
Did Lindsey make out with one of Devon’s friends?</description></item><item><title>Marquise C. Brown AKA Chandra Taylor on Taking A Break From Acting After Ned's | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070042/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re back this week with a special guest, our very own Marquise C. Brown! Marquise is an actor and writer, known for her time as Chandra Taylor on Ned’s Declassified. She breaks down her journey to Ned’s, the hardships of Hollywood, and is honest about why she’s taken a step back from acting and the healing she’s experienced. Marquise also talks about the personal development book she’s currently working on - be on the lookout!</description></item><item><title>Ned's Stars On All Their Bedroom Experiences Gone Wrong | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get ready Ned Heads, because things are getting a little spicy this week on Ned’s Pod. The gang talks all about one night stands, intimacy, and their weirdest bedroom experiences. Lindsey also spills some major tea about getting busy with Devon that you DON’T want to miss.
Why did Lindsey feel like a failure with Devon? When was Daniel truly heartbroken? Who’s been cheated on?! Tune in to find out!</description></item><item><title>Lindsey Shaw On All The Ned's Cast Members She Crushed On | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070002/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Ned’s team is once again reviewing episodes of Ned’s Declassified! This week on the show, we’re talking about love letters, hiding report cards from your parents, how Devon got in trouble in school for leading girls on, and whether or not Lindsey is a romantic. Plus, what’s the real reason these Ned’s Stars have trouble in relationships?
Is Lindsey a romantic?! Which Ned’s stars sent love letters? Who got into the most trouble at school?</description></item><item><title>How This Ned's Star Handled Drugs Being Used On Set | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070003/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Ned’s Pod, Jennifer Tedmori gets real about her struggles while working on Ned’s Declassified. Jennifer was a member of the “Huge Crew” on the show, a label that heightened her teenage issues with body dysmorphia. She breaks down her troubles with eating disorders, feeling like an outsider and distancing herself from Devon and Daniel, the difficulties of separating your character from who you are in real life, and what happened when she wasn’t invited back for season 3.</description></item><item><title>Ned’s Stars On Their Bizarre Habits | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070004/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Ned’s Pod we take questions from the fans, everything from being overly sweaty, weird eating habits, bearing your soul in your work and more! Plus, Devon drops his latest single and breaks down his process for making music, what led to his new sound, and who inspired him. Did Lindsey really ruin her friend’s wedding Anniversary? Who has the weirdest eating habits? Which Ned’s star is afraid to reveal their true self?</description></item><item><title>Ned's Stars On Ghosts And Halloween Hookups | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 03:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070005/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s spooky season, Ned Heads, and something strange is in the air. This week on the Ned’s Pod, the crew goes DEEP into everything from the supernatural, crop signs, mediums, alien abductions, flat earth theories and more. We’re sharing wild stories about Halloween party hookups, the shocking discovery Devon had outside his house, and hilarious trick-or-treat memories. What happened when Lindsey hired a medium? Why doesn’t Devon watch horror movies?</description></item><item><title>Lindsey Shaw Is Ready To Hookup | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070006/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Ned’s Pod, we welcome special guest (and Backpack Boy himself) Kendre Berry! The crew dives into dealing with the good and the bad in Hollywood, how Lindsey can’t seem to catch a break with guys, getting clear on what your ‘no’s are, and what it was really like working with Fred Savage. We’re covering serious ground this week! Who got their first big break on a competition show?</description></item><item><title>Lindsey Shaw Addresses Having a Huge Ego From Her Acting Career | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome back to Ned’s Declassified Strike Survival Guide! Jk, kind of. This week the gang is talking about what made them fall in love with acting, the danger of getting a big ego, using laughter as a superpower, and learning how to cry in auditions. Devon gets vulnerable about how his parents divorce impacted him, Lindsey shares how forgiveness changed her life, and Daniel digs deep into the complexities of parent relationships.</description></item><item><title>Devon Werkheiser and Jerry Crony On Battling Depression After Ned's | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 21:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070008/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Ned’s Pod, we reunite with long-time friend and part-time bully, Teo Olivares. Teo portrayed Jerry Crony in Ned’s Declassified as one of Billy Loomer&amp;rsquo;s trio of bullies. Teo shares hilarious and insightful stories about being roomies with Devon during Covid, and how they supported each other during a season of depression and self-discovery. From early 2000s Austin Butler parties to walking 31 miles together, the group reminisces on it all.</description></item><item><title>Addressing the Zoey 101 Feud with Chris Massey | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 11:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070009/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Ned’s Pod, we reconnect with a familiar face from our childhoods - Chris Massey! Chris is best known for his role as &amp;ldquo;Michael Barret&amp;rdquo; on the beloved Nickelodeon series &amp;ldquo;Zoey 101.&amp;rdquo; He and the crew reminisce about the joys of reuniting after years apart and share their experiences growing up together on different TV shows. From Devon&amp;rsquo;s secret DUI confession to Chris almost getting mauled by a hippo, the gang dishes out the dirt on some of their wildest mishaps!</description></item><item><title>How Lindsey Shaw and Daniel Curtis Lee BOTH Ended Up in a Psych Ward | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Strap in Ned Heads, because we’re going on quite the rollercoaster this week. Starting at one-night stands, moving to Daniel&amp;rsquo;s hallucinations, Lindsey’s overdose, and ending with two of the hosts&amp;rsquo; experiences in the psych ward. Intimate questions were asked and vulnerable stories were told. What song was playing when Devon lost his virginity? Why was Daniel so paranoid? How did Lindsey get a 5150 twice?? Get ready to go deep with your favorite besties.</description></item><item><title>Get to Know the REAL King Bach with The Ned's Cast | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Worlds collide as we have internet star, King Bach, on the pod this week! King Bach, or Andrew Bachelor, is known for making his mark on Vine by being the most followed user on the platform. From making sketches, to creating his own Marvel character, to acting alongside our very own Devon Werkheiser, King Bach can do it all. He brought great energy and even greater stories! What is King Bach’s disturbing secret talent?</description></item><item><title>Why Nickelodeon NEVER Paid The Ned's Cast Residuals | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Switching gears, this week the gang is discussing how the SAG-AFTRA strike in Hollywood has affected them and how the pod will pivot until the negotiations are resolved. We’re answering your questions and diving deep into topics like mental breakdowns, working for the machine, and how hard it is to find your place in this world. Does Nickelodeon really not pay their actors residuals? How did Lindsey almost burn down her house?</description></item><item><title>Why Ned's Declassified's Michelle Kim AKA Evelyn Kwong Quit Acting | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070013/</guid><description>Podcast Description We have a VERY special guest this week! Michelle Kim, AKA Evelyn Kwong, reunites with the gang to relive their awkward teen years, catch up on life since Ned’s, and to go deep about the reason she stepped away from acting. They share stories about a dodgeball game gone wrong, Cookie &amp;amp; Evelyn’s first kiss, Asian American representation, and how Michelle let go of her identity in acting. Which co-star was Daniel’s first kiss?</description></item><item><title>The Ned's Declassified Cast Reunites With Bully, Billy Loomer | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070014/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Ned’s Pod, the gang comes face-to-face with their childhood bully once again! Kyle Swann, AKA Billy Loomer, reunites with the cast for a trip down memory lane and to catch up on life since the show. They reminisce on intense Halo rivalries, the lasting impact of Ned&amp;rsquo;s, explicit paper airplane contests, and Kyle’s unique journey from childhood actor to a Marine Biologist Filmmaker. How did a destroyed VHS tape help get Kyle the role of Billy?</description></item><item><title>Unfabulous Star Chelsea Tavares Speaks Out About Nickelodeon | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070015/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Ned’s Pod we’re joined by Nickelodeon alum, Chelsea Tavares! Chelsea is best known for her roles as Cranberry in Unfabulous and Patience Roberts in CW’s All American. The gang reminisces on growing up in young Hollywood together, their crushes and heartbreaks, and mean girl cliques. Chelsea also opens up about her experience on Unfabulous and explains why she felt like the token black girl. Which Just Jordan Star broke Chelsea’s heart over Twitter?</description></item><item><title>"Computer Labs" | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070016/</guid><description>Podcast Description From fighting bullies to undercover costumes, this week we’re rewatching “Computer Labs.” While Ned procrastinates and Moze frantically tries to print her school project, Cookie embarks on a beautiful journey to learn to live without a computer. Devon, Lindsey, and Daniel talk about teenage hormones on set, their own computer lab experiences, and their love for acting. Devon also opens up about going back to finish filming Rust. Who did Lindsey blame her fart on?</description></item><item><title>Daran Norris on His Journey From Fairly Odd Parents to Ned's Declassified | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070017/</guid><description>Podcast Description We have the BEST surprise for you today. It’s finally time to hang out with our very favorite janitor, Daran Norris! Daran is both an on-screen and voice actor, best known for his role as Gordy in Ned’s Declassified and his many roles in The Fairly Odd Parents, including Cosmo. The gang and Daran talk about his crazy experience as Gordy, his unexpected career as a voice actor, and how the Fairly Odd Parents came to be.</description></item><item><title>"Elections" | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get your acceptance speeches ready, because this week we’re rewatching “Elections.” When Ned is nominated to run for class president, his reluctance turns to a desire to make a positive change in the school. In the end, Ned loses the popularity contest, but he learned some great lessons along the way! Things get a little spicy today as the gang talks about their first dating experiences, internet chat rooms, and browsing history.</description></item><item><title>Zeke and Luther's Hutch Dano on Sobriety and Finding His Way After Disney | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070019/</guid><description>Podcast Description We have a very special guest today, Daniel’s former co-star Hutch Dano! Hutch is an actor, writer, and producer, and is best known for his role as Zeke in Disney’s Zeke and Luther. The gang talks about money struggles after their child star days, dating icks, and sorority house parties. Hutch also shares some insane behind the scenes stories from his new movie starring Lindsey and Daniel! Did Lindsey and Daniel try to date?</description></item><item><title>"Talent Shows" | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you have any strange talents? Then you’re cordially invited to James K. Polk Middle School as we rewatch “Talent Shows.” As Mr. Wrights holds a traditional talent show strictly for students with classical talents, the gang decides to showcase the school’s weird talents by putting on an alternative show. In the end, everyone feels celebrated and Mr. Wright sees the error of his ways. Devon, Lindsey, and Daniel chat about their own experience with talent shows, only to learn that Lindsey has an unexpected past in child beauty pageants.</description></item><item><title>Creators Scott &amp; Michelle Fellows on the Ned's Declassified Reboot and Taking Risks | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070021/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, we have two of the MOST important guests on the pod. Please welcome the creators and executive producers of Ned’s Declassified, Scott &amp;amp; Michelle Fellows! The gang catches up with Scott &amp;amp; Michelle and talk about Scott’s creation of Big Time Rush, the high school guide that never happened, and how both Scott &amp;amp; Michelle intentionally made the Ned’s Declassified set one of the most fun and safest spaces for all of the actors.</description></item><item><title>Why Won't Netflix Buy Season Three of Ned's Declassified?! | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Wednesday, Ned Heads! It’s time for another Q&amp;amp;A. Devon, Lindsey, and Daniel dig deep to answer some of your best questions. They talk about all things skincare routine, having kids, and what exactly happened to the money they made from Neds. Devon and Lindsey also reveal what their on-set lunch breaks entailed. Why isn’t season 3 of Neds on Netflix? Did Daniel ever feel like a third wheel?</description></item><item><title>"Photo Day" | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comb your hair and check your teeth, because this week we’re rewatching “Photo Day.” Things go awry for Ned as he gives Moze tips on how to take the perfect picture, and Cookie goes to great lengths to avoid taking his own yearbook photo (did he invent Photoshop?!). The gang reminisce on their very own yearbooks, and Devon brings a VERY special surprise for everyone. They also talk about Lindsey’s jealousy of JoJo, Devon and Daniel’s pitch for a high school show, and some of the worst photos they’ve taken.</description></item><item><title>"Rumors" | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070024/</guid><description>Podcast Description From fake breakups to atomic flushes, this week we’re rewatching “Rumors.” The gang reveals rumors they’ve heard about themselves over the years and how they’ve addressed them. Devon talks about his strange run-in with Josh Peck, Lindsey opens up about her sexuality, and Daniel explains why he doesn’t want to deal with any drama. What happened after Devon and Lindsey broke up? What did Josh Peck say to Devon?</description></item><item><title>Rob Pinkston on How Coconut Head Became a Nickelodeon Legend | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get ready Ned Head’s, because the man, the myth, and the legend is FINALLY here. Please welcome Coconut Head! The gang sits down with Rob Pinkston to talk all about his time on Ned’s. They share the origins of Coconut Head’s character and how his beloved hair came to be. Rob also talks about his time as a Punk’d cast member, his funniest and most shocking memories with Lindsey, and what it was like working with Zac Efron before High School Musical.</description></item><item><title>Did the Ned's Declassified Friendships Almost End??? | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Time for another Q&amp;amp;A! This week, Devon, Lindsey, and Daniel answer the questions you’ve been dying to know. They chat about who had crushes on each other while filming Ned’s, their next dream project together, and the secret to maintaining strong friendships. Lindsey also opens up about coping with borderline personality disorder and the progress she’s made. Does Daniel miss Cowboy Cookie? Why is Lindsey always barefoot? Did Ned and Moze end up together?</description></item><item><title>“Spelling Bees” | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070027/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070027/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, we’re talking all about “Spelling Bees.” At the spelling bee, Cookie attempts to take down his rival, Ned gets all the easy words, and Moze has to deal with Mr. Gross. The gang talks through scenes of the show that wouldn’t air today, what it was like being forced to shave, and how much they love Lisa Zimo. They also reminisce about their very own spelling bees and the words that caused them to choke.</description></item><item><title>"Sick Days" | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get ready to transport back to pandemic days, because this week we’re watching “Sick Days.” While a contagious flu is going around, Ned goes to extreme lengths to protect himself, Moze tries to get out of public speaking, and Cookie gives BMX rider Matt Hoffman the flu. The gang talks about their love languages, souvenirs they’ve kept from past relationships, and a very special song Devon wrote for Lindsey.</description></item><item><title>Nickelodeon’s Secret About the Ned’s Declassified Reboot | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070029/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ready for another Q&amp;amp;A episode?! This week, Devon, Lindsey, and Daniel are back to answer your best questions. They share exactly what it was like growing up in the spotlight, why a reboot won’t happen anytime soon, and what the best and worst part of being an adult is. What time does Daniel wake up in the morning? How does the gang handle their money? Will Nickelodeon EVER let them do a reboot?</description></item><item><title>“Dances” | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070030/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Remember the days of awkward formals and proms? We’re about to relive them as we talk about “Dances.” Ned obsesses over dancing with Suzie, Moze is empowered to have fun with her friends instead of a date, and Cookie hacks into a supermodel’s limo. Devon, Lindsey, and Daniel talk about why self-care is so important, how toxic gender roles have played a part in their lives, and some of their weirdest Cameo requests.</description></item><item><title>“Crushes” | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070031/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070031/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re talking all about “Crushes.” Ned crushes on Suzie, Moze avoids Coconut Head at all costs, and Cookie creates a matchmaking algorithm for the entire school. The gang is open and honest, and they spill all the tea about their dating lives. They share their experiences on dating apps, horror stories about their long-term relationships, and what they think about dating and relationships today. Why did Devon cry so much?</description></item><item><title>“Tryouts” | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070032/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you ready to feel the adrenaline of trying out for a school sport? We hope so, because this week we’re rewatching “Tryouts.” Ned goes out for the basketball team despite his height, Cookie breaks gender roles by trying out for the cheer team, and Moze proves that she’s the school’s best athlete. The gang shares some of their most gruesome real-life injury stories and reveal the Nickelodeon stars they’d want to fight in a boxing match.</description></item><item><title>“Seating” | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070033/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get ready to battle for the cool table, because this week we’re watching “Seating.” Moze gets moved to the front of the class, Cookie creates the perfect butt bounce and Ned devises a plan to sit at the cool table. The gang talks about the cliques they hung out with in school and the horrors of homeschooling, and Devon shares some crazy European party stores that you don’t want to miss.</description></item><item><title>“Teachers” | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070034/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070034/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, we’re talking all about “Teachers.” Ned clashes with Mr. Sweeney, Moze has a new student teacher in math, and devises a plan to get the students to listen to him, while Cookie is distracted by the beautiful Ms. Enstile. The gang talks about their most memorable teachers, those who left a positive (and negative!) mark on their lives, and what it was like going through puberty on TV.</description></item><item><title>The Ned’s Declassified Cast on Breakups, Hollywood Ragers and Turning 30 | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070035/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070035/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Devon, Lindsey and Daniel are answering your questions and giving adult life tips in this special Q&amp;amp;A episode! The gang talks about embracing breakups, reevaluating priorities and goals as you get older, how to know if someone is “the one,” and what their favorite projects have been since Ned’s. Who threw parties for the Nickelodeon and Disney stars while their parents were out of town? Who’s never been through a breakup sober?</description></item><item><title>“Detention” | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070036/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alright bad boys and girls, this week we’re going back to “Detention.” Cookie makes the perfect paper airplane which lands the gang in detention, and Lindsey says one of her favorite lines from the show. Devon, Lindsey and Daniel remember the teachers they had on set, the types of kids they were in school, and talk about their run-ins with the law as adults. Grab your popcorn because Devon is giving the deets for the first time about the night he spent in jail.</description></item><item><title>“Project Partners” | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070037/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070037/</guid><description>Podcast Description From Moze’s social studies romance with the basketball hottie to Ned &amp;amp; Cookie’s alternative family…this week we are talking all about “Project Partners.” The gang discusses representation in the industry as child actors, breaking free from society’s expectations, and choosing project partners for life. Why didn’t Lindsey’s family watch her on Pretty Little Liars? Did Devon really attend Burning Man nude? What is their podcast survival guide tip of the day?</description></item><item><title>“Bathrooms” | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070038/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070038/</guid><description>Podcast Description From bullies in the bathroom, potty tips, and the hottie list…this week we are talking all about “Bathrooms.” Devon, Lindsey, and Daniel bring up their weirdest bathroom experiences, their popularity (or lack thereof) in school, and the steamy deets on losing their virginity! Why was Daniel so nervous about being in a bathroom with Lindsey? Which of the hosts is buying a bidet? What is their podcast survival guide tip of the day?</description></item><item><title>“Lockers” | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070039/</guid><description>Podcast Description The gang is taking us back to the days of competing for the coolest locker in school! Devon, Lindsey, and Daniel reminisce about the new characters and memorable gags that were introduced in this episode, and relive their best off-camera practical jokes. They discuss their love lives on set, navigating the industry as child actors, and Austin Butler’s beginnings as a background actor. Who was the funniest person on set?</description></item><item><title>“First Day” | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get ready Ned Head’s, we’re going all the way back to the first day of school! Devon Werkheiser (Ned), Lindsey Shaw (Moze) &amp;amp; Daniel Curtis Lee (Cookie) take a trip down memory lane as they look back on the audition process, the original pilot, and some of their favorite (and most cringy) memories from shooting the first episode. Get ready to laugh at the trio’s real life middle school memories together - from the fart stories to the tickle fights.</description></item><item><title>Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide Trailer | Ned's Declassified Podcast Survival Guide</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7498070041/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 21:28:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7498070041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to the Ned&amp;rsquo;s Declassified Podcast Survival Guide! Join Ned (Devon Werkheiser), Moze (Lindsey Shaw), and Cookie (Daniel Curtis Lee) as they rewatch their hilarious adventures on the series, share their own ups and downs from middle school to adulthood, and chat with special guests throughout the podcast. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>