<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The High Performance Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-high-performance-podcast/</link><description>Recent content in The High Performance Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 01:00:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-high-performance-podcast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>David Gandy: People underestimated me (E231) | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880375/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 01:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880375/</guid><description>Podcast Description David reflects on a career spanning more than 20 years in the modelling industry, his experiences defying expectations, and how he has reshaped the industry.
David Gandy is known as one of the most successful male fashion models of all time, having worked with brands such as Hugo Boss, Dolce &amp;amp; Gabbana and Carolina Herrera. Taking a big risk when leaving university early with only 2 modules left to complete, David entered the modeling industry.</description></item><item><title>Elizabeth Day, Fearne Cotton and Rangan Chatterjee - Why deep conversations matter more than ever (E230) | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880001/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 01:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880001/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this special roundtable, podcast hosts Fearne Cotton (Happy Place), Elizabeth Day (How to Fail), and Rangan Chatterjee (Feel Better, Live More) join Jake and Damian to explore the impact of long-form conversations, the interviews that have transformed their outlooks, and how making podcasts has changed their life. This episode is a deep dive into how powerful meaningful conversations can be. The hosts collectively share the importance of these deep conversations in fostering empathy, understanding, and compassion to others.</description></item><item><title>James Milner: Turning doubters into believers (E229) | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 01:00:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880002/</guid><description>Podcast Description This conversation offers valuable insights into leadership, resilience, and the key components of high-performance teamwork.
James Milner is a professional footballer with a 21-year long career and over 600 appearances; currently playing for Premier League club Brighton &amp;amp; Hove Albion. James shares with Jake and Damian how he has sustained his career, namely due to consistency and hard-work. Reflecting on the beginning of his career in early 2000s, James describes the 'old-school' values that shaped him – how cleaning boots earned him the right to be in the dressing room.</description></item><item><title>Stuart Broad: “Why I walked away at my peak” (E228) | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880003/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 01:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880003/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode explores the greatest lessons learnt from a 15 year Test cricket career, and why we should always be searching for fun and enjoyment.
Stuart Broad is a former England cricketer and is widely acknowledged as one of the greatest Test match bowlers of all time. Having stepped back from cricket earlier this year, Stuart explains the process behind this decision; why he made that choice and why he doesn’t like the word ‘retirement’.</description></item><item><title>will.i.am - Seeing things that others can’t (E227) | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880004/</guid><description>Podcast Description This conversation encourages us to be a spark of light in the room, foster positivity, creativity, and a relentless pursuit of personal growth.
will.i.am is a rapper, producer and artist. Identifying as a ‘futurist’ will.i.am defines what this means to him and how looking into the future informs all of his decision making. In this episode, Jake and Damian explore the philosophies and ideas guiding his personal and professional life.</description></item><item><title>Lessons from the month with Danny Drinkwater, Sarina Wiegman, Matt Fitzpatrick, Alex Albon and Shane Parrish | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880005/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 01:00:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Reflecting on the guests they’ve spoken to in the month of November, Jake and Damian discuss the greatest learnings from each guest and how they can be applied to our everyday lives.
Listening back to the conversation they had with Danny Drinkwater, they dive into the biggest lesson he was taught during his career, including those by Sir Alex Ferguson. Author and blogger Shane Parrish was another impactful guest in November; Jake shares with Damian how the conversation with Shane has been impacting every day of his life since, specifically in terms of where he spends his time.</description></item><item><title>Alex Albon: Why I'm ready to be a champion (E226) | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 01:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex Albon is one of the most exciting talents in Formula 1, currently driving for Williams Racing. He has previously raced for Scuderia Toro Rosso and Red Bull Racing where he was teammate to the current Drivers Champion, Max Verstappen. This episode was recorded across two occasions, with the first taking place at the Williams Racing headquarters just days after the now infamous Qatar Grand Prix, which saw Alex need medical attention due to the heat in the car.</description></item><item><title>How can you find your own path to lasting change? | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880007/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 01:00:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ahead of the launch of the new High Performance book, ‘How to Change Your Life: Five Steps to Achieving High Performance’, Jake and Damian discuss the waypoints that people should expect to travel through in order to make lasting change.
The patern of dream, leap, fight, climb and arrive has shown itself in the journeys of countless high performers and in this episode we discuss each stage, selecting a previous guest who exemplifies it.</description></item><item><title>Alex Albon Exclusive Preview - "THIS is F1" | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 09:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ahead of the release of our podcast with F1 driver, Alex Albon, this is an exclusive first listen which details Alex’s first ever appearance on an F1 grid, leading to him gaining a seat with the prestigious Red Bull Racing team.
The full episode covers Alex’s career to date, his ambitions for the future, and the incidents, struggles and circumstances which have challenged him and helped him to grow.</description></item><item><title>Matt Fitzpatrick: How to find your edge when you're playing to win (E225) | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880009/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 01:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880009/</guid><description>Podcast Description This conversation provides a glimpse into the mind of a golfer whose meticulous approach, dedication, and mental resilience has propelled him to the pinnacle of the sport.
Matt Fitzpatrick is a professional golfer, and won his first major championship at the 2022 U.S. Open. In this episode, Jake, Damian and Matt discuss the techniques and skills he employs in his professional and personal life that have shaped his career.</description></item><item><title>Mark Manson on why we should start saying no - Handpicked | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880010/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 01:25:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Returning to the episode with author of The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck, Mark Manson, Jake reflects on the lessons he still thinks about daily. Mark suggested parents should not be telling their children they can do anything, as it may set them up for a fall in the future. Telling them they’re going to be brilliant will ensure they don’t build their resilience muscle. Jake shares with Damian how after this episode he now talks to his children differently.</description></item><item><title>Sarina Wiegman: “I don’t care about making mistakes” (E224) | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880011/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 01:00:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880011/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this enlightening conversation, Sarina Wiegman offers a profound perspective on what it means to be a successful coach, leader, and advocate for women in football.
This conversation was recorded at a sold out High Performance event in Sarina’s only UK appearance. Sarina Wiegman is the coach that took the Lionesses to victory at Euro 2020. During this conversation, Sarina takes Jake and Damian through her career and the biggest lessons she has learnt along the way.</description></item><item><title>Making noise about bullying | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880012/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 01:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Next week (20/11/2023) is Anti-Bullying Week, a scheme created by the Anti-Bullying Alliance to raise awareness and to prevent bullying. Jake and Damian reflect on previous guest conversations they’ve had about bullying and share their own experiences. Author and inspiration speaker, Vex King, opens up about witnessing an assault on his family and the lasting impact it had on him. They also explore how you can be a bully without even knowing it, listening back to the conversation they had with Courtney Black.</description></item><item><title>Living life on your own terms with author of Clear Thinking, Shane Parrish (E223) | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 01:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880013/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode explores how by mastering the basics, we can unlock the secrets to living life in ‘easy mode’.
Shane Parrish is a former spy, founder of Farnam Street and author of ‘Clear Thinking: Turning Ordinary Moments into Extraordinary Results’. Jake, Damian and Shane discuss why it is crucial to do the basics right. By analysing our four default modes; Emotion, Ego, Social and Inertia, Shane studies how we can ensure we are thinking clearly.</description></item><item><title>The Alex Ferguson advice I chose to ignore, with Ole Gunnar Solskjær - Hand-picked | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880014/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 01:00:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jake and Damian explore the archives as Damian shares his favourite lessons from Norwegian football manager Ole Gunnar Solskjær.
They reflect on where Ole’s motivation came from and the biggest lessons his father taught him. Whilst he is now known for his football management skills, Ole was also an elite footballer and talented striker, being regarded as one of the “ultimate finishers”.
They discuss how Ole reframed the challenges of being a striker, and the advice he received from Sir Alex Ferguson and Danny Welbeck.</description></item><item><title>Danny Drinkwater: Why I’m walking away from football (E222) | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Danny Drinkwater joins us on High Performance, taking this opportunity to announce his retirement from professional football. After an almost 20 year career, Danny takes some time to look back on his accomplishments, greatest lessons and biggest challenges.
After rising through the Youth Academy at Manchester United, Danny played for some of the country’s biggest clubs, including Chelsea, Aston Villa, and Leicester City. He takes Jake and Damian through his football career; from sitting on the bench at Manchester United aged 18, to being a key part of Leicester City’s Premier League winning squad.</description></item><item><title>Lessons from the month with Gordon Ramsay, Professor Brian Cox, Delia Smith and Alain de Botton | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880016/</guid><description>Podcast Description In October, Jake and Damian spoke to a wide variety of guests, including a chef, philosopher, and physicist. Jake and Damian take some time to reflect on they key lessons and biggest take-aways from each guest, including why we should embrace being wrong with Professor Brian Cox and why we should aim for averageness with Alain de Botton. With Alain they also discuss parenting, how to have a successful relationship and what high performance really means.</description></item><item><title>Gordon Ramsay: 'It's f**king raw!' Reflections on a life of adversity and achievement (E221) | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880017/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode: a rare and poignant conversation on the life, aspirations, and motivations of chef and TV icon, Gordon Ramsay.
“I don’t want to stay in my lane, I want to own my lane”
Gordon Ramsay is a chef, restaurateur and television presenter, known for Kitchen Nightmares, Masterchef and Hell’s Kitchen. In this conversation, Gordon delves deep into what really drives him, how to cultivate a winning mindset and the most crucial lessons from his career so far.</description></item><item><title>Life is a negotiation, with Chris Voss - Hand-Picked | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880018/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 00:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jake and Damian re-wind the clock to when they spoke to FBI negotiator Chris Voss. In this discussion Chris explains how techniques used in kidnapping negotiations can be used in our everyday lives. Jake shares how Chris’ teachings from this episode helped him to communicate with his wife, children, colleagues and even himself. They reflect on some of the key missions in Chris’ career and how you can become an expert communicator.</description></item><item><title>Gordon Ramsay Exclusive Preview: “Becoming a beast” | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880019/</guid><description>Podcast Description To listen to the full episode right now, download the High Performance App and use code HPAPP: https://www.thehighperformancepodcast.com/app-link
Gordon Ramsay, chef and TV presenter, joins the podcast this coming Monday to discuss how he developed a winning mindset, how to grow from adversity and the highs and lows of his career so far.
In this exclusive episode preview, Gordon shares his advice for up-and-coming chefs facing challenges in their careers, and why finding your weakness is crucial to developing your skills.</description></item><item><title>Delia Smith: The power of silence (E220) | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Delia Smith CH CBE is a culinary icon having sold over 21 million cookery books, and is also joint majority shareholder of Norwich City FC. In this conversation, Delia opens up about her spiritual journey, the transformative power of community and her time at Norwich.
Her spirituality is a central theme of the episode - now at 82 years of age, she describes how her relationship to community, politics and silence has transformed over time.</description></item><item><title>Why perfectionism could be holding you back, with Dr Julie Smith (E219) | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880021/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 00:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880021/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is a fascinating conversation about self-worth, perspective, and the power of saying no.
Dr. Julie Smith is a highly regarded clinical psychologist known for her compassionate approach to mental health care and expertise in cognitive-behavioral therapy.
With over two decades of experience, she has positively impacted the lives of countless individuals by helping them navigate the complexities of their emotional well-being.
In this episode, Dr Julie discusses how our choices today can lead to a better tomorrow, finding merit in balance throughout life, and focusing on what matters to us individuals.</description></item><item><title>Alain de Botton on the joy of being average (E218) | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 00:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880022/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode encourages us to explore a deeper understanding of ourselves, our relationships, and why we should be seeking fulfilment not happiness.
Alain de Botton is an author and philosopher, known for co-founding The School of Life in 2008. The School of Life was created to fill a void in our current education systems with the teaching of emotional intelligence. Alain’s work also focuses on love, parenthood, mental health and the meaning of success.</description></item><item><title>Josh Warrington on the mindset of a champion - Handpicked | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 00:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880023/</guid><description>Podcast Description One of Damian’s all-time favourite episodes is the conversation they had with professional boxer, Josh Warrington.
Damian reflects out his key take aways from the episode and shares them with Jake. This includes, Josh sharing the techniques he uses to keep his anxieties and fear in control just before going into the ring. And in the event of a mistake, he ensures to take full responsibility, rather than making excuses and blaming others.</description></item><item><title>Professor Brian Cox on doubt, the universe and the future of humanity (E217) | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 00:00:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880024/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a conversation about science, philosophy, the meaning of life, and the unfathomable size of the universe. Professor Brian Cox is a physicist, known for his astronomy and cosmology series’, including The Universe and Stargazing Live. He has performed on several sell-out arena tours, setting the Guinness World Record for the biggest selling science tour. Before his career in science, at age 18 Brian embarked on a musical career, forming a band with the ex-keyboarder from Thin Lizzy.</description></item><item><title>Lessons from the Month with Will Still, Steve Hansen David Smith MBE and legends of the Ryder Cup | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880025/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 00:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880025/</guid><description>Podcast Description In September Jake and Damian chatted to a number of sports guests, but the conversations were far from sport centred. Each guest offered great learnings from their lives, including creating culture, what makes a great leader and how to be more present everyday.
They reflect on the conversation they had with Ryder Cup legends Luke Donald, Sam Torrance and Paul McGinley about their leadership styles and why Paul and Sam didn’t pick Luke to be in their team in 2014.</description></item><item><title>Luke Donald: The mastermind behind Europe’s Ryder Cup triumph with Paul McGinley and Sam Torrance (E216) | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880026/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 23:04:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880026/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is an open discussion about leadership, creating culture and what makes a winning team.
To mark the 2023 Ryder Cup in Italy, Jake and Damian host a roundtable discussion with current European captain, Luke Donald, and legends, Paul McGinley and Sam Torrance. As Team Europe Ryder Cup captains past and present, they offer a unique perspective on leadership, team culture, and the winning formula that defines this prestigious event.</description></item><item><title>The price of high performance | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880027/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 00:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880027/</guid><description>Podcast Description A common thread that runs throughout the hundreds of conversations on this podcast is the idea of sacrifice. In this episode, Jake and Damian explore what the price of high performance really looks like. Although success looks great on the outside, it can come at the cost of collateral damage and difficult decisions. Looking back on their conversation with Dame Kelly Holmes, when she shared the impact sacrificing her mental health to be at the top of her game had.</description></item><item><title>Facing death taught me how to truly live with David Smith MBE (E215) | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880028/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 00:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880028/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Paralysis taught me how to live”
This emotional conversation is an honest and vulnerable discussion about life, death and understanding our purpose.
In 2010, David Smith was given a life changing diagnosis: a rare, cancerous tumour was found in his neck. A focused athlete, previously competing in karate, running and bobsled, David aimed to put all of his energy into competing in the 2012 Paralympic games as a rower; “I didn’t have time for a tumour”.</description></item><item><title>Barry Hearn's 10 Life Lessons - Handpicked | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880029/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 00:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Barry Hearn joined the podcast in 2022 to share his 10 life lessons. In this episode, Damian shares with Jake the top 3 lessons he learnt from Barry; the ones he still uses in his everyday life. These 3 lessons include, "it’s better to be lucky than good looking", "life is not changed by sitting on the sofa" and "life is going to end in tears, so you might as well make the most of it"</description></item><item><title>Building the world's most successful rugby team with All Blacks legend Steve Hansen (E214) | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880030/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 00:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880030/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s episode provides a rare glimpse into the mind of a coaching legend Steve Hansen, revealing the key to success in the world of rugby and beyond.
Steve is a New Zealand rugby union coach and a former player. He famously led the All Blacks to victory during the 2015 Rugby World Cup as their head coach, a role he held from 2012 to 2019. This is a reflective, honest and vulnerable conversation with one of the world’s best coaches.</description></item><item><title>Reflections on the Rugby World Cup | Clive Woodward, Dan Carter, Siya Kolisi, Eddie Jones, Sam Burgess, Danny Cipriani and Eddie Jones | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880031/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 00:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880031/</guid><description>Podcast Description To mark the start of the Rugby World Cup, Jake and Damian reflect on the conversations they have had with some of the most influential people in the game. We have been lucky enough to go into the training grounds, stadiums and dressing rooms and to hear the innermost thoughts of the key players past and present.
Hear from Sir Clive Woodward on the power of the individual in a great team.</description></item><item><title>How Europe's youngest top-flight manager learned to BACK HIMSELF with Will Still (E213) | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880032/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 23:21:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Will's story is a testament to the power of authenticity and resilience in the world of football management. Will Still is a professional football manager and former player, currently managing Ligue 1 club Stade de Reims. Aged 30, he is the youngest manager in Europe's top five leagues, and first became a manager at age 24. Will shares with Jake and Damian how he deals with outside pressure and how his commitment to honesty, vulnerability, and staying true to himself has been his guiding force.</description></item><item><title>Lessons From The Month with Dr Waheed Arian, Katherine Ryan, Fernando Alonso and Peter Attia | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880033/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 00:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880033/</guid><description>Podcast Description August was filled with perspective changing and vulnerable conversations about what high performance really looks like. Jake takes a look back at some of the key insights from our guests over the last month.
Dr Waheed Arian challenged Jake's ever-shifting view of what high performance really means, by sharing the obstacles he overcame when moving from war torn Afghanistan to the UK at age 15 to become a doctor.</description></item><item><title>How to be fit forever with Peter Attia (E212) | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880034/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880034/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode contains the roadmap to a longer, healthier life.
Dr. Peter Attia is a physician, focused on the applied science of longevity and on a mission to unlock the secrets of extending human life. In this episode, he takes Jake and Damian through the 5 pillars of health, exploring the impact of nutrition, exercise, sleep, stress and supplementation.
These five essential aspects of our lives are the building blocks upon which our overall wellbeing is constructed.</description></item><item><title>WHY we started this podcast | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880035/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 00:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880035/</guid><description>Podcast Description After over 200 episodes and almost 4 years of the High Performance Podcast, Jake and Damian take a moment to rewind through the episodes. For any brand new listeners, this is your ultimate guide to the key High Performance moments. Jake and Damian reflect on their favourite guests, biggest lessons and most memorable moments from the very start of the High Performance journey to the most recent episode. To begin, Jake and Damian explore the why behind the podcast.</description></item><item><title>E211 - Fernando Alonso: 99% of the time you will not succeed | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880036/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 00:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fernando Alonso is a two-time Formula 1 World Champion, currently competing for the fast-rising Aston Martin F1 Team. Fernando has also driven for Alpine, McLaren, Ferrari, Minardi, and Renault, where he won the World Drivers' Championship in 2005 and 2006.
This episode explores what it takes to become an elite F1 driver, and how to maintain top level performance over a 20-year career.
Jake and Damian discover the origins of Fernando’s legendary racing career, dating back to his very first race at the age of three.</description></item><item><title>Purpose over profit with Joe Wicks | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880037/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 00:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jake shares with Damian the conversation with Joe Wicks that transformed his life, completely shifting his view on what it means to be driven by purpose. They reflect on the importance of purpose over profit and how understanding your purpose can lead to clearer and more informed decision making.
Joe also offered practical advice for staying present and making time for the people who matter. He suggested people take “mini retirements” every year: whether it is a weekend or a month, a mini-retirement is time away from work and the pressures of everyday life to focus on family, friends, rest and relaxation.</description></item><item><title>E210 - Katherine Ryan: When I had nothing, I had everything | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880038/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Katherine Ryan is a comedian and writer, best known for her appearances on 8 Out of 10 Cats, Taskmaster and her stand-up special on Netflix, Glitter Room. Originally from Canada, Katherine made the bold move to London in 2008, and shortly thereafter had her first daughter. Becoming a single mum at the age of 25 and isolated from family, Katherine shares with Jake and Damian how this experience fuelled her determination and resilience.</description></item><item><title>Vicky Pattison's formula for life | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880039/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Damian shares his key take-aways from one of his favourite episodes ever recorded with guest Vicky Pattison. Vicky completely shifted Damian's assumptions about reality TV stars and he came away with a brand new formula to view life.
Jake and Damian take a look back on the conversation they had with Vicky and they lessons she shared that they still use in their life today. Including, how she moved away from a strict work ethic to keep the passion for her career alive; the numbering system for everyday that has completely transformed her life and how we can categorise the most important people in our lives.</description></item><item><title>E209 - Dr Waheed Arian: How I escaped Afghanistan and became an NHS doctor | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880040/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Waheed Arian, a doctor and radiologist, endured a challenging upbringing in war-torn Afghanistan, and at 15, he was smuggled to the UK. He had a singular ambition: to become a doctor. In a heartfelt conversation with Jake and Damian, he candidly reveals the harsh realities of living amongst bombings and military presence. He recounts visiting his father in hiding, who sought to evade front-line military service.
Such traumatic experiences have shaped Waheed's character, instilling vital lessons he carries to this day.</description></item><item><title>Lessons from the month with Simon Sinek, Ashley Cain, Sabrina Cohen-Hatton and Dan Carter | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880041/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 00:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jake and Damian reflect on the insightful and inspiring conversations they’ve had in July, delving a little deeper into some of the key lessons from each episode.
They rediscover the teachings shared by Dan Carter on how to navigate change whilst entering retirement. In one of the most emotional episodes ever recorded, Ashley Cain reveals how his late daughter Azaylia transformed his life and how her memory lives on today.</description></item><item><title>E208 - Steve Parish: The Candid Journey from Crystal Palace Fan to Owner | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880042/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 00:00:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Steve Parish is a businessman and the co-owner and chairman of Crystal Palace F.C. After beginning his career in computer graphics, Steve went on to acquire multiple companies. He transformed TagWorldwide into a global production powerhouse with over 2,800 employees in 13 countries. In 2010, Steve acquired Crystal Palace, saving the club from administration, and building the foundations for the growth of the club over the 13 years that followed.</description></item><item><title>E207 - Emily Maitlis: How I Approached THAT Prince Andrew Interview | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880043/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880043/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the final episode of our new Leadership Series, sponsored by PwC, in which we will be diving deep into what it really takes to be a great leader.
Emily Maitlis is a journalist, presenter of the ground-breaking daily podcast The News Agents, documentary filmmaker and former BBC Newsnight anchor. She is known for her skilled and informative interviews including THAT interview for Newsnight. In this conversation, they explore what it means to be an excellent interviewer.</description></item><item><title>Learnings from the Lionesses' with Jill Scott, Steph Houghton, Alex Scott and Phil Neville | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 00:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880044/</guid><description>Podcast Description To celebrate the Women’s World Cup, Jake and Damian take a look back at the conversations they had with former England players Alex Scott, Steph Houghton, and Jill Scott, as well as former manager Phil Neville. Jake and Damian listen back to their chat with Jill about how the experience for female footballers has completely transformed. Steph shares what it was like to put women’s football on the map, and how she realised her life would change when she returned home after winning.</description></item><item><title>E206 - Simon Sinek: ‘Start with why’ when searching for High Performance | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880045/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Simon Sinek is an author and inspirational speaker. Simon is known for his books ‘Start with Why’ and ‘Find Your Why’, both of which focus on how to find your purpose and help those in your life find it too. Finding your Why, is the idea that “everyone knows what we do, some of us know how we do it, but very few of us can articulate why we do what we do.</description></item><item><title>E205 - Timo Armoo: How you can play the game by your own rules | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880046/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880046/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the third episode of our new Leadership Series, sponsored by PwC, in which we will be diving deep into what it really takes to be a CEO.
Timo Armoo is an entrepreneur, speaker and co-founder of Fanbytes, a social media and marketing agency. Timo founded Fanbytes at age 21 whilst in university, eventually selling at aged 27 for an eight figure exit. In this conversation, we delve deep into Timo’s entrepreneurial mind, exploring what makes a great business idea, finding a core purpose and knowing when a good opportunity arises.</description></item><item><title>E204 - Dr Sabrina Cohen-Hatton: Before I could thrive, I had to survive | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880047/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 00:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr Sabrina Cohen-Hatton is a firefighter, psychologist and writer. In this episode Sabrina proves that nothing is fixed, where you start isn’t important, it’s where you end up. From experiencing homelessness as a teenager, after the death of her father, to working her way up in the fire service, joining at age 18.
She shares with Jake and Damian her experience making life changing decisions whilst being in the fire service, offering a clear and concise decision making formula.</description></item><item><title>E203 - Tessa Clarke: What YOU can do to save the world | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880048/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 00:00:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880048/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the second episode of our new Leadership Series, sponsored by PwC, in which we will be diving deep into what it really takes to be a CEO.
Tessa Clarke is the co-founder and CEO of Olio, the free app that connects users with unwanted food (from households or local businesses) with neighbours living nearby who would like it. Tessa is driven by purpose, aiming to reduce food waste and tackle climate change.</description></item><item><title>E202 - Ashley Cain: Everything losing my daughter taught me | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880049/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ashley Cain is a former professional footballer and TV personality. In 2020, his 8 week old daughter Azaylia Cain was diagnosed with an aggressive form of leukemia. During Azaylia’s battle with cancer, Ashley and Azaylia’s mum, Safiyya, raised over £1 million in 24 hours for her health care. After her death in April 2021, at just 8 months old, Ashley and Safiyya set up ‘The Azaylia Foundation’, which supports families and provides memorable experiences for children fighting cancer.</description></item><item><title>E201 - Steve Hare: Remaining calm through chaos with the UK's highest rated CEO | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880050/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 00:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880050/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the first episode of our Leadership Series, sponsored by PwC, in which we will be diving deep into what it really takes to be a CEO.
Steve Hare is a businessman and CEO of Sage Group PLC, the leader in accounting, financial, HR and payroll tech for small and mid-sized businesses. With over three decades of experience in the industry, Steve shares with Jake and Damian his insights into the business world, including the benefit of being older in business, how to face the challenges of being CEO and the key advice he would give young entrepreneurs.</description></item><item><title>Looking Ahead to Lessons in Leadership | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880051/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 00:00:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880051/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is a look ahead to our forthcoming PWC leadership series which begins this Friday. Listen in to hear a preview of interviews with Steve Hare (Sage CEO), Tessa Clarke (Olio CEO) and Timothy Armoo (founder of Fanbytes).
Episodes will be released weekly on Fridays for the month of July
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>E200 - Dan Carter: The Art of Winning | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880052/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 23:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to our 200th Episode Special with Dan Carter, recorded live at Hackney Empire!
We first spoke to Dan, All-Blacks legend and one of the greatest rugby players of all time, almost 2 years ago. He returns to the podcast to discuss how his view of high performance, and his overall mindset, has evolved since the first conversation we had with him. He shares the struggles he faced after leaving the All Blacks and the issues and fears this brought up for him: navigating change, loss of identity and hiding from retirement .</description></item><item><title>Lessons from the month with Kevin Sinfield, Edwin van der Sar, Tom Grennan and Matt Willis | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880053/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jake and Damian take some time to reflect on the conversations they’ve had in June, delving a little deeper into some of the key lessons from each episode.
They explore the idea of finding your purpose with Kevin Sinfield, how they would have done the interview with Edwin van der Sar differently with the knowledge he left Ajax a few days later. They also examine how to challenge negative thoughts with Tom Grennan’s method of “thought flipping”, wrapping up the conversation with the importance of asking for help and the power you can find when all seems lost, with Matt Willis.</description></item><item><title>E199 - Matt Willis: How addiction nearly destroyed my life | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880054/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 23:38:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matt Willis, the musician and singer known for co-founding Busted, joins the podcast to speak about the true impact of addiction. We discuss why addiction is such a taboo subject, how to approach difficult conversations with your loved ones and the journey to recovery. Matt shares the struggles he faced in his youth and how they spiraled into addiction. After Busted split up when he was only 21, he felt his life lacked direction and purpose.</description></item><item><title>George Groves: Down but not out, how I became a world champion at the fourth attempt | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880055/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880055/</guid><description>Podcast Description George Groves is a former professional boxer, he competed for 10 years and held a WBA Super-Middleweight title. In March 2018, he was ranked as the Worlds Best Active Super-Middleweight Boxer. George shares his desire to lead to the front, going at things alone, and the negative impact that can have. He won the world title on his fourth attempt, he offers advice on never giving up and why he would always choose to go back to his most challenging defeats.</description></item><item><title>E198 - Tom Grennan: How I flipped adversity into energy | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880056/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 00:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we welcome musician Tom Grennan to The High Performance Podcast. I’m sure you immediately start to think of some of the awesome songs that Tom’s released, but there is so much about his story, his mindset and resilience that you don’t know. You’re about to hear a conversation with Tom, like you’ve never heard him before.
He’s going to share with you the hours of therapy he’s had, which has helped him when approaching any challenge in life to flip his thoughts.</description></item><item><title>Fathers Day Reflections: Raising a High Performer | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880057/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880057/</guid><description>Podcast Description To celebrate Fathers Day 2023 in the UK, Jake and Damian discuss the importance of father figures. They look back on how previous guests lives have been shaped by their dads. The two also share what Father's Day means to them now they're both dads and how their fathers have shaped and influenced their paths in life.
They discuss sacrifice, tough love and psychological safety whilst hearing from guests such as Johanna Konta, Jost Capito and Keir Starmer.</description></item><item><title>E197 - Edwin Van Der Sar: "It’s f***ing hard" - his final interview as Ajax CEO | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880058/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 23:03:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880058/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this interview, we welcome Edwin Van De Sar. The man who went from player to CEO, who won four Eredivisie titles, four Premier League Crowns and the Champions League, among many other accolades in his career.
We recorded this in a hotel room overlooking the Johan Cruyff&amp;nbsp;Arena in Amsterdam, the home of Ajax Football Club. Edwin, at the time of recording, was the Chief Executive of the football club.</description></item><item><title>Looking back on the Champions League | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880059/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 00:00:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880059/</guid><description>Podcast Description To mark the Champions League final, Jake reflects on the conversations they have had with a range of guests about the Champions League. In this episode, you will hear from Jordan Henderson, Kieran Trippier, Steven Gerrard, Frank Lampard and Mauricio Pochettino among others about their relationship to the competition.
This final of the Champions League also a very significant game for Jake as it will be the last ever match he hosts on BT Sport, after a decade of presenting on the channel.</description></item><item><title>E196 - Kevin Sinfield: Why I’ll never stop fighting for my friend Rob | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880060/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 00:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kevin Sinfield returns to the podcast, after two years, to discuss how his career, mindset and approach to life has changed since Jake and Damian last sat down with him.
Kevin is a rugby coach, currently the defense coach for the England Rugby Union national team. In his career as a player, spanning almost three decades with Leeds Rhinos, Kevin played 521 games for the club, finishing with 3,968 points.</description></item><item><title>Lessons from the month with Kieran Trippier, Gary Barlow, Paul Barber and Lord Bilimoria | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880061/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 00:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jake and Damian reflect on their key-takeaways from the guests that joined the podcast in May. They take a look at each episode from the previous month, curating the key lessons from each guest.
They analyse Lord Billimoria’s 10 P’s for business, how Gary Barlow creates the best concert experience and how he deals with failure. They delve deep into building partnerships with Premier League CEO of the Year, Paul Barber and Kieran Trippier on why team spirit is so important.</description></item><item><title>E195 - Gary Barlow: My biggest failure, and why I needed it | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880062/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 00:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gary Barlow is one of Britain’s most successful songwriters and record producers. As part of pop group Take That, he has won eight BRIT Awards and sold over 45 million records with almost four decades in the music industry.
Gary shares with Jake and Damian the exciting but tumultuous initial years with Take That, the relationships with his band members and how he dealt with world-wide success. He details his attempt to ‘break America’ and how this experience changed his life.</description></item><item><title>E194 - The $50 Million Brand Blueprint with Jason Daniel | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880063/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 17:46:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jason Daniel is founder and CEO of clothing brand LSKD (Loose Kid). LSKD grew from his pursuit of a sporting career in Motocross, whilst he built core business and work ethic skills as a carpenter. In this episode, he shares how his wife falling pregnant empowered him to pursue LSKD 100% and encouraged him to find his ‘why’.
He reflects on the power of vulnerability and naivety when starting any new venture.</description></item><item><title>E193 - The inside story of Brighton's greatest season with CEO, Paul Barber | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880064/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 00:00:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Paul Barber is the CEO of Brighton &amp;amp; Hove Albion FC. In Barber's first season at the club, they recorded their highest league finish for more than 30 years. How did he achieve it and what has he done since to instill the club’s values?
He reflects on how having a diligent and thorough approach has allowed the team to effectively review mistakes and revise for the future - the focus is always how to come back stronger.</description></item><item><title>The importance of opening up with Danny Cipriani, Courtney Black, Mark Cavendish and Gary Barlow | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880065/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 00:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880065/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this retrospective episode to mark Mental Health Awareness week, Jake and Damian look back on some of the conversations they've had with guests about overcoming struggles with their mental health. Featuring a sneak preview of an upcoming episode with Gary Barlow, there are also moments from Mark Cavendish, Courtney Black and Danny Cipriani.
Listen to the full episodes:
Danny Cipriani - https://pod.fo/e/14797e
Courtney Black - https://pod.fo/e/15a903
Mark Cavendish - https://pod.</description></item><item><title>E192 - Jax Jones: The letter I wrote that changed my life | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880066/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 00:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jax Jones, known privately as Timucin Lam, is a DJ, songwriter and record producer. He rose to fame in 2014 and since then has sold over 35 million records, with 4 billion streams. For the first time, he opens up to Jake and Damian about how his turbulent childhood, challenging family relationships and immense pressure to succeed from a young age has shaped him: “Music was a way out.</description></item><item><title>Dan Carter Live Event Announcement! | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880067/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 03:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880067/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are so excited to invite you to an Audience with All Blacks legend Dan Carter at Hackney Empire on June 14th 2023. The event will be a live podcast with Jake, Damian and Dan, followed by an audience Q&amp;amp;A.
Tickets go on general sale today (Friday 11th of May) at 10am. All tickets include a signed copy of Dan Carter's new book - THE ART OF WINNING.</description></item><item><title>E191 - Kieran Trippier: How struggle made me stronger | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880068/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 23:16:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kieran Trippier is the current captain of Newcastle United and is widely regarded as one of the best English right backs of his generation. As well as winning the La Liga title with Athletico Madrid, Kieran reached the Champions League final with Spurs and scored the opening goal for England in the 2018 World Cup semi-final against Croatia. He has played under some of the finest managers in the game including Diego Simeone, Mauricio Pochettino, Gareth Southgate, Sean Dyche and now Eddie Howe.</description></item><item><title>When does dedication become obsession? With Stephen Hendry, Jill Scott, Jonny Wilkinson and Brent Hoberman | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880069/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:07:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880069/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode we look back upon some of the guests whose dedication to High Performance has had a detrimental effect on other elements of their lives. Jake and Damian explore the difficulties associated with going 'all in', while reliving moments from Jill Scott, Brent Hoberman, Stephen Hendry and Jonny Wilkinson.
Listen to their full episodes here: Jill Scott: https://pod.fo/e/17147d
Brent Hoberman: https://pod.fo/e/172e1d
Stephen Hendry: https://pod.fo/e/c12f9
Jonny Wilkinson: https://pod.</description></item><item><title>Stepping outside of your comfort zone | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880070/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880070/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Jake has an honest chat about being out of your comfort zone. The High Performance Podcast is currently touring the UK and although this is extremely exciting, it can bring about lots of new challenges. For Jake, one of the challenges is public speaking to thousands of people.&amp;nbsp;
He opens up about the pressures of performing on stage, making sure the audience enjoy themselves and turning the podcast into an exciting live show.</description></item><item><title>E190 - Lord Bilimoria: Adversity into opportunity - Building a global beer empire with Cobra | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880071/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lord Bilimoria is a businessman and life peer in the House of Lords. Founding Cobra Beer in 1989, in this interview Lord Bilimoria distils decades of business experience into valuable lessons. After attending university at 16, Lord Bilimora came to the UK on a scholarship at 18. It was then he identified a space in the market for Cobra Beer, inspired by his youth in India.
In this episode, they discuss how being creative and an innovation is crucial for an entrepreneur and how to cultivate these skills.</description></item><item><title>The importance of adaptability with Neil Fachie | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880072/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 00:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880072/</guid><description>Podcast Description These bitesize episodes focus on the greatest lessons we’ve learnt from the guests we've had on the podcast.
In this episode Jake and Damian reflect back their conversation with Paralympian, Neil Fachie. This episode was recorded via Zoom during the pandemic, Jake and Damian discuss how this set up sometimes led to more open and honest conversations - this was definitely true in the case of Neil.
This bitesize clip explores how Neil dealt with the struggles of his disability and how it has taught him resilience and problem solving skills.</description></item><item><title>E189 - Guenther Steiner: No f**k's given, F1's most outspoken team boss | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880073/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Guenther Steiner is a renowned motorsport engineer and team manager, best known for his current position as the Haas Formula One Team Principal. With over 30 years working in motorsport, Guenther is highly admired throughout the community and has become a leading figure in popular Netflix series, ‘Drive to Survive’.
In this episode, he describes how he found his way to a career in racing, his approach to management and how he nurtures his relationships with drivers and team mates to help push the team forward.</description></item><item><title>What advice would you give your younger self? | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880074/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 00:00:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880074/</guid><description>Podcast Description “What advice would you give your younger self?” Since the beginning of the podcast, Jake and Damian have asked this question in almost every conversation as a way of finding out what a high performance life has taught the interviewee. In this episode, they reflect on why this question is important, what they’ve learned from asking it, and review a few of their favourites from Rio Ferdinand, Steven Bartlett and Lucy Easthope.</description></item><item><title>E188 - Phil Giles: The man who helped build Brentford FC | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880075/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 00:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Phil Giles is the current Director of Football at Brentford Football Club, responsible for overseeing player recruitment, scouting and youth development. With over a decade of experience at Brentford, Phil shares how to have honest conversations with staff and players, what it means to be a good Director and how to share bad news with a team, among much more.
In this episode, Phil shares the things he does to make Brentford different to any other club.</description></item><item><title>From the Pitch to the Classroom: Kit Brown's Playbook for High-Performance Teaching | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880076/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 00:00:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880076/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this special bonus episode in partnership with Get Into Teaching, Jake chats to Kit Brown, a primary school teacher and a semi-professional footballer. Kit has accumulated over 1 million social media followers sharing his passion for teaching and education. He shares the rewards of being a teacher and how the small wins make the hard work worthwhile.
Jake and Kit discuss the skills he has gained in football that he applies to his teaching, including how to build resilience in young people and how he brings a high performance mindset into the classroom.</description></item><item><title>E187 - Brent Hoberman, lastminute.com founder: the hard truths of entrepreneurship | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880077/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 00:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brent Hoberman is an entrepreneur and investor. He co-founded lastminute.com and made.com, both of which went on to be valued at $1 billion dollars. Being born in South Africa, from a Jewish family and moving to England to attend boarding school, Brent identifies being an immigrant and an outsider as a driving force in his work. He shares with Jake and Damian how he used his misfit status to create his own path, and now actively looks for outsiders and mavericks to work alongside him.</description></item><item><title>Discovering Your Ikigai: Finding Purpose, Passion, and Fulfilment in Life with Hector Garcia | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880078/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 00:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880078/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this special episode, Ikigai expert Hector Garcia joins Jake and Damian to discuss how utilising Ikigai will get you closer to finding your purpose.&amp;nbsp;
Ikigai is a Japanese word that means ‘reason for being’. Hector explains to Jake and Damian how people can find their Ikigai and the actions you can take to change your life once you find it. They reflect on previous podcast guests and see how their ideas apply to the theory of Ikigai.</description></item><item><title>E186 - Jill Scott: Inspire before you expire | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880079/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 23:08:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jill Scott is a former professional football player, namely playing for Everton and Manchester City. She was part of the winning team at Euro 2022 and has represented England in the Olympics multiple times. Jill is also known as ‘Queen of the Jungle’ after winning ‘I’m a Celeb Get Me Out of Here’ in 2022. In this episode, Jill, Jake and Damian discuss what Jill has learnt from an almost 20 year professional career in football.</description></item><item><title>How trauma can create triumph with Billy Monger | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880080/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 00:00:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880080/</guid><description>Podcast Description These bitesize episodes focus on the greatest lessons we’ve learnt from the guests we've had on the podcast.
In this episode Jake returns to an episode that has shaped his view of high performance and changed his mindset for the better. This guest was Billy Monger. Billy was just 17 when he lost both legs in a life-changing crash that took place during a Formula 4 race.&amp;nbsp;
This bitesize clip explores how Billy dealt with the trauma of the accident, whilst becoming an overnight celebrity and trying to protect his family.</description></item><item><title>Lessons from the Month with Dame Stephanie Shirley, Molly McCann, Ryan Mason and Keir Starmer | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880081/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jake and Damian reflect on their key-takeaways from the guest that joined the podcast in March. They summarise each episode from the previous month, covering the key stories and greatest lessons from each guest. What was Jake’s biggest takeaway? How will Damian be using these learnings in his everyday life?&amp;nbsp;
In this wrap-up they discuss the lessons on post-traumatic growth from Stephanie Shirley, dealing with setbacks and Ryan Mason’s life changing skull injury and how crucial communication is for Keir Starmer.</description></item><item><title>E185 - Keir Starmer: My learnings from life, loss and love | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880082/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 23:06:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Keir Starmer is the current Leader of the Labour Party. A self-described “undersharer”, Keir takes this opportunity with Jake and Damian to open up about his childhood, his leadership style and what it’s really like to be the Leader of the Opposition. As a big football fan, Keir shares what he has learnt from watching Arsenal play and why he has developed such a love for the game.</description></item><item><title>Inspiring the next generation with teaching - Ed Haslam | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880083/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 01:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880083/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this special bonus episode in partnership with Get Into Teaching, Jake is joined by Ed Haslam Whiston. Ed is the Trust Director of Sporting Excellence of the Laurus Trust he&amp;nbsp;oversees the 'electives programme' Trust wide which is their extra-curricular initiative to make sure 100% of KS3 students participate in sport or physical activity outside of lessons, securing the only official partnership with Loughborough University to make the offer truly aspirational.</description></item><item><title>E184: - Molly McCann (UFC): Forged in fire, how adversity creates winners | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880084/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 01:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Molly McCann, also known as Meatball Molly, is a mixed martial artist, currently competing in the Ultimate Fighting Championship. In this open and honest interview, Molly shares stories from her turbulent childhood, including her mum's struggle with addiction. Her mum was able to recover from addiction, get qualifications and turn her life around - Molly shares the immensely positive impact this has had on her, being able to follow the positive behaviour her mum illustrated.</description></item><item><title>E183 - Mothers Day Special: Lessons on Parenthood from Jake's Mum (Liz Humphrey) | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880085/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 02:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880085/</guid><description>Podcast Description To celebrate Mother’s Day, Jake and Damian sat down with Jake’s mum, Liz Humphrey, to chat about Jake’s upbringing and her parenting advice, among much more. Jake shares his experiences being the victim of bullying whilst at school, and Liz explores how she dealt with this challenging time as a parent and as a teacher. She offers advice that she would pass onto the next generation of parents, including how to make your children feel safe in their own home, offering them a space of solace.</description></item><item><title>E182 - Ryan Mason: How to focus on your comeback, not your set back | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880086/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 01:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ryan Mason is currently a first team football coach at Tottenham Hotspur FC and was the youngest person ever to manage a Premier League football match at 29. Ryan played football professionally until a life changing skull injury, which he suffered during a match and led to 48 staples in his skull. In this episode they discuss the injury and the struggles that took place in the following months.</description></item><item><title>Why Non-Negotiables Matter | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880087/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 01:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880087/</guid><description>Podcast Description “What are your three non-negotiables?” This is the question Jake and Damian ask at the end of every conversation they’ve had on the podcast. No two answers have been the same. In this episode, Jake and Damian reflect on the many varied non-negotiables from a wide range of guests including Eddie Howe, Owen O’Kane and Courntey Black.&amp;nbsp;
They discuss their own non-negotiables and how they have evolved since the beginning of the podcast.</description></item><item><title>Educating the leaders of tomorrow with Dr Nishma Manek | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880088/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 01:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880088/</guid><description>Podcast Description To mark International Women's Day, we hear from GP, writer and podcaster, Nishma Manek who describes the struggles and successes of working within the NHS, and the key learnings she's taken from her career so far.
Check out Nishma's podcast 'The Next GenCast' on all podcast platforms
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>E181 - Dame Stephanie Shirley: From child refugee to the Sunday Times rich list. What I’ve learned in 90 years | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880089/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dame Stephanie Shirley is a businesswoman, technology pioneer and philanthropist. Currently at the age of 89, Stephanie has had a long career championing women in the workplace and new forms of technology, including being part of the team that programmed Concorde’s black box flight recorder. After being born in Germany, Stephanie was brought over to the UK on the Kindertransport during the WWII and lived with foster parents for many years.</description></item><item><title>Planting the Golden Seed with Evelyn Glennie | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880090/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 01:00:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880090/</guid><description>Podcast Description These bitesize episodes focus on the greatest lessons we’ve learnt from the guests we've had on the podcast.
Today, Jake takes us back to episode 45 with Dame Evelyn Glennie. Evelyn is a Scottish percussionist, who has been profoundly deaf since the age of 12. In this clip, she discusses how important it is to open the world of children to new things that will inspire and ignite them.</description></item><item><title>E180 - James Clear: What you need to do today, to change your tomorrow | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880091/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 01:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880091/</guid><description>Podcast Description James Clear is a writer and speaker, known for his bestselling book Atomic Habits: An Easy &amp;amp; Proven Way to Build Good Habits and Break Bad Ones. Atomic Habits spent every week of 2021 on the New York Times best-seller list, usually in either the No.1 or No.2 spot and it has been translated into more than 50 languages. In this episode, James shares his insights on achieving your goals, building new habits and how to stay on track.</description></item><item><title>E179 - Omar Sharif: Stop looking up to people and start looking into them | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880092/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:01:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Omar Sharif is CEO and Founder of Omar Inspires, he is a speaker and consultant. In 2018 Omar won the Pride of Britain Award, he was then hand-picked to consult directly for the British royal family. After being heavily involved in gang crime and seeing three friends die as a result of knife crime, Omar sought to change his life. Jake, Damian and Omar discuss the events that led up to him changing his life and the struggle that followed that decision.</description></item><item><title>E178 - Jordan Henderson: Serve to lead - why being selfless matters | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880093/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 00:02:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jordan Henderson is the current captain of Liverpool FC and an England international. Under his captaincy, Liverpool have won six trophies including the Champions League and, their first Premier League title in thirty years.
In this episode Jordan shares how as an only child, the displacement of his parents divorce at the age of six, impacted his life. Although for Jordan, “football is everything” to him, when his dad was diagnosed with cancer his world was turned upside down, providing a shift in his perspective.</description></item><item><title>Walking a mile in the shoes of a Premier League referee, with Anthony Taylor | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880094/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 01:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880094/</guid><description>Podcast Description These bitesize episodes focus on the greatest lessons we’ve learnt from the guests we've had on the podcast.
Today, Jake reflects back on episode 106, an insightful conversation with football referee Anthony Taylor. In this episode Anthony was given the opportunity to share why he made certain decisions on the pitch. Jake discusses how this episode helped him to reframe criticising others and centre empathy, asking the question: how can we judge someone if we don’t understand them?</description></item><item><title>E177 - Matthew Syed: How to think outside the box | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880095/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:06:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matthew Syed is an author and highly acclaimed speaker, he has written six bestselling books focusing on mindset and high performance, including children's books. In his varied career, Matthew was England’s number one table tennis player for over a decade, and he has competed in the Olympics for Team GB twice. In this episode, Matthew shares his insight into education, parenthood and leadership.&amp;nbsp;
They discuss why it’s so important to bring the growth mindset into education, to teach our children that it’s about how you can develop your skills and talents, not just celebrating the end goal.</description></item><item><title>Responding to a Disaster with Lucy Easthope | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880096/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 01:00:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880096/</guid><description>Podcast Description The recent earthquakes in Turkey and Syria have left thousands of people killed, trapped and injured, with numbers continually rising. We will be donating all profits from this episode to the Red Cross, to provide help to those affected by the recent earthquakes.&amp;nbsp;
Today, we’re returning to the conversation we had with Lucy Easthope, expert and adviser on emergency planning and disaster recovery. In this snippet, she details how she deals with disaster, from the 9/11 and the July bombings to COVID-19, and the skills she uses to navigate these scenarios.</description></item><item><title>E176 - Maro Itoje: The distinction between High Performance and Elite Performance | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880097/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Maro Itoje is a rugby union player, currently playing for Saracens and the England national team. Having joined Saracens at 16 years old, Maro shares how the kindness, manners and dedication of the senior players has shaped him. He discusses how his parents never pushed him to focus on rugby, so all of his motivation was internal.&amp;nbsp;
Maro claims to not be the most talented player, rather his skillset is based on output and how hard he can work.</description></item><item><title>High Performance Live: Tour Preview | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880098/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 01:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880098/</guid><description>Podcast Description This coming Sunday (4th Feburary) is the first night in our 2023 High Performance Tour!
In this episode Jake and Damian take you through what you can expect from the 2023 High Performance Tour. It is not your typical podcast show, each night is filled with music, audience interaction and industry leading experts.
Two of the tour’s special guests, Kye Sones and Owen O’Kane, join this episode to discuss their high performance journey.</description></item><item><title>E175 - Sean Dyche: What Everton can expect | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880099/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:02:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880099/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been almost three years since Jake and Damian first sat down with football manager Sean Dyche. A lot has changed since that initial conversation, he is now manager of Everton FC. Sean left Burnley after a decade in charge of the team, keeping them in the Premier League for six seasons with a limited wage bill.&amp;nbsp;
In this episode, Sean seeks to challenge the myths told about him.</description></item><item><title>Year of Change: Week Four - Sustain | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880100/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 01:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880100/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the fourth, and final, episode in a special mini-series focusing on change. Rethinking how we can create change and helping you understand and implement the building blocks for lasting change.
This week the focus is SUSTAIN - taking the lessons you have learnt and making sure you sustain these changes in your everyday life. In this episode we feature: Vicky Pattison (Ep99): https://pod.fo/e/105426
Ben Ainslie (Ep22): https://pod.</description></item><item><title>E174 - Stef Reid: You can’t always change the world, but you can always change yourself | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880101/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stef Reid is a track and field Paralympian, who competes for Team GB. She is a World Champion, four-time Paralympian, triple Paralympic medallist, and five-time world record holder. Stef has a degree in biochemistry, and recently starred in the British reality TV show Dancing On Ice 2022.
In this episode she shares the story of the boating accident that caused the loss of her foot as a teenager and the struggle that followed.</description></item><item><title>The Year Of Change: Week Three - Consistency | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880102/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 01:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880102/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the third episode in a special mini-series focusing on change. Rethinking how we can create change and helping you understand and implement the building blocks for lasting change.&amp;nbsp;
This week we focus on CONSISTENCY - the drum beat in the background that keeps you going that all high performers need. In this episode we feature guests including: Jamie Peacock (Ep157) - Never Fail Twice: https://pod.fo/e/14af62
Sir Ian Mceechan (Ep72) - World Class Basics: https://pod.</description></item><item><title>E173 - Ross Clark: Prepare to meet the real Rylan | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880103/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 00:00:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rylan is a television and radio broadcaster. In this interview, Rylan shares the differences between Rylan, his public personality, and Ross, who he is in his private life. Today, Ross joins us, leaving Rylan behind and opening up in a way you’ve never heard before. He shares how he overcame his breakdown and serious depression, by taking it step by step and focusing on micro-achievements.&amp;nbsp;
Ross takes us through his career and personal journey, from his sudden rise to fame after his first appearance on X-Factor, how he turned being pigeon-holed as a ‘joke’ into a 10 year career and how he feels he is finally experiencing adulthood.</description></item><item><title>The Year of Change: Week Two - Motivation | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880104/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 01:00:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880104/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is our second episode in our special mini-series focusing on change. Rethinking how we can create change and helping you understand and implement the building blocks for lasting change.&amp;nbsp;
These short episodes every Friday in January look at some ideas which might help you to break that cycle featuring expert advice from our guests.&amp;nbsp;
In Week One we focussed on goals (listen here: https://pod.fo/e/15b825&amp;nbsp;). This week we look at MOTIVATION - the why we do anything.</description></item><item><title>E172 - Adrian Gore: Building a business empire on a core purpose | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880105/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 00:00:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adrian Gore is a businessman, entrepreneur, founder and CEO of multi-billion dollar company Discovery Holdings with 40 million customers around the world. Discovery is the parent company of Vitality. The Vitality Programme is the world’s largest incentive-based health promotion programme designed to encourage and reward people for having good lifestyle habits with a focus on prevention and wellness instead of curative care. Discovery was names in the top 5 companies changing the world by Fortune Magazine.</description></item><item><title>E171 - Mark Manson: How to give a f*ck about the right things | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880106/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 00:00:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mark Manson is a bestselling author best known for his book The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F**k, selling over 10 million copies worldwide. This episode dives deep into what it means to lead a great life, exploring questions such as, how to focus on the things we care about and shut out the rest? How to create a sense of purpose? How to prevent suffering more than you need to?</description></item><item><title>The Year of Change: Week One - Setting Goals | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880107/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 01:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880107/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a special mini-series focusing on change. Rethinking how we can create change and helping you understand and implement the building blocks for lasting change. If you’ve become used to setting New Year's resolutions which you don’t meet then you’re not alone.&amp;nbsp;
Jake and Damian have put together a short series of episodes to look at some ideas which might help you to break that cycle featuring expert advice from our guests.</description></item><item><title>E170 - Courtney Black: The Story I Haven't Told About My Fitness Empire | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880108/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 00:01:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Courtney Black is a fitness influencer, Sunday Times best selling author and the owner of one of the most successful UK fitness apps, ‘Courtney Black Fitness’. Courtney believes that high performance is 'being successful at something that you are truly authentic with', a motto she has employed in the building of her fitness empire. In this episode, Courtney shares how she scaled her business, utilising her social media following to grow her brand and having to change direction due to the pandemic.</description></item><item><title>Adventurer Oli France On Finding Light In The Darkest Places | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880109/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 01:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Oli France has led many expeditions, guiding groups through some of the world’s most hostile destinations, from Syria to Iraq, Somalia to Siberia, Congo to Yemen. Here, he has encountered countless bleak situations.&amp;nbsp;He has been caught in a 6.9 magnitude earthquake, held at gunpoint, detained for 5 days on the Afghan border and severely ill with meningitis, while facing spies, interrogations, militia groups, avalanches and more. All this, while attempting to complete intrepid journeys across the globe.</description></item><item><title>Lessons From The Year: The Most Impactful Of 2022 | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880110/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 01:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join Jake and Damian as they look back at the guests who have joined us in 2022 and highlight three key takeaways from the whole year after speaking to over 80 guests. Not an easy task! Listen to see who made the list, their key lesson and why it was chosen.&amp;nbsp;
You can listen to their full episodes via the links below;&amp;nbsp;
Bear Gyrlls: https://pod.fo/e/10702c
Vicky Pattison: https://pod.fo/e/105426</description></item><item><title>Jake on Embracing The Mundane And Ordinary | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880111/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Christmas from everyone at High Performance! Today Jake reflects on 2022 and delivers a short message for the start of a new year. If we break down an average life in numbers, from sunrise to sunset, taking in account the snoozing and everything in between - we have on approximately 5 hours a day to live our life. We need to embrace the mundane and thrive in the ordinary moments.</description></item><item><title>E169 - Mat Fraser, CrossFit legend: Being disciplined when no one is watching | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880112/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 01:00:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mat Fraser is a retired CrossFit athlete and legend of the sport. He is the first athlete to have won five CrossFit Games titles consecutively from 2016 - 2020. After breaking his back in two places as an Olympic hopeful weightlifter, Mat was told he'd never be able to lift again. In this episode he shares how he has overcome his setbacks through hard work and discipline. Discipline is a crucial aspect of Mat’s work, most importantly, being disciplined when no one is watching.</description></item><item><title>E168 - Barry Hearn: 10 life lessons that made me a multi-millionaire | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880113/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 00:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Barry Hearn OBE is a sporting events promoter and the president and founder of Matchroom Sport. Barry is involved in many sports including snooker, darts, pool and golf. Barry’s ‘10 rules for life’ have carried him through his career and personal life, today he shares them with Jake and Damian. These rules include: it’s better to be lucky than good looking; tell the truth, it’s easier than telling lies and life begins with smiles and ends with tears.</description></item><item><title>E167 - Nick Littlehales, elite sleep coach: Rethink what you know on sleep | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880114/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 00:03:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Expert sleep coach Nick Littlehales joins us for the second episode of our special series with WHOOP, speaking to world leading experts who can positively impact you and the life you live.&amp;nbsp;
Nick causes Jake and Damian to rethink how they look at their sleep patterns for high performance and provides practical tips we can all use for improving sleep patterns.&amp;nbsp;
Nick has worked with elite sports teams from Team Sky to Manchester United on improving performance through sleep patterns.</description></item><item><title>E166A - Michael Ball and Alfie Boe: How to prepare like it’s nothing, and deliver like it’s everything | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880115/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 00:07:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael Ball &amp;amp; Alfie Boe are a musical duo that have been recording music together since 2016,&amp;nbsp;their most recent record ‘Together in Vegas’ is their sixth studio album. They are known for their complimentary voices and opposing personalities.
This conversation comes to you in two parts: Part One is with Michael and Alfie together,&amp;nbsp;delving into how to handle rejection, the benefits and challenges of working in a team and how to master your craft.</description></item><item><title>E166B - Alfie Boe: The power of knowing it’ll be alright | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880116/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 00:01:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880116/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is Part Two of our podcast with Alfie Boe and Michael Ball where Jake and Damian talk to Alfie alone. This conversation is a deep exploration into Alfie’s mental health struggles, his time in rehab and the loss of his father.&amp;nbsp;
In Part One (go listen now on link below) Michael and Alfie delve into how to handle rejection, the benefits and challenges of working in a team and how to master your craft.</description></item><item><title>E165 - Dr Hazel Wallace: Your health is in your hands | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880117/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 01:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880117/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a first in a special series we have created with WHOOP speaking to world leading experts who can positively impact you and the life you live.&amp;nbsp;
Our first guest is Dr Hazel Wallace, medical doctor, registered nutritionist, best-selling author and founder of The Food Medic.&amp;nbsp;Food is more than just our fuel, but our energy source and something we have control over. Dr Hazel will help inform the decisions you make with the food you eat.</description></item><item><title>E164 - Adam Grant: Why you should stop trying to prove yourself and start trying to improve yourself | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880118/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 00:19:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam Grant is an organisational psychologist, author, professor and host of podcast ‘Work Life’. His work focuses on how people can find motivation and meaning, rethink assumptions and live more creative and generous lives.&amp;nbsp;
In this episode they focus on the best way to deal with criticism and feedback, why we should be fuelling our growth instead of our ego and why Adam’s close circle is made up of ‘disagreeable givers’.</description></item><item><title>5 Key Lessons From Within The England Camp | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880119/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 01:00:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880119/</guid><description>Podcast Description As we approach the last 16 of the World Cup, Jake and Damian jump into the rich archive of guests and bring out the key lessons learnt from the people who have featured in World Cup football including Gareth Southgate, Glenn Hoddle, Pippa Grange, Gary Lineker and Eric Dier.
Whatever happens over the next 2 weeks, we know that there will be judgements and opinions offered on why teams succeed or fail.</description></item><item><title>E163: George Russell - From penpal to podium: how one email changed my life | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880120/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 01:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880120/</guid><description>Podcast Description George Russell is a British racing driver, currently competing in Formula 1 for Mercedes. In this conversation, George reveals why he gave up formal education at 14 to pursue racing; he shares how he first made contact with Toto Wolff and he speaks about the dangerous crash he was in and the impact it has had on him.
An advocate of surrounding yourself with positivity, making hard choices and creating opportunities, there is a lot to learn from George’s attitude which can be taken into all areas of life.</description></item><item><title>Gabby Bernstein’s self-care practice ‘Rage on a Page’ | Bitesize #85 | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880121/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 01:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880121/</guid><description>Podcast Description These bitesize episodes focus on the greatest lessons we’ve learnt from the guests we've had on the podcast.&amp;nbsp;
This week we jump back to episode 107 with bestselling author, motivational speaker, podcast host and self-proclaimed “spirit junkie” Gabby Bernstein. Gabby shared with us her process of overcoming trauma. One effective exercise she described was ‘Rage on a Page’, based in the teachings of&amp;nbsp;Dr John Sarno who wrote a lot about how our physical conditions are psychosomatic.</description></item><item><title>E162 - World Cup Roundtable: Rio Ferdinand, Peter Crouch &amp; Joe Cole | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880122/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 01:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880122/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Jake and Damian are hosting a World Cup Special Roundtable with football legends, Rio Ferdinand, Peter Crouch and Joe Cole discussing what it's really like pulling on an England shirt. In this episode they discuss the differences between their generation and the current England team and how the lack of structure and leadership in their tactics and team affected their results.&amp;nbsp;
Rio, Peter and Joe reflect on the beginning of their careers, discussing the struggle of coming to terms with such an amazing achievement and the pressure that comes along with it.</description></item><item><title>Culture Coach Dr Pippa Grange on the importance of vulnerability | Bitesize #84 | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880123/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 01:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880123/</guid><description>Podcast Description These bitesize episodes focus on the greatest lessons we’ve learnt from the guests we've had on the podcast.&amp;nbsp;
This week we go back to episode 103 with sports psychologist and culture coach Dr Pippa Grange. Pippa was appointment by the FA as its Head of People and Team Development with the England football team and worked with the players during the buildup to the successful World Cup in 2018 on relationships, getting the players to drop their mask and work with greater cohesion.</description></item><item><title>E161 - Tyson Fury: Why I want to stop boxing, but I can’t | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880124/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 00:05:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tyson Fury, also known as The Gyspy King, is a professional boxer and the two-time World Heavyweight Champion. In this episode they dive into Tyson’s mental health struggles, his challenging childhood and the dangerous nature of obsession. They explore the difference between Tyson Fury and the Gypsy King, Tyson is a father, son, mental health patient and how the Gypsy King is mental concrete, unbeatable. Although Tyson has celebrated the highest-highs, he has also suffered the lowest-lows, with the most monumental events in his life leading into deep depression and suicidal thoughts.</description></item><item><title>Will Ahmed On The Biggest Lesson Learnt From The World's Greatest Athletes | Bitesize #83 | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880125/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 01:00:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880125/</guid><description>Podcast Description These bitesize episodes focus on the greatest lessons we’ve learnt from the guests we've had on the podcast.&amp;nbsp;
This week we go back to episode 86 with WHOOP founder Will Ahmed (https://pod.fo/e/f256a) and hear the biggest lesson he’s learnt from working with some of the world’s greatest athletes including LeBron James and Michael Phelps, and why passion can help build a multi-billion dollar business.&amp;nbsp;
We have also partnered with WHOOP to bring you an amazing competition where you can win: * WHOOP 12-month membership plus accessory bundle (worth over £350)&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>E160 - Eddie Howe: Turnaround: how to improve a culture | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880126/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 01:00:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eddie Howe is a professional football manager and former player, he is currently the head coach of Newcastle United. In this episode they discuss the difficult period Eddie experienced after leaving Bournemouth, likening it to a grieving period. During his year out, he was unsure if he would ever return to managing players, but he quickly found himself noting down training lessons until it consumed his everyday life.&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>E159 - Sam Tomkins: What comes easy, doesn’t last. What lasts, doesn’t come easy | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880127/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 00:24:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880127/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the last of our short series, inspired by the Rugby League World Cup, we're joined by the humble, hard-working and high-performing Sam Tomkins, the captain and talisman of England’s men’s team who are aiming to win the coveted trophy later this month.
&amp;nbsp;
In Sam Walker’s brilliant book, Captain Class, he identified that the best teams have great captains, those who play on the edge, make others better and step up at crucial moments.</description></item><item><title>Brian Pennie: How to Pause and Create Space During Emotionally Challenging Events | HP Circle | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880128/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 01:00:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880128/</guid><description>Podcast Description This month on the High Performance Circle we speak to the incredible Brian Pennie. On October 8 2013, Brian experienced his first day clean after 15 years of chronic heroin addiction. Since embracing his second chance at life, he has become a doctor of neuroscience and psychology.
Whether it's our career, our relationships, our health, or more global concerns, we all face challenges in life. However, this is not where our struggles lie.</description></item><item><title>E158 - Max Whitlock: Why even the most successful winners can struggle | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880129/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 01:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Whitlock is a six-time Olympic winning artistic gymnast. He became Britain's first ever Olympic gold medalist in artistic gymnastics in the 2016 Olympics. In this episode they dive deep into mental health, Max’s fear of failure and the pressures he faced as an Olympic gymnast. Max speaks openly about his battle with depression, how he struggled when gymnastics was removed from his life and how important self improvement and setting new goals has been in his recovery.</description></item><item><title>E157 - Jamie Peacock: Being the best at the things that require no talent | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880130/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 23:30:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880130/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the third of our series to celebrate the Rugby League World Cup, we are delighted to welcome&amp;nbsp;Jamie&amp;nbsp;Peacock, a man who has burnished his legendary status within the sport, by consistently doing “the things that require no talent” at the very moments when the pressure is at its greatest, the margins are at their narrowest and the competition is at its fiercest. In turn, he has acquired a medal haul which would fill a museum.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #82 | Brad Sugars: Grow into your goals | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880131/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880131/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s bitesize comes from a live audience conversation with bestselling author, business coach and ActionCOACH owner Brad Sugars.&amp;nbsp;
If you’re listening to this as an entrepreneur who’s just starting, struggling or in a difficult place - that’s exactly where Brad has been and why his valuable lessons can help.&amp;nbsp;
The audio isn’t as great as normal due to being recorded at a live event, but we loved the chat with Brad so much we wanted you to hear it.</description></item><item><title>E156 - Ryan Holiday: The Stoics Guide to High Performance | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880132/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ryan Holiday is an author, most well known for his philosophical insights in The Daily Stoic. For Jake, this conversation was “the single most exciting episode” they have recorded so far. They discuss everything Stoic, from ego to discipline and much more. Ryan shares how having a strong sense of who you are is crucial, having a set of key priorities will put you in the right direction, rather than following the flow of everyone else.</description></item><item><title>E155 - Lindsey Burrow: Finding reasons to live | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880133/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 23:27:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880133/</guid><description>Podcast Description High performance is many things too many people. For some, it's winning the coveted prizes. For others, it's being held in the highest esteem. Sometimes, it's about showing up, day after day, being courageous in the face of adversity.&amp;nbsp;
Today's High Performance Podcast guest is one half of an incredible team who have achieved all those definitions of high performance. It’s our privilege to welcome Lindsey Burrow as the latest guest in our series to celebrate the Rugby League World Cup.</description></item><item><title>E154 - Kevin Ellis: Building a culture that motivates talent | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880134/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880134/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the last episode in our CEO Series, in which we will be deep diving into what it takes to be a CEO.
Kevin Ellis is Chair and Senior Partner of PwC UK. Starting his career as a graduate, he has now worked for PwC for 38 years. In this episode they discuss Kevin's experiences of leadership, touching on the importance of nurturing a culture that motivates talented people, accepting difficult feedback, and creating a legacy by lifting others up - ensuring the success of the business for generations to come.</description></item><item><title>E153 - Danny Cipriani: The power of vulnerability and empathy | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880135/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 00:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Danny Cipriani is a professional rugby player, he has played for England, Bath and Gloucester among others. In this episode, Danny takes Jake and Damian through his life - the struggles he faced growing up as a “council house boy” in a private school, coming from a single parent family and the tragedy that has shaped him. He expresses how crucial empathy is and how although people shy away from difficult conversations they are the most important to have.</description></item><item><title>E152 - Sam Burgess: How you do anything, is how you do everything | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880136/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 09:27:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880136/</guid><description>Podcast Description We at HP are hugely excited for the start of the Rugby League World Cup 2021 so sent the Professor to record a series of interviews with some of the sports greatest names, where they share the insights, lessons and techniques they have used to scale their chosen heights.
In the first of this series, we welcome the magnificent Sam Burgess, the unassuming lad from Bradford who became a modern day gladiator in an unforgiving business.</description></item><item><title>E151 - Emma Sinclair: Why generosity pays so well | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880137/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 00:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880137/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the fourth episode in our CEO Series, in which we will be deep diving into what it takes to be a CEO.
Emma Sinclair is the CEO of EnterpriseAlumni and was the youngest person to IPO on the London Stock Exchange aged 29. She was a regular contributor to The Telegraph, UNICEF’s first Business Mentor and has been awarded an MBE for her Services to Entrepreneurship. In this episode Emma shares how she was constantly finding ways into finance and entrepreneurship, from putting her student loan into the stock market to consistently working harder than she needed to.</description></item><item><title>E150 - Danny Gray: Why we struggle and how to find help | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880138/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 00:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880138/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today is #WorldMentalHealthDay and so we are releasing a special episode where Jake, Damian and our guest, Danny Gray, get vulnerable about their mental health. It is so important to have open and honest conversations with those around us about mental health.&amp;nbsp;
Danny Gray, is founder of the mental health social media platform JAAQ and the pioneering men's makeup brand War Paint For Men. JAAQ offers reliable information on mental health issues from experts and credible sources.</description></item><item><title>E149 - Deborah Cadman: Why walking in the shoes of others can make you a better leader | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880139/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 00:00:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880139/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the third episode in our CEO Series, in which we will be deep diving into what it takes to be a CEO.
Deborah Cadman OBE is the current CEO of Birmingham City Council, Deborah has worked in public services for over 30 years and was appointed OBE for her services to local government. In this episode they discuss how crucial mentorship and building a supportive community is.</description></item><item><title>E148 - Ben Towers, leading young entrepreneur: Age is just a number | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880140/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ben Towers is co-founder of Happl, a platform with a mission to connect employees and tackle ill-mental health. Ben started his first company at the age of 11, after finishing school for the day he would spend the evening working to improve his business. In this episode Ben shares an insight to his mindset at such a young age and how parents can encourage and affirm their children’s goals.</description></item><item><title>E147 - Alex Scott: Walking into the light | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880141/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 00:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex Scott MBE is a sports presenter, pundit and former professional football player. She played for Arsenal and made 140 appearances for the England women’s national football team. In this episode, Alex reveals how she has dealt with fear from her childhood and through her career - witnessing abuse and being vilified through social media - and how her mindset has enabled her to reach a place of freedom.</description></item><item><title>E146 - Greg Jackson, CEO of Octopus Energy Group. | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880142/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 00:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880142/</guid><description>Podcast Description This the second episode in our CEO Series, in which we will be deep diving into what it takes to be a CEO.
Greg Jackson is the founder and CEO of Octopus Energy Group, which currently has over 3.1 million UK customers. Octopus are on a mission to bring cheaper, greener power to all. In this episode Greg shares not only what it means to be a successful leader and team player, but how to live a more authentic life altogether.</description></item><item><title>E145 - Kenton Cool: Finding your inner depths in the death zone | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880143/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 00:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kenton Cool is an English mountaineer, a performance coach and co-founder of In Cool Company. He has climbed Everest a record 16 times and, among many other accomplishments, he kicked off the 2012 Olympics’ when he fulfilled an 88-year old pledge to take a gold medal from the 1924 Olympic Games to the top of Everest.&amp;nbsp;
In this episode Kenton, Jake and Damian discuss how Kenton deals with ‘the death zone’ whilst on an expedition and the uncontrollables that comes with it.</description></item><item><title>E144 - Amanda Blanc: Finding your voice and speaking up | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880144/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880144/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is the start of our CEO Series, in which we will be deep diving into what it takes to be a CEO.
Amanda Blanc is a Welsh businesswoman and the current CEO of Aviva, stepping into the role in July 2020. Amanda grew up in Rhondda valley in Wales, both her grandparents were miners. In this episode she shares how her childhood in Rhondda instilled in her the importance of community, freedom, happiness and fun.</description></item><item><title>E143 - Mo Gawdat: The infinite power of gratitude | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880145/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mo Gawdat is an Egyptian author and entrepreneur. Previously he held the position of Chief Business Officer for Google X, he is now host of the popular podcast Slow Mo. Mo is known for creating the happiness equation. Mo has co-founded more than 20 businesses, and continues to mentor ten start-ups at one time.
In this episode Mo discusses how the death of his beloved son Ali, began his search for happiness and doing good.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #81 | Jo Malone: Bad times are not forever | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880146/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our chat with the irrepressible, inspirational and incisive Jo Malone (ep45) was one of the most moving interviews which we have been lucky to do on High Performance.&amp;nbsp;
Jo is a household name and one of the world’s most successful businesswomen. There aren’t many people who haven’t had a product of hers in their home at some point.&amp;nbsp;
Her quiet wisdom, including such golden nuggets that tough times don't last forever, is one which we regularly revisit.</description></item><item><title>E142 - Jost Capito: The upside of having nothing to prove | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880147/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 00:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jost Capito is a German Motorsport manager and current CEO and Team Principal of Williams Racing Formula One Team. He joined Williams during Covid, in this episode he shares the difficulties that came with joining then and how he cultivates a family feel in a large company, where many employees work remotely.&amp;nbsp;
Jost has an open door policy and chooses not to use an office, he discusses with Jake and Damian how important it is for his employees to feel valued and listened to.</description></item><item><title>E141 - Ellie Simmonds OBE: The unseen costs of being a pioneer in sport | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880148/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 00:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ellie Simmonds OBE is a former Paralympian swimmer. She won two gold medals for Great Britain at the age of 13 at the 2008 Paralympics; has many world and European titles and was awarded an MBE at the age of 14. In this episode, Ellie discusses what it was like to deal with immense pressure at a young age and how crucial a good team is.&amp;nbsp;
She was born with Achondroplasia (a form of Dwarfism), and discusses with Jake and Damian why it is so important to talk about disabilities in an open and upfront way.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #80 | Sir Clive Woodward: The Similarities Between Sport and Business | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880149/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 00:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880149/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s Bitesize, we’re returning to episode 28 with Sir Clive Woodward. The head coach who led England’s rugby players to World Cup glory in Australia in 2003.&amp;nbsp;
Clive discusses the similarities between sport and business, how he approaches running a small business, why personal relationships are so crucial and much more.&amp;nbsp;
Jake takes us through an in depth look at Clive’s answers, offering some inspiring and thoughtful insight.</description></item><item><title>E140 - Sunil Patel: The true cost of building a business worth millions. | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880150/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 00:52:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880150/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on The High Performance Podcast, we speak to Sunil Patel, the Co-founder and CEO of Whisper, an award winning production company to Sunil created with High Performance host Jake Humphrey.&amp;nbsp;
In this episode Sunil openly shares with us the highs and lows of being obsessed with your work and how this can impact your private life. He also goes into depth on how teamwork is at the heart of every decision he makes, and the importance of treating people with respect no matter what level you are operating at.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #79 | Kevin Sinfield: Getting the best out of the people around you | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880151/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 00:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880151/</guid><description>Podcast Description We had the immense good fortune to spend an afternoon in the company of Kevin Sinfield for episode 42, a leader who provided&amp;nbsp;so many golden nuggets of information. In the hard sport of rugby, we chatted about the importance of soft stuff: the ability to show our emotions, let people know we care and the power of friendship. In this key takeaway, Kevin talks about the moment as a young boy, he realised in order to succeed he needed to get the best out of the people around it and the value it carried for the rest of his life.</description></item><item><title>E139 - Zak Brown, McLaren CEO: How to make the big decisions in F1 | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880152/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 00:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880152/</guid><description>Podcast Description A special bonus episode for you this week with former racing driver and now Chief Executive Officer of McLaren Racing, Zak Brown.&amp;nbsp;
He shares his story from wannabe racer to McLaren boss, and highlights the importance of the attention to detail, surrounding yourself with mentors, and making tough decisions! With McLaren hitting the news this week with team changes, he also reflects on whether he could have done anything different.</description></item><item><title>E138 - James Patterson, world's best-selling author: 75 years of learning has taught me this… | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880153/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 00:00:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880153/</guid><description>Podcast Description James Patterson is one of the world’s most successful authors, having sold over four hundred million books.&amp;nbsp;
In this episode James takes us through the challenges of his career and the ‘Eureka moment’ that made him quit marketing and become a full time writer. Having co-authored books with Bill Clinton and Dolly Parton, James explores how to best build relationships, earn trust and the importance of laughter. Having grown-up working class, and gradually made his way to the wealthy upper class, James explains how authenticity is key within his work, and personal, life.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #78 | Ben Francis: The values that defined the culture at Gymshark | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880154/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 00:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880154/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week's bitesize lesson from the archive we jump back to episode 69 with the founder and CEO of leading fitness brand Gymshark, Ben Francis. We asked Ben to define the values which he enshrines within his business. His answer was compelling, illuminating and inspiring.
For the full episode with Ben Francis - listen or watch: https://www.thehighperformancepodcast.com/podcast/benfrancis - - - - - -
Pre-order the new High Performance Daily Journal - 365 ways to become your best!</description></item><item><title>E137 - Nick Cox: Why the future IS bright at Manchester United | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880155/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 23:45:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick Cox is the Head of Academy at Manchester United. He has previously been an Academy Manager at Sheffield United FC. In this episode, Nick shares with us the key to high performance - people and relationships. For Nick, high performance is about finding those small windows of alignment where you are in flow, and then when you are not in that state your time should be spent rebuilding to return to it.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #77 | Kelly Jones: Make time to understand the full picture | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880156/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 00:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Singer-songwriter Kelly Jones, frontman of the Stereophonics, opened up with us about his relationship with the press after his childhood friend and former band member Stuart Cable sadly passed.
The key lesson: Make the time to understand the full picture. It is not always as it seems.
Listen or watch the full episode with Kelly, episode 31: https://www.thehighperformancepodcast.com/podcast/kelly-jones&amp;nbsp;
- - - - - -
You can pre-order our the brand new book, the ‘High Performance Daily Journal’ - 365 ways to become your best!</description></item><item><title>E136 - Frank Lampard: Why I'm stronger from a setback | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880157/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 04:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880157/</guid><description>Podcast Description It has been 2 years since Jake and Damian first sat down with Frank Lampard. In this new episode the three of them return to their previous discussion to see what has changed, what has stayed the same and the steps he’s been taking to change his life…
Frank is the current manager of Premier League club Everton and former Chelsea manager and their record goal scorer. In this episode Frank reflects on his time at Chelsea, the things he was right about and what he could have done better.</description></item><item><title>Gemma Morgan: (WO)MAN UP! | HP CIRCLE EXCLUSIVE | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880158/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 00:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880158/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trigger Warning: Themes of trauma, sexual assault and suicide.
﻿Gemma Morgan began her career serving as an officer in the British Army and is now a speaker, writer and leadership coach. In this exclusive extract from this month's High Performance Circle keynote, Gemma exposes the life-changing impact that culture can have on our performance and wellbeing. Her message is hard-hitting and uncompromising - “Safety came from minimising myself, from denying large parts of me.</description></item><item><title>E135 - Owen O'Kane: Why self care is vital for high performance | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880159/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Owen O’Kane is a psychotherapist, former NHS Mental Health Lead and author of the best-selling book, How To Be Your Own Therapist. Owen grew up in Northern Ireland during the Troubles, he struggled to accept his sexuality as a gay man - once even trying to be 'healed' of his homosexuality during a visit to Lourdes. He has had a varied career, from training to be a priest, to working in palliative care - this is reflected in Owen’s open and well-rounded understanding of humanity.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #76 | Vicky Pattison: Your past does not define you | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880160/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 00:00:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880160/</guid><description>Podcast Description We were joined on episode 99 by Vicky Pattison, author and TV star and the reaction was incredible. The podcast was about challenging pre-conceptions and embracing a growth mindset. She shared, with real honesty and candidness, the perils of not investing time to work on developing your self esteem; the importance of managing your inner circle; and the benefits of numbering your days.
We recommend you watch or listen the full episode with Vicky if you haven't: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Introducing High Performance Plus! | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880161/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 19:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880161/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sign up for High Performance Plus here:&amp;nbsp;https://highperformanceplus.supercast.com/ and apple.co/highperformance
Welcome to High Performance Plus! Our brand new premium podcast service created for people who want to support the podcast, listen to ad-free episodes and have access to exclusive bonus content so we can get you even closer to a life of high performance.
We'll ask our guests extra questions, just for you and keep recording when the mic stops so you will hear those slightly more intimate conversations at the end of each record.</description></item><item><title>E134 - Alan Stein Jr, performance coach: Why mastering the basics matters | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880162/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880162/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alan Stein Jr. is a performance coach, speaker and author with a passion for helping others change behaviours. Alan spent 15+ years working with the highest performing basketball players on the planet including NBA superstars Kevin Durant, Steph Curry, and Kobe Bryant. Alan has a masterful ability to translate what he’s learnt from these high performers and provide real value for others with simple, inspiring language.&amp;nbsp;
Alan shares what he's learnt from working with the best how and how they hone their off-court skills and what the rest of us can learn from them and implement immediately.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #75 | Chrissie Wellington: The power of perspective | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880163/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 00:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880163/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week's bitesize comes from the incredible Chrissie Wellington, a former British professional triathlete and four-time Ironman Triathlon World Champion. She held all three world and championship records relating to ironman triathlon races and remains the world record holder for Ironman distance (8hrs,18 mins). Chrissie's story is utterly incredible. Her name - and most importantly, her lessons - should be well known. In this clip Chrissie talks to Jake and Damian about the power of perspective.</description></item><item><title>E133 - Marcus Wareing: How to stand the heat in the kitchen | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880164/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880164/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marcus Wareing is a Michelin-starred chef, ‘Masterchef: The Professionals’ judge and restaurant owner. Marcus is one of the most respected and acclaimed chefs in the world.
During this conversation, Marcus cites his father as the definition of high performance. Marcus’ admiration of his fathers hard work and determination inspired him to keep pursuing being a chef. He also shares with us where his mindset of focus stems from, how the pandemic transformed him and the real story behind his fallout with Gordan Ramsey, and what he learnt from it.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #74 | Tim Wigmore: Why younger siblings are better at sport | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880165/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 00:00:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Little siblings statistically have a significantly greater chance of becoming elite athletes….
This week we have an exclusive extract from an incredible keynote speech from our members club The High Performance Circle with sports journalist and author Tim Wigmore.
Tim unveils his research and explores why being a little sibling helps so much - younger siblings are challenged more, helping them develop the skills and psychological traits that athletes need - and how children without older siblings can enjoy the same advantages.</description></item><item><title>E132 - Steph Houghton MBE (Re-Release): Breaking barriers to become a professional footballer | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880166/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 00:00:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880166/</guid><description>Podcast Description In December 2020, we had an amazing conversation with the current captain of England and Manchester City at the time - Steph Houghton. Unfortunately due to injury, Steph didn’t make the current Euros squad but she is known as one of the most recognisable faces in women’s football.
With the Women’s Euros in full swing, we are releasing this fantastic episode to highlight just how far the women’s game has come on, but what it has taken footballer’s like Steph to get to this point.</description></item><item><title>E131 - Roxie Nafousi: Manifesting your best self | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880167/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 00:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Roxie Nafousi is a manifesting expert, self-development coach and author. Her recent book Manifest is a Sunday Times Best Seller, and reached the ‘Top 5’ for ten consecutive weeks.&amp;nbsp;
In this episode she shares with us how she turned her life around, from parties, drugs and recklessness to now living her dream life. Manifestation has played a key role in the changes in Roxie’s life, she talks through what manifestation is and how you can practice it in your everyday life.</description></item><item><title>E130 - ‘I AM…With Jonny Wilkinson’ Collaboration Special | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880168/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880168/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are extremely excited to have teamed up with Jonny Wilkinson and his podcast ‘I AM…’ to bring you a very special collaboration episode - revisiting our old conversation and exploring new ground. After such a phenomenal reaction to our first chat with Jonny (EP23), we wanted to return to the conversation after almost two years of reflection. Jonny is now the first ever guest who has appeared on the podcast twice!</description></item><item><title>I AM...With Jonny Wilkinson collaboration: EXCLUSIVE PREVIEW | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880169/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 00:00:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880169/</guid><description>Podcast Description He was the guest that changed everything for us, and now we go again! Listen to this exclusive preview of our special collaboration with the podcast 'I AM...with Jonny Wilkinson'. Jake and Damian tease the full episode, which is released on Thursday 7th July!
- - - - - -
Watch all our episodes on YouTube : https://www.youtube.com/c/HighPerformancePodcast/videos
Follow us on Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/highperformance/
Follow us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/highperformancepodcast</description></item><item><title>E129 - AJ Tracey: How my revenge list took me to the very top | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880170/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 00:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880170/</guid><description>Podcast Description AJ Tracey (Ché Wolton Grant) is a British singer-songwriter, producer, platinum selling and Brit nominated artist. AJ is known for his campaigns for justice, especially his ongoing support of Grenfell United. He was cited as one of the main reasons young people in his area of West London began voting. In this episode he shares the priceless opportunity his mum gave him by supporting him for a year to pursue music and how important that parental belief was.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #73 | Phil Neville: You can't understand someone until you've walked in their shoes | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880171/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880171/</guid><description>Podcast Description An important message on this week’s bitesize with former Lionesses manager Phil Neville on equality.&amp;nbsp;
Having worked in women’s sport, Phil reflected on his realisation of how hard things were for his sister Tracey Neville, who was competing as an elite international netball player while Phil and his brother Gary were at Manchester United. What more could he have done…
Listen to the full excellent episode with Phil here (ep18): https://www.</description></item><item><title>E128 - Jos Buttler: How quiet leadership can conquer the world | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880172/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jos Buttler is a professional cricketer and currently the best white-ball batsmen in the world. In the recent Indian Premier League, Jos enjoyed one of the best forms in history as he ended the 2022 season with an aggregate score of 863 runs in 17 games, earning himself the Most Valuable Player award.&amp;nbsp;
Jos was also part of the England team that won the infamous 2019 Cricket World Cup and made the run-out during the Super Over which sealed victory in the final.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #72 | Jo Konta: Pain x resistance = suffering | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880173/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 04:00:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880173/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s special bitesize clip features the engaging and illuminating Jo Konta, former British No.1 women’s tennis player who won four singles titles, reached the semifinals of Wimbledon and rose to a world ranking of number 4.&amp;nbsp;
In this powerful clip we spoke about the loneliness of pursuing a path of excellence. The harsh, unforgiving spotlight of constant scrutiny and the struggle to maintain equilibrium and balance whilst engaged in the struggle to perform.</description></item><item><title>E127 - Dame Kelly Holmes (Re-Release): Be kind - everyone is fighting a battle you know nothing about. | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880174/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 00:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880174/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the week that Olympic champion Dame Kelly Holmes has bravely revealed she is gay, Jake &amp;amp; Damian revisit the conversation we recorded with Kelly before our podcast journey had even begun, and at a time Kelly has now admitted she was in a very tough place. Her story of Olympic golds, doubt, depression, self-harm, and injury is one you need to hear and is just remarkable. - - - - - -</description></item><item><title>E126: Gary Lineker - Biggest mistakes, greatest achievements and the power of being yourself | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880175/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 00:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880175/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gary Lineker is a former professional footballer and a current sports broadcaster. In this episode Gary shares with us how the crucial positive thinking and practicing gratitude was for his success. He shares that although he worked hard, he didn’t put loads of thought into living a high performance life - he attributes a lot of his success to good luck and waiting his turn. Gary didn’t worry about achieving success, but rather focused on the process.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #71 | Aldo Kane - Lessons from the Edge | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880176/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 00:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880176/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week's bitesize comes from Aldo Kane, a trained Royal Marines Sniper, world record breaker and extreme TV adventurer. From a life spent abseiling into erupting volcanos in the Democratic Republic of Congo, rowing the Atlantic, getting locked in a bunker for 10 days with zero daylight... he has learnt that with the right head game, no matter how hard it gets, you can get through anything life throws at you.</description></item><item><title>E125 - Ash Dykes: How to survive and thrive - lessons from near-death. | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880177/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 00:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880177/</guid><description>Podcast Description Extreme athlete and adventurer Ash Dykes is a&amp;nbsp;three-time world-first record holder&amp;nbsp;and motivational speaker. Ash was the first person to hike the entire length of the longest river in the world - the Yangtze River, which took a year to complete, the first to walk the entire length of Madagascar and the first to hike across Mongolia.
Ash has an unbelievably infectious passion for adventure and an incredible ability to inspire.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #70 | Joe Wicks: Don’t wait till your older till retire | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880178/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 00:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880178/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s bitesize we’re joined by the nation’s greatest PE teacher Joe Wicks.&amp;nbsp;
It’s a lesson that resonated with our hosts Jake and Damian - taking time out to spend&amp;nbsp;with your family and friends in real time.&amp;nbsp;
&amp;nbsp;- - - - -
Listen: https://pod.fo/e/11450c
Watch: https://youtu.be/1dJjHw8K5qU
This month’s HIGH PERFORMANCE CIRCLE newsletter is out!&amp;nbsp;This month includes a very special High Performance collaboration with Headspace and an offer of a FREE month.</description></item><item><title>E124 - Harpreet Kaur: The superpower of self-belief | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880179/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 00:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Harpreet Kaur is the owner and co-founder (with her sister) of Oh So Yum. She is best known as the recent winner of the UK Apprentice 2022.
Her straight talking and strong leadership qualities have been attributed to her success. She takes the view that too much pressure is put on young people to find their passions and that we don’t need to be passionate about our jobs to work hard and achieve great things.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #69 | Lord Richard Dannatt: Reconciling your career and personal ambitions | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880180/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 00:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880180/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the weekend of the Queen’s Platinum Jubilee, today’s bitesize features General the Lord Richard Dannatt, who concluded his forty year military career as the head of the British Army. His leadership and decision making affected hundreds of thousands.&amp;nbsp;
This clip features Lord Dannatt talking about how his faith was challenged as a soldier, and how ambition in the job can unsettle the work-life balance if unchecked.&amp;nbsp;
This episode had an incredible reaction and it’s easy to know why.</description></item><item><title>E123 - Steve Clarke (Re-release): World Cup play-off special | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880181/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880181/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the day (Wednesday 1st June) of the emotional World Cup play-off game between Scotland vs Ukraine, we revisit an edited version of our conversion with Scotland manager Steve Clarke. The game was postponed in March after Russia's invasion of Ukraine, so this is the first competitive match Ukraine have been able to play since the declaration of war.
Steve's greatest achievement has been reversing the years of underperformance of the national football team, taking them to their first major tournament in over 20 years, and determined for them not to be one tournament wonders.</description></item><item><title>E122 - Russell Kane: Lessons and learnings about authenticity | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880182/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 00:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880182/</guid><description>Podcast Description Russell Kane is a writer, comedian and actor, he’s best known for his stand-up specials and his appearances on panel shows. Russell shared that he believes “everyone… has an amazing skill and talent, however not everyone has the ability or luck to find it". He takes us through his challenging journey of finding success, from living in a mother and baby shelter to his life now.&amp;nbsp;
He discusses his relationship with his father and what effect it has had on the way he parents his children.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #68 | Dan Carter: How I found my personal purpose | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880183/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 00:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880183/</guid><description>Podcast Description This was a real highlight moment in our archive, a conversation with All Black great Dan Carter.&amp;nbsp;
This bitesize clip focuses on how Dan came across his own personal purpose in life. How he wanted to be an All Black and add to the legacy. The All Blacks call it their ‘Whakapapa’ - looking back at where you’ve come from to know where you’re going.&amp;nbsp;
Listen to the full episode where Dan showed just what you can achieve when you set ambitious goals, have self-belief, and relentlessly pursue the skills to help you achieve them.</description></item><item><title>E121 - Glenn Hoddle: The power of believing there is no such thing as death | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880184/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 00:00:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880184/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glenn Hoddle is a former footballer and manager, regarded as one of the most gifted of his generation. He helped Spurs win the FA Cup twice and the UEFA Cup in the 1980s as a player and took England to the World Cup in 1998 as the manager.&amp;nbsp;
In October 2018, Glenn collapsed on the set of BT Sport on his 61st birthday suffering a cardiac arrest and required a quadruple bypass.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #67 | Tom Daley: Feeling different gave me the strength to succeed | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880185/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880185/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Daley, one of Britain’s most recognised sportsmen, joined us for Ep5 and spoke about how his feelings of being different growing up gave him the strength to succeed.&amp;nbsp;
Tom’s fame transcends his sport - he lost his father to cancer in 2011, publicly came out as gay, got married, had a baby and has became a key spokesperson for LGBT+ rights. His example has shown that all forms of difference can lead us to be more empowered, and self-assured.</description></item><item><title>E120 - Vex King: Understanding how good vibes lead to high performance | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880186/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 00:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880186/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vex King is a motivational speaker, author and influencer. His work focuses on sharing spiritual knowledge, inspirational moments and, most importantly, practical solutions. Vex’s debut book, Good Vibes, Good Life was on The Sunday Times Bestseller list for over 100 weeks, selling over 1 million copies. Vex grew up suffering grief, violence, racism and homelessness.&amp;nbsp;
In this episode Vex discusses his disruptive childhood, the power of the internet and how and why he chooses happiness.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #66 | Eric Dier: The importance of clarity in communication | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880187/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 00:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880187/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week's bitesize lesson comes from England and Tottenham footballer Eric Dier who discusses the need for clear direction and clarity from the manager in order to be successful as a team. This decisiveness from leaders in Eric's life such as Mauricio Pochettino and Antonio Conte has made it easier for the team to perform and confront each other if needed.
Listen to the full episode with Eric, titled - 'the benefits of stepping outside your comfort zone', to hear the valuable lessons he's learnt from his career to date: https://www.</description></item><item><title>E119 - Lucy Easthope: Advice from an expert on overcoming disaster | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880188/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 00:00:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880188/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lucy Easthope has been working in disaster management and recovery for 22 years. She has worked on every major indident that has affected the U.K since the start of her role; 9/11, the July bombings, Grenfell Tower, the Covid-19 Pandemic and she is currently working on the war in Ukraine.&amp;nbsp;
In this episode Lucy shares the techniques she uses to deal with disasters that we can utilise within our own lives; breathing techniques, being present, embracing a healthy work/life balance.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #65 | Steve Morgan: One moment can change your life | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880189/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 06:46:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880189/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s bitesize clip we go back to episode 90 with businessman and philanthropist Steve Morgan. Steve founded Redrow, one of the UK’s most successful house-builders and also is the former owner of Wolverhampton Wanderers.
Through his foundation, Steve donated millions to help families during the pandemic and recently made a £50 million donation to help advance treatment and try to find a cure for type 1 diabetes, the largest-ever single gift in the UK for diabetes research.</description></item><item><title>E118 - Chase &amp; Status: How to harness the power of obsession | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880190/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880190/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chase &amp;amp; Status are an electronic music duo comprised of Saul Milton and Will Kennard. They have released five studio albums and have worked with the likes of Rhianna, PlanB and CeeLo Green. This year they will be releasing their 6th studio album.&amp;nbsp;
Saul and Will are known for their privacy, but in this conversation they open up about their failures and successes as artists, their intense work ethic and their obsession with music: “almost verging on a sort of sickness”.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #64 | Sean Dyche: Transferable skills outside of football | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880191/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 00:59:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880191/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s bitesize highlight comes from former Burnley manager Sean Dyche, one the longest serving Premier League managers, who explains the transferable skills he's learnt from football management that applies to the outside world.
Listen to the full episode with Sean: https://www.thehighperformancepodcast.com/podcast/sean-dyche
- - - - - - -
Check out our new weekly addition The Monday Motivation Newsletter. The purpose of&amp;nbsp;Monday Motivation&amp;nbsp;is to connect more regularly with you!</description></item><item><title>E117 - Greg Hoffman: Harnessing the power of emotion to achieve high performance | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880192/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 00:00:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880192/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s episode is a conversation with Greg Hoffman, leader, creative and author. Greg worked at NIKE for almost 30 years, his last role being Vice-President of Global Brand Creative and Marketing Innovation. Greg shares with us how being a bi-racial man who was adopted by two white parents shaped his life. His relationship with NIKE first began when he saw they were the only advertising company, using people of colour in their advertisements.</description></item><item><title>E116 - Steve Borthwick: Learning from experience | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880193/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 00:00:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880193/</guid><description>Podcast Description Steve Borthwick is the current head coach of the England men's national rugby team. Prior to this he was appointed Head Coach at Leicester Tigers in February 2020 after five seasons as Forwards Coach with England. As a player Steve made 240 appearances and won 57 caps for England, including two years as captain.
This episode will explore how Steve has used his experiences of being a Saracens captain, working as a forwards coach at England and Bristol Bears to shape his team, their culture and ultimately their success.</description></item><item><title>E115 - Lewis Morgan: How I made £100m in 8 years and learned there is no secret | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880194/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 00:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880194/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lewis Morgan, Gymshark co-founder and entrepreneur, joins us on this week’s episode. Lewis has been an entrepreneur since the age of 16, when he first began selling item within a video game. Since then he has created global brands, Gymshark is now valued at more than £1 billion. He offers his insights into business and life and how important family is to him.&amp;nbsp;
Lewis shares with us what he would do if he only had £1000 left to his name… the answer is amazing!</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #63 | Mary Portas: Why being bored can be good for you | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880195/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 00:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880195/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s bitesize highlight comes from retail and brand communication expert Mary Portas, who explains why boredom can be good for you, as it enables creativity and problem-solving by allowing the mind to wander and daydream.&amp;nbsp;
Listen to the full episode with Mary:https://www.thehighperformancepodcast.com/podcast/maryportas&amp;nbsp;
- - - - - - -
This month on the High Performance Circle... Oli Patrick joined us on The&amp;nbsp;High&amp;nbsp;Performance&amp;nbsp;Tour 2022 and gave a great keynote on the three things you can do to improve your wellbeing and operate at the top of your game.</description></item><item><title>E114 - Alex Sanderson: Leading by example (Gallagher Leadership Series) | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880196/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880196/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex&amp;nbsp;Sanderson is the Director of Rugby for Sale Sharks. Alex started his senior playing career at Sale in 1998 and went on to make 90 appearances for the club, with his leadership qualities earning him the club captaincy.
Alex isn’t a coach that just stands on the side-line, in his own words he “wants to be on the coalface to feel what the players are feeling, to understand what they’re going through”.</description></item><item><title>E113 - David Moyes: How to successfully learn from failure | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880197/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 00:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880197/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s episode is with former football player and professional coach, David Moyes. David is currently the manager of Premier League club West Ham United, having previously managed Preston North End, Everton, Manchester United, Real Sociedad and Sunderland.
In this episode David shares with us why and how he developed a positive mindset in recent years. As a leader, David offers insights into how to best lead a team, by creating a space of open communication and encouraging vulnerability within his players.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #62 | Hector Bellerin: Be like a candle | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880198/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 23:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880198/</guid><description>Podcast Description This was one of our absolute favourite&amp;nbsp;moments in our chat with the irrepressible Héctor&amp;nbsp;Bellerín, a football player with Real Betis - how and what you choose to value. Does a good day at work make you more valuable? Are you less valuable if you’re having a tough time?
If we view through the world through a binary lens - good/bad, right/wrong, win/lose - we miss the details, the nuances, the lessons we can use over the long term pursuit of high performance on our own terms.</description></item><item><title>E112 - Rob Baxter: Building Resilience to Deal with Stress (Gallagher Leadership Series) | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880199/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 23:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880199/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rob Baxter is the Director of Rugby for Exeter Chiefs, a club he played at for 14 years and captained for 10 years. Having won the European Rugby Championship in the 2019/20 season, this special episode will explore how Rob has installed resilience in himself and in his team to deal with the stress of competing as champions and to prepare for the tough seasons ahead.
&amp;nbsp;
Listen to Rob discuss what ‘A.</description></item><item><title>E111 - Rachel Botsman: What it really means to trust | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880200/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 00:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880200/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rachel Botsman is a trust expert, author and academic at Oxford University. Her books ‘What’s Mine is Yours’ and ‘Who Can You Trust?’ are critically acclaimed. Rachel was named one of the world’s 30 most Influential Management Thinkers by Thinkers50. She is also the host of the podcast Rethink Moments.&amp;nbsp;
In this episode, Rachel shares with us how to successfully speak in public: letting go of the need to be liked and focus on the giving.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #61 | John McAvoy : Let go of your ego | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880201/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880201/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s bitesize clip comes from a man who has lived two lives - former convicted armed robber turned elite athlete, John McAvoy.
John became the proud holder of three world records and seven British records in indoor rowing, all achieved in confinement.
John talks about the power of letting go of his ego to move forward.&amp;nbsp;
Listen to the full episode with John and&amp;nbsp;understand how we can all change our situation by changing our mindset: https://www.</description></item><item><title>E110 - Rangan Chatterjee: The key to happier living | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880202/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 00:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880202/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we are chatting with Dr. Rangan Chatterjee. Rangan is a British physician, author and host of the podcast ‘Feel Better, Live More’. He’s known for the TV show ‘Doctor in the House’ and his appearances on BBC Breakfast. Rangan shares with us the simple techniques he uses to lead a more fulfilling and happy life. For Rangan, the most important aspect of life is nourishing our relationships and having “unmasking conversations” in which we are vulnerable and open with each other.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #60 | Kate Richardson-Walsh : The feeling of being dropped | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880203/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 01:00:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880203/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s bitesize clip GB’s most capped hockey player talks to Jake and Damian about the crushing feeling of being dropped from the England U16 team and the advice her mum gave her - “what are you going to do about it?”
Kate was captain of GB women’s hockey teams for 13 years and was one of the many key drivers of the incredible team ethos and commitment that drove the GB team to a nail biting victory at the Rio Olympic Games.</description></item><item><title>E109 - Joe Wicks: Find purpose over profit | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880204/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 01:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880204/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joe Wicks is a fitness coach, presenter, influencer and author. He has achieved over 80 millions views of P.E With Joe, sold 4 million books and over 4.3 million Instagram followers. Although Joe grew up in an uncertain and sometimes challenging household, he has turned his trauma into a positive thing, challenging it in a productive way.&amp;nbsp;
In this episode we discuss Joe’s “addiction” to helping people to feel good - getting them up, moving and cooking.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #59 | Kasper Schmeichel : How to handle ego | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880205/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 01:00:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880205/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s bitesize clip Kasper talks to Jake and Damian about how to manage ego.&amp;nbsp;
Kasper Schmeichel, a Premier League winner with Leicester City, a club where he’s been the No.1 goalkeeper throughout the entirety of his time at King Power Stadium, where he’s also lifted Championship titles, as well as playing in the UEFA Champions League.
Listen and watch the full episode with Holly: https://www.thehighperformancepodcast.com/podcast/kasperschmeichel
- - - - -&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>EP108 - Lando Norris: The truth about life in Formula One | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880206/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 01:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880206/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s episode we chat with 22 year-old, British-Belgian racing driver Lando Norris. Lando shares with us how he does not take his privilege for granted, he sees the life given to him by his parents as an investment by them, something he needs to repay. We chat about self-doubt, family and the importance of kindness.&amp;nbsp;
Lando talks about how although he is his “own biggest critic”, he now knows when to give himself a pat on the back and allow time to celebrate.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #58 | Holly Tucker: Turn imposter syndrome into a superpower | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880207/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 01:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880207/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s bitesize takeaway features Not On The High Street&amp;nbsp;co-founder Holly Tucker, who tells Jake and Damian how she turned her imposter syndrome into a superpower.&amp;nbsp;
Holly is one of the UK’s most respected entrepreneurs and UK Ambassador to Small Creative Businesses.
Listen and watch the full episode with Holly: :https://www.thehighperformancepodcast.com/podcast/holly-tucker
- - - - -&amp;nbsp;
We have created a FREE resource pack for teachers! High Performance is delighted to partner with National Careers Week!</description></item><item><title>Get Into Teaching Special: The impact of teachers on our high performers | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880208/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 15:12:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880208/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this special bonus episode Jake and Damian discuss a some key clips in which our guests have shared the impact their teachers had on their high performance journeys.&amp;nbsp;
&amp;nbsp;
Listen to the episode to hear the stories shared by Lee Child, Evelyn Glennie, Kelly Holmes and music agent Charlie Pearce. Jake and Damian share and reflect on these inspiring stories and reflect on how teachers have impacted their lives.</description></item><item><title>E107 - Gabby Bernstein: Looking at your past to face your future with confidence | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880209/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 01:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880209/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gabby Bernstein is a bestselling author, motivational speaker, podcast host and self-proclaimed “spirit junkie”. She has penned over 9 books, including her newest release, ​​Happy Days: The Guided Path from Trauma to Profound Freedom and Inner Peace. Gaby turned to spirituality after “hitting rock bottom” and becoming sober.&amp;nbsp;
In this episode Gabby shares with us her process of overcoming trauma and how she has “chosen survival”.&amp;nbsp;
You can find Gabby’s new book here: https://www.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #57 | Jonny Wilkinson: Maintaining passion to find flow | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880210/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 01:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880210/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s bitesize comes from our game-changing episode with Jonny Wilkinson. A conversation in our history that still resonates with so many.
It was an intriguing morning with Jonny, exploring his understanding of how to achieve, maintain and sustain high performance. Lessons that have been hard earned by a career he described as “surviving”.
In this clip Jonny describes beginning his rugby career in a ‘flow state’ of opportunity and passion.</description></item><item><title>E106 - Anthony Taylor: Thinking correctly under pressure | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880211/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 01:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880211/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anthony Taylor is a current professional football referee. He has been a member of the Select Group of referees since the 2010/11 season, who officiate primarily in the Premier League.&amp;nbsp;
Anthony has been chosen to referee the FA Cup Final, League Cup Final, Play-Off Final and the UEFA Nations League Final.&amp;nbsp;But before football, Anthony's first career was as a prison officer at a category A jail.
On 12 June 2021, Anthony was the referee&amp;nbsp;for the&amp;nbsp;EURO 2020 group stage match between Finland and Denmark when Danish midfielder&amp;nbsp;Christian Eriksen collapsed on the pitch and required emergency treatment before being transferred to a local hospital and stabilised.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #56 | Sir Jason Kenny: Get the most out of the people around you | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880212/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 01:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880212/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s high performance bitesize nugget comes from Sir Jason Kenny, Britain's most decorated Olympian, who collected seven gold medals and two silvers across four Olympic Games.&amp;nbsp;
We frequently hear about athletes setting targets, imposing strict rules and striving for the next level of performance but Jason certainly showed that there is no one way to be a high performer.&amp;nbsp;
Jason describes the importance of getting the most out of the people around you.</description></item><item><title>E105 - Josh Taylor: The road to become an undisputed world champion | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880213/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 01:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880213/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this special bonus mid-week episode we speak to Scottish boxing world champion Josh Taylor. Josh made history in 2021 in becoming Britain's first undisputed world champion in the four-belt era. He's a boxer that hasn't had the recognition he deserves. They talk about courage, how following your dreams will enable you to live a life with no regrets, and how loving and taking care of yourself will result in happiness and a sense of fulfilment.</description></item><item><title>E104 - Steve Clarke: Playing with the expectation of success and not the fear of failure | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880214/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 01:00:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880214/</guid><description>Podcast Description Steve Clarke is the current Scotland National Team Head Coach.
As a player Steve played for St Mirren and Chelsea winning three major trophies. He also won six Scotland senior caps. After finishing his playing career, Steve assisted Ruud Gullit at Newcastle United, Jose Mourinho at Chelsea, Gianfranco Zola at West Ham United and Sir Kenny Dalglish at Liverpool.
In his first outright managerial role, he led West Bromwich Albion to eighth place in the Premier League, achieving a record points total and highest-ever finish for the club.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #55 | Osi Umenyiora: The attention to detail that won the Super Bowl! | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880215/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 01:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880215/</guid><description>Podcast Description Osi Umenyiora was one of the NFL’s leading defensive ends for nearly a decade becoming an American Football icon in the process, winning Super Bowls XLII and XLVI.&amp;nbsp;
In this week’s bitesize, Osi tells the story of how he gained a game winning edge on Tom Brady and the New England Patriots to win the Super Bowl in 2007. Always do your homework!
Listen and watch to the full episode with Osi Umenyiora: How small details deliver big differences: https://www.</description></item><item><title>E103 - Pippa Grange: How to Fear Less | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880216/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 01:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880216/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pippa Grange is an applied psychologist, culture coach and author. She worked as the Head of People and Team Development at The Football Association until the end of 2019, leaving to focus on “the broadening definition of success and winning in sport, especially for women and girls”. Her most recent book, Fear Less: How to Win at Life Without Losing Yourself, Pippa shares how living with less fear allows us to experience a more fulfilling and passion-filled life.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #54 | Angela Ruggerio: Everything in life is a choice | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880217/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 01:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880217/</guid><description>Podcast Description Winter Olympic legend Angela Ruggiero brings the bitesize brilliance this week. Angela is a four-time Olympian and Gold Medalist in Ice Hockey and was the first female non-goalie to play in a men’s professional hockey league.&amp;nbsp;
In this clip, Angela talks about the advice her father gave her growing up - everything is a choice. You decide how you react. Angela took this advice to become one of the most influential people in sport.</description></item><item><title>E102 - Lee Child: Hoping for the best but planning for the worst | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880218/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 01:00:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880218/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lee Child (aka James Dover Grant CBE) is an author, most well known for his thriller series Jack Reacher. The novels follow Jack, a former American military policeman, who ambles around the United States. The series has sold over 100 million copies, selling 9 books every second.
Lee Child was born in Coventry, went to law school in Sheffield and after part-time work in the theatre, he joined Granada Television in Manchester for what turned out to be an eighteen-year career as a presentation director.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #53 | Eddie Jones: You have to love the grind! | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880219/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 01:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880219/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the eve of a new Six Nations campaign, we throw it right back to episode 40 with England Rugby Head Coach, Eddie Jones.&amp;nbsp;
In the episode Eddie shared insights from the lessons he had learned from the head of a top London hotel, how teaching children shaped his approach to elite athletes and the unintended benefits from suffering from a stroke.&amp;nbsp;
Through all of it, he advocates that you have to love the process - or, his own description “love the grind.</description></item><item><title>E101 - Karl Lokko: A lesson in the importance of placing empathy over opinion | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880220/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 01:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880220/</guid><description>Podcast Description Karl Lokko is an activist, public speaker, influencer and businessman. Son of previous illegal immigrants, Karl became a gang leader at 14 years old. His gang (Mayhem and Destruction) had over 60 members at its height. But, aftering finding spirituality in his late teens he has turned his life around. Now, he works to reform gang culture and empower black youth with his companies Black Seed and BRXTN Studio.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #52 | Grace Beverley: Passion &amp; purpose can come AFTER the hard work | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880221/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 01:00:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880221/</guid><description>Podcast Description We rewind back to episode 59 and our chat with Grace Beverley. Grace is founder and CEO of two successful businesses, Tala and Shreddy.
Grace talks brilliantly about how passion and purpose has now been sold as a ‘must have’. With the rise of social media, we now want this at the beginning of our working lives rather than finding it through our working life.
Sometimes we need to go through the hard stuff, before we get the good stuff!</description></item><item><title>E100 - Bear Grylls: Don't let success go to your head or failure go to your heart | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880222/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 01:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880222/</guid><description>Podcast Description We celebrate our 100th episode with a very special guest! Bear Grylls is an adventurer, writer and presenter. He’s helped many people explore, and learn to love, the wild; including some very famous faces in his show Running Wild with Bear Grylls. In 2009, Bear was appointed the youngest-ever Chief Scout at age 35.&amp;nbsp;
Bear shares the best way to deal with failure, how key family is in his life, why we should all try to deconstruct “the hero” and much more.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #51 | Dina Asher-Smith: Roots &amp; Wings | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880223/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 01:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880223/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s bitesize we jump back to episode 15 with the fastest women in British history, Dina Asher-Smith.&amp;nbsp;
Jake tells Dina his family motto passed down from his parents to him - roots &amp;amp; wings. A phrase that rings true with Dina and her own family. Having the confidence to go off to chase your dreams, but no matter what happens there are always roots to come home any time you need support and help.</description></item><item><title>E99 - Vicky Pattison: Listen without prejudice | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880224/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 01:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880224/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vicky Pattison is a bestselling author and TV star. Vicky began her career on reality TV (Geordie Shore, Masterchef, I’m A Celebrity Get Me Out Of Here), but now she uses her platform of 5 million followers to spread awareness of key feminist issues, such as body image, imposter syndrome and mental health. Vicky shares with us the value of maintaining good relationships and happiness in a high performance life.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #50 | Sir Ian McGeechan: Never do anything second rate | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880225/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 01:01:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880225/</guid><description>Podcast Description What a pleasure it was to welcome Sir Ian McGeechan to the podcast, one of rugby’s most popular and well regarded figures, most notably for being a true legend of the world’s most famous touring team - the British &amp;amp; Irish Lions.&amp;nbsp;
A PE and Geography teacher by profession, Ian has a great empathy with players, an ability to get the right people around him and is incredibly knowledgeable about the game.</description></item><item><title>E98 - Chrissie Wellington: Racing the imperfect race perfectly | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880226/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 01:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880226/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chrissie Wellington OBE is a former British professional triathlete and four-time Ironman Triathlon World Champion. She held all three world and championship records relating to ironman triathlon races and remains the world record holder for Ironman distance (8hrs,18 mins). But her success doesn’t stop there, she also has an MA in Econ Development Studies, is the Global Lead for Health and Wellbeing for parkrun and is a Sunday Times Best Selling author.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #49 | Chris Voss: Stop giving advice and just listen | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880227/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 01:01:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880227/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former FBI hostage negotiator and author Chris Voss joined us for E67 educating us on how to be a world class communicator.&amp;nbsp;
One of the most profound pearls of wisdom of the enlightening chat was also the simplest: just listen.&amp;nbsp;
We talk at around 150 words a minute yet are capable of listening to around 600 words in the same period. Our brains are often thinking ahead, planning our response.</description></item><item><title>E97 - Eric Dier: The benefits of stepping outside of your comfort zone | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880228/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 01:00:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880228/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eric Dier is a footballer who plays for Premier League club Tottenham Hotspur and England. Although Eric was born in Cheltenham, his family moved to Portugal when he was 7 - where he grew his talent at Sporting Lisbon through the youth ranks. Training in Portugal was a key aspect of Eric’s life, teaching him about respect, commitment and the importance of embracing discomfort.&amp;nbsp;
Eric shares with us the valuable lessons he’s learned from his career to date - “Comfort is the enemy.</description></item><item><title>E96 - Happy Place Podcast Collaboration | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880229/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 01:00:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880229/</guid><description>Podcast Description To celebrate the New Year, this is a very special episode of the High Performance Podcast! We were lucky enough to record a collaboration with the podcast Happy Place, presented by Fearne Cotton, in which Jake, Damian and Fearne all share their favourite moments from Happy Place and High Performance in 2021, and discuss the impact those chats had on them, as well as reflecting on what their guests have taught them this year.</description></item><item><title>E95 - Expert Special: Why High Performance nutrition can change your life, with Saliha Mahmood-Ahmed | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880230/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 01:00:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880230/</guid><description>Podcast Description Saliha Mahmood-Ahmed, also known as Saliha Cooks, is a chef, a Gastroenterologist working for the NHS and the 2017 winner of MasterChef UK.&amp;nbsp;
Her work for the NHS focuses on Digestive disorders, which she combines with her passion for gastronomy. Saliha began cooking at age 12, heavily inspired by the Kashmiri style of cooking she saw from her mother and grandmother. Now, she draws upon her family traditions when creating recipe books, with the goal of promoting healthier, more enjoyable meals.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #48 | Eddie Hearn: The greatest achievement is being comfortable in yourself | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880231/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 01:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880231/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Series 3 we had the pleasure of spending the afternoon with Matchroom chairman Eddie Hearn.&amp;nbsp;Eddie was humble, honest, driven, and delivered invaluable lessons based on hard work, passion and consistency.
In this featured clip Eddie speaks about the the greatest achievement being comfortable in yourself.&amp;nbsp;
Listen to the full episode: https://www.thehighperformancepodcast.com/podcast/eddie-hearn
.......
Tickets are on sale for our LIVE TOUR in 2022. Don't miss out! Buy here: https://sjm.</description></item><item><title>Nims Purja: Make your dreams a reality (re-release) | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880232/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 01:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880232/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we are returning to a very special episode from the beginning of 2021, when we were lucky enough to chat to mountaineer Nims Purja. Since then, Nims’ incredible documentary: 14 Peaks: Nothing Is Impossible has been released on Netflix, following Nims as he takes on the quest to summit all 14 of the world's 8,000-meter peaks in just seven months. To celebrate Nims’ success, we wanted to re-release this episode, sharing with you all of the insights, moments of inspiration and wisdom he imparted during our conversation.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #47 | Adam Peaty: Have a balance in life to perform at your best | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880233/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 01:00:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880233/</guid><description>Podcast Description Back in Series 5 we were extremely fortunate to spend an afternoon with the incredible&amp;nbsp;Adam Peaty.
Adam wrote his name into the history books once again as he powered to 100m breaststroke gold in Tokyo to become the first British swimmer to defend an Olympic title.
In the full episode we spoke about his intense focus on mental skills to allow his physical gifts to flourish. His use of visualising the waiting room before entering the arena, his refusal to engage in blame and his approach to developing bulletproof self-belief are all techniques we can apply in our world.</description></item><item><title>E94 - Series 6 Roundup with Jake and Damian | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880234/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880234/</guid><description>Podcast Description What a special series it’s been for all the HPP team! Our biggest series to date, we released our first book, met you at our first live shows and announced our 2022 Live Tour! 💥💥
As customary now, Jake and Damian reflect on the key takeaways from the incredible guests from Series Six including Mark Cavendish, Mel Robbins, Michael Bisping, John McAvoy, Will Ahmed, Alastair Campbell, Dan Carter, Andrew Trimble, Steve Morgan, Sam Heughan, Angela Roggiero and Mark Webber.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #46 | F1 World Title Showdown Special | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880235/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880235/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s bitesize we compare two former guests that go head-to-head for the F1 World Championship this weekend, Team Principals Toto Wolff and Christian Horner.&amp;nbsp;
Different characters that operate in different ways, but both lead to high performance.&amp;nbsp;
Listen to the full episodes…
Toto Wolff: https://pod.fo/e/c2b53
Christian Horner: https://pod.fo/e/cda02
.......
Tickets are on sale for our LIVE TOUR in 2022. Buy here: https://sjm.lnk.to/HPPL&amp;nbsp;
Buy our book ‘Lessons From the Best on Becoming Your Best: http://smarturl.</description></item><item><title>E93 - Mark Webber: Why grit is an essential element of high performance | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880236/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880236/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our special guest this week is nine-time Grand Prix winner and FIA World Endurance Champion, Mark Webber. Listen to his conversation with Jake and Damian about the importance of consistency, organisation, reliability and always staying true to yourself.
Mark has worked in some of the greatest, and most challenging, high performing cultures in the world. Despite the glamorous trappings and lifestyle of F1, Mark has stayed true to his laid-back Aussie roots and traditions.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #45 | The High Performance Live Tour 2022 – Unlock The Impossible | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880237/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880237/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jake and Damian discuss their forthcoming tour in 2022. Tickets for the High Performance Live Tour 2022 – Unlock The Impossible are on sale at 10am today (Friday): https://sjm.lnk.to/HPPL
The High Performance Podcast Live tour will be a truly unique and interactive event, where Jake and Damian reveal the secrets used by the world’s most remarkable athletes, coaches and entrepreneurs to excel, and teach you how to do the same.</description></item><item><title>E92 - Angela Ruggiero: The golden benefits of living a disciplined life | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880238/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880238/</guid><description>Podcast Description Angela Ruggiero is a pioneer and leading figure in the sports world. She is a four-time Olympian and Gold Medalist in Ice Hockey and was the first female non-goalie to play in a men’s professional hockey league.&amp;nbsp;
Angela is the Co-Founder of the Sports Innovation Lab, a technology-powered market research firm empowering industry-leading sports brands to identify the trends, products and services that will fuel the future of sports.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #44 | High Performance Book Exclusive: Jake's Introduction | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880239/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880239/</guid><description>Podcast Description An exclusive chance to hear Jake reading his introduction to our first book out on December 9th - 'High Performance: Lessons from the Best, on Becoming Your Best'. Listen to Jake describe the origins of the podcast and how it all began.
Pre-order your copy : http://smarturl.it/hv0sdz
Get a special signed copy: https://bit.ly/3kCqhFp
Pre-order the audiobook:&amp;nbsp;https://adbl.co/3xQQSCF&amp;nbsp;
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>E91 - Sam Heughan: How belief can make dreams come true | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880240/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880240/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Heughan is an actor and entrepreneur best known for his starring role in drama series Outlander.&amp;nbsp;
Sam is owner of The Sassenach Whisky brand, which has picked up a host of awards&amp;nbsp;and has been a sell out success both here in the UK and America.
He is also founder of My Peak Challenge, a community dedicated to inspiring its members to live healthier, happier and more balanced lives while raising funds to change lives.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #43 | Zack George: Gaining confidence from being healthy &amp; happy within yourself | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880241/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880241/</guid><description>Podcast Description Zack George, one of the world’s top CrossFit athletes, and UK’s Fittest Man 2020 joined in S4 with an incredible story of dramatic change, resilience and hard work. As a child and early teenager, Zack was severely overweight and deeply unhappy in his body. It was his father’s offer of a Playstation to lose some weight that became the catalyst for change in Zack’s life.&amp;nbsp;
The biggest learning Zack wanted to pass on was the confidence he got from being healthy and happy, something that far outweighed any external award.</description></item><item><title>E90 - Steve Morgan CBE: How hard work can make dreams come true | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880242/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880242/</guid><description>Podcast Description Steve Morgan is a businessman and philanthropist. Steve was born in Liverpool and started his first construction company at the age of 21 with a loan of £5,000 from his father. He founded Redrow, one of the UK’s most successful house-builders.&amp;nbsp;
A lifelong Liverpool FC fan he unsuccessfully tried to buy the club on several occasions before eventually buying Wolverhampton Wanderers in 2007, where he stayed until 2016.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #42 | Adrienne Herbert: How to focus on your goals and create a life you love | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880243/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880243/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we have an exclusive extract from an incredible keynote speech from our members club The High Performance Circle with leading wellness coach and author of 'The Power Hour' , Adrienne Herbert.
Whatever your goal is, the Power Hour will help you to reclaim your time and focus on making it happen. Whether you want to train for a marathon, write a book, or start a business, the Power Hour will show you how to get the most out of the first hour of each day, before the rest of the world wakes up and starts competing for your time and attention.</description></item><item><title>E89 - Andrew Trimble: Understanding the art and science behind high performance | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880244/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880244/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrew Trimble is a former Irish international rugby player turned entrepreneur and businessman. He won 229 caps for Ulster, and 70 caps for Ireland, winning the Six Nations and beating the All Blacks.&amp;nbsp;
Now instead of leading on the pitch, Andrew is producing software with Kairos as founder and CEO, that will give sporting clubs and players the chance to fulfil their potential with a digital planning platform to manage the complexities of elite sport.</description></item><item><title>E88 - Dan Carter: How to make the leap from being good to being great | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880245/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880245/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we welcome All Black legend Dan Carter to the podcast. Born and raised in New Zealand, Dan is one of the finest players in rugby union history.&amp;nbsp;
Dan played 112 test matches for the All Blacks, winning two Rugby World Cups. He is the highest point scorer in test rugby and the most capped All Blacks Fly Half of all time.
Get the pen and notepad ready as we delve into the lessons Dan has learnt from his incredible career and life to date - something he calls 'the art of winning'.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #41 | Adam Peaty: The power of acceptance | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880246/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880246/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam Peaty joined us in Series 5 with an inspiring insight into his mindset, key takeaways and direction that has led him to 8 world titles, 16 European titles, and breaking the world record on five occasions.&amp;nbsp;
Jake and the Professor dissect this clip about the power of acceptance after Adam received some memorable advice from a former SAS soldier.&amp;nbsp;
Listen to the full episode with Adam: https://pod.fo/e/dc641</description></item><item><title>E87 - Alastair Campbell: What I've learnt about winning in politics, sport and business | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880247/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880247/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alastair Campbell is a writer, communicator and strategist best known for his role as former British Prime Minister Tony Blair’s spokesman, press secretary and director of communications and strategy.&amp;nbsp;
Alastair has written seventeen books including a Number 1 best-selling analysis of what it takes to win in politics, business and sport, Winners and How They Succeed, and two personal memoirs on depression and the pursuit of happiness.&amp;nbsp;
His latest, Living Better: How I learned to survive depression, was also a Sunday Times best-seller.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #40 | Mel Marshall: Finding the purpose in your journey | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880248/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880248/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s bitesize burst of inspiration comes from Mel Marshall, the current Loughborough National Lead Coach with athletes including Olympic winning swimmer Adam Peaty.
This was an episode that had a profound effect on the whole HP team. It was an incredible conversation with so many take home messages.&amp;nbsp;
This clip is Mel talking about falling in love with the journey you take, finding a collective purpose and what a difference that can make.</description></item><item><title>E86 - Will Ahmed: How combining intensity, humility and passion can build a multi-billion dollar business. | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880249/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880249/</guid><description>Podcast Description Will Ahmed is the founder and CEO of Whoop, the wearable device that monitors your recovery, sleep, training, and health. Will launched Whoop in 2012 whilst he was at college. As an athlete himself, he was constantly overtraining, and as a result, got interested in how he could prevent it by learning more about his own physiology.&amp;nbsp;
Ten years on, Whoop has a valuation of $3.6 billion, some and 500 employees.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #39 | High Performance Book Exclusive! | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880250/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880250/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jake and Damian read an exclusive 'pit-stop' from our upcoming book 'High Performance: Lessons from the Best, on Becoming Your Best'.
.......
High Performance Live Podcast Tour 2022&amp;nbsp;- Sign up here - thehighperformancepodcast.com/signup&amp;nbsp;
Get a special signed copy of our first book, out Dec 9th: https://bit.ly/3kCqhFp
Pre-order link: http://smarturl.it/hv0sdz
Pre-order the audiobook:&amp;nbsp;https://adbl.co/3xQQSCF&amp;nbsp;
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>E85 - John McAvoy: It's not where you're from, is where you're at that counts | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880251/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880251/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Jake and Damian speak with current Nike athlete, and former convicted armed robber, John McAvoy.
John speaks about how his past and time in solitary confinement transformed his view of life and what fuelled him to succeed in the sporting world.
John became the proud holder of three world records and seven British records in indoor rowing, all achieved in confinement.
John’s book – Redemption is available to buy here.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #38 | Ric Lewis: Don’t confuse activity with productivity | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880252/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880252/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s bitesize brilliance is with leading businessman Ric Lewis, a massive highlight of Series 5. Ric was ranked first in the UK’s 2019 Powerlist, an annual list of the UK’s most influential people with African or Afro-Caribbean heritage.&amp;nbsp;
This episode had an enormous reaction. And we’ve just highlighted a few principles Ric shared that really resonated. Challenge the people around you to see who gets in your circle. And don’t confuse activity with productivity.</description></item><item><title>E84 - Michael Bisping: Having a plan after you get punched in the face | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880253/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880253/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael Bisping, remains the only British UFC champion and a key player in catapulting the sport to new heights in the UK. His undoubted career highlight came in June 2016 at UFC 199, when he knocked out Luke Rockhold to claim the UFC middleweight title on just a week’s notice. He defended that title on UK soil when&amp;nbsp;he beat Dan Hendersaon and also beat the legendary Anderson Silva during the same five-fight win streak that delivered his title.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #37 | Stuart Webber: Ignore the noise, listen to your inner circle | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880254/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880254/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stuart Webber, the Sporting Director of Norwich City Football Club, joined us at the end of Series 4 and spoke with incredible honesty about how he insulates himself from social media, ignoring the opinions of others he doesn’t know or trust.&amp;nbsp;
Jake and Damian discuss how all high performers have a committee of trusted people around them.&amp;nbsp;
. . . . . . .&amp;nbsp;
Get a special signed copy of our book - ‘Lessons from the Best on Becoming Your Best’ : htps://bit.</description></item><item><title>E83 - Mel Robbins: Can you really high 5 your way to happiness? | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880255/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880255/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our special guest this week is Mel Robbins. A best-selling author, tv host and motivational speaker. Mel’s books' include global phenomenon ‘The 5 Second Rule’ and her latest is called ‘The High 5 Habit’; a simple, proven tool you can use to take control of your life.
Mel is one of the most widely booked and followed public speakers in the world. Her social media platforms inspire more than 60 million people every month and her TEDx Talk is one of the most popular of all time, with more than 25 million views.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #36 | Lord Richard Dannatt: Aim high, be the best, courage is key | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880256/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880256/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lord Dannatt concluded his forty year military career as the head of the British Army. His leadership and decision making affected hundreds of thousands. This bitesize episode focuses one of the most impactful definitions of high performance we’ve heard so far…
Listen to Lord Dannatt’s full episode, The importance of moral and physical courage: https://pod.fo/e/c6a61&amp;nbsp;
. . . . . . .&amp;nbsp;
Get a special signed copy of our book: htps://bit.</description></item><item><title>E82 - Mark Cavendish: Navigating slippery descents and climbing personal mountains | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880257/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880257/</guid><description>Podcast Description We launch Series 6 with the ‘Manx Missile’ Mark Cavendish, cycling’s greatest sprinter of all time.
Mark sprinted into the history books on Stage 13 of the Tour de France in 2021, by equalling Eddy Merckx’s record of 34 stage wins at the Tour, a record that has been held since 1975.
It has been an extraordinary comeback for Mark, arguably one the&amp;nbsp;greatest in sports history, as he has battled depression, illness and injury.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE 35 | Season 6 Preview | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880258/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880258/</guid><description>Podcast Description A look ahead to Season 6 of the High Performance Podcast! Join Jake and the Professor as they reveal some of the incredible world-class performers we've got lined up!
Remember, episodes are released every Monday, with bitesize episodes every Friday. We kick off Series 6 with one the greatest road sprinters of all time - Mark Cavendish - out Monday 27th Sept!
. . . . . . .</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #34 | HIGH PERFORMANCE BOOK EXCLUSIVE! 📖 | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880259/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880259/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’ve got a special exclusive from our upcoming book, High Performance: Lessons from the Best on Becoming Your Best, read by Jake.&amp;nbsp;
It was a very special moment to get our hands on the first copies. We’re really proud of the book and can’t wait for you all to read it.&amp;nbsp;
. . . . . . .&amp;nbsp;
Special signed copy: https://bit.ly/3kCqhFp
Pre-order link: http://smarturl.it/hv0sdz
Pre-order the audiobook:&amp;nbsp;https://adbl.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #33 | Kevin Sinfield: Finding your path just takes getting started | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880260/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880260/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s bitesize brilliance is from rugby league legend Kevin Sinfield.
&amp;nbsp;
We chatted about the importance of soft stuff: the ability to show our emotions, let people know we care and the power of friendship. This is the intangible stuff that produces the hard currency of silverware.
&amp;nbsp;
"When it is all over, you don't remember games as well as the friendships and relationships you share."
In 2020 Kevin set the challenge to run 7 marathons in 7 days hoping to raise £77,777 in honour of his best Rob Burrow, who wore the No 7 shirt.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #32 | James Timpson: Never do a deal with someone you don’t like | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880261/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880261/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our bitesize dose of motivation today comes from James Timpson, the CEO of Timpson, a business that has been in his family for over 150 years.
The reaction to this episode was huge! It was a real pleasure to spend time with James and hear his lessons and values to building the business - something that resonated with so many.
James’ episode had a clear message - culture, when harnessed correctly, can be a competitive advantage.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #31 | Cath Bishop: Winning when it’s impossible | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880262/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880262/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we have an extract from our exclusive members club The High Performance Circle, with former Olympian and business coach, Cath Bishop.&amp;nbsp;
Cath believes that we have come to define winning too narrowly - as a moment in time crossing the line, winning a medal, and at a level set by others rather than ourselves. That 'win at all costs' mentality has seen 'the costs' rise to unacceptable levels.</description></item><item><title>E81 - Series 5 Roundup with Jake and Damian! | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880263/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880263/</guid><description>Podcast Description What a series it’s been! 23 episodes, millions of downloads, a new members club, our first live episode and a book announcement! 💥💥
As customary now, Jake and Damian reflect on the key takeaways from the incredible guests from Series Five including Christian Horner, Grace Beverley, Gareth Southgate, Chris Bosh, Tim Peake, Hector Bellerin, Julian Hearn, Chris Voss, Ben Francis, Mary Portas, Ian Thorpe, Sir Ian McGeechan, Grant Hanley, Hal Robson-Kanu, Kate Richardson-Walsh, Mel Marshall, Adam Peaty, Ric Lewis, Jason Kenny, Paul McGinley, Jo Konta and Jenson Button.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #30 | Ant Middleton: 100% responsibility and accountability | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880264/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880264/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s short, sharp hit of high performance comes from former special forces operator Ant Middleton. In our podcast with Ant, he opened up on his golden rules and unique beliefs for a high performance life. This clip talks about taking 100% responsibility for his actions, even if it meant going to prison.&amp;nbsp;
Go back and listen to one of our most popular episodes: https://pod.fo/e/15f9f
. . . .</description></item><item><title>E80 - Jenson Button: Going through the gears to succeed | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880265/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880265/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jenson Button is a former F1 world champion and one of the greatest racing drivers of his generation. Jenson grew up as part of a motor-racing-mad family under the guidance of his father, John, arriving at Williams as a 20 year-old, to being written off by some as a playboy and his fight back to the very pinnacle of his sport winning the world championship with Brawn GP in 2009</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #29 | Susie Ma: What’s your infinite purpose? | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880266/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880266/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s bitesize brilliance comes from Susie Ma, the founder of Tropic Skincare, who came on the podcast and was just incredible! It was a meeting with author Simon Sinek that made Susie define her infinite purpose for Tropic - to create a healthier, greener and more empowered world. It’s a mindset shift that has had a profound effect on Jake and Damian. Listen to find out…
Go back and listen to the whole episode with Susie here: https://pod.</description></item><item><title>E79 - Olympics Special #5: Johanna Konta | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880267/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880267/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last in our series of Olympic Specials is with the current British No.1 women’s tennis player, Johanna Konta. Johanna has won four singles titles on the Women’s Tennis Association Tour and in 2016, became part of Team GB at the Rio Olympics.&amp;nbsp;
Johanna reached the semifinals of Wimbledon in 2017 – the same year she achieved her highest ever world ranking of number 4.&amp;nbsp;
**
Thank you to our founding partners Lotus Cars for being our special partner in this Olympic series.</description></item><item><title>E78 - Paul McGinley: It’s not about being the best player in the team, but being the best team player. | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880268/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880268/</guid><description>Podcast Description Paul has been a European Tour golfer now for over 25 years. Despite winning several tournaments and being a former top 20 ranked player in the world, he is best known for his performances in team competitions, especially the Ryder Cup. He has represented Europe on 14 occasions as a player, Vice-Captain &amp;amp; Captain, winning an astonishing 13 times, most memorably in 2014 where he led Europe to a comprehensive victory over America at Gleneagles in Scotland as Captain.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #28 | Sir Chris Hoy: The importance of timekeeping and respect | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880269/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 01:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880269/</guid><description>Podcast Description With our founding partner Lotus Cars, we’re delving into the rich archive for lessons from Olympic legends! This week’s comes from Sir Chris Hoy -&amp;nbsp;is a true sporting legend and one of the most successful British athletes of all time with six gold medals and one silver.
Chris tells Jake and Damian a very simple lesson that was crucial to his success - being on time! It’s a sign of respect, crucial in a team environment and totally in our control&amp;nbsp;⏱️</description></item><item><title>E77 - Olympics Special #4: Jason Kenny | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880270/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880270/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jason Kenny has just won his eighth cycling medal at the Tokyo Olympics to become Great Britain's most decorated Olympian of all time.&amp;nbsp;
At the age of 20, Jason won his first Olympic gold, alongside Sir Chris Hoy, in the team sprint at the Beijing Games in 2008 and was one of the figureheads of the highly successful Great Britain Cycling Team at their home Olympics in London four years later, taking his career haul to three golds medals in the sprint and team sprint.</description></item><item><title>E76 - Ric Lewis: Guiding principles for business, life and happiness | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880271/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880271/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jake and Damian speak with leading businessman Ric Lewis and for the first time he shares his 12 principles to a successful life and business. Ric was ranked first in the UK’s 2019 Powerlist, an annual list of the UK’s most influential people with African or Afro-Caribbean heritage. He is a founding partner at Tristan Capital Partners, a British property investment firm and chair of The Black Heart foundation – a charity which is dedicated to supporting initiatives that improve educational benefits for under-resourced young people and providing opportunity to those who are otherwise denied it.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #27 | Dina Asher-Smith: Work hard to be in the best position | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880272/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 00:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880272/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are loving the Olympics! And alongside&amp;nbsp;our founding partner Lotus Cars, we’re delving into the rich archive for lessons from Olympic legends! This week’s comes from Dina Asher-Smith, one of GB’s medal hopes in the track and field. Dina’s episode on the podcast was bursting with enthusiasm, you just have to smile 😊&amp;nbsp;
Dina told Jake and Damian how a track and field championship will show any weakness you have.</description></item><item><title>E75 - Olympics Special #3: Adam Peaty | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880273/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880273/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam Peaty is the first British swimmer to retain their Olympic title after winning Team GB's first gold medal of Tokyo 2020 with victory in the men's 100m breaststroke.
Adam now has the 16 quickest times in history over the 100m breaststroke and is the only swimmer ever to dip under 57 seconds with his 2019 world record.&amp;nbsp;
With eight world titles, 16 European titles, Adam is one of GB’s greatest Olympian’s of all time.</description></item><item><title>E74 - Mel Marshall: The art and science of great coaching | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880274/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880274/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mel Marshall is the current Loughborough National Lead Coach where her swimmers include Olympic winning swimmer Adam Peaty.
Mel has overseen Adam Peaty's rise to the top of the international swimming stage, coaching him to gold medal success at every level - Olympic, World, European, Commonwealth and British.
In 2015 and 2016 Mel was awarded the title of British Swimming Coach of the Year. Before turning her hand to coaching, Mel had a successful career as a swimmer herself which included winning six medals at the 2006 Commonwealth Games in Australia and Bronze at the World Short Course Championships in 2008.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #26 | Tom Daley: Be Yourself | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880275/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880275/</guid><description>Podcast Description As part of our special Olympic series with Lotus Cars, we’re delving into the rich archive for lessons from Olympic legends! This week’s comes from Tom Daley, one of GB’s most recognised sportsmen. Tom has won a diving gold or finished first in a major competition every single year for 14 successive years! 🤯
Tom’s lesson is simply ‘be yourself’. We went to some difficult, but fascinating, and challenging places in our podcast so check out the full episode if you missed it.</description></item><item><title>E73 - Olympics Special #2: Kate Richardson-Walsh | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880276/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880276/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kate Richardson-Walsh is the most capped female hockey player in her country's history. Kate was captain of GB women’s hockey teams for 13 years and was one of the many key drivers of the incredible team ethos and commitment that drove the GB team to a nail biting victory at the Rio Olympic Games. One of UK's greatest Olympic moments of all time. Kate also made history in other ways, becoming one half of the first same-sex married couple to win an Olympic medal playing in the same team.</description></item><item><title>E72 - Sir Ian McGeechan: Doing the world class basics | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880277/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880277/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sir Ian McGeechan is distinguished as one of Rugby’s most popular and well regarded figures, most notably for being a true legend of the world’s most famous touring team - the British &amp;amp; Irish Lions. He is only person to have tasted series success as both a player and a coach.
During his playing career Ian won 32 caps for Scotland. He toured with the British Lions as a player in 1974 in the unbeaten tour to South Africa and in 1977 to New Zealand playing all eight tests.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #25 | Ben Ainslie: Focus on the failure with brutal honesty | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880278/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880278/</guid><description>Podcast Description As part of our special Olympic series with Lotus Cars, we’re delving into the rich archive for lessons from Olympic legends! This week’s comes from Ben Ainslie, the most successful Olympic sailor of all time, with four golds and one silver medal over a 16 year period.&amp;nbsp;
Ben talks about focussing on failure with brutal honesty, with the mindset of improvement. Don’t ignore the bad...or you’ll never turn it into the good 🙌</description></item><item><title>E71 - Olympics Special #1 - Ian Thorpe | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880279/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:20:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880279/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ian Thorpe won five Olympic gold medals, the greatest total of any Australian. As his first Olympics approached, in Sydney, he had broken 10 world records - four of them in four days at the 1999 Pan Pacific titles. On the first night of Sydney 2000 he won the 400m freestyle, breaking his own word record, then combined with his team to inflict the United States’ first defeat ever in the 4 x 100m freestyle relay, setting another world record.</description></item><item><title>E70 - Mary Portas: Changing your thinking to change your results | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880280/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880280/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mary Portas is an expert on retail and brand communication. Since 1997 she has been running Portas, a brand agency, producing challenging campaigns and championing brand development for clients.&amp;nbsp;
She is credited with turning Harvey Nichols into a modern fashion brand in the ’90s. She became a member of the company’s board at the age of 30.&amp;nbsp;She previously worked with John Lewis and Topshop.
In 2011 Mary was commissioned by Prime Minister David Cameron to lead an independent review into the Future of the High Street.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #24 | Gareth Southgate: Being prepared for any eventuality | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880281/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880281/</guid><description>Podcast Description It only felt right to dig a little deeper into the episode with the England boss as the whole country builds to only our second competitive final! Gareth Southgate recently joined us on the podcast just before the EUROS. He demonstrated humility, authenticity and integrity to all of us. Soft skills which deliver hard high performance results.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
In this clip Gareth shared a valuable lesson, one the England team have been working on (with great effect!</description></item><item><title>E69 - Ben Francis: How to step back to take a leap forward | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880282/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880282/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ben Francis is the founder and ambitious entrepreneur behind leading UK fitness brand, Gymshark.
Ben founded Gymshark when he was 19, while still a student at Aston University. In addition to his full-time commitment to his studies, Ben juggled working as a pizza delivery man to fund his Gymshark venture. In August 2020, Gymshark became the first DTC brand in the UK to achieve Unicorn status (valuation over $1 billion) with no external capital funding.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #23 Mauricio Pochettino: Attitude is everything | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880283/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880283/</guid><description>Podcast Description Before we had even released a podcast, we were invited to Mauricio’s house with the warmest welcome and the most incredible ATTITUDE! Mauricio shook our hands and judged our energy. An incredible moment we will never forget! Listen to Jake and Damian delve deep into the importance of attitude after we hear a classic clip from the PSG boss.&amp;nbsp;
ICYMI: https://pod.fo/e/16521
. . . . . . .&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>E68 - Daniel Sturridge: The power of unfinished business | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880284/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880284/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s the last in our EUROS special! Today we’re joined by footballer Daniel Sturridge.&amp;nbsp;
Daniel started his career at Manchester City before signing for Chelsea in 2009, where he scored 24 before he was sold to Liverpool for £12m in 2013.
Daniel played and scored regularly in the 2013-14 season, when Liverpool came close to winning the Premier League title and he was part of the squad that won the Champions League in 2019.</description></item><item><title>E67 - Chris Voss: How to be a killer communicator | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880285/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880285/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris Voss is former lead international kidnapping negotiator for the Federal Bureau of Investigation. Chris is current CEO of the Black Swan Group which specialises in solving business communication problems using hostage negotiation solutions. Chris helps companies secure and close better deals, save money, and solve internal communication problems between senior management and employees.
Chris is also author of the national best-seller&amp;nbsp;Never Split The Difference: Negotiating As If Your Life Depended On It, which is out now.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #22 | Tracey Neville: How to effectively deal with team conflict | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880286/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880286/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week's source of bitesize wisdom is Tracey Neville, the head coach who delivered one of this country's greatest sporting triumphs - winning a gold medal for England netball. Here she is talking about the importance of central values when dealing with conflict in a team.
ICYMI: https://pod.fo/e/17cd2
. . . . . . .&amp;nbsp;
We have a book coming out! You can pre-order a copy right here: smarturl.</description></item><item><title>E66 - Thomas ‘Hal’ Robson-Kanu: The real power of pure positivity | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880287/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880287/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s another EUROS special! Today we welcome Thomas ‘Hal’ Robson-Kanu, a professional footballer with West Brom and Wales. In 2016 Hal not only scored one of international football’s most memorable goals with his strike against Belgium at the European Championship but he also set up his own health drink company, the Turmeric Co.&amp;nbsp;
Inspired by his own injury troubles, The Turmeric Co now has tens of thousands of customers, including the England rugby team and professional football clubs.</description></item><item><title>E65 - Julian Hearn: Leaving a legacy your kids would be proud of | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880288/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880288/</guid><description>Podcast Description Julian Hearn is an entrepreneur and founder of Huel, a nutritionally complete food. Within four years of launch he built the company to over £40m in revenue, and a valuation of £220m.&amp;nbsp;
Prior to Huel, Julian founded Mash Up Media, which he built from scratch as the sole founder into a multi-million pound business with just £1500 investment.
******
Want more from the High Performance Podcast? We have a book coming out!</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #21 | Tyrone Mings: Being more than just a footballer | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880289/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880289/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s bitesize Friday! Today’s short, sharp boost of wisdom comes from England defender Tyrone Mings.&amp;nbsp;From being a mortgage advisor in non-league football to representing his country in the EUROS. Incredible. Tyrone identified the need to have an identity away from football.
Go back and listen to this full podcast! It was filled with lessons, insights, wisdom and learnings that can apply to anyone seeking high performance.
ICYMI: https://pod.fo/e/ae7be</description></item><item><title>E64 - Héctor Bellerín: How curiosity can seriously damage your ignorance | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880290/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880290/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s our third EURO 2020 special episodes, we are joined by Arsenal and Spain defender Héctor Bellerín.
Héctor joined Arsenal from Barcelona in 2011 before making his first-team debut, aged 18, in the 2013 League Cup. He has since gone on to lift two Emirates FA Cups.
As you will discover in this compelling podcast, Héctor has fascinating interests and insights outside of the game that all contribute to his lessons in high performance.</description></item><item><title>E63 - Tim Peake: Aiming high by staying grounded | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880291/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880291/</guid><description>Podcast Description Major Tim Peake, is an Army Air Corps officer and a European Space Agency astronaut. He was the first British astronaut to carry out a spacewalk.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Tim’s military career included service in Northern Ireland and the former Yugoslavia. In 2008, he answered an advert from the European Space Agency looking for astronauts and in December 2015 he headed to the International Space Station for six months.
Listen to the life lessons Tim has learnt from his extraordinary career so far.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #21 | Rio Ferdinand: Dealing with expectation | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880292/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880292/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s bitesize boost of inspiration comes from the first ever guest on the podcast - Rio Ferdinand! This chat set us on the way to where we are now, five series later.&amp;nbsp;
In this clip Rio tells us how he dealt with expectation…followed by a fascinating chat with Jake and Damian. Have a brilliant Friday.
ICYMI: https://pod.fo/e/15914
. . . . . . .&amp;nbsp;
We have a book coming out!</description></item><item><title>E62 - Grant Hanley: Why fear carries no value | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880293/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880293/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the second in our series of special EURO 2020 episodes, we are joined by Grant&amp;nbsp;Hanley, Norwich City captain and Scotland national team defender.
Grant has been a leader throughout his football career. He featured in the majority of Blackburn’s games in the Premier League &amp;amp; Championship from 2011, making a total of 200 appearances in all competitions. Grant joined Norwich in 2017 and became the club captain a year later.</description></item><item><title>E61 - Chris Bosh: How to successfully deal with change | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880294/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880294/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris Bosh is a NBA Hall of Famer, eleven-time All-Star, two-time NBA champion, Olympic gold medalist, and the league’s Global Ambassador. Chris had his playing days cut short at their prime by a freak medical condition. His extraordinary career ended not at a time of his choosing but “in a doctor’s office in the middle of the afternoon.”&amp;nbsp;
Forced to reckon with how to find meaning to carry forward, he found himself looking back over his path, from a teenager in Dallas who balanced basketball with the high school robotics club to the pinnacle of the NBA and beyond.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #20 | Reece Wabara: Keep the main thing, the main thing! | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880295/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880295/</guid><description>Podcast Description We love these bitesize eps! Going back to the brilliant conversations from the archive and highlighting the amazing lessons. Back in series 2 we sat down with&amp;nbsp;Reece, who played for Manchester City amongst other clubs, before he founded Manière De Voir - a sports luxe brand - in the midst of his football career. The learnings he made indulging in luxury and the attitude of those around him is something he reflects on here.</description></item><item><title>E60 - Gareth Southgate: How to be an emotionally intelligent leader | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880296/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 00:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880296/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the first of a series of special EURO 2020 episodes, we are joined by Gareth Southgate, the current England manager. Gareth took up the position in November 2016 and oversaw the Three Lions’ World Cup qualification campaign, leading England to Russia 2018 where they made the semi-finals. Gareth gained 57 international caps as a player taking part in 4 major tournaments.&amp;nbsp;
On the domestic front, after six years and almost 200 appearances for Villa, Gareth joined Middlesbrough where, as captain, he led the side to their first major trophy with the League Cup in 2004.</description></item><item><title>E59 - Grace Beverley: How to make your side hustle a success | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880297/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880297/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Jake and Damian are joined by successful entrepreneur, Grace Beverley. Named in the Forbes 30 under 30 list in 2020, Grace is founder and CEO of two successful businesses, Tala and Shreddy, which she launched in her final year at Oxford University.&amp;nbsp;
At just 23 years old, what gave her the confidence to get started? How does she manage those around her with more experience? What are her views on social media and navigating modern life?</description></item><item><title>Bitesize #19 | Matthew McConaughey: There is no yet! | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880298/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880298/</guid><description>Podcast Description What a moment and what a pleasure it was to welcome Matthew on the podcast. There were so great lessons and takeaways. Don’t avoid the bad stuff. It’s coming whether you like it or not. Remembering the good times &amp;amp; how we got there is a real superpower. But most of all, there is no yet!&amp;nbsp;
ICYMI:&amp;nbsp;https://pod.fo/e/a9e4a
. . . . . . .&amp;nbsp;
Remember to join our new members club ‘The High Performance Circle’ for exclusive podcasts, keynote speeches, a monthly newsletter and so much more: https://www.</description></item><item><title>E58 - Christian Horner: How reflection wins races | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880299/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 00:02:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880299/</guid><description>Podcast Description Christian Horner is the Team Principal of the Red Bull Formula One racing team.
Christian’s path to Formula One management ladder began behind the wheel, as a talented young racer, before at the age of 25 he founded the Arden International Race Team.
Three consecutive International Formula 3000 Team championships brought the young Team owner to the attention of Red Bull and when the company decided to field its own F1 entry in 2005, it turned to Christian to run the operation.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE # 18 | Jo Malone: The power of resilience | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880300/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880300/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jo Malone made a huge impact when she came on the podcast. Jo built her incredibly successful brand, Jo Malone London, that she eventually sold before launching her latest @jolovesofficial range. But there have been periods to her life that have been challenging to say the least. In this bitesize episode Jo talks about the power of resilience and how sometimes it’s just about holding your ground.
ICYMI:&amp;nbsp;https://pod.fo/e/bbdc9</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE # 17 | Frank Lampard: Have conviction and a willingness to learn | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880301/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880301/</guid><description>Podcast Description Great leaders have a conviction in their beliefs but show a willingness to learn.
In our chat with Frank Lampard, he described the importance to seek advice from a wide variety of ideas, arguments, and information in order to think rationally and come up with effective solutions.
Frank spoke about gaining the advice of his wife Christine to give him a rounded perspective.
ICYMI: https://pod.fo/e/29666&amp;nbsp;
. . . .</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE # 16 | Kelly Holmes: One person can change your life | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880302/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880302/</guid><description>Podcast Description Olympic legend Dame Kelly Holmes joined us back in series one for an incredibly powerful podcast. Sport became Kelly’s identity when she was the only mixed race person at her school. Her PE teacher made her believe that she had something special. One person has the ability to change your life! If you haven’t listened to the full episode, click here: https://pod.fo/e/1abee
A big thanks to our founding partners Lotus Cars and GIVEMESPORT - the exclusive sports partner of the High Performance Podcast.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE # 15 | Siya Kolisi: Always be ready for an opportunity | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880303/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880303/</guid><description>Podcast Description Siya’s podcast was one of the most humbling and powerful conversations we have ever had. His story growing up in poverty before becoming the first black man to captain South Africa and lead the team to World Cup glory is filled with inspiration, positivity and hope. This particular message from Siya is no matter who you are, always be ready for an opportunity. If you haven’t listened to the full episode, click here: https://pod.</description></item><item><title>E57 - Series 4 Roundup with Jake and Damian | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880304/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880304/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jake and Damian reflect on the key takeaways from the incredible guests from Series Four, including Kasper Schmeichel, Eddie Jones, Kevin Sinfield, Susie Ma, Jo Malone, Osi Umenyiora, Sol Campbell, Nims Purja, Toto Wolff, Stuart Webber and many more.
This series wrap up we’re basing around the five stages of successful change: Dream, Leap, Fight, Climb, Arrive. Jake and Damian talk through these stages and both pick out their favourite clips and tell you why.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #14 | Chris Hoy: Keep raising the bar | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880305/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880305/</guid><description>Podcast Description Listen to one of our greatest Olympians of all time, Sir Chris Hoy, tell the valuable lesson of how you need to keep raising the bar and never settle. Listen to his full episode right here: https://pod.fo/e/248ab
You can still get our exclusive offer of 20% off your first order with Mission. We love their teas so please check them out. Type HIGHPERFORMANCE at checkout at missionuk.com.&amp;nbsp;
A big thanks to our founding partners Lotus Cars and GIVEMESPORT - the exclusive sports partner of the High Performance Podcast.</description></item><item><title>E56 - General The Lord Richard Dannatt: The importance of moral and physical courage | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880306/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880306/</guid><description>Podcast Description A soldier for forty years, Lord The General Richard Dannatt concluded his military career as the head of the British Army. Since retiring from active duty in 2009, he was Constable of the Tower of London until July 2016 and became an independent member of the House of Lords in 2011. He is an expert on military affairs and leadership, was awarded the Military Cross for bravery and persevered after a major stroke in 1977 to eventually become the Chief of General Staff.</description></item><item><title>E55 - Stuart Webber: The vital importance of patience, preparation and planning | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880307/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 00:00:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880307/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stuart Webber is the Sporting Director of Norwich City Football Club, who have just secured promotion back to the Premier League.
Stuart took the role in April 2017, having previously worked as Head of Football Operations at Huddersfield Town and had previous roles at Wolves, Queens Park Rangers, Liverpool and Wrexham.
Stuart has transformed the Canaries on and off the pitch, with new facilities and sustained success, adhering to their long-term values rather than short-term interests.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE # 13 | Sir Clive Woodward: Creating and living by your own rules | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880308/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880308/</guid><description>Podcast Description It was a real privilege to be invited to Clive’s house and hear how the same principles he employed in his first business, he used to take a team to World Cup glory. If you haven’t listened to the full episode, click here: https://pod.fo/e/a7865
You can still get our exclusive offer of 20% off your first order with Mission. We love their teas so please check them out. Type HIGHPERFORMANCE at checkout at missionuk.</description></item><item><title>E54 - James Timpson: How generosity leads to wealth | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880309/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 00:00:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880309/</guid><description>Podcast Description James Timpson is the CEO of Timpson, a business that has been in his family for over 150 years. James helped grow Timpson to over 2100 shops, and developed several innovative ways to run the business at a time when traditional High Street retailing has suffered.
The key to the growth of the business has been the culture that James has pioneered, based on trust and kindness. Employee benefits such as free holiday homes, a Dreams Come True scheme, weekly Lotteries and mental health support has ensured Timpson has been one of the UK’s best companies to work.</description></item><item><title>E53 - Zack George: The power of internal motivation | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880310/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880310/</guid><description>Podcast Description Zack George is one of the world’s top CrossFit athletes, a fitness influencer and officially the UK’s Fittest Man 2020. Zack’s story is one of dramatic change, resilience and hard work. As a child and early teenager, Zack was severely overweight and deeply unhappy in his body. It was his father’s offer of a Playstation to lose some weight that became the catalyst for change in Zack’s life.&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE # 12 | Phil Neville: My biggest learning was leaving Man Utd | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880311/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880311/</guid><description>Podcast Description Phil Neville had an unbelievable playing career with Manchester United, Everton &amp;amp; England, and has already established himself as an elite manager. Leaving his beloved Man United at the time felt like the end of the world, but it actually turned out to be his biggest learning and even made him a better person.&amp;nbsp;
A big thanks to our founding partners Lotus Cars and GIVEMESPORT - the exclusive sports partner of the High Performance Podcast.</description></item><item><title>E52 - Steve Sallis: The importance of education in mindset | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880312/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 00:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880312/</guid><description>Podcast Description Steve Sallis is a former academy footballer, vice-principal teacher and author of the successful book ‘Educating Football’, a book that challenges thinking on teaching, learning, leadership and elite sport.
Steve is currently working with the England Under 15 National Squad and also supports Premier League and Football League Players with mental conditioning support.&amp;nbsp;
For more information check out www.solutionsmindset.com&amp;nbsp;or www.educatingfootball.com
PRE-ORDER THE NEW HIGH PERFORMANCE BOOK NOW! smarturl.it/hv0sdz</description></item><item><title>E51 - Toto Wolff: Empathy over engineering | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880313/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880313/</guid><description>Podcast Description Toto Wolff is Team Principal &amp;amp; CEO of the Mercedes-AMG Petronas F1 Team. After a short racing career competing in Austrian Formula Ford, Toto pursued a business career and found a new outlet for his talent – investment. He founded his own investment companies and in November 2009, Toto merged his passion for racing and investment by investing in the Williams F1 Team.&amp;nbsp;
By July 2012, Toto was the Executive Director of the team, playing a key leadership role as Williams scored its first win in eight years that season.</description></item><item><title>E50 - Neil Fachie: How to avoid getting stuck; the power of pivoting | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880314/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 23:27:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880314/</guid><description>Podcast Description Neil Fachie is a long-standing member of the Great Britain Cycling Team. Neil is a 2012 Paralympic champion and reigning world champion and tandem kilo world record holder.
A track and field athlete at his debut Paralympics, Neil made the switch to track cycling in time for the London Games four years later winning gold and silver in the tandem B events, for athletes with a visual impairment.</description></item><item><title>E49 - Stephen Hendry: No compromise; the cost of high performance | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880315/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 23:46:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880315/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stephen Hendry dominated the game of snooker in his prime. He won the World Championship in 1990 at just 21 years of age, a record that still stands today.
The Scotsman played on for a further 27 years and in that time he topped the world rankings for eight consecutive seasons, won seven world title wins, six Masters titles and five UK Championships. Dubbed the ‘King of the Crucible’, Stephen changed the game and many would argue that he is the greatest snooker player of all time.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE # 10 | Nims Purja: Excuses are for losers | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880316/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880316/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nirmal "Nims" Purja, 37, stunned the mountaineering world in 2019 when he summited all 14 of the world's 8,000-meter peaks in just six months and six days. Then in January this year Nims lead the first successful winter ascent of K2, himself climbing to the top without supplemental oxygen.
His one big learning he learnt from his time from the Gurkha’s to mountaineering legend? “Excuses are for losers”.&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>E48 - Susie Ma: The power of purpose | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880317/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 00:30:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880317/</guid><description>Podcast Description Susie Ma is the founder and CEO of Tropic Skincare, one of the UK’s fastest-growing skincare brands. Few successful entrepreneurs could claim to have more of a quintessential ‘rags to riches‘ story than Susie.&amp;nbsp;
Tropic Skincare, started life on a London market stall in 2004, where aged just fifteen, she was trying to find a way to pay the household bills.
Today, her ‘ethical first’ approach to brand building has seen her gain award nominations for entrepreneurship and work with Lord Alan Sugar after appearing on BBC’s 'The Apprentice' and becoming the first runner up candidate ever to receive investment.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE # 9 | Sean Dyche: The importance of good manners | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880318/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880318/</guid><description>Podcast Description We recorded this podcast with Sean at the Burnley training ground where he is the longest serving manager in the Premier League.&amp;nbsp;
His passion for making his players better people was epitomised by the importance he placed on good manners as a starting point for everyone in life.&amp;nbsp;
A big thanks to our founding partners Lotus Cars and GIVEMESPORT - the exclusive sports partner of the High Performance Podcast.</description></item><item><title>E47 - Evelyn Glennie: How to take responsibility, not search for blame | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880319/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880319/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dame Evelyn Glennie is the world’s premier solo percussionist, performing worldwide with the greatest orchestras, conductors and artists.&amp;nbsp;
Evelyn was eight when she started to lose her hearing, and 12 when she was diagnosed as profoundly deaf. But in her own words “losing my hearing made has made me a better listener and musician”.
Evelyn is a double GRAMMY award winner and BAFTA nominee and was awarded an OBE in 1993.</description></item><item><title>E46 - Sol Campbell: The importance of roots and wings | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880320/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880320/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sol made 646 appearances for five different clubs between 1992 and 2011, as well as playing 73 times for England, taking part in three World Cups and three European Championships.
Sol, who began his professional career with Tottenham, enjoyed his most prosperous seasons with Arsenal after making a free transfer ahead of the 2001-02 season.
At the Gunners, Sol went on to win two league titles and two FA Cups, scored in the 2006 Champions League final and was part of the legendary “Invincibles” team of 2003/4.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE # 8 | Jonny Wilkinson: All of me in every moment | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880321/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880321/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Friday! Today’s bitesize episode is the most impactful message from the most popular episode we’ve ever done. The continued feedback we get from our conversation with Jonny Wilkinson is truly humbling and mind-blowing.&amp;nbsp;
Listen to Jonny give his profound definition to living a high performance life - “all of me in every moment”.
From the moment we heard these words at the very start of the podcast, we were hooked!</description></item><item><title>E45 - Jo Malone: Finding your own superpower | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880322/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:46:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880322/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jo Malone CBE, is the Founder &amp;amp; Creative Director of Jo Loves, a household name and one of the world’s most successful businesswomen. There aren’t many people who haven’t had a product of hers in their home at some point.&amp;nbsp;
From modest beginnings, Jo fell in love with fragrance and built an incredibly successful brand, Jo Malone London, that she eventually sold and left the business before launching her ‘Jo Loves’ range inspired by the memories and moments in life that she loves.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #7 | Dina Asher-Smith: You have to believe | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880323/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880323/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s bitesize episode comes from the sprinter Dina Asher-Smith. Dina was a delight to have on the podcast, with such an incredible presence and personality, we were smiling all day! Here she is talking about the power of self-belief.&amp;nbsp;
&amp;nbsp;
Remember, you can get extended episodes of the podcast on our YouTube channel bit.ly/HPPYouTube and follow us on Instagram @highperformance.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>E44 - Charlie Pierce: Finding the courage to jump | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880324/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880324/</guid><description>Podcast Description Charlie Pierce is a Music Artist Manager from London and is&amp;nbsp;founder and CEO of Neverno Management Ltd, the home of artists Angaleena Presley and Grammy nominee Yola Carter.&amp;nbsp;
Prior to working in the music industry, Charlie spent the first eleven years of her career working in the financial services and made a decision in 2015 to completely shift direction and set on an entirely new path to work in the music industry.</description></item><item><title>E43 - Osi Umenyiora: How small details deliver big differences | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880325/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880325/</guid><description>Podcast Description Osi Umenyiora was one of the NFL’s leading defensive ends for nearly a decade becoming an American Football icon in the process. Osi was drafted by the New York Giants in 2003 out of Troy University and spent his first 10 seasons with the franchise before signing a two-year deal with the Atlanta Falcons in 2013.
Osi played on the Giants teams that won Super Bowls XLII and XLVI.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #6 | Kelly Jones: Don’t miss the moments right in front of you | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880326/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880326/</guid><description>Podcast Description Your response to the bitesize episodes has been incredible and we’re so pleased you're getting so much from our mini hits of inspiration!&amp;nbsp;
&amp;nbsp;
Today’s clip comes from songwriter Kelly Jones and his regret at losing years of his life not being present.&amp;nbsp;
&amp;nbsp;
A big thanks to our partners Lotus Cars. Remember, you can get extended episodes of the podcast on our YouTube channel bit.ly/HPPYouTube and follow us on Instagram @highperformance.</description></item><item><title>E42 - Kevin Sinfield: How to inspire through your actions | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880327/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:28:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880327/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kevin Sinfield is the current Leeds Rhinos Director of Rugby after returning to the club where he became a legend. Kevin won seven Grand Finals, two Challenge Cups, three World Club Challenges and three League Leaders Shields in his time with the Rhinos.&amp;nbsp;
Kevin played 521 games for the club, finishing with 3,968 points including 1,832 goals. Since leaving the Rhinos, he took up the position as Rugby Director with the Rugby Football League and was a key part of the World Cup management team that took England back to the World Cup Final in December 2017.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #5 | Steven Bartlett: How to make yourself achieve | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880328/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:40:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880328/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s another short bitesize episode on a Friday delving deeper into stand-out moments from the podcast.&amp;nbsp;
&amp;nbsp;
Today we hear from Steven Bartlett, the founder and former CEO of Social Chain, an agency he grew into a multi-million pound business, about the power of simply believing you can.&amp;nbsp;
&amp;nbsp;
As always, A big thanks to our sponsors Lotus Cars. Remember, you can get extended episodes of the podcast on our YouTube channel bit.</description></item><item><title>E41 - Carl Frampton: Making your dream a reality | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880329/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880329/</guid><description>Podcast Description Carl Frampton is a former two-weight world champion from Belfast.
By winning the featherweight world title in 2016, Carl became the first boxer from Northern Ireland to have held world titles in two weight classes.&amp;nbsp;
Nicknamed The Jackal, Carl is preparing to become only the third post-war British fighter to win world titles at three different weights as well as the only Irish fighter to have achieved the feat when he meets WBO super-featherweight champion Jamel Herring.</description></item><item><title>E40 - Eddie Jones: How to relentlessly pursue perfection | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880330/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880330/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eddie Jones one of the most experienced and decorated coaches in Rugby Union and the current head coach of England. Since taking over in in 2015, Eddie has orchestrated a complete revival of the national team, winning the Six Nations back-to-back, including England’s first Grand Slam in a generation and their first-ever whitewash of Australia in their own backyard. Eddie also led the team on their longest-ever winning streak, matching the world record held by the All Blacks.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #4| Robin Van Persie: How to Inspire Your Children | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880331/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880331/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to our new series of short bitesize episodes, looking at stand-out moments from the podcast.&amp;nbsp;
&amp;nbsp;
Today’s clip comes from our chat with former Arsenal and Manchester United striker Robin Van Persie and the advise he gave his son to take control of his life. This has been the most viewed clip in our whole archive. The guys discuss just why it rang so true.&amp;nbsp;
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>E39 - Josh Warrington: How to adopt a warrior mindset | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880332/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880332/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josh Warrington is the IBF Featherweight World Champion and the former WBC International European, British and Commonwealth Featherweight Champion.
Josh boasts a perfect record of 30 wins from 30 fights including 7 knockouts. Nicknamed the Leeds Warrior, Josh is the first World Champion to hail from Leeds.&amp;nbsp;
As Josh has progressed from English Champion to have now made himself the IBF World Champion. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #3| Marcelino Sambé: Be true to yourself | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880333/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880333/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s Friday! So here is another short bitesize episode, looking at stand-out moments from the podcast with more context, more discussion and more analysis from our hosts Jake and Damian. Today it&amp;rsquo;s with principal dancer of the Royal Ballet - Marcelino Sambé, and why you have to be true to yourself. Thanks to our sponsors Lotus Cars. Remember, you can get extended episodes of the podcast on our YouTube channel bit.</description></item><item><title>E38 - Dilbagh Gill: How to turn a dream into reality | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880334/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880334/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dilbagh Gill is CEO and Team Principal of the Mahindra Racing Team. Mahindra Racing is one of ten founding teams – and the only Indian team – to compete in the Formula E Championship. Dilbagh has built his team from the ground up which has led to multiple race victories and podiums.
With more than two decades of experience working in technology and business development and a Tech Mahindra family member for over 10 years, Dilbagh developed unique sporting technology practices that led him to working on high-profile programmes including Project Manager of FIFA World Cup and A1GP ahead of his work with Mahindra Racing.</description></item><item><title>E37 - Kasper Schmeichel: Making self belief your superpower | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880335/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 00:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880335/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kasper Schmeichel is a Premier League winner with Leicester City, a club where he’s been the No.1 goalkeeper throughout the entirety of his time at King Power Stadium, where he’s also lifted Championship titles, as well as playing in the UEFA Champions League.
Kasper has previously had loan spells from Manchester City to Darlington, Bury, Falkirk, Cardiff City and Coventry City, including a one-year permanent spell at Notts County, before signing from Leeds United for Leicester in 2011.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #2 | Holly Tucker : How great it is to be naive | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880336/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880336/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re back with another weekly Friday bitesize episode, looking at stand-out moments from the podcast with more context, more discussion and more analysis from our hosts Jake and Damian.
Today we go back to our conversation with ‘Not On The High Street’ founder Holly Tucker, and how naivety helped her grow her business from the ground up. Thanks to our sponsors Lotus Cars. Remember, you can get extended episodes of the podcast on our YouTube channel bit.</description></item><item><title>BITESIZE #1 | Steven Gerrard: How to deal with failure | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880337/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 07:54:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880337/</guid><description>Podcast Description Good news! Every Friday, we’re releasing new bitesize episodes that look at stand-out moments from the podcast with more context, more discussion and more analysis from our hosts Jake and Damian. Helping you live a more high performance life!
This week we go back to our conversation with Rangers boss Steven Gerrard, and his relationship with failure.
Listen to Steven's full episode here: https://pod.fo/e/a33ba
Thanks to our sponsors Lotus Cars.</description></item><item><title>E36 - Series Three Roundup with Jake and Damian | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880338/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880338/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jake and Damian reflect on the key takeaways from the incredible guests from Series Three, including Sir Clive Woodward, Steven Gerrard, Siya Kolisi, Steph Houghton, Matthew McConaughey, Kelly Jones and many more.
This series wrap up we’re basing around the five stages of successful change:&amp;nbsp;1.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Dream 2.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Leap 3.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Fight 4.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Climb 5.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Arrive
Jake and Damian talk through these stages and both pick out their favourite clips.&amp;nbsp;Thank you for all your comments and reviews this series, we really appreciate it.</description></item><item><title>E35 - Siya Kolisi: A simple guide to achieving greatness | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880339/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880339/</guid><description>Podcast Description Siya Kolisi is the captain of the South Africa national team and the Stormers in Super Rugby. He is the first black man to serve as captain, leading the team to a historic victory in the 2019 World Cup Final.
Siya lifting the trophy is the enduring image of the whole tournament. Having grown up in poverty, Siya has become an inspiration off the field as well as on it.</description></item><item><title>E34 - Tyrone Mings: How our struggles lead to our successes | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880340/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880340/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tyrone Mings is a defender for Aston Villa and England, with a real life story of rags to riches in English football.
Tyrone joined Southampton as a kid but suffered rejection when he was released by Saints in 2009 for being 'too small'. He dropped down to Non-League, playing for Yate Town and Chippenham Town while working as a mortgage advisor.
He seriously considered packing football in all together but got his break when Ipswich signed him up for a fee of £10,000 before sealing an £8 million move to Bournemouth and realising his dream of becoming a Premier League player.</description></item><item><title>E33 - Steph Houghton: Making your actions speak louder than words | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880341/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880341/</guid><description>Podcast Description Steph Houghton MBE is the current captain of England &amp;amp; Manchester City and one of the most recognisable faces in women’s football.
Steph has 120 caps for England and represented Team GB at the 2012 Olympics, scoring in all three group matches, including the winning goals against New Zealand and Brazil.
Steph has led Manchester City to two FA Women's Cups, three Continental Cup successes and the FA Women's Super League title as well as landing the PFA Merit Award in 2019.</description></item><item><title>E32 - Nims Purja: Make your dreams a reality | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880342/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880342/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nirmal ‘Nims’ Purja MBE became the fastest person to climb all of the 14 worlds highest 8000 meter mountains in 2019. The previous record for this achievement was just under 8 years. Nims achieved this in just 6 months and 6 days. Aptly named&amp;nbsp;Project Possible, Nims delivered on his promise and what many claimed to be ‘impossible’.
Previously, Nims served in The Gurkhas for 6 years before passing Special Forces selection and joining the SBS (Special Boat Service) where he served for a further 10 years.</description></item><item><title>E31 - Kelly Jones: Not being controlled by fear | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880343/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 01:01:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880343/</guid><description>Podcast Description Singer-songwriter Kelly Jones is the frontman of rock band Stereophonics. Kelly was born in South Wales, has achieved more than 10 million sales, six No 1 albums and 11 Top 10 singles (including the chart-topping&amp;nbsp;Dakota), along with 23 platinum sales awards and one BRIT Award.
Kelly spoke about the requirement to embrace - and "walk towards" - vulnerability, in order to access creativity. He recounted the benefits and cost of a furious work ethic and he shares the high performance lessons taught by Bono, Bowie and Bob Geldof.</description></item><item><title>E30 - Matthew McConaughey: Looking for life’s green lights | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880344/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880344/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our guest this week needs little introduction. He is one of Hollywood’s most sought after leading men, who launched his career in the cult classic Dazed and Confused and has since then has won an Academy Award for his portrayal of Ron Woodroof in Dallas Buyers Club and appeared in more than 40 feature films.
Matthew McConaughey is an actor producer, director, philanthropist and best selling author of ‘Greenlights’.</description></item><item><title>E29 - Billy Monger: It's not the fact but how you react | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880345/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880345/</guid><description>Podcast Description Billy Monger is an elite motorsport athlete who suffered a catastrophic accident in his Formula 4 car in 2017 where he received amputations to both of his legs.
The way Billy recovered and returned to the sport despite the huge personal challenges that lay ahead is simply remarkable. Billy has not only started competing at the same level but has also carved out a successful TV career.
Billy tells Jake and Damian the lessons he’s learnt through his life to date and how he's adjusted to life without legs.</description></item><item><title>E28 - Sir Clive Woodward: How to conquer the world with non-negotiables | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880346/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880346/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sir Clive Woodward is the head coach who led England’s rugby players to World Cup glory in Australia in 2003. A former England International and British &amp;amp; Irish Lion himself, prior to his full time coaching career Clive established a successful business career working for nine years with Xerox.
During Clive’s tenure as Head Coach England moved from 6th in the world to being the number one ranked team, winning every trophy an England team can win.</description></item><item><title>E27 - Lily Cole: Breaking barriers with courage | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880347/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880347/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lily Cole is an author, actress, entrepreneur, philanthropist and former supermodel.
Lily was well known for her modelling career but is now better known as co-founder of Impossible.com: a technology company that uses tech to solve social and environmental problems.
Lily was the youngest model to appear on the cover of British Vogue, and was listed by French Vogue as one of the top 30 models of the 2000s.</description></item><item><title>E26 - Eddie Hearn: Not getting high on your own supply | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880348/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880348/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eddie is one of the world’s most prominent sports promoters and the current managing director of Matchroom Sport. He is the son of promoter Barry Hearn, the founder of Matchroom.
Eddie’s company, Matchroom Boxing, expertly promotes more than 90 boxers, including several world champions such as Anthony Joshua. In 2018 Eddie negotiated boxing's first ever billion dollar streaming deal.
Relentless: 12 Rounds to Success by Eddie Hearn is out now (Hodder &amp;amp; Stoughton, Hardback, £20)</description></item><item><title>E25 - Steven Gerrard: how to make high expectations a reality | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880349/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880349/</guid><description>Podcast Description Steven Gerrard, the current manager of Rangers FC, is recognised as one of the greatest players in Liverpool FC’s history and one of the most outstanding midfield players of his generation.
Having progressed&amp;nbsp;through the youth ranks at the Merseyside club, he&amp;nbsp;went on to make&amp;nbsp;710 appearances for the Reds, scoring 186 goals. He won eight major trophies, including the famous Champions League comeback in 2005, before joining the MLS side LA Galaxy in 2015.</description></item><item><title>E24 - Series Two Roundup with Jake and Damian | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880350/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2020 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880350/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jake and Damian reflect on the key takeaways from the incredible guests from Series Two, including Ole Gunnar Solskjaer, Dina Asher-Smith, Shaun Wane, Michelle Mone, Frank Lampard, Jonny Wilkinson and more. They both pick out their favourite clips from the series and discuss the behaviours and common themes that came out of the podcasts. Thank you for all your comments and reviews this series, we really appreciate it. And thank you to Lotus Cars our sponsor for their continued support.</description></item><item><title>E23 - Jonny Wilkinson: how a mental health crisis led to a life of exploration | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880351/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 07:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880351/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jonny Wilkinson is one of the most decorated and recognisable faces in rugby history. Jonny scored 1,246 points from 97 Test appearances, the most famous being his drop goal that won the World Cup for England in 2003.
In a stellar career Jonny would accumulate four Six Nations titles with England and at club level he left Newcastle after helping them to Premiership and Powergen Cup titles and joined RC Toulon winning the Top 14 and European Cup.</description></item><item><title>E22 - Sir Ben Ainslie: The power of positive belief | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880352/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880352/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sir Ben Ainslie is the most successful Olympic sailor of all time, with four golds and one silver medal over a 16 year period.
Ben had the honour of being Team GB’s flag bearer for the London 2012 Olympic Closing Ceremony, was knighted in 2013 and in the same year added the America’s Cup to his list of achievements, with victory in the most remarkable of comebacks.
Ben is now the Team Principal and Skipper of British America’s Cup; INEOS Team UK.</description></item><item><title>E21 - Frank Lampard: Taking on 100% responsibility, whilst retaining humility | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880353/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880353/</guid><description>Podcast Description Frank Lampard is the current head coach of Chelsea FC. Frank retired as one of the greatest players of the modern era, with his legendary status cemented by his extraordinary achievements and statistics.
When he left Chelsea in the summer of 2014, Frank was the club's record goalscorer with 211 goals from 649 appearances - a truly remarkable return for a consummate professional plying his trade in midfield.</description></item><item><title>E19 - Reece Wabara: Taking control of your life, your business and your brand | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880354/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880354/</guid><description>Podcast Description Reece Wabara is a former professional footballer turned fashion CEO powerhouse.
Reece played for Manchester City and several loan spells at clubs including Ipswich, Oldham, Doncaster, Wigan and Bolton, before he founded Manière De Voir in 2014 - a sports luxe brand - whilst in the midst of a football career.
The multi-million pound Manchester-based online fashion brand has reported a 187% year on year increase in net revenue to over £5 million in the three months to 31 June.</description></item><item><title>E18 - Phil Neville: Exploring the boundaries of your comfort zone | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880355/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880355/</guid><description>Podcast Description Phil Neville was a serial winner in his illustrious 18 year career as a footballer. Phil won 59 caps for England and was a regular with Manchester United in the 1998-99 treble-winning campaign.
In total, he won six Premier League titles, three FA Cups and the UEFA Champions League before joining Everton, where he was club captain and played 303 times.
Phil was appointed England Women’s head coach in January 2018 winning the SheBelieves Cup title in 2019 and reaching the last four of the World Cup.</description></item><item><title>E17 - Shaun Wane: How to handle success and struggles exactly the same | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880356/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880356/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shaun Wane is the current England rugby league Head Coach.
Previously Shaun was Head Coach of Wigan, his hometown club for whom he made 149 appearances as a player, from 2011-18 - a period in which the Warriors won three Super League titles, reached five Grand Finals at Old Trafford, won the Challenge Cup at Wembley in 2013, and were crowned World Club Champions in 2017. Shaun also won two caps for Great Britain in 1985-86.</description></item><item><title>E16 - Sir Chris Hoy: The importance of doing the work so you can enjoy the experience | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880357/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880357/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sir Chris Hoy is a true sporting legend and one of the most successful British athletes of all time with six gold medals and one silver.
Chris won his first Olympic gold medal in Athens 2004, won three gold medals at the Beijing Olympics and cemented his name in the history books by winning two golds at the London Olympics in 2012.
Following his historic hat-trick of gold medals in Beijing , Chris was voted 2008 BBC Sports Personality of the Year.</description></item><item><title>E15 - Dina Asher Smith: Believe in your own sauce! Focus on your strengths | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880358/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880358/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s guest is Dina Asher-Smith, the reigning 200 metres World Champion and the fastest women in British history.
Dina took gold at the World Athletics Championships in Doha having already taken silver in the 100 metres.
She was also seriously impressive at the European Athletics Championships in Berlin in 2018, winning three gold medals in the 100m, 200m and 4x100m relay.
Dina is one of Britain's best prospects for gold at the Olympic Games in Japan next year.</description></item><item><title>E14 - Marcelino Sambe: Dance like no-one is watching | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880359/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880359/</guid><description>Podcast Description Portuguese dancer Marcelino Sambé is a Principal of The Royal Ballet. At just 25-years old, he already proved himself to be one of the most technically accomplished and inspiring stars in the world of dance, excelling in some of ballet’s trickiest roles – all delivered with his characteristic smile and optimism.
Born in a poor area on the outskirts of Lisbon, his father died when he was 8 and his guidance came from his local community centre.</description></item><item><title>E13 - Ole Gunnar Solskjear: Living authentically | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880360/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880360/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ole Gunnar Solskjaer scored 126 goals in 366 appearances for Manchester United, but that doesn’t go nearly far enough in explaining his legacy at Old Trafford.
On the field, the Norwegian became an embodiment of the Reds’ never-say-die spirit in their most successful decade, often scoring late goals when points or trophies looked to have been lost. The most special of all being the Champions League final in 1999 cementing his place in Man Utd folklore.</description></item><item><title>Series Two Preview | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880361/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880361/</guid><description>Podcast Description The High Performance Podcast is back for Series Two! Thank you to everyone who has been with us so far and welcome to all of you just joining in.
Returning for a second series, broadcaster Jake Humphrey and leading organisational psychologist Professor Damian Hughes speak to more world-class performers from business, sports, music and arts to hear their first-hand experiences and what lessons they've learned along the way.</description></item><item><title>E12 - Series One Roundup with Jake &amp; Damian | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880362/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880362/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jake and Damian reflect on the fantastic guests from series one, including Rio Ferdinand, Ant Middleton, Mauricio Pochettino, Steven Bartlett, Robin Van Persie, Holly Tucker, Kelly Holmes and many more. They both pick out their favourite clips from the series and discuss the&amp;nbsp;non-negotiable behaviours&amp;nbsp;and common themes that came out of the podcasts.&amp;nbsp;
It’s not goodbye for long though, series 2 will be coming very soon with more elite high-performance guests!</description></item><item><title>E11 - Sean Dyche: Allowing individual brilliance in a team environment | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880363/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880363/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sean Dyche is the current manager of Burnley, having been in charge since October 2012. For 20 years he was a professional footballer making over 450 appearances, but he is best known as a manager. His achievements since joining Burnley mark him as one of the club&amp;rsquo;s most successful managers in the modern era. Sean steered the club to promotion to the Premier League within 18-months of his arrival and in the 2017/18 campaign, Burnley finished 7th - their highest league standing since 1975 - bringing European football back to Turf Moor for the first time in 51 years.</description></item><item><title>E10 - Kelly Holmes: 20% talent, 80% mindset | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880364/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880364/</guid><description>Podcast Description Double Olympic Champion Col. Dame Kelly Holmes is one of the UK’s most popular athletes. Kelly is an Olympic, Commonwealth and European champion that has achieved seven Gold, eight Silver and four Bronze medals throughout her career. This includes her double win in the 800m and 1500m at the 2004 Olympic Games in Athens, becoming the first Briton in over 80 years to do so. Kelly won BBC Sports Personality of the Year, European Athlete of the Year and was honoured with a Damehood from the Queen.</description></item><item><title>E9 - Dylan Hartley: Learning independence and responsibility | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880365/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880365/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dylan Hartley won 97 caps for England, the most by any hooker, and as the England captain he had an incredible 85% win record. He led his country to two Six Nations titles – one of which was the first grand slam in 13 years – and a first away series win in Australia. Dylan also made 251 appearances for Northampton Saints and spent eight years as their skipper.</description></item><item><title>E8 - Holly Tucker: Wait for the right time and you’ll wait forever | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880366/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880366/</guid><description>Podcast Description Holly Tucker is one of the UK’s most respected entrepreneurs. She is the founder of Holly &amp;amp; Co, UK Ambassador to Small Creative Businesses and co-founder of notonthehighstreet.com. Holly’s purpose and passion is to mentor and support other small businesses and now during the Covid-19 outbreak she has launched SME:SOS, a free resource to empower small businesses and provide all the help they need in these uncertain times.</description></item><item><title>E7 - Robin Van Persie: Lessons for your children | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880367/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880367/</guid><description>Podcast Description Robin Van Persie is one the greatest strikers to win the Premier League. He scored 144 goals making him the highest-scoring player from the Netherlands in English top-flight history. He was a cult hero at Arsenal, before moving to arch rivals Manchester United in 2012, then finishing his career at his first club Feyenoord. Listen to the lessons he learnt through his career, the truth behind his controversial Arsenal and Manchester Untied exits, the sacrifices he made to be an elite athlete and so much more.</description></item><item><title>E6 - Tracey Neville: How sacrifice leads to success | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880368/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880368/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s guest comes from family of sporting superstars; her dad was a professional cricketer and her brothers were both international footballers, but Tracey Neville transitioned from being an elite athlete to an elite coach, delivering one of this country’s greatest sporting triumphs - winning a Commonwealth gold medal for England netball. Listen to her stories and secrets of changing a sport forever.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>E5 - Tom Daley: How trauma leads to triumph | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880369/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880369/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s guest is Tom Daley, one of Britain’s most recognised sportsmen. Tom has won a diving gold or finished first in a major competition every single year for 14 successive years! He won a national U18 competition aged just ten, competed in the Olympics at fourteen and won a bronze at London 2012. Tom’s fame transcends his sport - he lost his father to cancer in 2011, publicly came out as gay, got married, had a baby and has became a key spokesperson for LGBT+ rights.</description></item><item><title>E4 - Steven Bartlett: The importance of believing you can | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880370/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880370/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the pod we’re joined by Steven Bartlett, the self-made 27-year-old CEO of Social Chain, a leading global media agency, which he started at just 22. Jake and Damian delve deep into Steven’s unique philosophy, hearing about his relentless self-belief and entrepreneurial mindset.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>E3 - Mauricio Pochettino: How to build a team with compassion | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880371/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880371/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mauricio Pochettino is the current manager of PSG. He’s a man who creates a real family atmosphere wherever he coaches. He has won trophies at Espanyol and PSG as a player, but he’s now best known as a top-class manager with spells at Espanyol and Southampton before he took Tottenham to finals and their best league finish in 25 years, playing football as effective as it was impressive. Hear his stories of inspiring people, selecting players and his football philosophy.</description></item><item><title>E2 - Ant Middleton: How to create and maintain a zero excuses mindset | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880372/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880372/</guid><description>Podcast Description When I drew up a list of dream names for the High Performance Podcast, Ant Middleton was right at the top of that list. An accomplished military career that includes the coveted King’s Badge as a Royal Marine, before joining the Special Boat Service - Ant’s whole career epitomises high performance. He is now best known as the Chief Instructor for Channel 4’s hit show, &amp;lsquo;SAS : Who Dares Wins&amp;rsquo;, but is also a best-selling author, motivational speaker and tours the UK with his ‘Mind Over Muscle’ brand.</description></item><item><title>E1 - Rio Ferdinand: Lessons from loss | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880373/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880373/</guid><description>Podcast Description From an estate in Peckham, to the World Cup. From winning the Champions League to struggling at QPR. What was it really like in the Manchester United dressing room? Is he happy? What has personal tragedy taught him about being a better person? This is Rio Ferdinand as you’ve never heard him before, openly sharing his secrets to his High Performance life. Winning cultures, elite mindsets, and the tricks you can employ to enjoy success and taste happiness in your own life&amp;hellip;whatever comes your way.</description></item><item><title>Join Jake and Damian for High Performance... | The High Performance Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8182880374/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 12:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8182880374/</guid><description>Podcast Description Introducing your new favourite podcast, as sports presenter Jake Humphrey and leading organisational psychologist Damian Hughes introduce you to some remarkable people, operating at the top of their game.
Subscribe now!
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>