<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Head Game on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/head-game/</link><description>Recent content in Head Game on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 15:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/head-game/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bali Bombings Survivor Jason McCartney On The Comeback That Inspired A Nation | Head Game</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9622000001/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9622000001/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Ant speaks to Australian Rules footballer and survivor of the 2002 Bali terrorist attack, Jason McCartney. Jason shares what it was like being involved in the tragedy, his long road of recovery, and how his positive mindset helped to get him through.
LINKS
Find our more about Jason McCartney's inspirational speaking here
After Bali is available here
Want to see Ant live on stage? Click here for his current tour dates.</description></item><item><title>Climbing Took Jim Davidson's Best Friend, But Taught Him Resilience | Head Game</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9622000002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9622000002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jim Davidson and Mike Price, two friends and experienced climbing partners, summited Mount Rainier on June 21, 1992. As they descended, a hidden snowbridge collapsed beneath Jim’s feet and dropped him into a large glacial crevasse. Connected to Jim by the climbing rope, Mike tried to stop the fall but couldn’t.
In a heartbreaking conversation, Jim shares this painful memory with Ant - and how loss, resilience and the strength to survive has shaped not only that fateful day, but the rest of his life.</description></item><item><title>Surviving a Sydney Harbour Shark Attack | Head Game</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9622000003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9622000003/</guid><description>Podcast Description 'Improvise... Adapt... Overcome' - these three words always resonated with Paul de Gelder, but they took on a whole new meaning after he was attacked by a shark in 2009. Paul was working as an elite Navy clearance diver, and the incident caused him to lose two limbs. In this episode, Paul and Ant reflect on that day and what saved his life, his mental health in recovery and how humour, resilience and a few good mates can get you through anything.</description></item><item><title>Inside the Life of a Spy With Jack Beaumont | Head Game</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9622000004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9622000004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jack Beaumont has one incredible story. He was a fighter pilot for the French air force, when an injury during dogfight training changed his life forever.
Jack was then recruited by French intelligence to work for the DGSE - balancing family life with working undercover in clandestine foreign operations. In this episode, Jack takes us into the mindset of a spy. He delves into the moment where he felt he'd turned into a monster - and what ultimately made him walk away.</description></item><item><title>How Sean Turnell Survived the Toughest Prison in South East Asia | Head Game</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9622000005/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9622000005/</guid><description>Podcast Description February 6th, 2021 is the day that Sean Turnell's world got flipped upside down. After receiving an anonymous tip off that military leadership in Myanmar were coming for him, Sean went to check out of his hotel, and was arrested.
The 58 year old Economist from Australia would go on to spend 650 days behind bars. Sean shares the horrors of that period with Ant - how he survived Yangon's notorious Insein Prison, what it was like to face spy charges and his bizarre story of release.</description></item><item><title>How Jelena Dokic Became Fearless | Head Game</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9622000006/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9622000006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jelena Dokic is the epitome of strength. At just 16 years old and ranked World #129, Jelena pulled off a career-defining victory against then-World #1, Martina Hingis. At a time where her sporting career was on an incredible trajectory, behind closed doors she was facing the toughest challenge of her life - surviving harrowing domestic abuse from her father.
In a powerful and moving conversation, Jelena opens up to Ant about overcoming adversity, poverty and violence to rise to the top.</description></item><item><title>The Day That Changed Jackson Warne's Life Forever | Head Game</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9622000007/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9622000007/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 4th of March 2022 is a day that Jackson Warne will never forget. His father, legendary Aussie cricketer - Shane Warne, passed away suddenly whilst holidaying in Thailand. At just 22 years old, Jackson was forced to grieve with the world watching. Today, for the first time in 18 months - Jackson opens up. He shares with Ant the impact that his 'bestest mate' had on him, takes us inside the moment he received the devastating call, and describes some of the powerful messages he's had from his Dad, since his passing.</description></item><item><title>Chris Lemons' Miraculous Deep Sea Survival | Head Game</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9622000008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9622000008/</guid><description>Podcast Description On one September night in 2012, Deep Sea Saturation Diver Chris Lemons fought for his life. At 2am, 300 feet beneath the North Sea, Chris was stranded in total darkness. In a remarkable story of survival, best known from Netflix's Last Breath documentary, Chris takes Ant inside those terrifying moments, and shares how teamwork, resilience and remaining calm were crucial to keeping him alive.
LINKS
Learn more about Chris Lemons and his public speaking on his website https://www.</description></item><item><title>Life Lessons From The World's Most Extreme Ultramarathons | Head Game</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9622000009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9622000009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Just days after completing an incredible 14 400 kilometre run around Australia, ultra marathon runner Pat Farmer joins Ant for a raw, inspiring and honest conversation.
Pat touches on what it takes to run extreme distances through some of the harshest conditions on the planet, his 'purpose', and how he overcomes challenges on his toughest days. CW: This episode contains discussions of suicide. If this episode raises any issues for you, help is available through Lifeline on 13 11 14 or via their website lifeline.</description></item><item><title>What It Really Takes To Catch Killers With Gary Jubelin | Head Game</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9622000010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9622000010/</guid><description>Podcast Description CW: Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander listeners are warned the following episode mentions names of deceased persons. Gary Jubelin has led some of the country’s biggest cases and is responsible for bringing down many of Australia’s most notorious criminals – murderers, gangsters, even serial killers.
After dedicating 34 years of his life to the police force, in 2020 Gary controversially became the subject of his own investigation.
Today, the host of the hit podcast I Catch Killers reflects on his time as a Detective - sharing how he got into the minds of our worst criminals, felt he needed to 'cleanse his soul', and the price his family had to pay for his career.</description></item><item><title>Todd Russell Takes Us Inside His Mind During the Beaconsfield Disaster | Head Game</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9622000011/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9622000011/</guid><description>Podcast Description ANZAC Day 2006 was a day that changed the course of Todd Russell's life forever. Working a kilometre underground in Tasmania's Beaconsfield mine, Todd and workmate Brant Webb became trapped following a seismic event.
In one of the most extraordinary survival feats of all time, Todd and Brant remained underground for 14 days - 321 hours, before finally reaching the surface on the 9th of May, 2006. In this powerful conversation, Todd takes us inside what went through his mind in those 321 hours, how he and Brant found the strength to fight to be reunited with their families, and the impact the disaster has had on him today.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Head Game with Ant Middleton | Head Game</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9622000012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 22:44:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9622000012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join Ant Middleton as he speaks with people that have beaten the odds and achieved the unthinkable by getting their head in the game. You’ll hear extraordinary stories of survival, relive heroic moments, unpack the details of life-changing decisions, and celebrate the achievement of seemingly impossible goals. This podcast series highlights what we’re capable of when we harness the power of the mind.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item></channel></rss>