<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/solved-murders-true-crime-mysteries/</link><description>Recent content in Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/solved-murders-true-crime-mysteries/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Black Dahlia Murder Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Elizabeth Short’s gruesome murder is the LAPD’s most infamous unsolved case. But there’s one person who thinks he’s cracked it — the alleged killer’s own son. Today, we reopen the case against George Hodel, a certified genius and once-celebrated doctor who rubbed elbows with noted surrealists… and had a vile history of abuse and terror, even against his own family. This episode originally aired August 2022 - to hear more of Vanessa and Carter check out Serial Killers and Conspiracy Theories.</description></item><item><title>The Black Dahlia Murder Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780002/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1940s Hollywood, a 22-year-old aspiring actress is found mutilated and drained of blood. Her body is posed, and her mouth has been carved into a permanent smile. The investigation takes police into the hidden sides of the city — illicit romances and gang-related crimes. But when another mutilated body is found weeks later, the hunt is on for a possible serial killer. This is a crossover series with Unsolved Murders, looking at the murder of Elizabeth Short and other unsolved cases surrounding it.</description></item><item><title>Irene Garza Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780003/</guid><description>Podcast Description After the death of Irene Garza in a small Texas town, a massive cover-up ensued, headed by one of the most powerful institutions in the world.This episode originally aired in March 2022. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Irene Garza Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780004/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the evening of April 16, 1960, Irene Garza went to church in the peaceful town of McAllen, Texas but never came home. Less than a week later, her body was found in a canal. Residents were terrified. Had a predator come to town to prey on them, or was one of their own a murderer? This episode originally aired in March 2022. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Party Fouls: House Party Horror | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780005/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2011, 17-year-old Tyler Hadley threw a wild house party in Port St. Lucie, Florida. What his guests didn’t know was that on the other side of a locked door, dead bodies lay hidden. A jarring confession ignited a race against time to end the revelry for good. This episode originally aired in August 2021. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Clutter Family Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780006/</guid><description>Podcast Description After the massacre of the Clutter Family on November 15th, 1959, the Kansas Bureau of Investigation began an intensive probe into the crime. Their search for the killers would result in one of the greatest true crime stories of all time. This episode originally aired in June 2019. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Clutter Family Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780007/</guid><description>Podcast Description On November 15th, 1959, the small town of Holcomb, Kansas experienced one of the most gruesome crimes imaginable. Four members of the Clutter Family had been gunned down in their own home—but nobody knew why. This episode originally aired in June 2019. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Video Strangler Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Like many serial killers, Maury Travis became over-confident. In the summer of 2002, after reading a story in the newspaper about one of his victims, he mailed a letter to the local newspaper offering them information on the location of another. He was careful not to leave any fingerprints or DNA evidence before mailing it, so how did they track him down? This episode originally aired on Serial Killers in July 2018.</description></item><item><title>The Video Strangler Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780009/</guid><description>Podcast Description There was no evidence in Maury Travis’ childhood of arson or animal abuse, often seen as early warning signs for serial killers. And he didn’t appear to have been a victim of abuse from either of his parents. So what made this seemingly normal kid turn into a man who would rape, torture and murder as many as twenty women? This episode originally aired on Serial Killers in July 2018.</description></item><item><title>The Unabomber Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780010/</guid><description>Podcast Description By the 1980s, Ted Kaczynski had set off several bombs, causing only minor injuries — but for him, it wasn’t enough. What had started as a plot for revenge grew into an unrelenting need to change the world. To do that, he needed to kill. The reign of the Unabomber had begun. This episode originally aired on Serial Killers in April 2021. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>The Unabomber Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Spotting his genius at a young age, Ted Kaczynski’s parents pushed their son to academic excellence — but Ted never found a true home in the hallowed halls of academia. Instead, by 1969, he was a former math professor with a festering hatred for the modern world. This episode originally aired on Serial Killers in April 2021. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Message from Carter | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Solved Murders is coming to an end. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Victims of Dorothea Puente | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780013/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the mid 1980s a nightmarish story swept the nation. One man’s disappearance in Sacramento, California, led officials to investigate a boarding house with a sinister past…and horrifying secrets buried beneath its garden. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Babes in the Wood | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780014/</guid><description>Podcast Description When two young girls are found dead in Brighton, England, a local man does everything he can to avoid suspicion. Four years later, a young girl stumbles naked out of the woods north of Brighton, and police have to ask: Is history repeating itself? And if they can’t secure a conviction, will their prime suspect walk free… again? This episode originally aired on Cold Cases in December 2022. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>The Bombing of Flight 629 Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780015/</guid><description>Podcast Description 23-year-old Jack Graham unravels as the FBI uncovers his deadly vendetta against Daisie King, who was a passenger on Flight 629—and Jack’s own mother. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Bombing of Flight 629 Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780016/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the mid-1950s, a plane bound for Seattle from Denver exploded mid-flight. 44 people were killed. When investigators began analyzing the wreckage, they couldn’t help noticing a distinctive smell: gunpowder. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Eleventh Circuit Mail Bombings | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Around Christmas 1989, a series of pipe bombs sent through the mail killed two of its intended targets: Judge Robert Vance and attorney Robbie Robinson. Federal investigators set out to capture a serial bomber. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Murder of Timothy Coggins | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780018/</guid><description>Podcast Description The last time Telisa Coggins sees her brother alive, he’s walking out of a nightclub in Griffin, Georgia. Tim’s body is later found under an oak tree, mutilated almost beyond recognition. But just as police begin uncovering solid leads, the investigation grounds to a halt. Decades later, a new investigator will start asking: Why? This episode originally aired on Cold Cases in November 2022. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>The Missing Dead: Sarah Stern | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780019/</guid><description>Podcast Description On a December evening in 2016, a man called 911 when he spotted an abandoned car on a bridge. Police discovered that 19-year-old Sarah Stern of Neptune City, New Jersey, usually drove the vehicle. She was now missing, and police needed to determine if she had left the car voluntarily or was the victim of a crime.
If you’d like to learn more about the cases covered in this episode, or learn more about Missing and Unidentified Persons Awareness Month, head to www.</description></item><item><title>The Missing Dead: Girly Chew Hossencofft | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780020/</guid><description>Podcast Description In September 1999, 36-year-old Girly Chew Hossencofft was supposed to report to work at a local Bank of America branch in Albuquerque, New Mexico. Due to recent threats made by her husband, Girly’s co-workers were worried. When a colleague went to her house to check on her, she was gone. And she was never seen again.
If you’d like to learn more about the cases covered in this episode, or learn more about Missing and Unidentified Persons Awareness Month, head to www.</description></item><item><title>The Missing Dead: Kristin Smart | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780021/</guid><description>Podcast Description It was May of 1996 when college freshman Kristin Smart went to a party and never returned to her dorm. More than 20 years later, a stranger started a podcast that ignited interest in the case and brought a killer to justice.
If you’d like to learn more about the cases covered in this episode, or learn more about Missing and Unidentified Persons Awareness Month, head to www.spotify.com/disappearances. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>The Murder of Don Mellett Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780022/</guid><description>Podcast Description When his family realized that the Canton police would not conduct an honest investigation into the murder of journalist Don Mellett, they hired a PI named Ora Slater to look into the case. He quickly narrowed his suspect list down to three people. But finding eyewitnesses willing to cooperate proved to be an even bigger task. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Murder of Don Mellett Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780023/</guid><description>Podcast Description He had recently led a crusade against the city&amp;rsquo;s corrupt police force as the editor of the Canton Daily News. After exposing crooked officials and getting some officers fired, Don Mellett was shot dead outside his home by an unknown assailant. His family didn&amp;rsquo;t trust that the Canton police department would try to solve the murder, so they looked elsewhere. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description></item><item><title>The Pillow Pyro | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780024/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the mid-1980s Los Angeles is in the midst of a serial killer boom. But that’s not all. A serial arsonist has been setting blazes across the area, leading to millions of dollars in damage and the deaths of four people. Most of the fires started in bins of pillows, cushion stuffing, or bedding — lending the “Pillow Pyro” moniker to the slippery culprit. This episode originally aired on Cold Cases.</description></item><item><title>Front Line Defender: Berta Cáceres | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780025/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the evening of March 2nd, 2016, indigenous environmental activist Berta Cáceres was murdered in her home by armed intruders. Due to widespread corruption in Honduras, police weren&amp;rsquo;t motivated to solve the case. Her family knew she was killed for trying to stop urban development on sacred land. They just needed to prove it.
If you’d like to take action on the climate or learn more about the topics covered in “Dark Green: Earth Crimes and Conspiracies,” visit www.</description></item><item><title>The Fight for Humanity: Chico Mendes | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780026/</guid><description>Podcast Description He dedicated most of his life to protecting rubber trees in the Amazonian town of Xapuri, where he lived. During that time, Chico Mendes received countless death threats. But on the night of December 22nd, 1988, somebody made good on their promise. If you’d like to take action on the climate or learn more about the topics covered in “Dark Green: Earth Crimes and Conspiracies,” visit www.spotify.com/darkgreenresources. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>The Yogurt Shop Murders | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780027/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780027/</guid><description>Podcast Description It was 1991 when four teenage girls were brutally killed inside a yogurt store in Austin, Texas. With no witnesses to the crime, police had very little to go on. But soon, there was a confession. Then another. And another. It was up to investigators to sort through the evidence and discover the truth. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Alone in Ossipee: Florence Small Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Prosecutors Walter Hill and James P. Tuttle were faced with a difficult task. They had to convince a jury that Frederick Small could burn down a cottage from a hundred miles away. They would get their chance with the help of an electrician who was ready to testify. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Alone in Ossipee: Florence Small Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780029/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Late one night in September 1916, a cottage in New Hampshire burst into flames. Florence Small’s body was eventually found in the cellar — but it was clear she’d suffered more than just burns. Less than 24 hours later, police had a suspect. There was only one problem: he had an alibi. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 4: Oklahoma Burning | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780030/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780030/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a firestorm of racial violence rages through the territory, Bass Reeves learns of his next arrest: his own son. Soon after, statehood and Jim Crow laws force Bass into retirement, while whitewashing covers up his accomplishments as Oklahoma&amp;rsquo;s Lone Ranger. In search of justice, we consider his complex legacy. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 3: Lawman vs. The Law | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780031/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Accused of murdering his cook in cold blood, Bass stands up for his own innocence - breaking himself financially. Not long after he frees himself, the Marshals become embroiled in a bloody war with a legendary Cherokee leader. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 2: U.S. Marshal | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780032/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eager to protect his growing family, Bass becomes one of the first Black Deputy U.S. Marshals West of the Mississippi. The face of the law in a lawless land, Bass outwits and outshoots countless criminals. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 1: Bass in the Wild | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780033/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780033/</guid><description>Podcast Description As an enslaved man, Bass Reeves fights hand-to-hand with his enslaver. Victorious, Bass escapes, becoming a fugitive in America’s most dangerous, lawless territory just before the Civil War. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Introducing Bass Reeves: No Master But Duty | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780034/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the next four weeks, Carter and Wenndy are handing over the reins to Darnell Ishmel, guest host of a four-part miniseries exploring the exploits of a legendary figure of the Wild West. The man widely believed to have inspired the Lone Ranger… Who was born into slavery and became one of America’s most revered lawmen. His name was Bass Reeves. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>The Smuttynose Murders Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780035/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Prosecuting attorney George Yeaton was certain who committed the gruesome murders on Smuttynose Island. To him, the evidence pointed to a robbery gone wrong. But what motivated the suspect to kill the only friends he had? A follow-up conversation with the lone survivor would give him the answer. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Smuttynose Murders Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780036/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780036/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1873, two women were brutally murdered on Smuttynose Island just off the coast of Maine. A woman who escaped the attack reported her story to the police. Though she didn&amp;rsquo;t see him, she claimed to know who the killer was. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Marlborough Mystery Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780037/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Based on witness testimony, authorities believed that Scott Watson killed Olivia Hope and Ben Smart. The jury agreed and took less than 24 hours to convict him. But since his incarceration, several witnesses have recanted their testimony, saying they were pressured by police. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Marlborough Mystery Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780038/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780038/</guid><description>Podcast Description It was New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve 1997 in the Marlborough Sounds of New Zealand when 17-year-old Olivia Hope and 21-year-old Ben Smart enjoyed a long night of partying. When friends couldn&amp;rsquo;t locate the pair the following day, they assumed the two may have gone off on their own. But after days without contact, it became evident that something was very wrong. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description></item><item><title>Lucina Broadwell | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780039/</guid><description>Podcast Description It was May of 1919 in Barre, Vermont, when the body of Lucina Broadwell was found naked on her stomach, hands tied behind her back. To solve the crime, investigators must uncover a dark secret that the entire town is hiding. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Coors Heir Murder: Adolph Coors III Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780040/</guid><description>Podcast Description It was the most extensive manhunt since John Dillinger. Authorities believed they’d found the identity of the man who’d kidnapped and murdered Ad Coors. But when they finally tracked him down in Canada, he refused to talk. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Coors Heir Murder: Adolph Coors III Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780041/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adolph “Ad” Coors was a father of four and an heir to the Coors brewing dynasty when he was kidnapped in 1960. Breakthroughs in the case put the FBI hot on the trail of Ad’s kidnapper, until leads ran dry. Seven months after he disappeared, Ad’s body was found off a hiking trail in Denver. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2022: Madalyn Murray O'Hair Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 08:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780042/</guid><description>Podcast Description When reporter John McCormack went looking for missing celebrity pundit Madalyn Murray O’Hair, he thought it might be more than a simple case of tax evasion. Sure enough, he found a trail of stolen gold, disgruntled employees, and a disembodied torso&amp;hellip; But it would still take years to uncover the truth about Madalyn’s tragic last days. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2022: Madalyn Murray O'Hair Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780043/</guid><description>Podcast Description She was a popular atheist speaker who challenged American evangelicals wherever she went. She was also called &amp;ldquo;the most hated woman in America&amp;rdquo; and had no shortage of enemies. So when Madalyn Murray O&amp;rsquo;Hair and her family went missing in 1995, no one went looking&amp;hellip; for two whole years. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Dayton Christmas Killings Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 08:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780044/</guid><description>Podcast Description The spree continues into Christmas Day and beyond, during which the teen gang murders their third, fourth, fifth and sixth victims. After a tip, police catch the group wearing victims’ clothing, driving a victim’s stolen car, and in possession of the guns they used in their murders. A Parcast holiday special from Serial Killers. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Dayton Christmas Killings Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780045/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780045/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the early hours of Christmas Eve 1992, a senseless murder in Dayton, Ohio, marks the beginning of a rampage. What started as a desire for Christmas cash turns into a three-day killing spree that leaves six people dead. Even more shocking was that the brazen killers were just teens. A Parcast holiday special from Serial Killers. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Sweet" Fanny Adams | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780046/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780046/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s August in Alton, a small farm town in the English countryside. Eight-year-old Fanny Adams goes out to play with her friends, but never returns home. When she’s finally found, it’s a gruesome scene. In their tight knit community, there’s one man who stands out. A man who might be responsible for the death of an innocent girl. If only police could get him to crack. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Solved or Unsolved? The Death of Ned Doheny Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780047/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780047/</guid><description>Podcast Description The deaths at Greystone mansion were far from straightforward — at least as far as Detective Leslie White was concerned. But shortly after the DA announced they’d be launching a full investigation, they closed the case. The official narrative was that Hugh Plunkett shot Ned Doheny before turning the gun on himself. The evidence tells a different story. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kim Kardashian’s The System — All Episodes Out Now | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780048/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Carter introduces Spotify’s latest true crime podcast, delving into the case of Kevin Keith. Listen to an exclusive clip from the first episode right here, then head to The System to finish the episode and hear more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Solved or Unsolved? The Death of Ned Doheny Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780049/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ned Doheny found himself embroiled in a huge bribery scandal. On behalf of his father, oil baron Edward Doheny, Ned illegally obtained drilling leases from the US government. His close friend and personal secretary, Hugh Plunkett, was present for the transaction and would likely have to testify. But before either man could even walk into a courtroom, they would wind up dead. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>Thanksgiving Special: Just Add Arsenic | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780050/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the ages, arsenic has had many lives — beauty fad, household product, medical prescription… and weapon of choice wielded by killers everywhere from Alabama to ancient Rome. Brine your turkey, knead your dough, and listen to our Thanksgiving Special on the regime-changing, assassination-aiding King of Poisons. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Three in Chicago Pt. 3: The Pieces Come Together | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780051/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780051/</guid><description>Podcast Description By the early ‘90s, the case of Helen Brach was heating up. But to get answers, police needed to go deeper into Chicago’s cutthroat Horse Mafia. As agents worked their informants, the pieces of two cases, decades apart, finally came together. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Three in Chicago Pt. 2: The Missing Heiress | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780052/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780052/</guid><description>Podcast Description In February 1977, 65-year-old candy heiress Helen Brach disappeared, and her case went cold almost immediately. Over a decade later, investigators searching for her killer stumbled upon a vital clue that might not only solve her case, but the case of three missing Chicago boys decades earlier. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Three in Chicago Pt. 1: Tragedy in Jefferson Park | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780053/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780053/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1955, the quiet community of Jefferson Park in Chicago was known as a peaceful suburb. But its innocence was stripped away when three local boys went to a movie and never came home. Days later, their bodies were found. The case went cold for years before a seemingly unrelated crime provided the key to solving the mystery. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Eric Tombe | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780054/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eric Tombe’s parents had last heard from him in mid-April 1922 when he sent them a letter about an upcoming trip to Paris. Shortly after, Eric’s mother began having nightmares about her son. By mid-summer, she was convinced he was dead. By 1923, Scotland Yard would find his body. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Toolbox Killers | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780055/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two felons who met in prison decided to stay friends on the outside. They spent the summer and fall of 1979 kidnapping and murdering teenage girls in southern California. Police didn&amp;rsquo;t even have them as suspects. Until an unlikely source came forward with crucial information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Unsolved Murders: Theodosia Burr | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780056/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Aaron Burr is most infamous for killing Alexander Hamilton in a duel. But Burr was also a father — one whose daughter, Theodosia, vanished one night at sea. No one can say for sure what happened to her ship, The Patriot, or its passengers&amp;hellip; though a centuries-old portrait may hold a clue. This episode originally aired on Unsolved Murders. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deathbed Confessions: John Kelley | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780057/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780057/</guid><description>Podcast Description The estranged adult children of Geraldine Kelley long suspected foul play in their father’s death. Though she had told them that John Kelley had died in a road accident, Geri revealed on her deathbed in 2004 that she’d shot him in the head and kept his body in a storage facility freezer for years. This episode originally aired on Deathbed Confessions. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>The Hamilton-Burr Duel | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780058/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780058/</guid><description>Podcast Description There is no debate about who killed Alexander Hamilton. His infamous duel with Aaron Burr was held according to the standards at the time. But many, including the states of New York and New Jersey, concluded that Burr was a cold-blooded killer who got away with murder. This is a special one-part crossover with Unsolved Murders, a Spotify Original from Parcast. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>Dorothy May Grammer | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780059/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780059/</guid><description>Podcast Description On an August night in 1952, a blue Chrysler raced down a hill, hit a barrier, and flipped onto its side. Nearby police officers rushed to help the driver, 33-year-old Dorothy May Grammer, but it was too late. A few days later, the autopsy revealed it was no accident. It was a homicide. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The London Body Snatchers Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780060/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Four men received a guilty verdict for the murder of a person whose identity was unknown. Charges against one of the men would eventually be dropped, but the remaining three men were sentenced to die the next day. Then one of them made a startling confession. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The London Body Snatchers Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780061/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780061/</guid><description>Podcast Description In November of 1831, four men tried to sell a fresh body to the anatomist at King’s College in London. But a quick look at the body revealed it to be a little too fresh. Had these bodysnatchers robbed a new grave or murdered an innocent human to keep up with rising demand? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Madalyn Murray O'Hair Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780062/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780062/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Reporter John McCormack went looking for missing celebrity pundit Madalyn Murray O’Hair, he thought it might be more than a simple case of tax evasion. Sure enough, he found a trail of stolen gold, disgruntled employees, and a disembodied torso&amp;hellip; But it would still take years to uncover the truth about Madalyn’s tragic last days. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Madalyn Murray O'Hair Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780063/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780063/</guid><description>Podcast Description She was a popular atheist speaker who challenged American evangelical thought wherever she went. She was also called &amp;ldquo;the most hated woman in America&amp;rdquo; and had no shortage of enemies. So when Madalyn Murray O&amp;rsquo;Hair and her family went missing in 1995, no one went looking&amp;hellip; for two whole years. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Candy Box Killings Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780064/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780064/</guid><description>Podcast Description 44-year-old Cordelia Botkin was the sole suspect in a murder-by-mail case that killed two sisters and involved two jurisdictions on two different coasts. Authorities knew she had an affair with the husband of one of the victims, but could they find enough evidence to prove it? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Candy Box Killings Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780065/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780065/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the summer of 1898, two sisters died after eating chocolates they received in the mail. Their suffering was inexplicable — until their father discovered a sinister clue. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Solved or Unsolved? The Death of Danny Hansford Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780066/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jim Williams had the money to hire the best attorneys around. After a fourth trial for the same crime, he was finally found not guilty. Was the law truly upheld that day or did a rich man buy his freedom? This is a crossover series with Unsolved Murders, looking at two complicated cases where the conclusions are far from forgone. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description></item><item><title>Solved or Unsolved? The Death of Danny Hansford Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780067/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780067/</guid><description>Podcast Description In May of 1981, shots rang out at a mansion known as the Mercer House. When officers arrived, a young man was dead. The estate’s lone resident, a 50-year-old antique dealer, claimed self-defense. But to investigators, the crime scene told a different story. This is a crossover series with Unsolved Murders, looking at two complicated cases where the conclusions are far from forgone. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Solved or Unsolved? Murder at Lake Waco Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780068/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780068/</guid><description>Podcast Description The people of Waco wanted justice to be served. Four suspects emerged, but would that be enough to close the case? This is a crossover series with Unsolved Murders, looking at two complicated cases where the conclusions are far from forgone. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Solved or Unsolved? Murder at Lake Waco Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780069/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780069/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1982, three teenagers were found murdered along Lake Waco. There was very little evidence, but Sergeant Truman Simons had a hunch. And he knew it would pay off. He just needed more time. This is a crossover series with Unsolved Murders, looking at two complicated cases where the conclusions are far from forgone. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Sausage Vat Murder Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780070/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Known locally as &amp;ldquo;The Sausage King,&amp;rdquo; Adolph Luetgert found himself in hot water after police found evidence of his wife Louise&amp;rsquo;s murder. Shards of bone and a ring inscribed with the initials &amp;ldquo;L.L.&amp;rdquo; were found in a vat at his factory. But Adolph was adamant — he would never harm his &amp;ldquo;Sausage Queen.&amp;rdquo; Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Sausage Vat Murder Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780071/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adolph Luetgert came from Germany to chase the American dream. He started a successful sausage factory and even married a woman from his home country. But one morning in 1897, he woke up for breakfast and his wife Louise was gone. Days later, when authorities came to investigate the plant, they found her jewelry floating in one of the vats.
Parcasters, we have exciting news! Our first book hits bookshelves July 12th.</description></item><item><title>"The A6 Murder" Michael Gregsten Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780072/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Detectives identified 25-year-old James Hanratty as their primary suspect. While in custody, he even admitted to his crime. But some of the public believed that the wrong man was executed. Decades after his execution, DNA testing would determine if the right man was convicted.
Countdown to the CULTS book release! Parcast’s first book hits shelves July 12th. It’s an unflinching exploration of shame, secrecy, power, exploitation, and destruction. Learn more at www.</description></item><item><title>"The A6 Murder" Michael Gregsten Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780073/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael Gregsten and Valerie Storie were kidnapped, shot, and left on the side of the A6 at Deadman&amp;rsquo;s Hill. The gunman then took off in Michael&amp;rsquo;s car. When Scotland Yard released a composite drawing of the suspect, the tips came flowing in. But would any of them pan out?
Parcasters, we have exciting news! Our first book hits bookshelves July 12th. Don’t miss this chilling summer read that takes you deep into the darkest sides of human nature.</description></item><item><title>Grace Budd Pt. 2: The Murder | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780074/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Authorities tracked down Albert Fish to a boarding house in New York. From the outside, he appeared to be a harmless old man. But inside, he was a cold-blooded child murderer. And detectives were sure there had to be more victims. This is the final episode of a two-part crossover with the hosts of Serial Killers. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Grace Budd Pt. 1: The Disappearance | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780075/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780075/</guid><description>Podcast Description After the kidnapping of 10-year-old Grace Budd, authorities sifted through countless tips to locate the man who took her: Frank Howard. But after years of investigating, they realized that Frank Howard was actually Albert Fish. And time was running out to find him. This is a crossover episode with the hosts of Serial Killers, a Parcast show that delves into the lives and crimes of notorious murderers. Parcasters, we have exciting news!</description></item><item><title>George Bailey Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780076/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780076/</guid><description>Podcast Description The murder at Breakheart Hill Farm led reporters into the violent past of John Best, a farmhand who had worked under George Bailey. As the trial against him made headway, John maintained his innocence. The evidence at the farm told a different story. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>George Bailey Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780077/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780077/</guid><description>Podcast Description His dismembered body was found in a series of burlap bags at Floating Bridge Pond in Massachusetts. Farm caretaker George Bailey had made quite a few enemies during his lifetime, so it&amp;rsquo;s no surprise that somebody had killed him. The surprise was who did it. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Thomas Briggs Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780078/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Franz Müller was arrested in New York and extradited back to England for a criminal trial. The case against him was far from cut and dry, but that didn’t stop a jury from convicting him. In 1964, the 24-year-old was led to the gallows, and all of England was left with a question. Did Franz really do it? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Thomas Briggs Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780079/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780079/</guid><description>Podcast Description On July 9th, 1864, a driver of a locomotive noticed the broken and bloodied body of banker Thomas Briggs. With the help of some key witnesses, authorities identified a suspect. But when they arrived at his home, Franz Müller was already aboard a ship to America. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Anna Brown and the Osage Hills Murders Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780080/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anybody investigating the mysterious death of Anna Brown, or any of the other suspicious deaths in the Osage Nation, had either been threatened or killed. But with new FBI director J. Edgar Hoover in charge, solving these murders became a priority. The deeper they dug into the case, the more they realized how vast the conspiracy was. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Anna Brown and the Osage Hills Murders Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780081/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780081/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the 1920s, the people of the Osage Nation in Oklahoma were the wealthiest people per capita in the entire world because their land sat on one of the largest oil reserves ever discovered. But even with all this money, they were powerless. So when Anna Brown and others from the Osage Nation turned up dead, authorities felt little motivation to solve the cases. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>The Easter Sunday Killings Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780082/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780082/</guid><description>Podcast Description By the time NYPD detectives learned the identity of the &amp;ldquo;Easter Sunday Killer,&amp;rdquo; Robert Irwin had long since left the city. But a tip from a pantry maid in Cleveland and an unexpected headline in a Chicago newspaper led authorities straight to their suspect. But was he fit to stand trial? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Easter Sunday Killings Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780083/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780083/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the early hours of Easter Sunday in 1937, model Ronnie Gedeon, her mother Mary, and their boarder Frank Byrnes were brutally murdered inside their apartment. After many leads fell through, authorities found the best clue came from Ronnie&amp;rsquo;s diary and a bar of soap. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Irene Garza Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780084/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780084/</guid><description>Podcast Description After the death of Irene Garza in a small Texas town, a massive cover-up ensued, headed by one of the most powerful institutions in the world. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Irene Garza Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780085/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780085/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the evening of April 16, 1960, Irene Garza went to church in the peaceful town of McAllen, Texas but never came home. Less than a week later, her body was found in a canal. Residents were terrified. Had a predator come to town to prey on them, or was one of their own a murderer? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr. Patrick Henry Cronin Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780086/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Captain Schaack was dismissed for withholding that his partner, Dan Coughlin, was connected to the murder of Patrick Cronin. New detectives on the case uncovered an elaborate scheme involving a secret group of Irish revolutionaries. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr. Patrick Henry Cronin Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780087/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780087/</guid><description>Podcast Description In May of 1889, in the Lake View area of Chicago, well-known and respected doctor Patrick Henry Cronin disappeared. Police Captain Michael Schaack investigated a variety of leads. Unfortunately, one of them pointed directly to a suspect Schaack saw almost daily. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Palmyra Island Murders Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780088/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780088/</guid><description>Podcast Description When human remains washed up on Palmyra Island, authorities confirmed they belonged to Muff Graham who had disappeared along with her husband seven years earlier. Immediately, the FBI had suspects in mind. But when they went to serve indictments, they learned some shocking news. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Palmyra Island Murders Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780089/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780089/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a couple goes missing from a tiny, uninhabited ring of islands in the Pacific, their yacht is discovered in Hawaii with the last people who ever saw them alive. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Charles Sherman Ross | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780090/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780090/</guid><description>Podcast Description On September 25th, 1937, 72-year-old businessman Charles Sherman Ross was kidnapped. His wife wanted to pay the ransom, so the FBI took down the serial numbers of every bill she used. Weeks later, a single 20 dollar bill on the other side of the country broke the case wide open. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Officer Ian Campbell Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780091/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780091/</guid><description>Podcast Description After LAPD officer Ian Campbell was shot at close range, officer Karl Hettinger ran into the onion field to try to escape. He heard more shots go off, but had no idea which of the two kidnappers was firing. And the ensuing murder case would depend on his testimony.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Officer Ian Campbell Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780092/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780092/</guid><description>Podcast Description In March of 1963, two LAPD officers were kidnapped at gunpoint by two men. They were forced to drive two hours north of Los Angeles to an onion field. After being ordered out of the car, shots rang out. And chaos ensued. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>“Grosse Pointe Murder” Jane Bashara | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780093/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780093/</guid><description>Podcast Description In January 2012, the body of 56-year-old Jane Bashara was found in the back of her SUV. Almost immediately, police start zeroing in on her husband – known as “Big Bob” around the neighborhood, and “Master Bob” in his underground sex dungeon. As the details of Bob’s secret life come to light, a twist in the case marks it as one of Michigan’s most sordid. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>The Brides in the Bath Murders Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780094/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780094/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1915, Scotland Yard detective Arthur Neil had three deceased brides, one suspect, and tons of circumstantial evidence. But he needed something more concrete. Luckily for him, that something walked right through the door. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Brides in the Bath Murders Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780095/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780095/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the 1910s, two women suffered the same tragic fate a year apart. Scotland Yard called upon the legendary pathologist Bernard Spilsbury, called the real-life Sherlock Holmes, to investigate.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>“Murder on the Mignonette” Richard Parker | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780096/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780096/</guid><description>Podcast Description When an aging yacht is shipwrecked in the middle of the Atlantic Ocean, the crew will do anything to survive. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Houston Mass Murders Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780097/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780097/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Dean Corll’s crimes finally came to light in 1973, grief and outrage flooded the community. The trials of his two teenage accomplices would paint a picture of one of the most gruesome serial killers in American history. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Houston Mass Murders Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780098/</guid><description>Podcast Description When teen boys start disappearing in Houston in the 1970s, they’re mostly written off as runaways by local police. Their true fate is only revealed after Dean Corll, known around town as “the Candyman,” is shot and killed. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rita Morel | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780099/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780099/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a plane crashed in Canada in 1949, investigators uncovered a conspiracy that had 29-year-old Rita Morel at its center. The full plot became clear only after they tracked down a woman known around town as “The Raven.” Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dagmar Petrzywalski Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780100/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780100/</guid><description>Podcast Description In late 1946, police zeroed in on the primary suspect in Dagmar Petrzywalski&amp;rsquo;s murder. He said his name was Sidney Sinclair — but officers soon realized he was living under a secret identity. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dagmar Petrzywalski Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780101/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780101/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1940s England, an unlucky passerby found a woman&amp;rsquo;s body on the side of a busy roadway. With a knitted bag as their primary clue, local police teamed up with Scotland Yard to solve the case. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>“Halloween Panic” Timothy O'Bryan | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780102/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Every Halloween, an urban legend makes the rounds about a child dying after eating poisoned candy. The reality is that it rarely happens. But in 1974, 8-year old Timothy O&amp;rsquo;Bryan died after eating a tainted Pixie stick. It&amp;rsquo;s where he got it that makes this story so scary. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nell Cropsey Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780103/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780103/</guid><description>Podcast Description About a month after her disappearance, two fishermen found Nell Cropsey&amp;rsquo;s body in a nearby river. With Jim Wilcox the last to see her alive, he was already convicted in the court of public opinion. While he maintained his innocence, the townspeople vowed that no matter the verdict, Jim Wilcox would pay for his crime. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nell Cropsey Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780104/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Within two hours of 19-year-old Nell Cropsey’s disappearance on November 20th, 1901, the town of Elizabeth City began the search for her. Her 25-year-old boyfriend, Jim Wilcox, was the last to be seen with her and insisted she was alive when they parted ways. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Acid Bath Murders Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780105/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780105/</guid><description>Podcast Description The only chance John George Haigh stood to avoid hanging for the murder of Olive Durand-Deacon was to plead insanity. While he claimed to drink the blood of his murder victims, would it be enough to convince the jury? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Acid Bath Murders Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780106/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780106/</guid><description>Podcast Description 69-year-old Olive Durand-Deacon disappeared from a London hotel in 1949. The investigation led police to one of the most infamous serial killers in British history. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jean-Baptiste Nozière Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780107/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780107/</guid><description>Podcast Description By August of 1933, everyone in Paris knew 18-year-old Violette Nozière was a murderer. But the real question wasn&amp;rsquo;t if she killed her father — it was why. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jean-Baptiste Nozière Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780108/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who would want to poison an engine driver in Paris? The 1933 murder of Jean-Baptiste Nozière set police on the trail of a surprising killer, with a devastating motive. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Saville Kent Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780109/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780109/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1860, two Scotland Yard detectives raced to find evidence that would confirm a hunch… But Saville Kent’s killer was shrewd and calculating, and the case went cold. Five years later, a startling confession changed everything. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Saville Kent Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780110/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780110/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the middle of the night, 3-year-old Francis &amp;ldquo;Saville&amp;rdquo; Kent disappeared from the room he slept in with his baby sister. His body was found hours later. The murder investigation by the Wiltshire police was incompetent at best. So when Detective Inspector Jonathan Whicher from Scotland Yard arrived, everybody who lived in the home was a suspect. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Party Fouls: The Corpsewood Manor Murders | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780111/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780111/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1977, a couple built a Satanically-inspired mansion in rural Georgia. They called their abode Corpsewood Manor. Five years later, a gruesome double-murder made the home true to its name. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Party Fouls: Murder on Cielo Drive | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780112/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780112/</guid><description>Podcast Description In August 1969, eight-and-a-half-months-pregnant actress Sharon Tate was on top of the world, living the Hollywood dream. That is, until it turned into the bloodiest kind of Hollywood nightmare. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Party Fouls: House Party Horror | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780113/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780113/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2011, 17-year-old Tyler Hadley threw a wild house party in Port St. Lucie, Florida. What his guests didn’t know was that on the other side of a locked door, dead bodies lay hidden. A jarring confession ignited a race against time to end the revelry for good. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Party Fouls: The Club Kid Killers | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780114/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780114/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the 1990s, the Club Kids ruled the New York City party scene. They represented fun, freedom, and self-expression — until a grisly murder rocked their tight-knit community. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>“Ransomed for Pennies” Marion Parker Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780115/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780115/</guid><description>Podcast Description With Marion’s killer in custody, a trial was set for January 1928. 19-year-old William Hickman immediately began laying the ground for his defense. But no matter how outrageous his tactics, Hickman eventually had to face the punishment for his grisly crime. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>“Ransomed for Pennies” Marion Parker Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780116/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ten days before Christmas 1927, a smooth-talking man walked into a school in Los Angeles and convinced the office to let him take 12-year-old Marion Parker. Despite her desperate father’s attempts to get her back, she was murdered in a manner so ghastly, thousands of officers and volunteers organized an interstate manhunt for her killer. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Felony at the Firing Range" Theora Hix Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780117/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. James Snook was a respected veterinarian, family man, and former Olympian. But by the time his trial was over, he was a condemned murderer. Revealing details about his affair with Theora that were too salacious to print, Snook confessed to the gruesome events that ended his young lover’s life. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Felony at the Firing Range" Theora Hix Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780118/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780118/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the summer of 1929, the body of 24-year-old Theora Hix was found on a shooting range in Columbus, Ohio. The investigation into her murder surfaced two suspects: a jilted ex, and a secret lover. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Wickham Axe Murders Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780119/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780119/</guid><description>Podcast Description There was no doubt who committed the brutal assaults, or why. As another victim succumbed to his wounds, a search party hunted for Nicholas Behan — who, long after his trial and execution, remained a ghoulish figure in Long Island. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Wickham Axe Murders Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780120/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780120/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the spring of 1854, a failed courtship exploded into violence at a farm in Long Island. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>JoAnn Dewey Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780121/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Using little more than witness reports and a beer bottle, officers tracked down the kidnappers haunting Vancouver, Washington. In 1953, authorities finally put an end to the pair&amp;rsquo;s reign of terror. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>JoAnn Dewey Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780122/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780122/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1950, countless locals watched two men force JoAnn Dewey into a dark sedan — but nobody tried to intervene. Police in Vancouver, Washington used what little evidence they had to track down the kidnappers. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bridget Cleary Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780123/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780123/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1895, Bridget Cleary vanished from her home after weeks of a protracted illness. Many in the area suspected she had been abducted by fairies, but investigators would discover that something much darker explained her strange disappearance. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bridget Cleary Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780124/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780124/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1800s Ireland, County Tipperary was steeped in superstitions and folk traditions. Many who lived there believed in the existence of fairies. Those beliefs would result in one of the most brutal and vicious murders in Irish history: the killing of Bridget Cleary. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Graeme Thorne Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780125/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780125/</guid><description>Podcast Description After his abduction on July 7th, 1960, Graeme Thorne&amp;rsquo;s body was discovered in a vacant lot in Sydney, Australia. The entire country longed to see his killer brought to justice, and the identity of his killer would surprise everyone who followed the case. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Graeme Thorne Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780126/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780126/</guid><description>Podcast Description On July 7th, 1960, eight-year-old Graeme Thorne vanished from the convenience store he often visited before walking to school. His disappearance would turn into the first child abduction and ransoming Australia had ever experienced, and would shake his hometown of Sydney to the core. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Francis Rattenbury Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780127/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780127/</guid><description>Podcast Description The atmosphere was tense as the trial against Alma Rattenbury and her 18-year-old lover began. After five days of testimony, the jury returned their verdict. But the fates of Alma and the young George Stoner would not follow any ruling from the court. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Francis Rattenbury Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780128/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Late one evening in March 1935, Alma Rattenbury found her husband barely alive in the drawing room of their Bournemouth, England home. As Francis Rattenbury’s life hung in the balance, police began to investigate, and two shocking confessions complicated the case. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Patricia Walsh &amp; Mary Anne Wysocki Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780129/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780129/</guid><description>Podcast Description By February 1969, Patricia Walsh and Mary Anne Wysocki had been missing for weeks, and things were looking grim. What began as a search for two missing women exploded into a hunt for a serial killer. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Patricia Walsh &amp; Mary Anne Wysocki Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780130/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780130/</guid><description>Podcast Description On January 23, 1969, two college students went on a weekend trip to Provincetown, Massachusetts. They never returned. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lord William Russell Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780131/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780131/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 1840 trial for the calculated murder of Lord William Russell had one defendant and multiple witnesses — but everyone seemed suspect: the housemaid who discovered his body, the valet who had been pilfering his money, even the police investigating the case. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lord William Russell Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780132/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780132/</guid><description>Podcast Description In May 1840, a well-known English aristocrat was found dead in his London home after what appeared to be a botched robbery. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Wilson Turner Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780133/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780133/</guid><description>Podcast Description After the slaying of Wilson Turner, the all-powerful bootlegger who killed him seemed untouchable. But dramatic turns in the investigation would change one county in Georgia forever. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Wilson Turner Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780134/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780134/</guid><description>Podcast Description On April 20, 1948, residents of rural Coweta County, Georgia, saw a man named Wilson Turner get chased down and beaten in the middle of a campground parking lot. As his attacker hauled him away, witnesses were sure they recognized the man who beat him… but they weren&amp;rsquo;t convinced the legal system could do anything to stop him. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bobby Franks Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780135/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Just over a week after Bobby Franks’ body was found, his teenaged killers confessed, revealing a motive too callous to believe. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bobby Franks Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780136/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780136/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the early 1920s, some of Chicago’s wealthiest families became horribly intertwined after the murder of 14-year-old Bobby Franks. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Oceana Snead Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780137/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780137/</guid><description>Podcast Description The death of young Oceana Snead was dubbed a “bathtub tragedy” — but as investigators tracked her mysterious, veiled caretakers, they uncovered evidence of a callous crime. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Oceana Snead Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780138/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780138/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1909, 24-year-old Oceana Snead died of an apparent suicide — but the case was far less clear-cut than the woman’s aunt, Virginia Wardlaw, would have police believe. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jane Britton Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780139/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780139/</guid><description>Podcast Description After Jane Britton&amp;rsquo;s death in 1969, police suspected that one of her instructors may have been responsible for her gruesome murder. But the ensuing investigation would reveal the real culprit in a way nobody could have predicted.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jane Britton Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780140/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780140/</guid><description>Podcast Description In January 1969, anthropology student Jane Britton was brutally murdered in her own apartment. The case gained national attention when evidence at the scene seemed to implicate certain members of Harvard&amp;rsquo;s faculty.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Martha "Mamah" Borthwick Cheney Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780141/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780141/</guid><description>Podcast Description It didn’t take long to find the perpetrator of the Taliesin massacre: 30-year-old Julian Carlton. But though they had the “who,” police still needed to uncover the “why” — and as Julian himself approached his deathbed, time was running out. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Martha "Mamah" Borthwick Cheney Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780142/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780142/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1911, Frank Lloyd Wright built a mansion in Spring Green, Wisconsin. The sprawling estate was a haven for him and his mistress, “Mamah” Cheney. But in 1914, it became the scene of a massacre that would claim seven lives. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Robert Piest Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780143/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780143/</guid><description>Podcast Description As police zeroed in on a local contractor named John Wayne Gacy, they began to suspect they weren’t investigating the disappearance of one missing teenager — but the murders of several. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Robert Piest Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780144/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780144/</guid><description>Podcast Description After ending his shift at Nisson Pharmacy in Des Plaines, Illinois, fifteen-year-old Robert Piest asked his mother to wait while he spoke to a man about a construction job. It was December 11, 1978 — the last time Elizabeth Piest saw her son alive. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Captain Joseph White | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780145/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780145/</guid><description>Podcast Description The brutal murder of one of the wealthiest ship owners in the world shocked the town of Salem, Massachusetts in 1830.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>David Blakely Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780146/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780146/</guid><description>Podcast Description After Ruth Ellis murdered her lover in April 1955, people throughout London thought she was guaranteed the death penalty. But as investigators began looking into her past, they found new information that cast her case in new light.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>David Blakely Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780147/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780147/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1955, wealthy racecar driver David Blakely was gunned down outside a bar in London. Passersby were shocked to see a petite, picturesque woman standing over his corpse with the smoking gun.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mary Hogan Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780148/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Following a lead, police zeroed in on the home of one local man. It was eventually dubbed a “House of Horrors” after news of its contents spread, with its owner inspiring a string of movies and books that drew on his heinous crimes. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mary Hogan Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780149/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780149/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1954, a 55-year-old tavern owner in central Wisconsin went missing, leaving behind a disturbing crime scene. Police caught a break in her case when a similar abduction occurred nearly three years later.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Carol Thompson Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780150/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780150/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Carol Thompson’s murderer confessed to his crime, he implicated another person in the ordeal — and a shocking murder-for-hire plot began to unravel.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Carol Thompson Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780151/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780151/</guid><description>Podcast Description In March 1963, a Minnesota housewife named Carol Thompson was attacked in her home, later dying from her wounds. Months later, two men were indicted for her murder — but the case was far from resolved. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ali Kamel Fahmy Bey Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780152/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marguerite Alibert was found holding the gun she used to kill her husband, but her trial was far from an open-and-shut case. The courtroom proved as dramatic and explosive as the relationship that resulted in Ali Kamel Fahmy Bey&amp;rsquo;s death.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ali Kamel Fahmy Bey Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780153/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780153/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1922, Egyptian millionaire Ali Kamel Fahmy Bey became smitten with French socialite Marguerite Alibert. She was charming, and accustomed to keeping the company of rich and powerful men — including England’s Prince Edward VIII. But while their romance was passionate, it was also ill-fated. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lesley Whittle Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780154/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Months after the 17-year-old went missing, an investigation into the underground sewage tunnels in Bathpool Park turned up a torrent of clues—and Lesley Whittle’s body. But it wasn’t until nearly a year after her kidnapping that detectives would find her killer. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lesley Whittle Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780155/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780155/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a young heiress went missing in 1975, her family found a ransom note demanding £50,000. The police coordinated a plan to secure her safe return, but a series of missteps and mistakes meant time was running out for Lesley Whittle.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Helen Potts Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780156/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780156/</guid><description>Podcast Description By March of 1891, the coroner’s office failed to find evidence of foul play, and investigators moved on from Helen Potts’ case. Even so, reporter Dilworth Choate felt the story deserved a closer look… Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Helen Potts Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780157/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780157/</guid><description>Podcast Description It became one of the most sensationalized cases of the late 19th century: The young wife of a playboy medical student died not long after a botched abortion. But it wasn’t the dangerous procedure that killed her. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Benjamin Pitezel Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780158/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780158/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the chaotic search for Benjamin Pitezel&amp;rsquo;s murderer, investigators enlisted authorities from multiple states, and even crossed the border into Canada. Meanwhile, the remaining members of the Pitezel family fell one by one at the hands of a ruthless, depraved killer.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Benjamin Pitezel Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780159/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780159/</guid><description>Podcast Description In September 1894, conman Benjamin Pitezel met a mysterious, violent end in Philadelphia. For years, he&amp;rsquo;d been committing petty crimes across America, fleeing the authorities across multiple states. And the deeper authorities dug into Pitezel&amp;rsquo;s background, the more baffling his death became. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The List Family Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780160/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780160/</guid><description>Podcast Description The search for John List spanned two decades and all 50 states. But it took a supermarket tabloid and a TV crime show to finally break the case—and unravel the full story of what drove a man like List to murder. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The List Family Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780161/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780161/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1971, a middle-aged accountant woke up, put on a tie, and shot his entire family to death in their home. Then he disappeared, leaving behind two glaring questions: What drove this religious family man to murder—and, more importantly, where did he go?
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jerry Dean &amp; Deborah Thornton Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780162/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780162/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1983, police closed in on the murderers of Jerry Dean and Deborah Thornton, thanks to a well-placed informant. Their capture led one killer to have a dramatic change of heart, sparking a world-wide debate about capital punishment. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jerry Dean &amp; Deborah Thornton Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780163/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780163/</guid><description>Podcast Description They were two strangers, crossing paths at a pool party in Houston, Texas in the summer of 1983. Jerry Dean and Deborah Thornton spent the night together—and by morning, they were both dead. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>William Guldensuppe Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780164/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780164/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1897, the discovery of a severed torso led to an explosion of investigative activity in the media. The identification of the body and the arrest of the dead man’s murderers would prove to be one of the most incredible true crime stories ever told.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>William Guldensuppe Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780165/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780165/</guid><description>Podcast Description On June 26, 1897, four boys discovered a package wrapped in red oilcloth floating in New York City’s East River. It contained the upper torso of an unknown man, launching one of the largest media murder mysteries ever, and igniting newspaper wars that would last a decade. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Agnes LeRoi &amp; Hedvig Samuelson Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780166/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780166/</guid><description>Podcast Description In October of 1931, two bloody trunks arrived at the Los Angeles train station containing the bodies of Anne LeRoi and Hedvig “Sammy” Samuelson. What followed was one of most scandalous murder cases of the Roaring Twenties… One that has left detectives with more questions than answers.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Agnes LeRoi &amp; Hedvig Samuelson Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780167/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780167/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1931, the friendship between three women living in Phoenix, Arizona was torn apart when they all fell for the same man: 44-year-old “Happy” Jack Halloran. Slowly, their rift began to heal, and they planned a gathering one night in October—but the reunion proved deadly. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sal Mineo Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780168/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780168/</guid><description>Podcast Description After Sal Mineo was murdered in February of 1976, the LAPD did their best to track down every lead they could find. They searched for over a year in vain, until they received a tip that forced them to reconsider every assumption they&amp;rsquo;d made about the case. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sal Mineo Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780169/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780169/</guid><description>Podcast Description On February 12th, 1976, actor Sal Mineo, best known for his role in Rebel Without a Cause, was stabbed outside his apartment building in Los Angeles. Authorities desperately searched for evidence, but hit dead ends everywhere they turned. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Clutter Family Pt. 2 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780170/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780170/</guid><description>Podcast Description After the massacre of the Clutter Family on November 15th, 1959, the Kansas Bureau of Investigation began an intensive probe into the crime. Their search for the killers would result in one of the greatest true crime stories of all time. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Clutter Family Pt. 1 | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780171/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780171/</guid><description>Podcast Description On November 15th, 1959, the small town of Holcomb, Kansas experienced one of the most gruesome crimes imaginable. Four members of the Clutter Family had been gunned down in their own home—but nobody knew why.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Welcome to Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries! | Solved Murders: True Crime Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1496780172/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1496780172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Every murder case has clues: an errant fingerprint, a spatter of blood, a forgotten bullet casing. But these investigations can go awry. Clues disappear, trails go cold, and cases are reduced to nothing more than files forgotten in a police precinct basement. But on Parcast’s newest series, you’ll explore a different kind of case. Join Carter Roy and Wenndy Mackenzie, and the entire team that brought you Unsolved Murders as they dive into investigations where the clues never run dry, and the story doesn’t stop until the crime is solved.</description></item></channel></rss>