<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Untidy on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/untidy/</link><description>Recent content in Untidy on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/untidy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Birthday stitch-ups, a stray package, and the Code Brown | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060001/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060001/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Untidy Hannah and Matty discuss December birthdays, Hannah reflects on the results of doing no dating in NO-vember, reveals that she’s the dirty neighbour, and delivers on the latest Code Brown incident. Matty shares her Christmas tree shame and its aspirations for being sent to the rainbow forest in the new year. The unbridled fawning over baby Penelope continues ...
Thanks for listening! If you enjoyed this episode of Untidy, subscribe to the show in your podcast app so you never miss and episode and help us build this supportive community.</description></item><item><title>Breaking news! Matilda’s homebirth story! | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 02:49:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Breaking news! Penelope Green, our first Untidy baby has finally arrived! In this episode of Untidy, Matty introduces 4-day-old, Penelope, and gives us all the details of her home birth, including a rousing performance of the noises she made during labour ... We take a deep-dive into this positive, empowering birth journey from timelines to techniques to logistics and finally, the cup of tea Matilda never forget. We’re so excited to share the news of the safe arrival of Penelope, and introduce everyone to this long-awaited baby who enjoys her first broadcasting cameo on the pod!</description></item><item><title>Playful psychology with Emily Hanlon | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060003/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060003/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Untidy, we talk to Emily Hanlon @theplayfulpsychologist, a child &amp;amp; adolescent clinical psychologist who is all about rethinking our approach to emotions. Emily takes a practical and accessible approach to her work and generously shares her wisdom and humour to her audience online. In this conversation, we wanted to ask every aspect of the age-old parenting questions ... which essentially boils down to wondering if we’re doing it right and if we’re doing enough!</description></item><item><title>Snippet - Hannah axes dating for NO-vember | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 04:22:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hannah’s given up dating for DIY and decided to make it a NO-vember challenge. She’s taken an axe to her dating apps and is setting new boundaries through the power of saying, ‘NO’.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mixing rugby and motherhood with Les Elder | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060005/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060005/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Untidy we talk to former Black Ferns captain and māmā of two, Les Elder. Les was part of the World Cup winning squad in 2017 and later became captain while trying to start a family at the same time. With both her babies conceived by IVF, the process of conception was complicated whilst meeting the rigorous training schedule as a professional rugby player. Les continued training throughout her first pregnancy and returned to her career soon after giving birth.</description></item><item><title>Meeting the inner critic with Mike King | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060006/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060006/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Untidy we talk to the iconic Kiwi entertainer, now, mental health advocate Mike King. Mike gives us a warts-and-all account of his evolution from an edgy and turbulent life as a breakthrough comedian, to his life-threatening reckoning that changed his path forever.
Mike is now the founder of I Am Hope Foundation and initiative, Gumboot Friday, which fundraises to provide free and timely counselling for young people across Aotearoa.</description></item><item><title>Snippet: Matilda’s Hen’s Do horror show | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060007/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 02:58:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matilda reveals her own stripper story from her Hen’s Do, which she remembers for all the wrong reasons.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Connected parenting Q&amp;A with Genevieve Muir | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060008/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060008/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Untidy we welcome back Obstetric Social Worker, Parent Educator and mum of four boys, Genevieve Muir to answer your questions with more non-judgemental, ‘boots on the ground’ parenting advice. Gen is so reassuring and relatable to listen to and this time we cover off ‘moody’ kids, bedtime anxiety, bullying, sulking, potty training, teens and phones, kids that hit, and much more. We also have a great chat about how much ‘good’ parenting it takes to actually be a good parent .</description></item><item><title>Q&amp;A with meditation teacher, Georgia Vavasour | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060009/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060009/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Untidy, we have a question and answer session with Vedic Meditation teacher, Georgia Vavasour. Georgia answers listeners’ questions such as ‘where do I start with meditation?’ She also delves into the differences between learning from an app and a trained teacher, what to do about feeling constantly overwhelmed, battling brain fog, as well as addressing the common ‘I don’t have time’ mindset around fitting meditation into an already busy life.</description></item><item><title>Snippet: Matilda's best home birth advice | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 03:34:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matilda Green shares her best advice for a successful home birth ... even though it freaked her out! Hear how she handles it when birth starts to feel completely 'out of control'.To listen to the full episode head to 'Prepping for a Positive Birth with Helen Bartrom' from Positive Births NZ.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Toe cigars, stage noodles, and rickshaw racing | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060011/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060011/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Untidy, Matty’s thrown the book at turning this breech baby on its head ... has she done it?? She talks about her home birth plan, and how she’s handling niggling fears and worries and the due date approaches. Hannah reveals her rural midwifery skills, and shares a dating app voice note which leaves Matty speechless.
Hannah also talks about her next great adventure. She’ll be competing in The Rickshaw Run Sri Lanka to raise funds for Gumboot Friday.</description></item><item><title>Prepping for a Positive Birth with Helen Bartrom | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060012/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060012/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Untidy we talk to Helen Bartrom from Positive Births. Helen is a Clinical Hypnotherapist, mum of three, and host of The Positive Birth NZ podcast. She is also the author of ‘Positive Birth in New Zealand: using Relaxation, Hypnobirthing and Mindfulness’.
Helen helps women and birthing people feel empowered for their upcoming birth, using hypnobirthing techniques. Matty recently had a session with Helen, so the girls dive into what hypnobirthing actually is, and the common misconceptions around it — i.</description></item><item><title>Snippet: Matilda’s tips for keeping cool in a meltdown | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 08:24:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matilda Green shares her top tip for staying calm and regulating her emotions in the midst of a meltdown. And - like so many parents - honestly admits it’s a work in progress. To listen to the full episode head to 'Connected Parenting' with Genevieve Muir.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Snippet: Genevieve Muir reveals the life lesson in ‘losing it’ | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060014/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 08:23:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Connected parenting expert Genevieve Muir shares her strategies on navigating through the times when we ‘lose it’ as a parent. In this a-ha moment we hear that compassion and kindness to self is key, as well as tips on how to say sorry, stay grounded, and move forward.
To listen to the full episode head to 'Connected Parenting' with Genevieve Muir.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The myth of ‘Baby Brain’ with Dr Sarah McKay | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060015/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Untidy we talk to Dr Sarah McKay. Originally from Christchurch NZ, Sarah is an Oxford University-educated neuroscientist, author, speaker and director of Think Brain's suite of online training programs. Sarah now resides in Sydney with her husband and two boys.
We cover a lot of ground in this episode. We delve into the findings from Sarah’s recent book ‘Baby Brain’ - a term often used to describe the perceived cognitive decline a lot of new mums experience.</description></item><item><title>Dating big decks, breech babes, and white vinegar victories | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 01:53:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060016/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Untidy, we celebrate the solution to all problems — white vinegar. Matty wonders if it could turn her breach baby before she tries home birth. Hannah’s giving up dating for DIY unless she can get smuggled into Scott Base with the fruit and veg. And both discover they’re not just podcast partners but Yum Cha soul mates, as well.
We ponder the escalating costs of quality time, and Matty wonders if she should feel guilty for not feeling guilty enough.</description></item><item><title>Spring flinging, ‘hysterical’ women, and that hardware store swagger | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060017/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060017/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Untidy, Hannah’s doing a deep spring clean and nothing is safe from dust bunnies to dating apps. We talk sledgehammer therapy, gym grunting and why emotional outbursts in women make them ‘hysterical’ while men have simply been, ‘pushed too far’.
We wonder if we’re making our eldest kids tolerate too much, and if Matty has any right to adopt that ‘hardware store swagger’ if she abandons her botched drawers on the roadside.</description></item><item><title>Surviving Domestic Violence with Zoe Marshall | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060018/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060018/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Untidy we talk to Zoe Marshall, media personality, creator of ‘The Deep’ podcast, and self-described over-sharer. Our conversation with Zoe is about her experience of surviving domestic violence. We talk about what made her a target for getting drawn into that relationship, how she got trapped, and why it’s so hard for the victims of abuse to get out and stay safe.
CONTENT WARNING: Some of this conversation may be triggering to some listeners.</description></item><item><title>Snippet: Matilda explains "Grantgate" | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 19:48:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matilda spills the tea on Celebrity Treasure Island
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Snippet: Matilda's strategy secrets revealed! | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 19:46:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matilda spills the tea on Celebrity Treasure Island
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Matilda spills the tea ... Celebrity Treasure Island uncut | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 19:35:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060021/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Untidy, Matty takes us behind-the-scenes of Celebrity Treasure Island to what we didn’t see in the final cut. She shares her reactions to discovering what also went on as she watches the show for the first time and the gameplay is revealed.
We talk Tāme Iti’s shock departure and how he impacted his team, puzzle performance, Jordan’s cultish maneuvering and his cheeseburger chow-down, and, how Matty feels about being left out of an alliance and ultimately leaving the show.</description></item><item><title>A fresh rant, needy mates, and Celebrity Treasure Island | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060022/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Untidy, we kick things off with a fresh rant as Hannah nominates a worthy candidate for the dating hall of shame. We answer a listener's question about how to handle a needy mate, and, Matty gives us a behind-the-scenes peek at the drama that unfolded in the first three episodes of Celebrity Treasure Island. We find out about how she won the wall challenge, if she really had beef with Grant, and what her strategy was for ‘playing the game’.</description></item><item><title>Emotional diarrhoea, car crying, and cake wars | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060023/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Untidy, we get a little bit emotional. We talk about why Hannah’s committing to the discomfort of awkward conversations, the benefits of a good cathartic cry, and share a resilience tool to turn the solo car ride into a space for radical self-expression.
Matty wonders why we set the bar so high for kids’ birthdays. Does anyone care enough about elaborate cakes other than the people that lost sleep to make them?</description></item><item><title>Alcohol, baby loss &amp; finding love with Hayley Holt | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060024/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060024/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Untidy, we share our live chat with Hayley Holt. One of New Zealand's most well-known journalists and television hosts. Hayley’s recent book ‘Second Chances: Facing my demons and finding a better me’ shares the raw and honest story of her journey through alcoholism, finding sobriety, baby loss, and her unconventional love story.
Hayley sat down with us at our first-ever live Untidy podcast event in Warkworth, and talked about her early days of high-performance competition, discovering alcohol, why she got sober, and her difficult path to motherhood.</description></item><item><title>Not Like Other Dads with Sean Szeps | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060025/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060025/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Untidy we talk to Sean Szeps, host of the popular podcast, ‘Come Out Wherever You Are’, and author of ‘Not Like Other Dads’. As well as a writer, podcaster and content creator, Sean is most well-known for his accidental advocacy, which arose from sharing his journey as a gay dad raising boy-girl twins alongside his husband, Josh. We speak to Sean about what it was like growing up in a conservative Roman Catholic home whilst grappling with his sexuality.</description></item><item><title>No time for UFOs, a good release and listener questions | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060026/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060026/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Untidy, it turns out there are UFOs but no one cares, Hannah rates her colonic decluttering and shares her story of a teenage girl’s worst nightmare. Matilda has bikini shopping woes which she tries and fails to solve with new make-up, and the girls answer your listener questions, tackling; how you know if you should have a baby and if podcasts actually make money.</description></item><item><title>Connected parenting with Genevieve Muir | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060027/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060027/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Untidy, we talk to Obstetric Social Worker, Parent Educator, and mum of four boys, Genevieve Muir. With a passion for helping parents in the first five years of raising kids, Gen has worked with over 40,000 parents to navigate the real challenges facing modern parents. What we love about Gen is that she gives us the real ‘boots on the ground’ advice about how to handle tricky and awkward situations with our kids, like; meltdowns in public, biting, hitting, sibling conflict, when fun play goes wrong, and, what to do when we’re about to lose our sh*t ourselves.</description></item><item><title>Gym creeps, Matty’s calmbirth and weeping for Disney | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060028/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060028/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Untidy, the girls discuss the psychological minefield that is the gym. Matty gives an update on her calmbirth plan, and the girls discuss practical tips for mentally and physically preparing for labour; including a map of buttons ...
Hannah prepares for her first-ever colonic irrigation, and they ponder what might be lurking in her bowels. Hannah shares advice for supporting kids going through a separation (or any big life change), and Matty discusses the family-wide emotional rollercoaster that was Disney on Ice.</description></item><item><title>Big ‘icks’, love languages &amp; colonic decluttering | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060029/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060029/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Untidy the girls get the virus they always wanted, discuss their big ‘icks’ and, wonder if Matilda’s intestinal anaconda was a mythical creature. Hannah decides she also needs a colonic decluttering. After spending some time in ‘bowel corner’, Matilda reveals her not-so-humble dressing gown confession. They wrap things up with more wholesome chat about the relationship revelation that is the ‘love languages’.
Untidy is made for you – the people right at the heart of this steaming hot mess we call parenthood.</description></item><item><title>Maternal mental health with Hannah Hardy-Jones | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060030/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060030/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Untidy we talk to mum of two, Hannah Hardy-Jones. Hannah suffered a severe manic episode triggered by the traumatic birth of her first child, which brought on a diagnosis of Bipolar Disorder. We speak to Hannah about how this experience led her to start Kite Program – a tech platform that creates apps for specific organisations, occupational groups and mental health causes. We also talk about the impact this experience had on her family, and how she navigated the decision to have a second child.</description></item><item><title>Sex Dilemmas Q&amp;A (Part Two) with Melody Thomas | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060031/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060031/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of our Untidy conversation with sex podcaster and educator, Melody Thomas, we tackle more spicy listener questions. Melody is the creator and host of The Good Sex Project, a podcast about good sex, good relationships, and how to have them. Melody also made the hit series BANG! for RNZ, which was awarded both bronze and silver medals at the New York Festival Radio Awards. Melody is a writer and columnist and is currently working on her first book.</description></item><item><title>Sex dilemmas Q&amp;A (Part One) with Melody Thomas | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060032/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 08:40:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060032/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Untidy we talk to sex podcaster and educator, Melody Thomas. She is the creator and host of The Good Sex Project, a podcast about good sex, good relationships and how to have them. Melody also made the hit series BANG! for RNZ, which was awarded both bronze and silver medals at the New York Festival Radio Awards. Melody is a writer and columnist, and is currently working on her first book.</description></item><item><title>How Hamish Blake ‘dads’ | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060033/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060033/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Untidy we talk to Hamish Blake, one half of the comedy podcasting duo, Hamish &amp;amp; Andy, host of the parenting podcast, ‘How Other Dads Dad’, host of LEGO Masters Australia, the voice of ‘Jack’s dad’ on Bluey, Cake Night masochist, husband to Zoë, and, dad to Sonny and Rudy.
Hamish’s approach to ‘dadding’ is full of presence, effort and playfulness. In this hilarious episode we learn how he developed his philosophy.</description></item><item><title>Real-talk rants and public pyjama parenting | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060034/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 22:03:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060034/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Untidy the girls get it all off their chests with some real-talk rants about travelling with toddlers, airport overwhelm, and mansplainers. Matilda’s been running through hotels like a deranged pyjama woman, and Hannah's had a first and only date that’s doused her feminist fire with diesel. It’s a week for a good old purge of frustrations to lighten the load. Untidy is made for you – the people right at the heart of this steaming hot mess we call parenthood.</description></item><item><title>Notorious pussies | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060035/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060035/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Untidy it’s all fannies and cats! In this pussy-heavy instalment the girls cover a full spectrum of topics from getting recognised with your pants off, Hannah’s most toxic relationship, what’s happened to Brian, and Matilda’s vulva varicose vein’s rise to stardom. Get ya girdle on, your headphones in, and join us for a very Untidy chat. Untidy is made for you – the people right at the heart of this steaming hot mess we call parenthood.</description></item><item><title>Not ‘just a mum’ with Georgia Vavasour | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060036/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060036/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Untidy we talk to Vedic Meditation teacher, Georgia Vavasour. Georgia has taught both Matilda and Hannah to meditate with this ancient technique. They discuss what Vedic Meditation is, how it’s a game changer for mums, the Vedic perspective on motherhood, along with their own personal journeys with meditation. Georgia initially discovered this technique after suffering several long-term health conditions – depression, chronic fatigue, digestive issues, and ultimately, bowel cancer.</description></item><item><title>A very special guest, getting outnumbered and sanity hacks | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060037/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060037/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Untidy the girls interview Flicka Williams, co-founder, designer and official cat wrangler of My Big Moments and Untidy podcast. With Matilda’s third baby promising to outnumber its parents, Flicka gives her best advice on how to create a rhythm in the chaos of having three kids under five, and sanity hacks for making it through in one piece (there or thereabouts).
Untidy is made for you – the people right at the heart of this steaming hot mess we call parenthood.</description></item><item><title>The BIG reveal, 'Girdle Gate', and #mumsgonemild | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060038/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060038/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is an Untidy bed special as Matilda and Hannah have both taken to their beds for very different reasons ... suffice it to say, it’s coming out every orifice. This could be their untidiest episode yet ... There’s a BIG reveal for the Untidy whanau, Matty has a girdle dilemma, and the girls look forward to an extremely gentle Sydney interview junket which has earned the hashtag, #mumsgonemild.</description></item><item><title>Bali debacles, kids say the darndest things, and punching the Ozone layer | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060039/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hannah navigates deafness in a Bali debacle and records from a ... unique ... hotel to share the news. Matilda's publically shamed by her 3-year-old and sparks listener feedback on what kids say to embarrass their parents. They also rewrite the facts on climate change. Some ground is covered in this one!
Untidy is made for you – the people right at the heart of this steaming hot mess we call parenthood.</description></item><item><title>The secrets of resilience with Dr Lucy Hone | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060040/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060040/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Untidy, we talk to resilience researcher and leading international authority on wellbeing and resilience, Dr Lucy Hone. Beyond academia, Lucy has experienced devastating personal tragedies giving her a deep understanding of what truly helps when it comes to moving forward through grief and loss. That journey has led her to teach practical resilience strategies to others, helping people continue living while facing their most challenging times.</description></item><item><title>Turning 40, the sex hotel update, and butter chicken baths | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060041/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matilda and Hannah start off wholesome as Hannah reflects on turning 40 before the girls descend back into the gutter. They get an update on one listener's accidental sex hotel holiday, another listener’s voice note confessions, traumatic Brazilians, the ‘fake news’ of underwater nudity, and the guilty pleasure of dinner in the bath.
Untidy is made for you – the people right at the heart of this steaming hot mess we call parenthood.</description></item><item><title>Big news, a swim in human soup, and the Turkish car wash | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060042/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matilda and Hannah have big news about the future of the podcast, they reveal Part One of a listeners story as they gear up to accidentally visit a sex hotel, reminisce over their own awkward travel stories, and wonder when it’s appropriate to boast about your excellent bowel function. Untidy is made for you – the people right at the heart of this steaming hot mess we call parenthood.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Buster’s got a kink, shit dudes and the dating graph | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060043/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matilda and Hannah hash out some big, pointy topics including; Buster’s shocking kink, dogs on dates, autumnal feels, and, Hannah’s life-cycle graph of dating app romances. Untidy is made for you – the people right at the heart of this steaming hot mess we call parenthood. Follow the show and get in touch on Instagram @untidypodcast. Find Matilda at @matootles and get your copy of The Feel Good Guide.</description></item><item><title>Untidy Easter Egg Special | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060044/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matilda and Hannah hop on the mics to lay you an Easter Egg for your holidays. Matty’s fallen into the comparison trap while Hannah’s Easter went viral. There’s wholesome chat about books and documentaries which is complimented by a cracking poo story, in true Untidy fashion.
Untidy is made for you – the people right at the heart of this steaming hot mess we call parenthood. Follow the show and get in touch on Instagram @untidypodcast.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Hot pants, handbag jocks and hurling prawns | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060045/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060045/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this bonus episode, we find out Hannah’s become a Slumlord and Matilda has a filthy chandelier. We asked for your confessions, and you delivered... Untidy is made for you – the people right at the heart of this steaming hot mess we call parenthood. Follow the show and get in touch on Instagram @untidypodcast. Find Matilda at @matootles and get your copy of The Feel Good Guide. Find Hannah at @hannahedavison and her children’s books at @mybigmoments.</description></item><item><title>The Vagina Olympics with Caitlin Day and Sophie Lax | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060046/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Untidy, we talk to Pelvic Health Physiotherapists, Caitlin Day and Sophie Lax from Unity Studios about what we never knew, but should have learnt about our pelvic floors. We talk about what can be done to recover from childbirth and how long it really takes to get back into activity and intimacy. Plus — The Vagina Olympics! Hannah and Matilda get their pelvic floors assessed and challenge each other to see who can forge the mightiest vagina and be crowned, The High Pussy Priestess!</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Deep-tissue parenting, rant responses and facing rejection | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060047/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060047/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this bonus episode, actually talk about parenting in our parenting podcast, hand in our homework for ‘embracing the awkward’, and hear from a listener with a rant response.
Untidy is made for you – the people right at the heart of this steaming hot mess we call parenthood. Follow the show and get in touch on Instagram @untidypodcast. Find Matilda at @matootles and get your copy of The Feel Good Guide.</description></item><item><title>Pros and Cons of Contraception with Dr Lara Briden | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060048/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060048/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode we’re speaking to Dr Lara Briden to get the health class we never got at school. Author of ‘Period Repair Manual’ and ‘Hormone Repair Manual’, Dr Briden is a Naturopathic Doctor and Women’s hormone specialist. Dr Briden is also a women’s health activist, and passionate about helping women feel empowered when it comes to their bodies. In this interview, we dive deep into a discussion about the contraceptive pill.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Speed bumps, butt cheeks and the quality ‘no’ | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060049/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060049/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this bonus episode, we get a little ranty about bad kisses, fast cars, and the need to deploy the quality ‘no’ much more often. We’re joined by another champion Untidy listener for her bad dating stories, and discover Matilda is not a hugger but is ready to ‘embrace the awkward’. Untidy is made for you – the people right at the heart of this steaming hot mess we call parenthood.</description></item><item><title>Fearlessness and feminism with Clementine Ford | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060050/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060050/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Untidy, we talk to Clementine Ford about why outspoken women seem threatening, finding her voice to speak up for feminism, and an exploration of love in all its forms which she’s written about in her book, ‘How We Love’. Clementine ford is a feminist community builder, writer, public speaker, and host of the podcast, ‘Dear Clementine’. She’s the author of three books, with her fourth due out in October 2023.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Car snacks, couple goals and tragic dating stories | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060051/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060051/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this bonus episode we arrive reliably unprepared to discuss troublesome car snacks, how Matilda and Art got crowned NZ’s best celebrity couple, and dive into tragic dating stories from our heroic Untidy listeners. Untidy is made for you – the people right at the heart of this steaming hot mess we call parenthood. Follow the show and get in touch on Instagram @untidypodcast. Find Matilda at @matootles and get your copy of The Feel Good Guide.</description></item><item><title>Loss, love and surrogacy with Toni Street | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060052/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060052/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we talk to Toni Street. Toni is a mum of three, and a certified ray of sunshine! She’s one of New Zealand's most popular television and radio personalities — a journalist, broadcaster, former co-host of top-rating TVNZ current affairs show Seven Sharp, and current breakfast radio host on Coast. Given her sunny disposition and bubbly personality, it would be easy to assume that Toni hasn’t had to deal with a lot of adversity, but that couldn’t be further from the truth.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Poo news, bad bios and a book club | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060053/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060053/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this bonus we saunter into the latest unplanned segment: poo news, dredge the bottom of the dating pool to bring you more bad bios, and decide to start a book club.
Untidy is made for you – the people right at the heart of this steaming hot mess we call parenthood. Follow the show and get in touch on Instagram @untidypodcast. Find Matilda at @matootles and get your copy of The Feel Good Guide.</description></item><item><title>Healing trauma with Matt Brown | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060054/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060054/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we talk to Matt Brown, author of the bestselling book, She is Not Your Rehab, barber, hair artist, and alongside his wife, Sarah, the co-founder of a global anti-violence movement to break the cycle of abuse and intergenerational trauma. We talk about his work to help men face their pasts, embrace vulnerability and find healing to transform their lives. Follow Matt and Sarah’s work on Instagram at @sheisnotyourrehab and visit https://www.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Bad tinder bios and listener letters | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060055/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 03:39:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060055/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this bonus we review dating profile low-lights from Hannah’s growing collection of bad tinder bios, and respond to some incredible listener letters. We talk about bottle-feeding judgement, facing career crises, and rediscovering your true self after kids. Plus! There’s another giveaway! To win a copy of That’s Not the Plan send us your most outrageous dating stories. There are three copies to give away.
Untidy is made for you – the people right at the heart of this steaming hot mess we call parenthood.</description></item><item><title>'F*** off Gary' with Kate Twigg | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060056/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060056/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, we chat to devoted mum, Kate Twigg, about her journey with breast cancer (that would be Gary), and more recently, Leukaemia (Gary’s uninvited mate, Larry). Through breathwork, meditation, yoga, and a richly stocked dress-up box, Kate’s found her own way to cope through diagnosis, treatment and the repercussions that a cancer journey brings. The unexpected by-product of Kate’s cancer diagnosis was the confronting realisation she was using alcohol as a coping mechanism.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Ring-sting, rogue guests and a giveaway! | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060057/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 05:02:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Apparently, our episodes can’t be two hours long just because we like a yarn ... So, we’re dropping in a bonus to reminisce about ring-sting, peek behind the podcasting curtain, and riffle through Matilda’s drawers for prizes to send our reviewer of the week!
To win a copy of The Feel Good Guide write a review on your favourite listening platform. There are three copies to give away to our reviewers of the week.</description></item><item><title>Redefining intimacy with Morgan Penn | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060058/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 16:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060058/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we ask Somatic Sexologist, Morgan Penn, if putting 'tab A' into 'slot B' is the only way to have sex. (Spoiler — it's not). Morgan tells us how to redefine intimacy in our relationships with our partners and ourselves. We talk about reclaiming your post-partum body, navigating post-partum sex, and how to have those conversations that feel all kinds of awkward. Untidy podcast is about honouring the person within the parent.</description></item><item><title>This steaming hot mess with Matilda Green and Hannah Davison | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060059/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060059/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this first episode of Untidy, hosts, Matilda Green and Hannah Davison answer the question, "What the hell are we doing here?" It's a love story that embraces leaky boobs, crying in the laundry and the admission that neither has it all together.
They compare notes on the messiest birth stories and confess parental insecurities as they try to figure out directions to this 'village' that's supposed to help them raise their kids.</description></item><item><title>UNTIDY TRAILER | Untidy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2882060060/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:09:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2882060060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Untidy honours the person within the parent. Hosts, Matilda Green and Hannah Davison, dive into the undergrowth of sex and relationships, mental health, healing, body issues, identity questions, and more with a range of guests. Connect, laugh, learn, and keep moving forward.
Follow the show and get in touch on Instagram @untidypodcast. Follow Matilda at @matootles and Hannah’s work at My Big Moments and @mybigmoments.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item></channel></rss>