<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Office Ladies on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/office-ladies/</link><description>Recent content in Office Ladies on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 05:05:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/office-ladies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Free Family Portrait Studio | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840001/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Free Family Portrait Studio” and it’s the last episode of Season 8! Dwight sets up a portrait studio at Dunder Mifflin for the employees to take pictures with their families. Angela Martin catches on quickly that this is a ploy to determine if Dwight is the father of her baby and unfortunately, Jim becomes a casualty in this mission. Jenna discusses the changes that were happening from Season 8 to 9, Angela breaks down the car chase with Mose and we have some duck catches!</description></item><item><title>Office Ladies Live: Fan Mailbag | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Monday, we have a bonus episode for you! The ladies answer fan mail from the Los Angeles SiriusXM Garage in front of a special audience. The ladies celebrate doing their first live show for the podcast, Angela levels up as a hummingbird watcher and Jenna reveals watching something we never thought she would. This is a fun episode to show our appreciation for our fans. Thanks for listening!</description></item><item><title>Turf War | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840003/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Turf War.” Dwight and Jim work together to secure a client from a Syracuse branch salesman after Robert drunkenly shuts down the Binghamton branch. Meanwhile Pam and Angela try to help Robert figure out what he said to Nellie on a voicemail. This episode also has Dan Castellaneta (“The Simpsons”) and Chris Bauer (“The Wire”) as guest stars! The ladies embrace being in your 50s and how to use your bra in a zombie apocalypse, and Angela points out a deleted scene where the documentary crew films the Dunder Mifflin Syracuse branch.</description></item><item><title>An Interview with Zach Woods | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840004/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week the ladies chat with Zach Woods! Zach played Gabe Lewis on “The Office” and he shares what it was like to join the cast in the middle of Season 6. He also talks about some of his favorite memories from making the show, they all laugh over their love of “close call” moments, and Zach asks the ladies some questions of his own like what would you tell your younger self on the show if you could go back in time.</description></item><item><title>A Look Back on Sabre | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840005/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re taking a look back on “Sabre” and the director of this ep, John Krasinski, sends in clips to share what it was like directing this very big episode. Dunder Mifflin has been acquired by the printer company, Sabre, and its CEO is the very powerful, no nonsense Jo Bennett played by Kathy Bates. This is also the episode that introduces Gabe Lewis played by Zach Woods!</description></item><item><title>Fundraiser | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840006/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week is “Fundraiser”. The office attends a fundraiser hosted by Angela’s husband, State Senator Robert Lipton. Andy crashes it and ends up stress adopting 12 dogs, and Dwight “wins” the auction. Jenna shares how the Dwight storyline was based on a true story, Angela gives reasons why “Life is Downton Abbey” and the ladies wonder how game show prizes get delivered. So have Nellie buy you tacos and enjoy this episode!</description></item><item><title>Angry Andy with Claire Scanlon | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840007/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week is “Angry Andy”. Andy has returned to Dunder Mifflin only to discover he’s been usurped by Nellie. Meanwhile Ryan tries to win back Kelly who’s fallen in love with Pam and Jim’s pediatrician, Ravi. And the ladies talk with director and editor Claire Scanlon! “Angry Andy” was Claire’s first time directing an episode of TV and she shares what the experience was like, plus what editing for “The Office” was like.</description></item><item><title>Welcome Party | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840008/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week is “Welcome Party”. The Dunder Mifflin employees reluctantly throw a welcome party for Nellie. Meanwhile, Andy ungraciously breaks up with Jessica. “Office Ladies” fans go crazy over Nellie’s shoebox, the ladies share their warm up songs, Jenna points out the moment Jessica lost her a little, and get ready, because Angela reads from her travel journal! So whether you know if Stanley has a mustache or not, you can enjoy this episode.</description></item><item><title>Get the Girl | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840009/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week is “Get the Girl”. Andy disappears from the office to confess his love to Erin and bring her back to Scranton. Nellie seizes this opportunity and takes over as manager. The ladies learn the technical term for “fishing line”, Angela gives out a “Worst Green Screen Award” and Jenna stumbles upon another soapbox moment. So sit back and enjoy this episode, it’s better than a trip to DisneyTown.</description></item><item><title>Last Day in Florida | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840010/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week is “Last Day in Florida”. Robert California reveals that he plans to tank the Sabre store that Nellie, Dwight and the rest of the Tallahassee team worked so hard on. Upon the insistence of Pam, Jim does his best to save Dwight from getting fired. Meanwhile Erin tells Andy she won’t be returning to Scranton. The ladies discover they both deep dived Girl Scout Cookies, the team clears the air about Angela thinking “lol” means “lots of laughs”, and Jenna brings in a taste/smell game.</description></item><item><title>Dear Office Ladies | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840011/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week it’s &amp;ldquo;Dear Office Ladies&amp;rdquo;! Jenna and Angela are answering workplace advice questions from listeners. This includes tips to nail an interview, deal with a supervisor who takes personal calls on speaker phone and how to be the coolest person in the office using sauce packets. So sit back, relax and see if your office is as wild as Creed hanging out in the women’s bathroom. Theme Song by Jordan Duffy Insta: @JordanKDuffy Website: www.</description></item><item><title>Test the Store | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840012/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week is “Test the Store”. Dwight continues to try to impress Nellie and must depend on Jim for an epic Sabre store opening. Meanwhile Andy and Pam get harassed in the parking lot by some kids. The ladies tell some baby shoe stories, Angela has an update to Jenna’s coconut water share and Jenna wonders how quickly a bruise appears if you get punched in the face. This is a fun episode so enjoy it while you practice your sign spinning skills!</description></item><item><title>After Hours | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840013/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week is “After Hours”. In Florida, Dwight and Packer compete to impress Nelly for the Vice President position, while Jim gets unwanted attention from Cathy. Back in the office, Andy has the rest of the staff stay late which leads to Darryl getting confronted by Val’s boyfriend (Jerry Minor). Jenna shares how she discovered she loves to wear the color gold, Angela reveals some of her favorite cheeses, and the ladies give you the inside scoop on how Mom Detectives sneak around.</description></item><item><title>A Look Back on Double Date | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840014/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re taking a look back on “Double Date”. To celebrate Helene’s birthday, Michael treats Jim, Pam and Helene to lunch, and of course, it ends up being a very cringey disaster. Meanwhile Dwight and Andy struggle to outdo each other in nice favors. Angela reads from her personal journal about her first New York bagel experience, Jenna shares a story about joining what she thought was an international Spice Girls group and of course, the ladies break down Pam hitting Michael.</description></item><item><title>Tallahassee | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840015/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week is “Tallahassee”. Dwight tries to impress Sabre’s special projects president (Catherine Tate) while dealing with appendicitis. Meanwhile, Andy finds his true calling as a receptionist. Talk of open wounds makes Jenna queasy, Angela shares some fun Tallahassee facts and the ladies also receive some fan mail that saves them a deep dive on appendicitis symptoms. So listen to this episode fast and leave a sexy corpse! An Evening with Office Ladies at Toronto’s Just For Laughs: https://toronto.</description></item><item><title>Special Project | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840016/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week is “Special Project”. Dwight is tasked to go to Tallahassee for a work assignment and both he and Andy must choose which Dunder Mifflin employees will go with him. Also, Pam has returned from maternity leave! Jenna looks into some animal facts, Angela shares a sweet “lol” story and the ladies have a bff basket moment. So be like Florida Stanley and smile because this is another great episode!</description></item><item><title>Jury Duty | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840017/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week is “Jury Duty”. Jim gets quickly dismissed from jury duty but decides to take a few days off to help Pam at home. When Dwight finds out, he tries to turn the office against Jim. Jenna researches the tri-fold tongue, Angela discusses “Six Degrees of Kevin Bacon&amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; and the ladies document a best friend moment. This episode is great, which is good because usually I’m a burrito guy.</description></item><item><title>Pool Party | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840018/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s episode is “Pool Party”. Robert California invites the office to a pool party at his fancy home he’s about to sell. Angela shares how to repurpose an empty box wine bag, Jenna shares a story about the 2011 World Series and the ladies discuss a wedding ring superstition. So you can try to leave this party early but we think you’re gonna end up having a pretty great time.</description></item><item><title>A Look Back on Michael’s Birthday | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840019/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we take a look back on “Michael’s Birthday”. Michael is full of excitement and tantrums to celebrate his bday at the office. Angela talks skating, Jenna describes a wild present she received from her mom and we have some original PPC moments. Enjoy!
Office Ladies Website - Submit a fan question: https://officeladies.com/submitaquestion Follow Us on Instagram: OfficeLadiesPod Check out Office Ladies Merch at Podswag: https://www.podswag.com/collections/office-ladies
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Look Back on The Carpet | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840020/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we take a look back on “The Carpet”. Michael discovers a repulsive substance on his office carpet that pushes him to work in the bullpen with the rest of the Dunder Mifflin employees. Angela gets a little edgy talking about the TV Show “Fear Factor,” Jenna does a deep dive on Rock 107 and you know we got plenty of sass. Enjoy! Office Ladies Website - Submit a fan question: https://officeladies.</description></item><item><title>Trivia | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840021/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s episode is “Trivia”. Andy finds out about Oscar’s Trivia Night and gets the office to crash it in hopes of winning the grand prize. Meanwhile Dwight goes to Sabre headquarters in hopes of moving up the corporate ladder but gets stalled by Gabe. Angela’s friend Brian Gattas sends in an audio clip, Jenna breaks down the Hydrox cookie and the Office Ladies team plays a round of trivia.</description></item><item><title>Christmas Wishes with Ameenah Kaplan | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840022/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s episode is “Christmas Wishes” and the ladies chat with Ameenah Kaplan who played Val. Determined to make this the best holiday party at Dunder Mifflin, Andy tries to make everyone’s Christmas wishes come true. Erin deals with meeting Andy’s new girlfriend, Jessica, and Val shows up overdressed to the holiday party thanks to Darryl. Ameenah talks about being a professional drummer, Angela loves when people go all out in a holiday party outfit and Jenna shares some porcupine facts.</description></item><item><title>Mrs. California | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840023/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s episode is “Mrs. California”. Robert California’s wife (played by Maura Tierney) wants a job at Dunder Mifflin and Robert doesn&amp;rsquo;t, which causes Andy to be stuck in the middle of the two. Meanwhile, Dwight opens a “Gym for Muscles,” Angela can’t get people’s names right, Jenna breaks down the origins of the term “Mrs” and the custom of women taking their husband’s last name, and Mom Detectives solve “The Case of the Windowless Building”.</description></item><item><title>Gettysburg | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840024/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Gettysburg”. Andy tries to motivate the staff by taking them on a field trip to Gettysburg Park. Those who stayed behind end up having to present the company’s next big idea to Robert California. Jenna reveals something that unexpectedly happened to Meredith’s van during the shooting of this episode, Angela reads a letter from an actual soldier who fought in the Battle of Gettysburg, and the ladies learn what “DM Does GB” on the pink hats mean.</description></item><item><title>Pam’s Replacement | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840025/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Pam’s Replacement”. Pam is getting ready to go on maternity leave but starts to feel insecure that Jim may be attracted to her temp replacement Cathy, played by Lindsey Broad. In the warehouse, Robert California discovers Andy, Darryl and Kevin’s band, Kevin and the Zits, and takes over. Jenna shares a scene she could not get through with Mindy and Rainn and Mindy Kaling sends in a clip about it too.</description></item><item><title>Doomsday | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840026/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Doomsday”. To minimize office mistakes, Dwight sets up a tracker that if the office makes three mistakes, an email will automatically be sent to Robert California telling him what the office really thinks of him and it’s not good. The office struggles to get Dwight to remove this tracker before it’s too late. Jenna connected with the writer of this episode, Danny Chun, who explains how the writers used this season to figure out what fans responded to best post-Michael.</description></item><item><title>A Look Back on Koi Pond | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840027/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840027/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s summer break so why not remember when Michael fell in a koi pond? Writers Warren Lieberstein and Halsted Sullivan sent in audio clips about the inspiration behind this episode and our audio engineer, Sam, soundscaped it! Angela discusses her squirrel eating performance, Jenna reminisces on spending the day shooting with Ed Helms for their cold sales call storyline and the ladies break down everything behind shooting the koi pond incident.</description></item><item><title>A Look Back on Fun Run Pt. 1 | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840028/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re on summer break so we’re taking a look back on “Fun Run”. To kick off this two part episode we are joined by the hilarious Kate Flannery. Kate shares her memories from this episode, her time on The Office playing Meredith, and gives us insight into what it was like to do most of her own stunts. Then we answer fan questions about Pam&amp;rsquo;s questionable internet search, the changes to her hair and wardrobe, and of course we chat about what is going on with Jim and Pam.</description></item><item><title>Spooked | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840029/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840029/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Spooked”. Erin feels the pressure to put on a spectacular, spooky Halloween party and Robert California brings his son to work who seems to have an incredible power over Dwight. Angela breaks down what Halloween costumes all the characters are wearing including Darryl, Jim, and Kevin who are dressed as Miami Heat players which feels topical despite being a Halloween episode in June. Jenna does a deep dive on candy corn, which leads to uncovering how many bugs the average person eats in a year and the Office Ladies team share if they believe in ghosts or not.</description></item><item><title>Garden Party with Josh Groban | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840030/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840030/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Garden Party” and the ladies are joined by multi-platinum singer, songwriter, actor Josh Groban who played Andy’s brother, Walter Jr. Josh talks about how fun it was to be on the set of “The Office” and a connection he now shares with Andy. Angela uncovers more Big Pregs Little Pregs moments and Jenna shows how this episode is up there with “Scott’s Tots” in terms of cringy.</description></item><item><title>Lotto with Mark Proksch | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840031/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840031/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Lotto” and the ladies are joined by Mark Proksch (“What We Do in the Shadows”, “Better Call Saul”) who played Nate on “The Office”! When the warehouse employees win the lottery, they all quit, forcing Andy to hire new warehouse employees and Darryl to grapple with how he missed out on this lucrative opportunity because he moved upstairs to be warehouse manager. Mark Proksch shares how he yo-yo’d his way onto “The Office”, Angela has a “Sass Tracker” and Jenna points out a dream she has in common with Pam.</description></item><item><title>The Incentive | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840032/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840032/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “The Incentive”. In an attempt to please Robert California by doubling sales, Andy creates an incentive program that really motivates the employees to achieve the grand prize of tattooing his butt. Jenna shares an email “Office Ladies” got from TV critic Myles McNutt, Angela uncovers a Dwight “chunk” deleted scene and the ladies share what kind of tattoo they would get. So let’s cut out the unnecessary words like Kevin - Listen Office Ladies, you feel good.</description></item><item><title>The List | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840033/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840033/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “The List” and can you believe it? It’s Season 8 of “The Office”! Robert California (James Spader) is the new CEO of Dunder Mifflin and Andy is the Scranton Branch manager. Erin stumbles upon Robert California’s notebook with a list of all the employees’ names in two mysterious columns and they must figure out what it means. Jenna shares how the writers chose who would be the new manager, Angela does a plank and we hear an audio clip from Kate Flannery.</description></item><item><title>An Interview with Beth Grant on “Speed” | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840034/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Bonus Episode Friday! We continue our movie breakdown of “Speed” with an interview with actress Beth Grant! Beth played Helen in “Speed” and shares what it was like to act alongside Keanu Reeves and Sandra Bullock in a runaway bus on the 105 freeway. Beth shares how much the script changed since her audition and how making a mistake during a take was a huge ordeal, like 300 cars having to all turn around ordeal.</description></item><item><title>Movie Breakdown: Speed | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840035/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840035/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down the hit action movie, “Speed” starring Keanu Reeves and Sandra Bullock! A bomb has been planted on a city bus and a young cop must stop it from exploding by keeping the bus above 50 miles per hour. The ladies tell you everything you want to know about the stunts, including stunts Keanu did himself. Angela shares commentary from director Jan de Bont including how he pulled from real life experience to direct this film.</description></item><item><title>Search Committee, Part 2 with Rainn Wilson | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840036/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840036/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down the second part of “Search Committee”, and we are joined by Rainn Wilson! The hunt for the next manager continues and Jo Bennett (Kathy Bates) arrives to help out. Rainn shares what it was like to play Dwight during the Dunder Mifflin manager transition and he also shares a Creed episode he pitched to the writers. Then the ladies and Rainn discuss his new book, “Soul Boom: Why We Need a Spiritual Revolution”.</description></item><item><title>Search Committee, Part 1 | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840037/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840037/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Search Committee, Part 1”. Jim, Toby and Gabe are on Dunder Mifflin’s search committee to find the next Dunder Mifflin manager. Darryl, Andy and Dwight all throw their names in the ring, along with some outside candidates. This episode is jam packed with cameos and we hear audio clips from Will Arnett! Jenna shares the Cliffhanger Document for this episode and Angela has a deep dive/old tech alert on Clippy, the Microsoft Word paperclip mascot.</description></item><item><title>Dwight K. Schrute, (Acting) Manager | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840038/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840038/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Dwight K. Schrute, (Acting) Manager”. Dwight’s time as manager has arrived! Dwight immediately implements his unique management style and literally terrorizes the office with a bang. Jenna does a deep dive on piranhas, the ladies break down Dwight’s office decorating style and Angela uncovers a deleted scene that gives a shout out to Keanu! We also find out who Jo Bennett’s favorite Scranton branch employee is.</description></item><item><title>A Look Back on Heavy Competition | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840039/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s still spring break so let’s reminisce on the 100th episode of “Office Ladies”! The ladies break down “Heavy Competition”, where Michael tries to steal Dwight’s customers while running Michael Scott Paper Company. To celebrate, Angela pops some champagne and Jenna demonstrates the skill needed for that super fun cheeseball opening. So as you’re deciding whether “Pachelbel” is a better wedding song than “You Can Call Me Al”, enjoy this ep and thanks for being an “Office Ladies” fan!</description></item><item><title>A Look Back on Hot Girl | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840040/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s Spring Break and why not celebrate with “Hot Girl,” the Season One “Office” finale?! This ep co-stars Amy Adams and is written by Mindy Kaling. Jenna and Angela share an Amy Adams story that may involve Meryl Streep, and is Jenna an international poker champion? The ladies also explore the disappearing - reappearing E.T. on Jim’s desk and answer some burning fan questions about this episode. Enjoy! Office Ladies Website - Submit a fan question: https://officeladies.</description></item><item><title>An Interview with Will Ferrell | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840041/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840041/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re interviewing Will Ferrell! Will chats with the ladies about what it was like to guest star on “The Office” as Deangelo Vickers during the transition of Steve Carell leaving the show. Will shares how he was a fan of “The Office,” reached out about guesting and was surprised to be offered a four episode arc. The ladies ask Will some fan questions, they also share some fun ski stories, and Will weighs in on the basketball dunk stunt gone wrong.</description></item><item><title>The Inner Circle | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840042/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “The Inner Circle.” Deangelo Vickers has created an exclusive inner circle at the office that is composed only of men and it pisses off the women. Angela reads from her college journal where she reflects on a breakup, Jenna discovered this episode had a lot of “Drama Alerts” involving soda and music, and the ladies talk about a stunt that went wrong on the set of this episode.</description></item><item><title>Interview with Steve Carell | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840043/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re interviewing Steve Carell! Steve talks about what it was like to be on “The Office,” play Michael Scott and everyone reminisces over some favorite Michael moments. Steve answers fan questions from the “Office Ladies” Facebook fan page including questions like “Do you have a Toby in your life?”. The ladies also give Steve a “Regular Guy” quiz. This is a delightful, funny conversation we’ve all been waiting for and we know you’re gonna be just as happy as we were to hear from Steve.</description></item><item><title>Goodbye Michael with Greg Daniels, Pt 2 | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840044/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we finish breaking down “Goodbye Michael” and we are joined again with the writer of the episode, Greg Daniels! The ladies and Greg get into what filming the last scenes with Steve Carell were like. Greg shares how he believed the show could survive after Steve’s exit because of how strong the ensemble cast was. Jenna gets into how they shot the airport scene and Angela shares an interview she did with Steve Carell during his last week on “The Office” set.</description></item><item><title>Goodbye Michael with Greg Daniels, Pt 1 | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840045/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840045/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we break down the first part of “Goodbye Michael” and we are joined by the writer of this episode, Greg Daniels! The office thinks tomorrow is Michael’s last day, but Michael has decided to secretly leave a day early. Greg shares his joy of writing this episode, including the easter egg of Michael pushing his Dundie on his desk to match the opening credits shot. Jenna points out how Michael has grown since the first Party Planning Committee meeting in Season One, but maybe the PPC hasn’t changed so much.</description></item><item><title>A Look Back on Frame Toby | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840046/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840046/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s almost time to say goodbye to Michael, so today we’re taking a trip down memory lane with “Frame Toby.” NOOOOOOOOOO! Toby’s back and Michael is horrified. Michael does what anybody would do to get rid of Toby, frame him with drugs and get him fired. Meanwhile, the office fights over a very disgusting microwave and Jim buys his parents’ house. Jenna does a deep dive on how to clean a microwave, Angela has a soap box moment about street names, and we find out who ended up cleaning the microwave which was accompanied by… a slow clap!</description></item><item><title>Michael’s Last Dundies | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840047/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840047/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Michael’s Last Dundies.” Michael tries to teach Deangelo how to host the Dundies Award show but Deangelo’s extreme stage fright gets in the way. Meanwhile Pam gives Erin some relationship advice that results in her very public breakup with Gabe. We hear clips from the director and writer of this episode, Mindy Kaling! Mindy talks about what it was like to direct her very first TV episode and how she wrote both this episode and the first “Dundies” episodes in Season Two.</description></item><item><title>Training Day | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840048/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840048/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Training Day.” Michael becomes fast friends with the man who’s been hired to replace him at Dunder Mifflin, Deangelo Vickers, who is played by the very funny Will Ferrell! But once Michael introduces Deangelo to the office, Michael begins to have second thoughts about his replacement and leaving. The ladies make some Kahlua Sombreros in honor of Michael and Deangelo’s meet up and talk about what it was like to work with Will Ferrell for four episodes.</description></item><item><title>Garage Sale | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840049/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840049/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down “Garage Sale.” Dunder Mifflin is having a big garage sale and Michael plans to propose to Holly. Meanwhile Dwight goes on a quest to get the most expensive item at the garage sale by starting out with trading only a thumbtack. Jenna breaks down where the inspiration for this episode came from, and Angela gives us a table-by-table breakdown of everything the Dunder Mifflin crew is trying to sell, including Michael’s unforgettable tiny broken plasma screen TV and more.</description></item><item><title>Todd Packer | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840050/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840050/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Todd Packer.” Dunder Mifflin employees are upset when traveling salesman Todd Packer gets a permanent job at the office. Meanwhile, Pam uses her power as Office Administrator to help Andy get a new computer. Then, the ladies reveal how David Koechner came to play Todd Packer, Jenna explains what a bottle episode is and how this episode is an example of it, and Angela deep dives into ant farms.</description></item><item><title>Threat Level Midnight with B.J. Novak | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840051/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840051/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Threat Level Midnight” with writer of the episode, B.J. Novak! After years of working on his personal passion project, Michael finally finishes his movie “Threat Level Midnight” and screens it for the office. Unfortunately Holly isn’t really impressed. B.J. shares his joy of writing this episode and making Michael Scott’s movie a reality. Afterwards, the ladies reminisce on how fun it was to act and dress as their characters from earlier seasons.</description></item><item><title>A Conversation with Billie Eilish | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840052/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840052/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we have a special episode where Jenna and Angela sit down with “The Office” superfan and popstar, Billie Eilish! Billie shares her favorite episodes, seasons and what “The Office” means to her. Billie also shares how “The Office” made her learn a couple things incorrectly including thinking that the band U2 was from Scranton. The ladies talk with Billie about what it was like to sample a clip from “Threat Level Midnight” in her song, “My Strange Addiction.</description></item><item><title>A Look Back on Casino Night with John Krasinski | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840053/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840053/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, we’re taking a trip down memory lane with “Casino Night,” which includes an interview with John Krasinski! This episode was written by Steve Carell and the ladies start this JAM packed episode by explaining how Steve ended up writing this episode, we chat about Pam&amp;rsquo;s wink to Jim, and Jenna shares some behind the scenes tidbits about the Scrantonicity video. Then we get some fan catches about Pam&amp;rsquo;s casino night dress paired with her watch, and that Dwangela slap heard around the world.</description></item><item><title>Holiday Mailbag | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840054/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840054/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Jenna and Angela answer your fan mail questions and revisit some past “Office” episodes. Jenna brings in Michael’s “coffee” drink from “Chair Model” to share and it quickly gets turned into an adult beverage. Angela gets redemption over saying “chunk it,” and the ladies go through some wedding invitations, baby pics and more, sharing some wonderful, heartfelt fan stories. Plus we have some exciting upcoming news. So please enjoy this episode while you get ready for the holiday break, we love ya!</description></item><item><title>PDA with Greg Daniels | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840055/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840055/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “PDA” and we’re joined by Greg Daniels who directed this episode! Michael and Holly are happily back in a relationship but they are not shy of expressing it in the office with a lot of PDA. Meanwhile Jim and Pam get drunk at lunch and spend the rest of the work day trying to hide it, among something else. Greg talks about directing this episode and what it was like anticipating the last few Michael Scott episodes.</description></item><item><title>The Search | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840056/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840056/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “The Search.” When Jim leaves Michael at a gas station to attend to baby Cece, Michael wanders around Scranton causing Dwight, Erin and Holly to go look for him. Meanwhile, the office has a caption contest to Pam’s drawings even though Gabe keeps trying to institute unfun rules. Brent Forrester sends in clips on what it was like to write this “The Office” meets “Sleepless in Seattle” episode.</description></item><item><title>The Seminar | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840057/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840057/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “The Seminar.” Andy hosts a small business seminar in the conference room with the help of some of his fellow coworkers. Meanwhile, Pam and Oscar try to help Erin beat Gabe in a game of Scrabble. Jenna breaks down the special Ricky Gervais cameo, Angela points out some great Creed moments including an alternate Creed seminar speech and the ladies discuss a business idea of Jenna’s.</description></item><item><title>A Look Back on Company Picnic | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840058/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840058/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s Thanksgiving break and what better way to spend it than reminiscing on another great Michael and Holly episode? Take a look back when all the branches of Dunder Mifflin gathered for a company-wide picnic. Michael reconnects with Holly and the Scranton branch come together to slay at volleyball until Pam and Jim discover some very surprising news. The ladies break down why this episode needed “special business performers,” Angela reveals some epic volleyball moves and Jenna shares how the big season finale news was kept under wraps.</description></item><item><title>Ultimatum | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840059/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840059/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Ultimatum.” Michael and the office finds out how Holly’s ultimatum to AJ went and Pam gets the office to make New Years’ resolutions. The ladies share what would be in their happy and sad boxes, Jenna gives a location breakdown of the roller rink used in this episode and what the building is today. Angela is inspired by Darryl, Dwight and Andy and brings her roller skates into the studio to skate around.</description></item><item><title>Classy Christmas, Part 2 | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840060/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840060/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we finish breaking down “Classy Christmas.” Holly has arrived to Pam’s new Classy Christmas party and Michael is disappointed to discover Holly is still dating AJ. Meanwhile Pam gives Jim the comic book she made for him, “The Adventures of Jimmy Halpert.” Jenna breaks down the comic book made by artist Tone Rodriguez. Angela with the help of her husband Josh creates Ryan’s fictional cocktail, F Train to Brooklyn, and serves it to the Office Ladies team.</description></item><item><title>Classy Christmas, Part 1 | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840061/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840061/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down the first half of “Classy Christmas”! This year, Pam is in charge of the Christmas party and it’s the least dramatic and best holiday party in the office yet, until Michael discovers Holly is coming back and cancels the party to demand a new Classy Christmas party for her. Jenna gives us some Hello Kitty facts including how easy the clearance to use the Hello Kitty laptop cases was in comparison to another famous item used in this episode.</description></item><item><title>China | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840062/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840062/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “China.” When Michael outsmarts Oscar in front of the office, Oscar can’t let it go. Meanwhile Andy keeps bothering Darryl via text messages. Jenna goes over texting etiquette, Angela does some real Mom Detectives’ work on finding the lunch spot that’s featured on Dwight’s mug and we learn how Phil Shea made that toilet paper spooling machine. We also have a little treat from The Office’s first assistant director, Kelly Cantley.</description></item><item><title>WUPHF.com with Aaron Shure | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840063/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840063/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “WUPHF.com” and we are joined by the writer of this episode, Aaron Shure! The smartest and brightest of the office workers have invested in Ryan’s Internet startup business, WUPHF.com. It only takes a few days to realize it’s a bad investment and everyone but Michael wants to sell. Writer Aaron Shure shares what it was like to write this episode, along with writing some very iconic cold opens.</description></item><item><title>Viewing Party | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840064/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840064/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Viewing Party.” Gabe and Erin host a “Glee” viewing party at their home and Michael can’t help but wreck the party due to his disdain of Gabe. Meanwhile, Pam discovers Dwight is the answer to help regulate Cece’s sleeping cycle. We learn the interior of Gabe’s apartment was built on the warehouse set, Angela uncovers what Stanley would rather be doing than attend Erin and Gabe’s viewing party and Jenna shares how surprisingly easy it was to shoot the scene where Dwight instantly calms Cece.</description></item><item><title>Christening | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840065/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840065/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Christening.” It’s baby Cece’s christening and Michael has invited the entire office to attend the ceremony without telling Jim and Pam. Jenna has a gift for Angela, Sam points out another clue to who the Scranton Strangler may be and Office Ladies fans, the day has come… Angela brought in one of her journals and she shares a couple entries with us! So don’t be a Sconesy Cider and enjoy this ep!</description></item><item><title>Costume Contest | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840066/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840066/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Costume Contest”. The office competes in a costume contest to win a questionably impressive coupon book. Meanwhile Michael discovers Darryl went behind his back to give corporate an idea and Jim helps Pam figure out why Danny didn’t ask Pam for another date. The ladies share their appreciation to fans after spending 2 days going through physical Fan Mail, which includes sharing some specialty potato chips with Phil Rosenthal (Everybody Loves Raymond, Naked Lunch).</description></item><item><title>The Sting with Craig Robinson | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840067/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840067/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “The Sting” and the ladies are joined by the one and only Craig Robinson! To take down the rival paper salesman Danny Cordray (played by Timothy Olyphant), Michael puts together a sting operation. Meanwhile, Andy forms a band with Darryl and Kevin. Craig shares how he got his job on “The Office” and what it was like to play Darryl, including how his musical skills were often incorporated into episodes.</description></item><item><title>Sex Ed with Nancy Walls Carell | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840068/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840068/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Sex Ed” and we are joined by Nancy Walls Carell! The office convinces Michael that he has herpes so he does the “right thing” and contacts all his past girlfriends to inform them of his newly discovered STD. Nancy discusses with the ladies what it was like to play Carol Stills, including how Nancy justified why Carol would even date Michael in the first place.</description></item><item><title>Andy's Play with Ed Helms | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840069/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840069/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Andy’s Play” and the ladies are joined by Ed Helms! Michael becomes jealous when he discovers his “Law and Order” audition didn’t get him a part in the local production of “Sweeney Todd” but Andy did. Ed Helms shares what it was like to prep for this episode, Angela reveals why Angela Martin looks so cute and Jenna makes orange juice and Baileys for everyone to try inspired by Jim and Pam.</description></item><item><title>Counseling | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840070/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840070/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Counseling.” After spanking his nephew at work, Michael undergoes counseling with Toby. Meanwhile, Dwight attempts to get his “Pretty Woman” revenge at a Steamtown Mall shop and Pam gives herself a promotion. We hear an original “Whispers in the Breakroom” by musician Elyse Myers. Jenna reveals the backstory behind how Michael came to hate Toby, Angela shares why Dwight wanted that wizard statue so bad, and we get a fun audio clip from actress, Kate Walsh!</description></item><item><title>A Look Back on Beach Games | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840071/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840071/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s the end of summer break so why not take one more trip to the beach with “Beach Games”?! Relisten to writer Jen Celotta sharing her memories from this episode. From the &amp;lsquo;Survivor&amp;rsquo; theme to the challenges that went into shooting Andy floating away in the Sumo suit, we get all of the behind the scenes details! Then, we dive into the hilarious hot dog eating contest and Angela schools us with her basketball knowledge.</description></item><item><title>Nepotism | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840072/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840072/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Nepotism.” And holy smokes, it’s Season 7! Michael got his nephew, played by Evan Peters, a job at Dunder Mifflin and he’s terrible. Like soy ice cream and bagel chips terrible. The ladies tell you everything you want to know about the lip dub opening, and Kate Flannery sends in a clip about her experience being strapped to Brian Baumgartner’s back. Then Angela shares a story full of twists and turns about trying to find a Blu-ray player in her hometown so she could research this episode, Jenna explains a seemingly strange reaction Pam has in a conference room scene and the ladies wonder about being able to pee in the ocean.</description></item><item><title>Whistleblower | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840073/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840073/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down the finale of Season Six, “Whistleblower”! When the news gets out that Sabre’s printers catch on fire, Jo Bennett returns to the Scranton branch to find out who the whistleblower is. Nelson Franklin sends in clips to share what it was like to play not one, but two characters on “The Office”! The ladies share how the crew shot on a real private plane, Angela points out a Kathy Bates moment in this episode that made it into the “Office BFFs” book and Jenna breaks down how Toby was able to get stuck holding the vending machine.</description></item><item><title>The Chump | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840074/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840074/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “The Chump.” Michael and Andy go spy on Donna’s husband while he coaches a high school baseball game. Meanwhile Dwight and Angela Martin sit down with a lawyer to dispute their childbearing contract. Writer Aaron Schure sends in a clip about a memory he had involving the negotiation scenes for this episode. Jenna shares a fan theory involving radon poisoning, Angela shares some strange ice cream flavors and of course, the ladies talk about the famous Dwanglea rendezvous in the warehouse that Jim and Pam overhear.</description></item><item><title>The Cover-Up | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840075/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840075/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “The Cover-Up.” The office convinces Michael that Donna is cheating so Michael hires the best private detective he knows to find out! (It’s Dwight.) Rainn Wilson sends in clips sharing what it was like to both act and direct this episode. Jenna does a deep dive on signs someone may be cheating, Angela shares a deleted runner that adds another layer to Ryan and Kelly’s relationship and the ladies come to terms with the fact that their friendship entails many things, but not exercising together.</description></item><item><title>Body Language | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840076/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840076/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Body Language”. Michael tries to decipher Donna’s body language to determine if she has feelings for him. Meanwhile Dwight encourages Kelly to apply for the Sabre minority management training program, only to realize Kelly Kapoor cannot be controlled. Angela gets in touch with Hidetoshi Imura who played Hide Hasegawa in the Dunder Mifflin Warehouse and shares his thoughts on what it was like to play such a memorable warehouse character, Jenna reveals the discussion behind Pam’s hair after becoming a new mom and the ladies got some hot takes on bras.</description></item><item><title>Secretary's Day with Ellie Kemper | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840077/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840077/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Secretary’s Day” and the ladies chat with the wonderful Ellie Kemper (Unbreakable Kimmy Schmidt, Bridesmaids) who played Kelly Erin Hannon! It’s Secretary’s Day and Andy convinces Michael to take Erin out to lunch to celebrate her being the office receptionist. Michael begrudgingly does so while also letting slip out to Erin that Andy was previously engaged to Angela Martin. Ellie Kemper shares what it was like to become a regular cast member and shows the ladies an iconic poster she took from the set.</description></item><item><title>Happy Hour | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840078/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840078/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Happy Hour.” Oscar wants to spend more time with Matt from the warehouse, so he puts together a Dunder Mifflin Happy Hour at Sid &amp;amp; Dexter’s. Pam tries to sneakily introduce Michael to her single friend but when he finds out, “Date Mike” appears. Meanwhile, Dwight attempts to break his childbearing contract with Angela when he reconnects with Isabel. “The Office” cinematographer, Matt Sohn, sends in clips on what it was like to direct this episode including shooting most of the episode outside of the typical office location, Jenna gives a deep dive on the origin of Happy Hour and Angela points out one of Angela Martin’s most famous memes.</description></item><item><title>New Leads | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840079/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840079/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “New Leads.” Sabre’s no cap on commission policy has gone to the sales team’s heads, and to get them under control, Michael hides the new leads which accidentally end up in the Scranton dump. Writer and director of the episode, Brent Forrester, sends in clips about working on this episode, Jenna breaks down how they made and shot the landfill scenes, and Angela gives Jenna and Sam a garbage quiz.</description></item><item><title>St. Patrick’s Day | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840080/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840080/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “St. Patrick’s Day.” Michael learns to put his need for friendship aside to confront Jo Bennett for keeping the office late on St. Patrick’s Day. Meanwhile Darryl gets promoted when he shares a great shipping idea, and Erin and Andy have their first date despite Erin feeling under the weather. Kate Flannery sends in a clip about participating in the real Scranton St. Patrick’s Day Parade, Jenna shares a story about meeting Molly Shannon when she was first starting out in Hollywood, and Angela shares some fun candy bag alts as to why Angela Martin is anxious to get off work.</description></item><item><title>The Delivery, Pt 2 with Lee Kirk | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840081/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840081/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, we’re breaking down the second part of “The Delivery, Pt 2.” Pam is having trouble breastfeeding Cece, and back at the office, Michael is playing matchmaker to Erin and Kevin, making Andy jealous. We have a special guest today! The ladies chat with Jenna’s husband Lee Kirk, who played Clark the Lactation Consultant. Jenna’s sister also sends in a clip about what it was like having The Office baby named after her daughter, we find out what special holiday this episode was shot on, and we hear another interesting fan theory about the Scranton Strangler.</description></item><item><title>The Delivery, Pt 1 | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840082/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840082/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down the first part of “The Delivery.” Jim and Pam’s baby is on the way! Pam is having “contraptions” at work but insists on holding off on going to the hospital until after midnight so her health insurance will cover an extra day. Meanwhile, Dwangela is back when Dwight realizes he must have a child of his own and sparks a contractual agreement with Angela Martin.</description></item><item><title>“The Office BFFs” Book Q&amp;A | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840083/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840083/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week is a special episode of “Office Ladies,” Jenna and Angela answer fan questions about their brand new book, “The Office BFFs: Tales of The Office from Two Best Friends Who Were There.” The ladies talk about how they came to write the book which included finding a perfect system that worked for their different writing styles. And the ladies share another part of their audiobook! Have you grabbed your copy yet?</description></item><item><title>Chapter 1 from “The Office BFFs” Audiobook | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840084/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Surprise! Jenna and Angela are giving you Chapter 1 from their audiobook, “The Office BFFs: Tales of The Office from Two Best Friends Who Were There”! Take a listen and get excited for the official release on May 17th. Thank you for being an “Office Ladies” fan!
Link to Audiobook: https://www.audible.com/pd/The-Office-BFFs-Audiobook/0063007614?source_code=GO1GB547041122911G&amp;gclid=CjwKCAjwjtOTBhAvEiwASG4bCOzLiCAWalvLaPDRen-cDeWWixSdg0ACpGzqZSCn4U6QPUsmnOkmhxoCfTcQAvD_BwE&amp;gclsrc=aw.ds Link to Book, Ebook, Audiobook: https://www.harpercollins.com/pages/OfficeBFFs
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Manager and the Salesman | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840085/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840085/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “The Manager and the Salesman.” Sabre CEO Jo Bennett, played by the Kathy Bates, visits Dunder Mifflin only to discover there are two co-managers, Michael and Jim. She gives them the ultimatum that there can only be one manager. Meanwhile it’s Valentine’s Day and Andy confuses Erin by giving Valentine’s Day cards to everyone in the office, including a pretty romantic one to Kelly.</description></item><item><title>Sabre | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840086/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840086/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Sabre” and the director of this ep, John Krasinski, sends in clips to share what it was like directing this very big episode. Dunder Mifflin has been acquired by the printer company, Sabre, and it’s CEO is the very powerful, no nonsense Jo Bennett played by Kathy Bates. This is also the episode that introduces Gabe Lewis played by Zach Woods! Angela talks about a “Save David Wallace” fan campaign, Jenna gives us everything we want to know about those special prop scissors used in the cold open and the ladies share about the real life inspiration behind that “bathroom moment” when Jim and Pam tour a local daycare.</description></item><item><title>The Banker | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840087/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840087/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “The Banker.” Since Dunder Mifflin is being sold, an investment banker visits the office to talk with HR, a.k.a. Toby. And what do ya know? It’s a clip show! Actor David Costabile (“Breaking Bad”, “Billions,” “The Wire”) sends in clips about his experience playing the banker, Eric Ward. Jenna breaks down the history of clip shows on television, Angela gives a list of the most popular books people read while on the toilet and we also learn the Top 5 “Office” quotes that fans loved up to the airing of this episode.</description></item><item><title>Secret Santa | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840088/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840088/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Secret Santa” and Green Day’s Billie Joe Armstrong reads this week’s summary! To raise spirits, Jim and Dwight plan a fun holiday Christmas Party and Phyllis gets to realize her dream of playing Santa Claus! However, Michael hijacks the party when he shows up dressed as Santa and won’t back down. Meanwhile, Andy accidentally torments Erin with Secret Santa gifts from the song, “The 12 Days of Christmas.</description></item><item><title>Scott’s Tots with B.J. Novak | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840089/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840089/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Scott’s Tots” and the ladies chat with the director of this episode and the man behind the sometimes-fedora-wearing Ryan Howard, B.J. Novak! Ten years has passed since Michael promised 15 third graders that he would pay for their college if they graduated high school, and guess what? They’ve all graduated and Michael cannot afford to fulfill this promise. So he must do the right thing, give them all lithium laptop batteries and break the bad news.</description></item><item><title>Shareholder Meeting | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840090/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840090/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Shareholder Meeting.” Michael, Oscar, Dwight and Andy go to New York for a Dunder Mifflin’s shareholder meeting where Michael is being recognized as a top manager. Back at the office, Jim is having trouble getting the rest of his co-workers to respect his authority. Jenna shares costume designer Alysia Raycraft’s experience designing Recyclops, Angela gives us a deep dive on limousines with the help of Google Translate, and the ladies have a true Mom Detectives’ moment where they take on the case of mysterious gift bags sitting on Kelly’s desk.</description></item><item><title>Happy Spring Break and a Look Back on "Chair Model" | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840091/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Spring, all! Let’s take a look back on a classic cringey Michael ep. After a disastrous dinner party, Michael is single and finds himself falling in love with a chair model from an office supply catalog. Meanwhile Kevin and Andy fight to get their parking spaces back from a construction project by confronting the Five Families. We hear from Paul Faust who actually played himself as one of the heads of the Five Families.</description></item><item><title>Murder | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840092/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840092/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Murder!” When the office learns Dunder Mifflin might be going bankrupt, Michael tames their nerves with a good ol’ Southern game of “Murder!” Jenna points out Pam is wearing the same outfit two episodes in a row, Angela shares the time she played a murder mystery game at a party hosted by Oscar Nuñez, and of course, the ladies give you all the details behind Tube City.</description></item><item><title>Double Date | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840093/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840093/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Double Date.” To celebrate Helene’s birthday, Michael treats Jim, Pam and Helene to lunch, and of course, it ends up being a very cringey disaster. Meanwhile, Dwight and Andy struggle to outdo each other in nice favors. Angela reads from her personal journal about her first New York bagel experience, Jenna shares a story about joining what she thought was an international Spice Girls group and of course, the ladies breakdown Pam hitting Michael.</description></item><item><title>Koi Pond | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840094/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840094/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Koi Pond.” After falling into a koi pond, Michael gets teased by the office. Meanwhile, Pam and Andy go on cold sales calls together and are mistaken for a married couple. Writers Warren Lieberstein and Halsted Sullivan sent in audio clips about the inspiration behind this episode and our audio engineer, Sam Kieffer, soundscaped it! Angela discusses her squirrel eating performance, Jenna reminisces on spending the day shooting with Ed Helms, and the ladies break down everything behind shooting the koi pond incident.</description></item><item><title>The Lover | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840095/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840095/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “The Lover.” Jim and Pam return from their honeymoon and discover that Michael is dating Pam’s mom, Helene. Let’s just say, Pam is not ok with it. Meanwhile, Dwight spies on Jim with a deceptive spy trick that involves a wooden mallard. Jenna talks about how playing super angry Pam was a challenge, Angela unveils a deleted scene where Michael plays with Helene’s socks, and the ladies have a much needed “BFF download.</description></item><item><title>Mafia | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840096/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we’re breaking down “Mafia”. Jim and Pam are on their honeymoon leaving the office deficient in reasonable people. So when an Italian insurance salesman tries to sell Michael life insurance, Dwight and Andy convince him he’s with the Scranton mafia. Writer of this episode, Brent Forrester, sends in clips breaking down how this farcical episode is legendary. Jenna reveals how Pam’s watercolor was almost destroyed in this episode and Angela uncovers that Scranton had real mafia members including Russell Bufalino who was later played by Joe Pesci in “The Irishman”.</description></item><item><title>Niagara, Pt 2 | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840097/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840097/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we finish breaking down “Niagara”. On their wedding day, Jim and Pam sneak off to get married on the Maid of the Mist while their guests wait in the church and Michael hits it off with Pam’s mom. The ladies go into greater detail about the lost storyline that involved a horse and Roy unsuccessfully trying to stop the wedding. Angela found a stunt photo to fool the paparazzi featuring Pam and Toby, Jenna breaks down the viral dance video that inspired “The Office” cast to dance at Jim and Pam’s wedding and the ladies point out a very special cameo by Randy Cordray!</description></item><item><title>Niagara, Pt 1 with Greg Daniels | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840098/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Niagara”. To kick off this two-part episode, the ladies are joined again by showrunner Greg Daniels! (“The Office”, “The Simpsons”, “King of the Hill”, “Upload”, “Space Force”) Together they talk about everything that went behind creating the much anticipated Jim and Pam wedding, which includes finding that special balance between funny and heartwarming. Anna Camp (“Pitch Perfect”, “True Blood”) also sends in clips to share what it was like to play Pam’s sister.</description></item><item><title>The Promotion | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840099/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840099/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “The Promotion”. Jim and Michael must now work together as co-managers and they’re given the difficult task of deciding who and who will not get a raise among the Dunder Mifflin employees. The ladies discuss Jim’s glass office that magically appears, Jenna gives a shout out to a famous nurse who popularized the pie chart, and Angela may just admit to a love of trains.</description></item><item><title>Interview with Mike Schur | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840100/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840100/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Jenna and Angela interview Mike Schur! Mike Schur wrote on the first four seasons of “The Office” and played Dwight’s mysterious cousin, Mose Schrute. Mike also worked on “Saturday Night Live” and created shows like “Parks and Recreation”, “Brooklyn Nine-Nine”, “The Good Place” and “Rutherford Falls”. Angela talks with Mike about a scene where she slapped him so hard he spun, Jenna and Mike talk about the difference between acting on a TV show vs a movie, and of course, Mike talks about his love/hate relationship with playing the character of Mose.</description></item><item><title>The Meeting | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840101/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we’re breaking down “The Meeting”. Jim attempts to have a meeting with David Wallace to push for a promotion without Michael knowing, but of course, it backfires. Meanwhile, Dwight and Toby team up to try to see if Daryl is faking a work injury, and Pam struggles to get RSVPs to her and Jim’s wedding. Jenna reminisces about the yellow pages, Angela discovers a unique wine inspired by a condiment and Andy has a lot to say about cheese.</description></item><item><title>Gossip | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840102/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we’re breaking down “Gossip”. Michael attempts to cover up some gossip he spread about Stanley by telling lies about everyone else in the office, except he’s accidentally right about one. We hear audio clips from Max Carver who played Eric, one of the interns. Jenna reminisces on the summer between Season 5 and 6, Angela does a deep dive on the history of the building Tinks was in and the ladies share an Office Ladies’ dream that revolves around a soup party.</description></item><item><title>Company Picnic | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840103/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840103/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Company Picnic” and it’s the 100th episode of “The Office”! All the branches of Dunder Mifflin gather for a company-wide picnic. Michael reconnects with Holly and the Scranton branch comes together to slay at some volleyball until Pam and Jim receive some very surprising news. The ladies break down why this episode needed “special business performers”, Angela reveals some epic volleyball moves and Jenna shares how the big Season 5 finale news was kept under wraps.</description></item><item><title>Happy New Year &amp; A Look Back on Traveling Salesman | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840104/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy New Year! This week we look back on “Traveling Salesman”. What a great way to bring in 2022 with some “Laundry and Betrayal”, clips from Greg Daniels and some Dwangela Heartbreak in the Break Room. And, a special bonus to kick things off as the ladies break down the History of New Years. Enjoy, and we&amp;rsquo;ll see you next week for &amp;ldquo;Company Picnic&amp;rdquo;!
Vote “Office Ladies” for the iHeart Podcast of the Year!</description></item><item><title>Happy Holidays and A Look Back on Christmas Party | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840105/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Holidays, everyone! The ladies take us back to the great “Christmas Party” episode and Angela even uncovers a mysterious Creed deleted scene! Enjoy this “Office Ladies” festive gem, and thank you for listening to “Office Ladies”! Have a wonderful holiday season with your loved ones. Vote “Office Ladies” for the iHeart Podcast of the Year! Go to Twitter and use hashtags #PodcastOfTheYear + #iHeartPodcastAwards + #OfficeLadies
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cafe Disco | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840106/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840106/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Cafe Disco”. Michael still has that seven year lease on the Michael Scott Paper Company office so he turns it into a cafe disco! Meanwhile Jim and Pam plan to sneak away to Ohio to elope. The ladies reveal how the writers came up with the idea of a cafe disco, Angela shares what she calls the “Kevin Bacon” deleted scenes and Jenna breaks down some of the cast’s dancing moves and the songs chosen for cafe disco.</description></item><item><title>Casual Friday with Brian Baumgartner | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840107/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840107/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Casual Friday”, and the ladies talk with the actor behind the famous chili cold open, Brain Baumgartner! Brian, who played Kevin Malone, shares how he got his role and what it was like to play this oddball accountant. Afterwards the ladies discuss this episode; Michael is back as the Dunder Mifflin manager of the Scranton branch and he reinstates Casual Friday. He also seems to be giving preferential treatment to Pam and Ryan causing resentment among some of the other employees.</description></item><item><title>Broke | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840108/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840108/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Broke”. The Michael Scott Paper Company is struggling to stay in business after Ryan made a serious accounting error. Meanwhile, Dunder Mifflin has taken a hit from all the customers they lost to the Michael Scott Paper Company, so with the help of Jim, Dunder Mifflin decides to buy out the Michael Scott Paper Company even though they have no idea that’s exactly what Michael, Pam and Ryan want.</description></item><item><title>A Look Back on Diwali | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840109/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Thanksgiving! Our “Office Ladies” team is enjoying a break with our families but before we left, Jenna and Angela share a “Diwali” deleted scene that reveals another Andy nickname and we hear a clip from Mindy Kaling! While you enjoy the holiday, you can relisten to this amazing interview with the boss lady triple threat herself, Mindy Kaling! Mindy walks us through how she came to work on “The Office”, what it was like for her to be able to pitch and write “Diwali”, and explains why the show cast her actual parents in this episode.</description></item><item><title>Heavy Competition | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840110/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840110/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Heavy Competition” and it’s the “Office Ladies” 100th episode!!! As Michael tries to steal Dwight’s customers, the ladies celebrate this very special podcast milestone. Angela pops some Champagne, the ladies listen to a very special fan song and Jenna demonstrates the skill needed for that super fun cheeseball opening. So as you’re deciding whether “Pachelbel” is a better wedding song than “You Can Call Me Al”, enjoy this episode and thank you for listening!</description></item><item><title>Michael Scott Paper Company | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840111/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840111/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Michael Scott Paper Company”. Michael throws a pancake luncheon to promote his new company, Jim struggles with making Charles a “rundown” and the new receptionist has newfound friends, Dwight and Andy, in yet another romantic competition. By the way, the new receptionist is Erin Hannon, played by Ellie Kemper! Angela points out that Jenna has been a Fun/Fast Fact Queen well before “Office Ladies”, Jenna reveals that while shooting this episode paparazzi snuck onto “The Office” set and both ladies have something to say about a couple pairs of sunglasses.</description></item><item><title>Dream Team | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840112/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840112/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Dream Team”! Michael puts together his dream team for the Michael Scott Paper Company which consists of Vikram, Pam and… Ryan. Meanwhile, Jim kisses up to Charles Miner by pretending to be a soccer player and this fib results in Phyllis getting hit in the head with a soccer ball and possibly swallowing a crown. Angela breaks down the OG Dream Team from the 1992 Men’s Olympics Basketball team, Jenna is bringing back the flower lapel and the ladies discuss Vikram&amp;rsquo;s famous quote, “Confidence.</description></item><item><title>Two Weeks | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840113/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840113/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Two Weeks”. Michael puts in his two weeks notice at Dunder Mifflin and when he learns finding a new job is hard, he decides to start the Michael Scott Paper Company. The ladies celebrate Michael’s new endeavor by trying his drink of choice, Scotch and Splenda. Is it drinkable?! Angela points out a deleted scene that reveals why Michael has a big tub of cheeseballs, Jenna describes how the monster sounds were made for Monster.</description></item><item><title>New Boss | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840114/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840114/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “New Boss”. Michael’s 15th Anniversary work party gets thwarted by the new, no-nonsense Vice President of the Northeast Region, Charles Miner, played by Idris Elba. The ladies dish some fun fast facts about Idris, Angela explains what she thinks a petting zoo at Burning Man is and Jenna addresses a couple “fan mail flurries” on how long Michael has actually worked at Dunder Mifflin and Jim’s &amp;ldquo;number two&amp;rdquo; position.</description></item><item><title>Golden Ticket with Rainn Wilson | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840115/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840115/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Golden Ticket”, and Rainn Wilson calls in to give an in depth interview about his experience playing the eccentric, unforgettable Dwight Schrute. When Michael’s Willy Wonka inspired “golden ticket” idea backfires, Michael tries to get Dwight to take the blame. Angela tells a story about her dad winning a pink car, Rainn reveals a mysterious white peacock that’s moved into his yard and Jenna shares a great product idea a friend and her came up with in school that involves a baster.</description></item><item><title>Blood Drive | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840116/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840116/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down Blood Drive! Michael throws a Lonely Hearts Club party at the office for Valentine’s Day, hoping the woman he met earlier at the blood drive shows up. Meanwhile Jim, Pam, Phyllis and Bob Vance (of Vance Refrigeration) go on a double date that ends in Phyllis needing to chug a bunch of water. Katie Aselton sends in clips on what it was like to play the mysterious glove girl, Jenna does a deep dive on blood drives, and Angela discusses the new controversial trend of solo moons.</description></item><item><title>Lecture Circuit, Pt 2 | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840117/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840117/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we finish breaking down Lecture Circuit. Pam and Michael make a detour to visit Holly at the Dunder Mifflin Nashua branch only to encounter her new boyfriend, AJ. Angela Martin sold her engagement ring from Andy to buy Princess Lady, a fancy cat, and now has to intervene with her other cats to make sure Princess Lady is bonding appropriately. We hear clips from guest star, Rob Huebel, on what it was like to play AJ, Angela gives us a breakdown of the cat licking scene and Jenna reveals who wrote the Holly letter she read on Michael’s behalf.</description></item><item><title>Lecture Circuit, Pt 1 | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840118/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840118/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down the first part of Lecture Circuit! To help improve sales across all the Dunder Mifflin, Michael and Pam travel to different branches and attempt to give helpful lectures. Meanwhile, Jim and Dwight have taken over the Party Planning Committee and they do their best to make Kelly happy after forgetting her birthday. The ladies talk precision driving vs fakey driving, Jenna points out suitcase acting and Angela does a deep dive on the candy, Mounds Bar.</description></item><item><title>Stress Relief, Pt 2 | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840119/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840119/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we finish breaking down “Stress Relief”. In a continued effort to relieve the office’s stress, Michael demands a comedic roast of himself; meanwhile Pam, Jim and Andy finish watching the very saucy film, “Mrs. Albert Hannaday”, starring Jack Black, Cloris Leachman and Jessica Alba. Jenna does a deep dive on Cloris Leachman, the ladies share stories of acting on a sitcom vs a single camera comedy, and Angela reveals that Angela Martin’s comedic inspiration is Jeff Foxworthy.</description></item><item><title>Stress Relief Pt 1 | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840120/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840120/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down “Stress Relief”! To kick off this two-part episode, the ladies break down one of the most famous cold opens of “The Office”, featuring clips from Rainn Wilson, Oscar Nuñez, Brian Baumgartner and cinematographer, Randall Einhorn. When Dwight stages a fake fire, Stanley has a heart attack and Michael goes into overdrive to protect Stanley. The ladies reveal how much went into this episode that premiered right after SuperBowl XLIII, which includes Angela walking us through everything that went behind “Save Bandit!</description></item><item><title>Prince Family Paper | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840121/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840121/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down Prince Family Paper! When David Wallace asks Michael and Dwight to go undercover and scout out a family-owned paper business, Michael’s conscience gets to him. Meanwhile back in the office, everyone debates whether Hillary Swank is hot or not. (The ladies may get on a soapbox or two for this one.) Jenna does a deep dive on Hillary Swank, the ladies delve into all the creative production work that went behind building and shooting the Prince Family Paper company, and Angela shares a funny blooper where a cast member got bits of smoked almonds spit on them.</description></item><item><title>A Look Back on Conflict Resolution | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840122/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840122/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re taking a look back on Conflict Resolution. This is the episode where Oscar and Angela feud over the babies playing jazz poster, Jenna shares some amazing insights on the talking heads, both ladies talk about magazine photoshoots with their cats, and we discover whose names are on the plaques hung all around Dunder Mifflin. The ladies also wonder if ‘save the dates’ are worth the trouble, and then we get into Michael’s conflict resolution style, along with some major Pam sass.</description></item><item><title>The Duel | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840123/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840123/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down The Duel! When Michael tells Andy that Angela and Dwight are having an affair, Andy and Dwight challenge each other to a duel for Angela’s hand! Jenna does a deep dive on duels, Office writer Ryan Koh calls in to share a behind-the-scenes racing accident, and Angela breaks down all the fakey items used to create the duel scene. There’s also talk of a casting sheet filled with cat headshots!</description></item><item><title>Moroccan Christmas | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840124/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840124/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down Moroccan Christmas! When Meredith gets too drunk at Phyllis’ Moroccan themed Christmas party and lights her own hair on fire, Michael forces an intervention. Phyllis also reveals to the entire office that Angela is having an affair with Dwight. Well, everyone in the office except Andy… The ladies talk about how this was a big prop week for prop master, Phil Shea, Jenna finds something special while cleaning out her desk and Angela shares one of the best Michael Scott alts that didn’t make it into the show.</description></item><item><title>The Surplus | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840125/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840125/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down The Surplus! When Michael announces to the Scranton Branch that they have a surplus, the office fights over whether to use the leftover money to buy new chairs or a new copier. Meanwhile Dwight “helps” Angela and Andy plan their wedding. Angela tells us about shooting on Disney Ranch which was once known as Golden Oak Ranch, Jenna does a deep dive on Iowa State Farm&amp;rsquo;s butter sculptures, and the ladies gush over one of the best Hank scenes in the entire run of The Office.</description></item><item><title>A Look Back on Branch Closing | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840126/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840126/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re taking a look back on Branch Closing. This is the episode that spawned the famous Michael Scott &amp;ldquo;This Is The Worst&amp;rdquo; meme, and the ladies dig into those Angela and Roy flirtations, along with getting into the intricacies of low-pony tails. There’s a great fan catch at David Wallace&amp;rsquo;s house, and we find out Jim is coming back to Scranton. Finally, we couldn&amp;rsquo;t say goodbye to Josh Porter without bringing on the amazing Charles Esten (Outer Banks on Netflix).</description></item><item><title>Frame Toby | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840127/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we’re breaking down Frame Toby. NOOOOOOOOOO! Toby’s back and Michael is horrified. Michael does what anybody would do to get rid of Toby, frame him with drugs and get him fired. Meanwhile, the office fights over a very disgusting microwave and Jim buys his parents’ house. Jenna does a deep dive on how to clean a microwave, Angela has a soap box moment about street names, and we find out who ended up cleaning the microwave which was accompanied by… a slow clap!</description></item><item><title>Business Trip with Rich Sommer | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840128/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we’re breaking down Business Trip. The ladies kick off this episode by interviewing Rich Sommer, who played Alex, Pam’s art school friend. Rich shares what it was like to play Alex and navigate being a character that Office fans were afraid was going to get in between Jim and Pam. Afterwards, the ladies breakdown Business Trip. Michael, Oscar and Andy go on a business trip to Winnipeg, Canada, while everyone back at the office count down the days until Pam comes home from art school.</description></item><item><title>Customer Survey with Stephen Merchant | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840129/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840129/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down Customer Survey, and the ladies interview Stephen Merchant! Stephen shares with us how he met Ricky Gervais and came to co-create the UK version of The Office, along with directing this very funny episode. When both Jim and Dwight get bad customer survey reviews, they team up together to uncover the truth behind who&amp;rsquo;s calling them arrogant and smudge. Angela shares her struggle with that &amp;ldquo;hand-plowed field&amp;rdquo; scene and Jenna talks about the infamous moment between Pam and Alex, and of course, there&amp;rsquo;s talk about those fakey, tiny Bluetooths.</description></item><item><title>Employee Transfer | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840130/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840130/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down Employee Transfer. When David Wallace finds out Michael and Holly are dating, he transfers Holly to the Nashua branch. Meanwhile Pam attempts to pull a prank on Jim with his brothers, and Dwight pushes Andy’s Cornell buttons. Writer Anthony Q. Farrell sends in clips sharing what it was like to write this big episode. The ladies pitch a salad dressing, Angela gives a Halloween costume breakdown and Jenna reconnects with Tug Coker, an actor who played one of Jim’s brothers.</description></item><item><title>Crime Aid | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840131/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840131/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down Crime Aid! Michael and Holly get caught up in the magic of their third date and consequently, the office gets robbed. Meanwhile Phyllis helps Dwight deal with his Angela romantic woes. The ladies give Roy a Show Bible Goodbye, Angela does a deep dive on the Pennsylvania Anthracite Heritage Museum, and Jenna reveals why Wikipedia doesn’t have an “Office Robbery Statistics” page. Also, there’s a lot of great talk about auctions.</description></item><item><title>Revisited with Carey Bennett | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840132/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840132/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s time for a second drink! Today we are revisiting Season 4. We kick off this episode with an amazing interview with the original Office costume designer, Carey Bennett. Carey talks with Jenna and Angela about how she designed the look for The Office cast, including what Dwight’s mustard shirt means to her. And how she influenced the overall look of the show. Afterwards, Jenna breaks down the opening credits and theme song, the ladies get to the bottom of what Michael was eating inSurvivor Man and Angela uncovers even more for Dinner Party.</description></item><item><title>Baby Shower | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840133/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840133/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down Baby Shower. Michael has the Party Planning Committee throw a baby shower for Jan, while Jan has already had her baby and just didn’t tell Michael about it. Jenna does a deep dive on the history of baby showers, the ladies explore the song Son of A Preacher Man, and Angela shares what Phil Shea gifted her after shooting this episode. So you can put this episode to the test, just like Dwight did with Jan’s stroller, but we guarantee it’s a very good, indestructible episode.</description></item><item><title>Business Ethics with Amy Ryan | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840134/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840134/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down Business Ethics. Jenna and Angela interview Amy Ryan on what it was like to play Holly Flax! Amy even shares her own Coopers Seafood House story. Angela shares about some very special DVD commentary guests who worked as craft services and caterers on The Office set. Jenna does a deep dive on how the Cookie Monster’s parody of Tay Zonday’s “Chocolate Rain” was made after this episode aired, and the ladies discover they both did the same deep dive on what people can do in, let’s say, 19 minutes.</description></item><item><title>Weight Loss, Part 2 | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840135/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840135/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we finish breaking down Weight Loss. The Office gang continues to lose weight for the Dunder Mifflin Weight Loss Challenge, and a truly unexpected proposal happens. We hear an audio clip from Paul Feig about what it was like to be the Season 5 “Tastemaker”. Jenna tells us about some very special cats at Pratt Institute, Angela breaks down what it was like to have a fruit fly wrangler on set and we learn everything we ever wanted to know (and maybe not wanted to know) about the famous Jim and Pam gas station proposal.</description></item><item><title>Weight Loss, Part 1 | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840136/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we’re breaking down Weight Loss. To kick off Season 5 and this two part episode, Angela shares that the DVD commentary features commentary from The Office crew! The crew gives the lowdown on how they shot this episode that spans over an 8 week period. It was a continuity nightmare with fruit flies, goatees, and a cast member that had to have their shirt digitally altered in post.</description></item><item><title>A Look Back on Grief Counseling | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840137/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840137/</guid><description>Podcast Description As Jenna and Angela prepare for Season 5 of The Office, Office Ladies takes a look back at Grief Counseling. This episode starts off with some real life bird trouble, and we get some special audio treats from Mindy Kaling and the episode writer herself, Jen Celotta. Then we dig into chip rankings, we clear up a fan theory around Ed Truck’s death, and we find out who’s been moving the conference table.</description></item><item><title>Goodbye Toby, Part 2 | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840138/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840138/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we finish breaking down Goodbye Toby. During Toby’s goodbye party, Michael tries to get closer to Holly but finds himself being pulled back to Jan after discovering some big news that involves a pro tennis player. Meanwhile, an unexpected proposal happens. Jenna and Angela give Toby a “Show Bible Goodbye”, Angela shares how she almost didn’t make it to set for a very important scene and a couple of Michael’s parody songs are brought to life!</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode: Monday Motivation | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840139/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today is an extra dose of Office Ladies for your Monday! The theme is “What keeps you motivated and moving?” Jenna and Angela break down their friendship, what led them to make this podcast and how Office Ladies comes together each week. This episode is jammed packed with daily rituals that help get the ladies through their week, more Office casting stories and even a best friends quiz! Kick your week off right with this Monday Motivation episode.</description></item><item><title>Goodbye Toby, Part 1 | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840140/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we’re breaking down Goodbye Toby. To kick off this two part episode, Paul Lieberstein sent in audio clips to talk about what it was like to write himself off the show and introduce Holly Flax, played by Amy Ryan. When Toby has his last day at Dunder Mifflin, Michael insists on throwing him a huge going away party. Angela Martin scoffs at the idea, so Phyllis steps in.</description></item><item><title>Job Fair | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840141/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we’re breaking down Job Fair. Michael, Pam, Oscar and Darryl set up a booth at Valley View High School’s Job Fair in hopes of finding a new intern. Jim, Andy and Kevin golf with a potential client. Jenna and Angela speculate what a crossover episode between The Office and Monk would have been like, a fan gives a theory on why Pam skipped volleyball during PE and the ladies reveal which Office castmember is really good at golf.</description></item><item><title>Did I Stutter? | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840142/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840142/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down Did I Stutter? When Stanley snaps at Michael, Michael must stand up for himself as Stanley&amp;rsquo;s manager. Meanwhile Dwight buys Andy’s car, and Pam has to forgo contact lenses and wear her backup glasses to work. Angela rocks her original Did I Stutter? shooting draft, Jenna does a deep dive on Mad Libs and the ladies reveal The Office writing staff’s mantra: “small, real, relatable”.</description></item><item><title>Night Out | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840143/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840143/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down Night Out. In pursuit of finding the love of his life, Michael clup-hops with Ryan and Dwight in New York City. Meanwhile, the rest of the Dunder Mifflin crew gets locked in the parking lot. Terry Carnation, host of the podcast Dark Air, reads today’s episode summary and we hear from Noel Petok on what it was like to play Ryan’s friend, Troy. Angela gives us the history of the slow clap, Kate Flannery sends in an audio clip about what it was like getting hit in the head with that football and Jenna gives great advice on how to avoid a UTI.</description></item><item><title>Chair Model | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840144/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840144/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down Chair Model. After a disastrous dinner party, Michael is single and finds himself falling in love with a chair model from an office supply catalog. Meanwhile Kevin and Andy fight to get their parking spaces back from a construction project by confronting the Five Families. We hear from Paul Faust who actually played himself as one of the heads of the Five Families. Jenna spots a sparkling Michael accessory, Creed Bratton gives theories on why the character Creed was trying to score three office chairs, and Angela reveals something pretty special about the chair she’s been using to record Office Ladies.</description></item><item><title>Happy Spring Break and A Look Back on Booze Cruise with Greg Daniels | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840145/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840145/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s Spring Break and what better way to enjoy the week off than with Booze Cruise!? Take a trip down memory lane to when Jenna and Angela sat down with living legend Greg Daniels (The Office, Upload, Star Force). Jenna, Angela and Greg break down this episode together and Greg brought his own notecards! They chat about creating the U.S. version of The Office, Brenda from corporate, and Greg shines a light on the Kelly to Mindy transition.</description></item><item><title>Dinner Party | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840146/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840146/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down Dinner Party! Michael finally outsmarts Jim and Pam forcing them to come over to his condo for dinner. Steve Carell reads this week’s summary, and we hear from Melora Hardin, John Krasinski, Rainn Wilson, Ed Helms, Beth Grant and director Paul Feig on what it was like to be a part of this infamous episode. The ladies also discuss the writer’s strike, which scene was the hardest to get through without laughing and a gassy car incident.</description></item><item><title>The Deposition | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840147/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840147/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down The Deposition. When Jan sues Dunder Mifflin, she brings in Michael as a witness which to no surprise, doesn’t go well. Back at the office, Kelly smack talks Pam when Jim loses to Darryl at ping pong. Angela shares how her kitchen table has been turned into a ping pong table, Jenna looks up the difference between “trash talk” and “smack talk” in the Merriam Webster dictionary and the ladies discuss a missed storyline simply labeled “Dwight gets stuck in the wall”.</description></item><item><title>Survivor Man | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840148/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840148/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down Survivor Man. When Michael is excluded from Ryan’s corporate camping trip, Michael ventures out into the woods and goes on his own solo camping adventure. Meanwhile, Jim tries to consolidate the office’s birthdays. The ladies break down Dwight’s menagerie of weapons, they talk about using tiny potatoes for bird eggs and Angela gets personal about birthday cakes. This episode is like a montage of birthday celebrations and you’re invited!</description></item><item><title>Branch Wars | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840149/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840149/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down Branch Wars. When Karen tries to poach Stanley to come work for the Dunder Mifflin Utica branch, Michael, Dwight and Jim, against his will, slap on some fakey ‘staches and go to Utica to prank Karen. Meanwhile back at the office, it’s the Finer Things Club! Adam Jamal Craig (NCIS: Los Angeles) sends in clips to share his experience of playing Rolando, the Utica receptionist.</description></item><item><title>Local Ad | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840150/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840150/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down Local Ad. Director Jason Reitman sends in clips about his experience directing this great episode. The ladies talk about Michael getting the entire office to shoot their own Dunder Mifflin commercial, as Dwight deals with his breakup with Angela by retreating further into his Second (Second) Life. Jenna does a deep dive on earworms, the ladies make crossover connections that all seem to lead to the TV show, Monk, and Angela shares why she had to be superimposed onto the rooftop scene.</description></item><item><title>Revisited with Randall Einhorn | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840151/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840151/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re taking a Second Drink of the second half of Season 3. To kick off this Revisited, we are joined by cinematographer and director, Randall Einhorn! Randall discusses what it was like to shoot The Office, direct episodes and the invention of the pooty scooty. Afterwards, Jenna and Angela answer more fan questions and go over everything we missed from Back from Vacation to The Job. We learn about a Spam museum, we hear from Jackie Debatin who played Elizabeth the Stripper, and we have some Keanu Reeves crossover with The Office.</description></item><item><title>Money Part 2 | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840152/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840152/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we finish breaking down Money. Jenna and Angela geek out over fancy porta potties as we watch Michael DECLARE BANKRUPTCY in an effort to deal with his money problems. We’re also introduced to a new office couple, Kelly and Darryl. Jenna and Angela discuss the hardest word to spell as a new parent, Jenna gets on a panty line soapbox and Angela discovers a dark truth involving John Wick.</description></item><item><title>Money Part 1 | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840153/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840153/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down Money. To kick off this two part episode, Jenna and Angela discuss how they would love to visit Angela’s family farm together, along with giving a very big “Thank You” to their Office Ladies fans for winning iHeart Radio’s “Podcast of the Year”! The ladies talk about how Michael is having money troubles and has to take a second job as a telemarketer, while Jim and Pam have their first getaway together at Dwight’s agritourism Bed and Breakfast on Schrute Farms.</description></item><item><title>Launch Party Part 2 | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840154/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840154/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we finish breaking down Launch Party. The ladies start off by giving the full deep dive behind Pam’s reception plants. Guest star Kevin McHale shares what it was like to work on the set of The Office at the age of 17 as the Pizza Delivery Kid from Pizza by Alfredo’s, otherwise known as home of the hot circle of garbage. Angela is Jenna’s plus one at the Emmys, we have another roof dinner date with Jim and Pam, and Jen Celotta talks about how Andy ended up serenading Angela with a cappella.</description></item><item><title>Launch Party Part 1 | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840155/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840155/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down Launch Party. To kick off this two part episode, Jenna and Angela, with the help of Jen Celotta, give an exclusive behind-the-scenes breakdown of how the famous DVD-logo-in-the-corner cold open was shot. This reminds Angela of some juicy parking garage drama. We hear from Kate Flannery on how Meredith’s cast was made and Jenna realizes that Paul Reiser may be her soulmate. Angela tracks Michael Scott’s short jokes and with the help of Phyllis, we all learn how and how not to deal with difficult people.</description></item><item><title>Dunder Mifflin Infinity Pt 2 | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840156/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840156/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we finish breaking down Dunder Mifflin Infinity. We start off by answering some fan questions from the Office Ladies’ mail bag, including the scoop on where some mics were hidden around The Office set. A fan writes in to tell the ladies how the Office Ladies show inspired her to ask for more time off at work and she got it! Then the ladies break down Michael and Dwight’s quest to win over past clients with gift baskets, causing Angela to confess to her own basket obsession.</description></item><item><title>A New Years Message from your friends at The Office and Halloween with Creed Bratton | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840157/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840157/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Jenna and Angela, along with some very special friends at The Office wish you all a very happy New Year. And to kick-off the New Year right, we&amp;rsquo;re giving you the Halloween episode w/ Creed Bratton.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Happy Holidays And A Look Back At An Office Christmas | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840158/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840158/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Jenna and Angela wish everyone the happiest of holidays. Angela also has a Christmas crafting brag. Since it&amp;rsquo;s Christmas this week, we thought we&amp;rsquo;d give you the Christmas Party episode to help get you into the Yankee Swap spirit.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dunder Mifflin Infinity Pt 1 | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840159/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840159/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down Dunder Mifflin Infinity. To kick off this two-part episode, Angela announces herself as &amp;lsquo;Kinseypedia&amp;rsquo; for this episode and gets the inside scoop on the Dunder Mifflin Infinity website. Then, we discuss Toby outing Jim and Pam&amp;rsquo;s relationship to the whole office, we learn how to make a cat look feral, and we get a major Old Tech Alert with Ryan&amp;rsquo;s mandated Blackberry&amp;rsquo;s. Finally, we discuss some very funny Kelly-Ryan drama, Jan&amp;rsquo;s trendy outfit that is not too dissimilar to something Jenna may have worn, and Creed helps us answer fan questions about his hair dye job in this episode.</description></item><item><title>Fun Run Pt 2 | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840160/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840160/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we finish breaking down Fun Run. We start off with Jenna giving us the inside scoop on why we got so many big one hour episodes to start off Season 4, we get a Jenna and Angela BFF story for the books, and an amazing Fun Run wardrobe breakdown from wardrobe designer Carey Bennet. Then, we chat rabies quilts, answer everything you wanted to know about nipple chafing, and we get a &amp;lsquo;fan soapbox&amp;rsquo; with an interesting take on who&amp;rsquo;s responsible for the death of Sprinkles.</description></item><item><title>Fun Run Pt 1 | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840161/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840161/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down Fun Run. To kick off this two part episode we are joined by the hilarious, Kate Flannery. Kate shares her memories from this episode, her time on The Office, and gives us insight into what it was like to do most of her own stunts. Then, we answer fan questions about Pam&amp;rsquo;s questionable internet search, the changes to her hair and wardrobe, and of course we chat about what is going on with Jim and Pam.</description></item><item><title>Revisited: Season 1 | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840162/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840162/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re taking a Second Drink of our Season 1 episodes. We&amp;rsquo;ll be answering more fan questions and going over everything we missed from The Pilot all the way through to Hot Girl. Jenna tries to put to rest what we have dubbed &amp;lsquo;shredder gate&amp;rsquo;, we get a great Bob Barker background catch, and we chat with Prop Master, Phil Shea, who helps us answer two big fan questions from the Basketball and Healthcare episodes.</description></item><item><title>The Job Part 2 | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840163/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840163/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we finish breaking down The Job. We start off on the streets of New York with Jim and Karen and get some great background catches, and Angela does a fun deep dive on the &amp;ldquo;bar that used to be a Church&amp;rdquo; mentioned by Jim. Then, we discuss the very funny scene&amp;rsquo;s back in Scranton where Pam accepts Dwight&amp;rsquo;s offer to be the Secret Assistant to the Regional Manager and we get the introduction of the Schrute Bucks.</description></item><item><title>The Job Part 1 w/ Paul Lieberstein | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840164/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840164/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re breaking down The Job. To kick off this 2-part episode we are joined by Paul Lieberstein (Toby from The Office, Space Force), who shares his memories from The Office, his “acting school”, and what characters he misses writing for the most. Then, we answer fan questions about Jim’s ‘big haircut’, and we examine all the ways Pam is enjoying her newfound confidence. Finally, we dig into the hilarious ‘Creed Thoughts’ blog, and we chat about Jan’s new boob job and everything that went into making them look realistic.</description></item><item><title>Beach Games | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840165/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840165/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down Beach Games. Writer, Jen Celotta sends us her memories from this episode. From the &amp;lsquo;Survivor&amp;rsquo; theme to the challenges that went into shooting Andy floating away in the Sumo suit, we get all of the behind the scenes details! Then, we dive into the hilarious hot dog eating contest and Angela schools us with her basketball knowledge. Finally, we answer fan questions about the hot coal walking scene, and discuss Pam&amp;rsquo;s new found courage to tell the truth to Jim.</description></item><item><title>Women's Appreciation | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840166/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840166/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down Women&amp;rsquo;s Appreciation. Jenna and Angela start this episode off with some fun Fast Facts about where the idea for this episode came from, and answer all your questions about what it was like filming in that mall. Then, we discuss Dwight&amp;rsquo;s solutions to catching a flasher, and we get Angela&amp;rsquo;s grandmother&amp;rsquo;s review of Michael Scott and how long she lasted watching this episode. Finally, we hop into Meredith&amp;rsquo;s van and hit the mall, discuss Kate Flannery&amp;rsquo;s stunt driving, and chat about keeping restrooms clean for everyone.</description></item><item><title>Product Recall | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840167/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840167/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down Product Recall. We start this episode off with some Bears, Beets, and Battlestar Galactica, and answer fan questions about this very funny, very quoted cold open. Then, we get a historical deep dive on watermarks and paper making, we chat about Michael and Creed’s different versions of damage control, and Angela reveals her all time favorite line from The Office. Finally, we get some on-set memories from Shira Scott Astrof, the actress who played Andy&amp;rsquo;s young girlfriend, and we come full circle with this episode&amp;rsquo;s tag where Dwight&amp;rsquo;s plan of imitating Jim totally backfires.</description></item><item><title>Safety Training | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840168/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840168/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down Safety Training. And in lieu of fast facts we have one big Office Ladies fact, it&amp;rsquo;s our ONE YEAR BIRTHDAY! We take a moment to celebrate and the Ladies answer a few general fan questions. Then, we get into the episode with Andy&amp;rsquo;s return, and we dig into the hilarious scene with Darryl, Michael and the baler. Finally, the ladies explain a Netflix old tech alert, Kentapedia (Kent Zbornak) gives us some good info about the watermelons on the roof scene, and yes, Creed did bite into that potato.</description></item><item><title>The Negotiation w/ David Denman | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840169/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840169/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down The Negotiation, and we couldn&amp;rsquo;t do this episode without an interview with the amazing David Denman. David shares his memories from this episode, saying goodbye to the show, and we get his take on a potential Roy and Angela relationship. Then, the ladies deep dive on the art of negotiation, chat about Daryl&amp;rsquo;s negotiation strategy and Micheal&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;ladies clothes&amp;rdquo;. Finally, we get another Heartbreak In the Breakroom moment with a song brought to us by Josh Compton, we take a fun movie tangent, and we discuss that emotional scene between Pam and Roy.</description></item><item><title>Cocktails | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840170/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840170/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down Cocktails. We start this episode off by discussing your questions about David Wallace&amp;rsquo;s house, the hilarity of Jan and Michael going public, and Jenna shares some fun memories from her journal. Then, we get another great fan catch about The Office&amp;rsquo;s loose mentions of Casual Fridays, we chat about the &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t call me Pammy&amp;rdquo; moment, and we get some fun Poor Richard&amp;rsquo;s trivia. Finally, grab a snack for your cocktail because we discuss what kind of food we like to bring to a party, and we try to figure out what the weird thing is in the background of Michael&amp;rsquo;s talking head.</description></item><item><title>Business School | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840171/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840171/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down Business School. We reached out to writer Brent Forrester, to get his memories about this episode and what it was like working with director Joss Whedon (Buffy The Vampire Slayer, Avengers). Then we dig into everything you want to know about filming those hilarious scenes with Michael at Ryan&amp;rsquo;s business school, and we get some amazing insights from Brent about what went into picking Pam&amp;rsquo;s watercolor paintings for her art show.</description></item><item><title>Revisited w/ Dave Rogers | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840172/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840172/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re going back and revisiting the Gay Witch Hunt through the A Beninhana Christmas episodes of Office Ladies podcast. We go over things we may have missed the first time around and answer more of your questions. We start with a big boat correction, and we get a wonderful rendition of Heartbreak In The Breakroom by the amazing singer-songwriter Rhett Miller. Then, we&amp;rsquo;re joined by long time The Office editor, Dave Rogers.</description></item><item><title>Phyllis' Wedding w/ Ken Whittingham | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840173/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840173/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down Phyllis&amp;rsquo; Wedding. We are joined by this episode&amp;rsquo;s director, Ken Whittingham, who shares his memories of this episode and his time on The Office. And we aren&amp;rsquo;t stopping there, the shimmy queen herself, Phyllis Smith, sends in audio memories for this episode as well. We jump in by discussing Pam clocking Phyllis using all of her wedding ideas, we get a &amp;lsquo;shallow dive&amp;rsquo; on Ivan Pavlov, and we get a Dwight talking head that will be important later in the show series.</description></item><item><title>Ben Franklin | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840174/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840174/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down Ben Franklin. We start things off with some facts about the real Benjamin Franklin, and we get some audio memories from the incredible Andy Daly (Review, VEEP) who played the Ben Franklin impersonator in this episode. Then, Angela debunks Prima Nocta, Jenna answers everyones burning questions about Pam&amp;rsquo;s hair color, and we chat about the &amp;lsquo;guy shower&amp;rsquo; down in the warehouse. Finally, we get a &amp;lsquo;proof of cold&amp;rsquo; fan catch, Jenna does a deep dive on Elizabeth&amp;rsquo;s no secrets quote to Michael, and we end with some more memories from Andy Daly.</description></item><item><title>The Return w/ Ed Helms | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840175/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840175/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down The Return. This is the second episode in the two episode arc with Traveling Salesmen, and you know we have more memories from Greg Daniels for you. We&amp;rsquo;re also joined by the hilarious Ed Helms, who shares his memories of this episode, including Andy&amp;rsquo;s ringtone and punching that wall. Then, we talk about Oscar&amp;rsquo;s return to Dunder Mifflin, Dwight working at Staples, and we get another fan rendition of Heartbreak In The Breakroom by Carmen and Camille.</description></item><item><title>Traveling Salesmen | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840176/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840176/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down Traveling Salesmen, the first episode in a two episode arch directed by Greg Daniels (Upload, Space Force). Greg sends in some amazing memories from this episode, the ladies give a little TV production crash course, and discuss those really fun character pairings. Then we get a hilarious laundry call back from The Coup (or should we say laundry and betrayal?), and the ladies share their memories of those Pam and Angela scenes in the coffee shop.</description></item><item><title>Back From Vacation | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840177/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840177/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down Back From Vacation and we reached out to some of our favorite The Office cast and crew for the inside scoop on this episode. First, Kentapedia (Kent Zbornak) and Phil Shea help us answer fan questions about Michael and Jan&amp;rsquo;s vacation photo, and Kim Ferry sends in her memories of creating Michaels beaded vacation hair. Then Angela does some amazing detective work to discover just what was written on that Post-it note on Angela Martin&amp;rsquo;s partition, and we head to the warehouse inventory-luau and discuss what Spam is made of.</description></item><item><title>A Benihana Christmas w/ Rashida Jones and Jen Celotta | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840178/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840178/</guid><description>Podcast Description Break out the nutcrackers and fire up the karaoke because we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down A Benihana Christmas. This is a supersize episode and we&amp;rsquo;re bringing on not one but TWO amazing guests! Actress Rashida Jones and writer Jen Celotta join us to share their memories and insights of this episode. We deep dive on the history of Benihana, and we talk about The Party Planning Committee v. The Committee to Plan Parties.</description></item><item><title>The Convict | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840179/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840179/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down The Convict. We reached out to this episode&amp;rsquo;s director, Jeffrey Blitz, and actor Wayne Wilderson, to get their memories and insights of this episode. We start with a haunted hotel story, the ladies discuss Pig Latin and Jenna explains the language of Ab. Then we get the origins of Prison Mike, and the scoop on how hard it was to get through those conference room scenes without breaking or sweating.</description></item><item><title>The Merger | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840180/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840180/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down The Merger, and the ladies reach out to director Ken Whittingham, and writer Brent Forrester, who share their memories and insights on this episode. Then we chat about Pam&amp;rsquo;s plants and homemade sexy sweater, and we get the lowdown on that Staples shredder in the original airing of this episode. Finally, we get a little heartbreak in the breakroom (and maybe a new country song?</description></item><item><title>Casino Night Revisited w/ Ken Kwapis | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840181/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840181/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re shaking things up and revisiting Casino Night! We&amp;rsquo;re answering more fan questions and covering things we missed from that episode like, Mindy&amp;rsquo;s hair extensions, why some actors share their characters&amp;rsquo; names, and we clear up the My Buddy - Kid Sister debacle. We&amp;rsquo;re also joined by Casino Night director and early The Office visionary himself, Ken Kwapis. Ken gives us his The Office origin story, chats about his favorite moments from the show, and helps us dig a little deeper into Casino Night.</description></item><item><title>Branch Closing w/ Charles Esten | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840182/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840182/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down Branch Closing and we have a lot to cover. We have to start by mentioning this is the episode that spawned the famous Michael Scott &amp;ldquo;This Is The Worst&amp;rdquo; meme, we dig into those Angela and Roy flirtations, and get into the intricacies of low-pony tails. Then, we get a great fan catch at David Wallace&amp;rsquo;s house, and we find out Jim is coming back to Scranton.</description></item><item><title>Diwali w/ Mindy Kaling | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840183/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840183/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down Diwali! And we couldn&amp;rsquo;t even think about breaking down this episode without checking in with the amazing triple threat herself, Mindy Kaling! Mindy walks us through how she came to work on The Office, what it was like for her to be able to pitch and write Diwali, and explains why they cast her actual parents in this episode. Then Jenna and Angela dig into this episode even deeper covering Kevin&amp;rsquo;s sweaty feet, and what went into filming and costuming the Diwali festivities.</description></item><item><title>Initiation w/ B.J. Novak and Rainn Wilson | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840184/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840184/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down Initiation, our journey begins now. This episode can really only be defined as &amp;ldquo;the works&amp;rdquo;, we get introduced to Pretzel Day, Schrute Farms, and Mose and we&amp;rsquo;re going to talk about them all. We check in at Stamford and that squeaky chair and a fun Jim-Pam background catch. Then we explore Stanley&amp;rsquo;s love of Pretzel Day and the unexpected bond between him and Michael.</description></item><item><title>Grief Counseling | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840185/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840185/</guid><description>Podcast Description What do we know about this week? We know that this week, we are breaking down Grief Counseling. We start this episode with some real life bird trouble, and we get some special audio treats from Mindy Kaling and the episode writer herself, Jen Celotta. Then we dig into chip rankings, we clear up a fan theory around Ed Trucks death, and we find out who&amp;rsquo;s been moving the conference table.</description></item><item><title>The Coup | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840186/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840186/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down The Coup, so you better get ready for a fashion show, fashion show, fashion show at lunch! We start off with Movie Monday, Rainn Wilson shares a few memories about this episode, and a fan submits an interesting theory about Jim&amp;rsquo;s shirt sleeves. Then we talk about Stamford and Call of Duty, we get Outlet Mall deep dives, and of course we couldn&amp;rsquo;t forget Crentist the Dentist.</description></item><item><title>The Convention | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840187/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840187/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pass those freedom fries because this week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down The Convention. We can&amp;rsquo;t start this episode without checking in with Kentapedia (Kent Zbornak), to get the inside scoop on how the crew pulled off a full paper convention, and Jenna gives us a missed Dwight - Gareth meeting. Then we get a fun fan callback to those pesky bugs on set, Jenna&amp;rsquo;s got some beef and Angela reveals she watched The Edge!</description></item><item><title>Gay Witch Hunt w/ Oscar Nuñez | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840188/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840188/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down Gay Witch Hunt. This is the Season 3 premiere of The Office and there is a lot to talk about. Jim is no longer in Scranton and we meet two new characters, Andy Bernard and Karen Filippelli! Of course the ladies reach out to Ed Helms and Rashida Jones to get some behind the scenes tidbits from them. Then the ladies out Toby for outing Oscar, Angela shares a silly nickname from college, and Jenna discovers the amazing all female acapella group, Nothing But Treble.</description></item><item><title>Casino Night w/ John Krasinski | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840189/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840189/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lady Luck roll those dice because we’re breaking down Casino Night written by Steve Carell! We start this JAM packed episode by explaining how Steve ended up writing this episode, we chat about Pam&amp;rsquo;s wink to Jim, and Jenna shares some behind the scenes tidbits about the Scrantonicity video. Then we get some fan catches about Pam&amp;rsquo;s casino night dress paired with her watch, and that Dwangela slap heard around the world.</description></item><item><title>Conflict Resolution | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840190/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840190/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down Conflict Resolution from the comfort of our own closets. The baby poster returns, Jenna shares some amazing insights on the talking heads, both ladies talk about the magazine photoshoots with their cats, and we discover whose names are on those plaques hung all around Dunder Mifflin. Then the ladies wonder if &amp;lsquo;save the dates&amp;rsquo; are worth the trouble, and we get into Michael&amp;rsquo;s conflict resolution style, and we get some major Pam sass.</description></item><item><title>Drug Testing | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840191/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840191/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down Drug Testing&amp;hellip;JINX! Buy Me a Coke! We start off this episode by checking in with Kentapedia (Kent Zbornack) to get some facts straight on the shooting schedule, Jenna gives some Micheal Scott trivia, and we get a little deductive sass from Dwangela. Then we get into Micheals fear of being drug tested, Dwight&amp;rsquo;s hilarious struggle with helping Micheal pass his drug test, and Jenna does a deep dive on what could possibly make your urine green.</description></item><item><title>Michael's Birthday | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840192/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840192/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down Michael&amp;rsquo;s Birthday! We chat Micheal&amp;rsquo;s excitment and tantrums on his big day, Angela&amp;rsquo;s work with a stunt skater, and we get the scoop from Kentapedia (Kent Zbornak) about all the locations they shot at for this episode. Then, baby, we get some OG PPC moments, Jenna describes a wild present she received from her mom, and we break down some Dwangela sass. Finally, we get some good Jim and Pam flirtation, Angela explains how hard it was to film the scene with Kevin on the ice, and we end the episode with a hilarious deleted scene.</description></item><item><title>Take Your Daughter To Work Day | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840193/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840193/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down Take Your Daughter To Work Day, so let&amp;rsquo;s keep it G-rated, okay? The ladies give some background info about all the child actors on set that day and chat about Stanley&amp;rsquo;s daughter flirting with Ryan, and Pam&amp;rsquo;s struggle to befriend just one kid. Then the ladies give history lessons on Shaggy Peter and the Green Sleeves song that ends in a fun revelation, and we get an update on Game of Thrones.</description></item><item><title>Dwight's Speech | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840194/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840194/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down Dwight&amp;rsquo;s Speech. Jenna hits up The Office Line Producer, Kent Zbornak for some behind the scenes info on who exactly is in the audience during Dwight&amp;rsquo;s speech. Then the ladies track the thermostat fight, Pam&amp;rsquo;s wedding invites causes some &amp;ldquo;Ryan Sass&amp;rdquo;, and Angela tries to explain Lord of The Rings to Jenna. Finally, the ladies dive deep into the big speech from it&amp;rsquo;s historical inspirations to how many takes it took Rainn to nail it, and they explain that wizard appearance.</description></item><item><title>Valentines Day with Andy Buckley | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840195/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840195/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pack your day bags because we&amp;rsquo;re headed to New York! This week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down Valentines Day, and we are joined by the wonderful Andy Buckley (The Office, Veep, Avenue 5). Andy chats with Jenna and Angela about his time as a stock broker, how he got the part of the David Wallace, and his surprise to be a recurring character. Then Jenna does a deep dive on Sbarro Pizza and Angela gives us some insider info on 30 Rockefeller Plaza, and the ladies ponder the best and worst Valentine&amp;rsquo;s gifts.</description></item><item><title>Boys and Girls | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840196/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840196/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ladies, please report to the conference room, boys to the bowels of the office! That&amp;rsquo;s right, this week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down Boys and Girls, an episode of The Office based of a pitch straight from Jenna and Angela themselves! We chat about those classic Angela Martin moments, alpha wombs vs beta wombs, and do you call Jim and Pam JAM, or PB&amp;amp;J? Finally, we talk about Michael wrecking the warehouse, Jan union busting, and Pam and Jims first fight.</description></item><item><title>The Carpet | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840197/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840197/</guid><description>Podcast Description We have a real &amp;ldquo;who done it&amp;rdquo; episode for y&amp;rsquo;all! That right, this week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down The Carpet, and you better buckle up because we have officially reached FULL MINDY! Angela gets a little edgy talking about the TV show Fear Factor, and we answer the question &amp;ldquo;why are the warehouse guys changing the carpet?&amp;quot;. We also get some Michael Sass, Jenna does a deep dive on Rock 107, and of course we can’t end the episode without talking about those Pam voicemails.</description></item><item><title>The Secret | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840198/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840198/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;re starting our spring cleaning early this week and breaking down The Secret! Jenna and Angela chat about Steve Carrell&amp;rsquo;s charming Golden Globe speech from 2006 and Angela notices it&amp;rsquo;s another Friday that&amp;rsquo;s not a Casual Friday. And of course the ladies cover the hilarity of Micheal&amp;rsquo;s struggle to bond with Jim over &amp;ldquo;the secret&amp;rdquo;, Dwight spying on Oscar, and hold the chicken breast, because Jenna does a deep dive on Hooters.</description></item><item><title>The Injury | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840199/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840199/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hold on to your George Foreman grills and watch your feet because this week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down The Injury episode of The Office. The ladies chat about Dwight and Pam&amp;rsquo;s blossoming friendship, Michael&amp;rsquo;s hilarious talking head, and what&amp;rsquo;s with the sofa in the conference room?! Then Jenna reveals that yes, that really was Steve Carell&amp;rsquo;s foot, and Angela reads from her journal about that Dwangela moment in the breakroom.</description></item><item><title>Booze Cruise w/ Greg Daniels | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840200/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840200/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lake Wallenpaupack, listeners! We&amp;rsquo;ve made it to the Booze Cruise episode of The Office and we&amp;rsquo;re joined by living legend, Greg Daniels (The Office, The Simpsons, King of the Hill, Upload, Star Force). Jenna, Angela and Greg break down this episode together and Greg brought his own notecards! They chat about creating the U.S. version of The Office, Brenda from corporate, and Greg shines a light on the Kelly to Mindy transition.</description></item><item><title>Christmas Party | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840201/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840201/</guid><description>Podcast Description PPC, Yankee Swap, and the Tea Pot, that&amp;rsquo;s right, this week we&amp;rsquo;re breaking down the Christmas Party episode of The Office, and it&amp;rsquo;s a big one! The ladies chat about British director Charles McDougall coming on for this episode, the process behind choosing the right gift for Jim to give Pam, and &amp;ldquo;what are the right type of lights for a Christmas tree?&amp;rdquo;. Then, Jenna and Angela break out their old journals for more insights into what was going on when they were filming this episode, and of course we couldn&amp;rsquo;t not talk about that iPod and Michael&amp;rsquo;s famous Yankee Swap line.</description></item><item><title>Email Surveillance w/ Ken Jeong | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840202/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840202/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week the Office Ladies break down Email Surveillance. They are joined by a member of Michael&amp;rsquo;s improv group, and Office Ladies super fan, Ken Jeong (Community, The Masked Singer). Ken shares is memories from set, and his love of The Office. We are introduced to the beginnings of the Dwight and Angela romance (aka Dwangela). Then, Jenna and Angela chat about Pam in Jim&amp;rsquo;s bedroom, double posters, those amazing karaoke scenes.</description></item><item><title>Performance Review w/ Larry Wilmore | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840203/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840203/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Office Ladies we break down the Performance Review episode of the Office. We&amp;rsquo;ve confirmed &amp;lsquo;Chunk It&amp;rsquo; is an acceptable saying and Jenna and Angela share behind the scenes info about the famous fitness orb cold open. Then Larry Wilmore joins us to talk about his time working on The Office and playing Mr. Brown in Diversity Day. Finally, we chat about Dwight&amp;rsquo;s Motley Crue hallway moment and Jan&amp;rsquo;s big speech at the elevator.</description></item><item><title>The Client w/ Melora Hardin | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840204/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840204/</guid><description>Podcast Description I want my baby-back, baby-back, baby-back&amp;hellip; This week Jenna and Angela break down The Client episode of The Office, and Mrs. Michael Scarn herself (Cathrine Zeta-Jones) reads the summary for this week&amp;rsquo;s episode. (Yes! It&amp;rsquo;s really her!) There&amp;rsquo;s big news in our &amp;ldquo;Mindy&amp;rsquo;s Hair Watch&amp;rdquo;, and the ladies call up Melora Hardin to chat about those hilarious scenes in the Chili&amp;rsquo;s with Steve Carell and Tim Meadows.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Fight | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840205/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840205/</guid><description>Podcast Description Palm Reading, Armageddon and the 10 Rules of Karate. This can only mean one thing, we&amp;rsquo;ve reached The Fight episode of The Office. Jenna and Angela talk about the amazing Lance Krall, who played Sensei Ira, wonder where that door next to the urinal goes to, and reveal Micheal had two offices for shooting scenes. We want you to be afraid of how much you love this episode.</description></item><item><title>Halloween w/ Creed Bratton | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840206/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840206/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Jenna and Angela welcome their Office co-star and Angela&amp;rsquo;s real-life neighbor, Creed Bratton, to the pod to discuss the Halloween episode. Creed talks about memorizing his first big scene on The Office, and his wild life as a musician. Then Jenna, Angela and Creed discuss the hierarchy of cat whiskers, Three Hole Punch Jim, PPC category drama, and how to complete a successful air high-five. We end this episode with new song from Creed, called The Ride.</description></item><item><title>The Fire | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840207/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840207/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dunder Mifflin, this is Pam&amp;hellip; That&amp;rsquo;s right, The Office Ladies are back and covering The Fire episode of The Office. This week Jenna and Angela discuss Woofle Ball vs Wiffle Ball, what their Deserted Island movies would be, and what is a Cheese Pita anyways? Finally, it is declared, Ryan started the fire and Legally Blonde is a great movie.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Happy New Year! | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840208/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840208/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Office Ladies are taking this week off, but we have a special New Years Eve memory shared by the one and only, Creed Bratton. We&amp;rsquo;ll be back January 8th with The Fire. For more Office Ladies content, head over to Stitcher Premium for the Office Ladies Candy Bag episodes, where Jenna and Angela answer more fan questions. For a free month of Stitcher Premium use code OFFICE.</description></item><item><title>Christmas Greetings! | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840209/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840209/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Office Ladies are taking this week off to celebrate the holiday with their families, and Jenna is making a fancy panettone! We&amp;rsquo;ll be back January 8th with The Fire.
For more Office Ladies content, head over to Stitcher Premium for the Office Ladies Candy Bag episodes, where Jenna and Angela answer more fan questions. For a free month of Stitcher Premium use code OFFICE.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Office Olympics w/ Paul Feig | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840210/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840210/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Jenna is on a cleanse and Angela falls into an &amp;lsquo;Amish In The City&amp;rsquo; hole, but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t stop them from covering this week&amp;rsquo;s episode, Office Olympics. The ladies discuss how the animated series, King Of The Hill, inspired Office Olympics, and they take a call from this episodes director, Paul Feig (Freaks and Geeks, Last Christmas). Paul chats about shooting in Micheal&amp;rsquo;s condo, the most he&amp;rsquo;s ever laughed on set, and the intricacies of picking the famed yogurt lid medals.</description></item><item><title>Sexual Harassment | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840211/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840211/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;ve made it to the infamous Sexual Harassment episode of The Office, written by B.J. Novak and directed by Ken Kwapis. The ladies talk about the inner workings of picking out a blow up doll, Angela has an issue with Pam&amp;rsquo;s mom, and we finally meet the one and only, Todd Packer. This weeks episode will definitely leave you satisfied&amp;hellip;That&amp;rsquo;s What She Said!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Dundies | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840212/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840212/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fun-raiser vs Fundraiser, Second Drink, and Hottest In The Office. All of this can only mean one thing, we&amp;rsquo;ve made it to The Dundies episode of The Office! The Ladies talk about the origin of The Dundies, Jenna shares a mishap from The 40 Year Old Virgin premiere, and the biggest question of them all is answered, &amp;ldquo;Is this Pam and Jim&amp;rsquo;s first kiss?&amp;rdquo;. We hope you feel God in this podcast tonight.</description></item><item><title>Happy Thanksgiving Week! | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840213/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840213/</guid><description>Podcast Description Office Ladies is taking the week off for the Thanksgiving Holiday. We&amp;rsquo;ll be back next week with The Dundies.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hot Girl | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840214/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840214/</guid><description>Podcast Description We wrap up season one of The Office with Hot Girl, co-starring Amy Adams and written by Mindy Kaling. Jenna and Angela share an Amy Adams story that may involve Meryl Streep, and is Jenna an international poker champion? Later the ladies explore the disappearing - reappearing E.T. on Jim&amp;rsquo;s desk and answer some burning fan questions about this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Basketball | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840215/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840215/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we have a really special episode. Not only do we head down to the warehouse for a &amp;lsquo;friendly&amp;rsquo; basketball game and meet Daryl, but this is the episode of The Office Jenna and Angela became real life BFF&amp;rsquo;s! Then the ladies talk about real life injuries and Kevin (Brian Baumgartner) sinking all those baskets. Finally, Jenna reveals the story behind why Pam and Roy have been engaged for so long.</description></item><item><title>The Alliance with Phil Shea | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840216/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840216/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Birthday, Surprise! This week&amp;rsquo;s episode is chock full of goodies. We have the birthday party, the Jim and Dwight alliance, and the introduction to the notorious PPC (Party Planning Committee). Angela has a realization about Dwight&amp;rsquo;s bobblehead collection, and both ladies catch a few continuity errors. Finally, Jenna and Angela call up Phil Shea, Prop Master of The Office, to answer the big questions about that box!</description></item><item><title>Health Care with Rainn Wilson | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840217/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840217/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hot Dog Fingers! The Health Care episode is here! The Ladies kick things off with some Fast Facts, Pam Sass, and Jenna&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Sounds of Scranton&amp;rsquo; soundtrack. Then, the Lion himself, Rainn Wilson (Metaphysical Milkshake Podcast), calls in to discuss this Dwight-centric episode. Rainn reminisces about listing all the fake diseases (Count Choculitis) and being a new dad during the filming of this episode. Check out Rainn Wilson and Reza Aslan&amp;rsquo;s new podcast, Metaphysical Milkshake here https://soulpancake.</description></item><item><title>Diversity Day | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840218/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840218/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Jenna and Angela tackle episode two of The Office. They cover Michael Scott&amp;rsquo;s cringe-worthy jokes, their own harassment training as actors, and how offices all over the country use clips from Diversity Day as examples of bad office behavior. Finally, they reveal the origins of the famed line &amp;ldquo;I will attack you with the North&amp;rdquo;, and beg the question &amp;ldquo;was Angela in the right dressing room for the 2004 World Series?</description></item><item><title>The Pilot | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840219/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840219/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Jenna and Angela start at the beginning and break down The Pilot episode of The Office. The ladies hit you with some Fast Facts, insights from Ricky Gervais, and the origin of Angela&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;cat party&amp;rsquo;. And if you&amp;rsquo;re wondering about secret messages hidden in The Pilot episode, Jenna and Angela break those down as well.
We&amp;rsquo;re not the experts on The Office, you are! If there&amp;rsquo;s anything we missed, or if you have any burning questions you wanted answered about upcoming episodes, please send them to officeladies@earwolf.</description></item><item><title>Office Ladies Trailer | Office Ladies</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6282840220/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6282840220/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join Jenna Fischer and Angela Kinsey as they give you a sneak peak of what&amp;rsquo;s to come. Office Ladies premieres October 16th!
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>