<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Walking The Dog with Emily Dean on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/walking-the-dog-with-emily-dean/</link><description>Recent content in Walking The Dog with Emily Dean on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 01:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/walking-the-dog-with-emily-dean/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tim Peake | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890128/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily and Raymond head to London’s Regent&amp;rsquo;s Park to take a walk with actual astronaut, Tim Peake! Tim chats about his dog Woody, reflects on his childhood dreams and the journey that led him to spending six months on the International Space Station. And, of course, Emily finds out whether Tim thinks Ray would be a good space dog! Tim Peake’s latest book Space: The Human Story is out now published by Penguin.</description></item><item><title>Alastair Campbell | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890001/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890001/</guid><description>Podcast Description To kick off their first show back, Emily and Raymond take a walk with political legend and host of the UK’s biggest podcast, Alastair Campbell. Strolling over London’s Hampstead Heath with his dog Skye, he reflects on his family and childhood, his time at Number 10, how he manages his mental health and what he loves most about The Rest is Politics. He also takes Skye for a dip and bumps into some old friends from his days in politics…</description></item><item><title>Walking The Dog is back! | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dust off your walking boots because Emily and Raymond are back - with the all new Walking The Dog, now releasing episodes weekly. Join writer and broadcaster Emily Dean, with the world&amp;rsquo;s most ridiculous Shih Tzu, Raymond, as they join household names for an extraordinary dog walk. Make sure you&amp;rsquo;re subscribed - so you don&amp;rsquo;t miss the first episode on Tuesday 12th December.
Follow Emily: Instagram - @emilyrebeccadean X - @divine_miss_em</description></item><item><title>Fern Brady | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 18:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890003/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily and Ray went for a walk in Catford with Fern Brady. They chatted about her childhood in Scotland, growing up with undiagnosed Autism and why comedy is the perfect career for her. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tom Allen Returns! | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890004/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily and Ray went to South East London to catch up with Tom Allen. They chat about Tom’s lovely Dad who he sadly lost last year and his new book, Too Much. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Susie Dent | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 17:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890005/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily and Ray headed to the Oxfordshire countryside for a walk with Susie Dent. They chatted about growing up with her love of languages, being the Queen of Dictionary Corner and her podcast, Something Rhymes with Purple.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Martin Kemp Returns! | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890006/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily and Ray went for a stroll with Martin Kemp in Battersea. They chatted about his years in Spandau Ballet, the pressures of fame that came from his time in Eastenders and his new book, Ticket to the World: My 80s Story.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bez | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890007/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily headed to Herefordshire for a walk with Bez and his dogs, Snoop and Yoko. They chatted about how he came to join Happy Mondays, being a first-time dog owner, and his new book, Buzzin’ By Bez. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dawn O’Porter | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890008/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily and Ray took a stroll in Hyde Park with Dawn O’Porter. They chatted about Dawn’s pet history, dealing with grief, meeting her husband, Chris O’Dowd and her new book, Cat Lady. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nick Grimshaw | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890009/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890009/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily and Ray went to North London to meet Nick Grimshaw and his dog, Stinky Blob. They chatted about Grimmy’s childhood in Oldham, his incredible experiences during his radio career and his new memoir, Soft Lad.
Season 2 of Nick&amp;rsquo;s podcast, Dish is is launching in November.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dan Walker | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 08:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890010/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily and Ray headed to Sheffield for a walk with Dan Walker and Winnie the Cockapoo. They chatted about Dan’s journey into broadcasting, his experience on Strictly and his new book, Standing on the Shoulders. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kelvin Fletcher and Liz Fletcher | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890011/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890011/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily and Ray headed to the Peak District to take a stroll with Kelvin Fletcher, Liz Fletcher and their cavapoochon, Ginger. They chatted about how they manage being parents of four, farmers and performers! They also discuss their new book, Fletchers on the Farm. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Gary Lineker Returns! | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 08:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890012/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily and Ray popped to South West London to take stroll with Gary Lineker and his new dog, Filbert. They chatted about Gary bringing Filbert into his life since losing his beloved Labrador, Snoop.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Susannah Constantine | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890013/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily headed to West Sussex for a walk with Susannah Constantine and her dogs Fern and Rocco. They chatted about Susannah’s early life when she dated Princess Margaret’s son, her TV partnership with Trinny Woodall and her new book, Ready for Absolutely Nothing. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Greg James | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 08:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890014/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the first episode of the new series, Emily and Ray head to Hampstead Heath for a walk with Radio 1’s Greg James and his chocolate Labrador, Barney. They chat about Greg growing up with teacher parents, his love of radio, his first date with his wife, Bella and his latest book, Super Ghost.
Super Ghost by Greg James and Chris Smith with illustrations by Amy Nguyen (Puffin) is out now!</description></item><item><title>Richard Herring | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 10:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890015/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily went to Hertfordshire for a stroll with Richard Herring and his dog, Wolfie. They chatted about Richard growing up with his dad as his headmaster, his experience at Oxford University and his fabulous podcast, RHLSTP. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Michael Whitehall and Hilary Whitehall | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 08:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890016/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily went for a stroll in Putney with Michael and Hilary Whitehall and their dog, Philomena. They chatted about their early years, their new podcast The Wittering Whitehalls and cleared up a few inaccuracies from Jack’s episode!
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chris Addison | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 08:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890017/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily and Ray headed to Beckenham Place Park for a stroll with Chris Addison. They chatted about Chris being a committed cat-person, his time on Mock the Week, and the upcoming third series of Breeders. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Fern Britton | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 13:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890018/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily went for a walk with Fern Britton and her Goddaughter Cavapoo, Olive. They chatted about Fern’s childhood in Ealing, her chihuahua Grandson, her wonderful career in television and her new book, The Good Servant. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Roisin Conaty | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890019/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily went for a stroll round Highgate Wood with Roisin Conaty and her Maltese, Harpo. They chatted about her childhood in Camden, the epiphany she had when she tried stand up for the first time and her fabulous show, GameFace.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Anthony Horowitz | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 10:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890020/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily went for a stroll in Suffolk coast with Anthony Horowitz and his Labrador, Chase. They chatted about his childhood in North London, his gap year at a cattle ranch in Australia, creating Alex Ryder and his latest Bond thriller, With A Mind To Kill. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonnie Langford | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 08:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890021/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily went for a walk around Chiswick House and Gardens with Bonnie Langford and her maltipoo, Poppy. They chatted about her incredible theatre career, her stint working with two Doctors in Doctor Who, and her current tour – ‘Anything Goes’. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Paul Chowdhry | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890022/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Ray and Emily went for a walk in Glastone Park with Paul Chowdhry. They chatted about their first meeting on Celebrity Deal or No Deal, the impact of losing his mum, Paul&amp;rsquo;s experience of racism when he was growing up, and his stand up tour, Family Friendly Comedian.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Angela Scanlon | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 10:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890023/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily and Ray went for a walk around Highgate Wood with Angela Scanlon. They chatted about growing up with red hair, how Angela got into performing, how she felt she was winging her first time presenting The One Show, and her new book, Joyrider. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Aled Jones | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890024/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily and Ray went for a walk around Green Park with Aled Jones. They chatted about his incredibly early start in show business, what it was like to sing privately for Prince Charles and new children’s book, Bobby Dean and the Golden Egg. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Michael Owen and Gemma Owen | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890025/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily went for a walk in Flintshire with football legend Michael Owen and his international dressage champion and fashion entrepreneur daughter, Gemma Owen. They chat about their three adorable dogs, the competitive streak in the Owen family and their pocket money rules! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rachel Parris | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890026/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890026/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily and Ray went for a stroll around Clapham Common with Rachel Parris. They discuss Rachel’s childhood in Leicester, the surreal nature of going viral with The Mash Report and her book, Advice from Strangers.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Graeme Hall Returns! | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890027/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890027/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Ray and Emily went for a walk in the Cotswolds with the Dogfather, Graeme Hall. Graeme comes to see Ray in person for a one-to-one session. They also discuss Graeme’s new book and live show. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mark Watson | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890028/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890028/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily and Ray take Mark Watson for a walk round Lloyd Park in Walthamstow. They chatted about Mark’s passion for writing, discovering stand-up comedy at university and how he changed his life to focus on the work that made him happy. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rhys Stephenson | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890029/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890029/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the first episode of the new series Emily and Ray take Rhys Stephenson for a walk around Greenwich Park. They chatted about his decision to shift from a medical career into entertainment, working with a talking dog and of course, his time on Strictly Come Dancing. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jack Whitehall | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890030/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 09:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890030/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Christmas special Emily and Ray went for a walk round Regent’s Park with Jack Whitehall and his Cavapoo, Coco. They chatted about the Whitehall family dogs, his childhood where he was an extroverted kid, his rebellious phase at school, and his new film, Clifford the Big Red Dog. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Angela Barnes | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890031/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 10:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890031/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily went for a walk in Brighton with Angela Barnes and her Cockapoo Tina. They chatted about Angela’s fabulously unconventional dad who inspired her to go into comedy, her podcast ‘We Are History’, and her recent wedding to husband, Matt. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ivo Graham | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890032/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890032/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily and Ray went for a walk with Ivo Graham and Irish Terrier, Fox. They chatted about Ivo’s origin story at Eton and then Oxford, his decision to be a stand-up and his childhood pet Labrador. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chris and Rosie Ramsey | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890033/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 07:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890033/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily and Ray went to the Northumberland countryside to take a stroll with Chris and Rosie Ramsey. They chatted about their childhoods, Chris’s bold chat up line to Rosie, their family life with their two boys and the Sh**ged Married Annoyed empire! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Georgia Toffolo | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890034/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily took a stroll round Hyde Park with Georgia Toffolo and her Cavalier King Charles Spaniel, Monty. They chatted about her childhood in Devon, her decision to abandon her law degree to focus on her media career and her friendship with Stanley Johnson.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Shirley Ballas | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890035/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890035/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily and Ray went for a walk with Shirley Ballas and her Lhasa Apso, Charlie. They chatted about how Shirley fell in love with dancing at a young age, her role as a mum, and of course, the current series of Strictly Come Dancing.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Andrew Cotter | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890036/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 16:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890036/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily went for a stroll with Andrew Cotter and his Labradors Olive and Mabel (or is that Mabel and Olive?). They chatted about Andrew’s passion for dogs, his career as a sports journalist and broadcaster, and of course his viral commentary videos.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Katy Wix | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890037/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 05:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890037/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily and Ray took Katy Wix for a walk in Peckham. They discuss Katy’s book, Delicacy, her childhood in Wales and the forthcoming series of Stath Lets Flats. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nick Helm | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890038/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890038/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily and Ray went for a stroll with Nick Helm. They chat about Nick’s childhood in North London, how he discovered comedy and how he copes with mental health struggles. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lucy Beaumont | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890039/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily and Ray went for a walk with Lucy Beaumont. They chatted about how Lucy broke into acting and stand-up comedy, being set up with her husband, Jon Richardson and her new book, ‘Drinking Custard: The Diary of a Confused Mum’. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Isy Suttie | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890040/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890040/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily and Ray went for a stroll with Isy Suttie in Crystal Palace Park. They chatted about Isy’s childhood in Matlock, when she fell in love with her partner, Elis James and her latest novel, Jane Is Trying. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Adam Kay – Returns! | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890041/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 13:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890041/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily went for a walk with Adam Kay and his Airedale, Pip. They discuss Adam’s move to the country, the joys of dog ownership and the books he’s written recently including his upcoming ‘Kay’s Marvellous Medicine’.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Anita Rani | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890042/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890042/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the first episode of the new series Emily goes for a stroll with Anita Rani and her Bedlington Whippet, Rafi. They talk about Anita’s new memoir, her Punjabi family life, her natural performing instinct and her husband, Bhupi.
The Right Sort of Girl by Anita Rani, is out now, (Blink Publishing, £16.99)
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Geoff Norcott | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890043/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890043/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of ‘at home’ with the dog, Emily is joined by Geoff Norcott and his Cockapoo, Lily. They discuss Geoff’s childhood in South London, his years as a teacher and his new book, ‘Where Did I Go Right?’.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Doc Brown | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890044/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 15:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890044/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily went for a stroll on Hampstead Heath with Doc Brown and his Patterdale Terrier, Miko. They discuss his childhood in North London his with sister Zadie Smith, the phone call from Ricky Gervais that has a huge impact on his career, and his new book ‘Something I Said’. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Alex Horne | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890045/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 06:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890045/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily goes for a stroll with Alex Horne and his Cockapoo, Loky. They discussed Alex’s entry into performing, his childhood Labrador, his first date with his wife, Rachel and the story behind his creation, Taskmaster.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Zoe Lyons | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890046/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily chatted to Zoe Lyons and her dog, Groucho. They spoke about Zoe’s childhood and the things that made her feel different to her peers, her unusual start to her showbiz career, and her new BBC quiz show, Lightning.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Evan Davis | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890047/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890047/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily went with a socially distanced stroll with Evan Davis and his Whippet, Mr Whippy. They discuss his childhood in Surrey, his love of radio, his experience of coming out and meeting his partner, Guillaume. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tony Parsons | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890048/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 08:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890048/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily is joined by best-selling novelist, Tony Parsons and his Cavalier King Charles Spaniel, Stanley. They spoke about his Essex childhood, his memories of George Michael, how he bonded with David Bowie over a shared life experience and what it felt like when his book ‘Man and Boy’ went on to become a global phenomenon.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nicky Campbell | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890049/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890049/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week it’s another ‘At Home’ with the dog as Emily chats to Nicky Campbell. They discuss adoption, his extraordinary bond with his childhood dog, his broadcasting career and his new book, ‘One of the Family: Why A Dog Called Maxwell Changed My Life’. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Graeme Hall - 'The Dogfather' | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890050/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 17:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890050/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily chats to The Dogfather himself, Graeme Hall. They discuss Graeme’s childhood in Yorkshire, why he decided to change his life at 40 and become a dog trainer and his book ‘All Dogs Great and Small’. And yes, Emily even picks Graeme’s brain about some of Ray’s habits!
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Matt Goss | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890051/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890051/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week is more of an ‘at home’ with the dog! Emily is joined by Matt Goss and his French Bulldog, Reggie. They discuss the highs and lows of fame, Matt’s relationship with his twin brother, Luke, how he restarted his life in America and his new album.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sindhu Vee | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890052/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890052/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily takes Sindhu Vee and her Frenchie, Bowler out for a stroll around Regent’s Park. The discuss Sindhu’s passion for dogs, her views on parenting and how she got into stand-up comedy. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rebecca Front | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890053/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890053/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily and Ray go for a walk on Hampstead Heath with Rebecca Front and her Cockapoo, Bailey. They talk about how Rebecca’s comedy career began, how she overcame some challenging experiences in childhood and how she deals with anxiety.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lee Mack | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890054/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890054/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily is joined by her first returning guest, Lee Mack, to introduce his silver Labrador puppy, Ludo. They discuss adjusting to dog ownership, his fear of flying, his views on class and also Lee’s fabulous podcast, ‘I Can&amp;rsquo;t Believe It&amp;rsquo;s Not Buddha’.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jamie Cullum | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890055/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 10:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890055/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Christmas Special Emily goes for a walk with Jamie Cullum and Daniel the Spaniel from The Dog’s Trust. They talk about Jamie’s early years, his relationship with his wife Sophie Dahl, his new Christmas album and getting to play for Barack Obama. To find out more about The Dog’s Trust, visit dogstrust.org.uk/changethetale.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jake Humphrey | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890056/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890056/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily went to Norfolk for a country stroll with Jake Humphrey. They chat about Jake’s big break, his moments of self-doubt, and feeling in his element on live TV.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jamie Demetriou | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890057/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890057/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily goes for a walk with comedy actor and writer Jamie Demetriou. They chat about his childhood with his Greek Cypriot dad, wanting to perform from a young age and the award-winning Stath Lets Flats.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mark Gatiss | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890058/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890058/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily goes for a walk with Mark Gatiss and his Labrador, Bob. They talk about Mark’s childhood in the North East, his experience of coming out and the award-winning Sherlock.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Scarlett Moffatt | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890059/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890059/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Emily has a socially distanced chat with Scarlett Moffatt and her chihuahua, Bonnie. They talk about how she was thrust into the spotlight at a young age after appearing in Gogglebox and I&amp;rsquo;m a Celebrity Get Me Out Of Here, being comfortable with her own company and why she&amp;rsquo;s happiest being at home in County Durham with her boyfriend, Scott.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>Ricky Wilson | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890060/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890060/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Emily goes for a stroll with Kaiser Chiefs frontman Ricky Wilson and his dog Reedus - they talk about Ricky&amp;rsquo;s childhood in Leeds, the ingenious song-writing formula behind Kaiser Chief&amp;rsquo;s success, and why Ricky is happiest when he&amp;rsquo;s with his partner Grace.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jeremy Paxman | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890061/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily goes for a walk with broadcaster and writer Jeremy Paxman and his dog Derek. They talk about his childhood, why he hated boarding school, his encounters with Tony Blair and Bill Clinton and what makes him laugh.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sally Phillips | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890062/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890062/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily goes for a stroll with writer, actor and comic Sally Phillips and her two dogs Lola and Teddy. They chat about her childhood moving around the world, getting embarrassed by compliments, Steve Coogan, and teenage fashion struggles.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Gavin Rossdale | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890063/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890063/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily chats to Bush frontman Gavin Rossdale whilst he&amp;rsquo;s out walking his Pomeranian Chewy in Los Angeles. They talk about rebellious teenage years, fame, fatherhood and Bush&amp;rsquo;s new album The Kingdom.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lorraine Kelly | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890064/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily chats to Lorraine Kelly over a stroll with her border terrier, Angus. They talk about Lorraine&amp;rsquo;s childhood dreams of being a fighter pilot, why Piers Morgan calls her ‘an iron first in a velvet glove’, and how she fell in love with her husband Steve. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mel and Coky Giedroyc | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890065/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890065/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily chats to presenter, actor and comic Mel Giedroyc and her director sister Coky Giedroyc. They talk about their respective dogs, Mel’s successful TV partnership with Sue Perkins and their decision to leave Bake Off, and Coky’s new film adaptation of Caitlin Moran’s How To Build A Girl released via Amazon.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tim Key | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890066/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890066/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily and Ray go for a stroll in North London with comedian, actor and poet Tim Key - they chat about Tim&amp;rsquo;s childhood cats, his route into comedy and working with his hero Steve Coogan. Tim has released his poems via a set of cards - to order Tim Key&amp;rsquo;s Poetical Playing Cards go to timkey.co.uk
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Suzi Ruffell | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890067/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily goes for a stroll with comic Suzi Ruffell. They chat about her childhood growing up in Portsmouth, how she was drawn into stand up comedy and the importance of a good cry. To find out more about Suzi&amp;rsquo;s tour Dance Like Everyone&amp;rsquo;s Watching go to Suziruffell.com Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Martin and Shirlie Kemp | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890068/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890068/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily goes for a walk with Martin Kemp and Shirlie Kemp and their toy poodle Pops. They talk about their first date 40 years ago, their friendship with George Michael and finally performing together for their new album In the Swing Of It.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tom Allen | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890069/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890069/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily takes Ray for a stroll in London’s Barbican with comedian Tom Allen. He talks about feeling fabulously different growing up, his strong work ethic and the awkwardness of being set up on dates with friends. For more info on Tom go to tomindeed.com
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>George Northwood | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890070/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily goes for a stroll with celebrated hairdresser, George Northwood and his whippet Willow. George has created iconic hair looks for Alexa Chung, Rosie Huntington Whiteley, Gwyneth Paltrow as well as Meghan Markle’s evening look on her wedding day. He talks about his Nan who inspired him to get into hairdressing, coming out as a young man, and how a large part of hairdressing is being a good therapist.</description></item><item><title>A Message From Emily | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890071/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily has a message about her book&amp;hellip; Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Judy Murray | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890072/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily and Judy take Judy&amp;rsquo;s father&amp;rsquo;s black retriever, Penny, out for a walk on the grounds&amp;rsquo;s of Andy Murray&amp;rsquo;s Cromlix Hotel in Perthshire. They discuss Judy&amp;rsquo;s childhood, competitiveness and what her stint on Strictly Come Dancing did for her.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Richard Madeley | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890073/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily and Richard take Ray for a walk on Hampstead Heath. They discuss Richard&amp;rsquo;s childhood, meeting and falling in love with Judy and his incredible career - including Britain&amp;rsquo;s most successful book club in conjunction with WHSmith.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kerry Godliman | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890074/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily goes for a stroll with After Life actor and comic Kerry Godliman and her Westie-Scottish terrier cross Molly. They discuss Kerry’s fast paced approach to life, meeting her husband and the call from Ricky Gervais that changed her life. To find out more details about Kerry’s 2020 tour go to kerrygodliman.com Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Heston Blumenthal | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890075/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily and Ray go for a stroll with legendary chef Heston Blumenthal, around the village of Bray in Berkshire, the location of his world famous restaurant. They talk about Heston&amp;rsquo;s childhood Christmas dinners, the meal that changed his life as a teenager, and his bulldog Harry. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mariella Frostrup | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890076/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890076/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily goes to Somerset to visit broadcaster and journalist Mariella Frostrup and her two dogs Katyusha and Bomb. They talk about her bohemian childhood, fighting female stereotypes, and how to choose the right partner. Mariella&amp;rsquo;s BBC podcasts Books to Live by and Open Book are available to download. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dick Clement and Ian La Frenais | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890077/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily takes Ray out for a stroll in Regents Park with legendary writing duo Dick Clement and Ian La Frenais. They talk about how they introduced Emily&amp;rsquo;s parents! And what brought the boys together to create their amazing biography of work including The Likely Lads, Auf Wiedersehen Pet and Porridge. They discuss the art of collaboration and how they approached their new memoir More Than Likely. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Emma Barnett | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890078/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily takes Ray out for a stroll with broadcaster and journalist Emma Barnett to Regents Park. They talk about Emma&amp;rsquo;s family parrots growing up, what it feels like to grill Theresa May and the difficult issues she faced trying to get pregnant. She also reveals why she&amp;rsquo;s so keen for women to talk more openly about periods, something she discusses in her book, Period, It&amp;rsquo;s About Bloody Time. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Diane Morgan - The Sequel | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890079/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890079/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Walking the Dog Emily checks in with recent guest Diane Morgan to meet her new Blue Cross toy poodle, Bobby. On a walk around Russell Square with Bobby and Raymond, Diane talks about how she’s finding being a dog owner and why she&amp;rsquo;s totally fallen for her new four legged pal. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Diane Morgan | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890080/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890080/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily goes for a walk with actor, comedian and writer Diane Morgan and two pugs belonging to Emily’s friends. Diane talks about her childhood dogs in Bolton, her job in a chip shop and her rise via Charlie Brooker’s Weekly Wipe into one of the country’s best loved actors. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jack Thorne | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890081/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2019 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890081/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily takes award winning playwright and screenwriter Jack Thorne for a stroll with her dog Raymond. They talk about being shy, how it felt to be a state school kid at Cambridge and his huge body of writing - from Harry Potter and the Cursed Child to The Virtues. Jack also tells Emily about meeting his wife and naming his son after his favourite film. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Konnie Huq | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890082/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily goes for a walk with TV presenter Konnie Huq in her local Ealing park - they chat about the Bangladesh culture her parents grew up in, her early start in television aged just 16, her years as Blue Peter’s longest serving female presenter and meeting her husband Charlie Brooker. Konnie also tells Emily all about writing her first children’s book, Cookie and the Most Annoying Boy in the World out on August 8th.</description></item><item><title>Jenny Eclair | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890083/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890083/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on walking the dog Emily goes for a stroll with comic, writer and co- host of the Older and Wider podcast Jenny Eclair. Jenny is currently considering becoming a dog owner so Emily brought along her dog Raymond and Bruce a French Bulldog who was rescued from a puppy farm by the dogs trust. They talk about Jenny’s childhood growing up in an army family, becoming a female comic when it was a male dominated world and dealing with eye gunk in dogs.</description></item><item><title>Reverend Richard Coles | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890084/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890084/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily heads to Northampton for a walk with the Communards star who became an Anglican priest, Reverend Richard Coles. They take out one of his five dachshunds, Daisy, and he tells Emily about coming out as a gay man to his mother, his wild days as an 80’s pop star, and his decision to give it all up and enter the priesthood. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Ed Miliband | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890085/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 11:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890085/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily takes her dog Raymond out for a walk with former Labour leader Ed Miliband - they talk about growing up in a family of academics, being mistaken for Nick Clegg on the tube and what it felt like to lose the 2015 General Election. They also chat about his podcast with Geoff Lloyd, Reasons to be Cheerful. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description></item><item><title>Simon Thomas | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890086/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890086/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily and Raymond, her Shih Tzu, go out for a walk in Reading with ex Blue Peter and Sky Sports presenter Simon Thomas who tragically lost his wife to Gemma in 2017, prompting a wave of public support. Simon chats about how he&amp;rsquo;s coped with grief, and attempted to rebuild his life and about the process of writing about it in his book Love, Interrupted. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Emily Maitlis | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890087/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890087/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily goes out for a walk with broadcaster, journalist and Newsnight presenter Emily Maitlis and her beautiful whippet Moody. They talk about Emily’s childhood in Sheffield, the question she wishes she’d asked Bill Clinton, and proposing to her husband on millennium eve. She also chats about her new book Airhead, which goes behind the scenes of some of her most pivotal career moments. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Lesley Sharp | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890088/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily goes for a stroll with celebrated actor Lesley Sharp and her beautiful border terrier Mrs Miggins. They talk about Lesley’s early life and how it felt to be adopted, the dogs she’s had throughout her life, juggling motherhood with theatre work and her starring role in a new Royal Court play by Jack Thorne, The End of History. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dave Berry | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890089/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890089/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily goes out for a stroll with Absolute Radio Breakfast show host Dave Berry in London&amp;rsquo;s Regents Park. They talk about his childhood in Lewisham, his early years as a shop assistant and model, breaking into radio and the very rom-com-hero way in which he met his wife. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Adrian Chiles | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890090/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily takes a stroll with British writer and television presenter Adrian Chiles. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Andrea McLean | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890091/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily takes her Shih Tzu Raymond to visit Loose Women presenter Andrea Mclean. They talk about her childhood which took her around the world, becoming a well loved TV face, learning from relationships and finally meeting the one, as well as coping when a beloved pet dies. Andrea also tells Emily about the importance of women talking openly about the menopause, which she writes about in her book Confessions of a Menopausal Woman - soon in live form on her autumn 2019 tour, for more info go to thisgirlisonfire.</description></item><item><title>Nihal Arthanayake | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890092/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily goes out for a stroll with radio presenter Nihal Arthanayake and meets his beautiful Staffie, Luna. Nihal talks to Emily about growing up in Essex with Sri Lankan parents, meeting his wife and knowing she was ‘the one’, handling tricky interview subjects on his BBC Radio 5 Live show and encouraging his daughter to play the drums.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Adam Kay | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890093/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890093/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Walking The Dog Emily goes out for a stroll with comic and author of the acclaimed best selling book This Is Going To Hurt, Adam Kay. Emily brings along Archie a golden lurcher from the Dog’s Trust for her chat with Adam in West London. They talk about Adam’s childhood growing up in a medical family, the moment when he realised a surgeon’s life wasn’t for him, and why he’s so passionate about the NHS.</description></item><item><title>Al Murray | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890094/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily goes out for a stroll with comic Al Murray and brings along her Shih-Tzu Raymond. Al tells Emily about his childhood labradors, his family and his famous literary ancestor. He discusses his days at boarding school, his hatred of confrontation and his start in comedy. They also chat about his famous alter ego the Pub Landlord and forthcoming tour, Landlord Of Hope and Glory (for tickets go to thepublandlord.</description></item><item><title>Ricky Gervais | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890095/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890095/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily goes out for a stroll with legendary comic Ricky Gervais. Ricky brings along beautiful German Shepherd Anti who plays his dog in Afterlife, Ricky’s brand new Netflix series. He talks about his childhood pets, his mum’s brilliantly dark sense of humour and explains why he thinks dogs really are the best. Afterlife is available now to stream on Netflix.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>Walking The Dog Live - with Katherine Ryan | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890096/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 06:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890096/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week in a very special edition of Walking the Dog, Emily Dean is interviewed by Katherine Ryan, in front of a live audience with their two dogs Meg Ryan and Raymond. They chat about Emily&amp;rsquo;s new memoir Everybody Died So I Got A Dog, and Katherine asks her about her eccentric childhood, how she dealt with loss and the miniature Chewbacca lookalike who turned out to be her saviour.</description></item><item><title>Josh Widdicombe | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890097/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily takes her dog Raymond out for a walk in East London’s Victoria Park with comic and Last Leg star Josh Widdicombe. They talk about how fatherhood is a lot less stressful than he imagined, his hatred of confrontation, why he wishes he could bottle some of Rob Beckett’s enthusiasm and his new TV show with James Acaster, Hypothetical. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mark Kermode | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890098/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890098/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily takes a stroll in the New Forest with legendary film critic Mark Kermode and his Labrador Martha. Mark talks to Emily about the band he started at school with David Baddiel, his love of Richard Curtis movies, why his faith is important to him and his podcast Kermode on film. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cariad Lloyd | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890099/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 18:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890099/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily goes out with comic, writer, actress and host of the hugely successful Griefcast podcast - Cariad Lloyd. They go for a stroll in London’s Waterlow Park with Willow, a fabulous poodle. Cariad talks about her love of poodles, losing her dad as a teenager, sharing a flat with Sara Pascoe and the brilliant Griefcast. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Matt Forde | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890100/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily goes for a stroll with Matt Forde, along with Boost the Staffi and Gem the lurcher - two dogs that found a home with with Josie, the Dog’s Trust resident vet. Emily chats to Matt about his early years in Nottingham, his glass half full approach to life and she also persuades him to give us a burst of his legendary Donald Trump and Tony Blair impressions. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Greg Davies | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890101/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily goes out for a walk with Greg Davies and introduces him to the fabulous Bruno - a Rottweiler/ German Shepherd cross from The Dog’s Trust. They chat about inheriting the funny gene from his dad, his childhood pet Rex, and the epiphany in a flotation tank which changed his life. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Alun Cochrane | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890102/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890102/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily heads up to Manchester to visit her co-host on the Frank Skinner show - comic Alun Cochrane. They go out for a stroll with his beautiful whippet Lucky. He talks about how losing his dad at a young age propelled him into being funny for a living, why he admires Frank’s approach to stand up and why he’s a bit of an eccentric at heart. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Noel Fitzpatrick - The Supervet | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890103/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890103/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a very special edition of Walking the Dog Emily goes to visit The Supervet, Dr Noel Fitzpatrick at his veterinary centre in Surrey. They brave the rain with Keira his border terrier and Noel gives Emily a little tour of the place where he and his team perform miracles. They chat about his childhood in Ireland with his dog Pirate, his life working with animals and his current tour Welcome to My World - (for further details and to book tickets go to noelfitzpatricklive.</description></item><item><title>Adam Hills | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890104/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily and her dog Raymond went for a summer walk in Regents Park with comic and Last Leg host Adam Hills. They talked about his childhood in Australia, writing wedding speeches with Ross Noble and his ‘hairy godfather’ figure Billy Connolly. Adam also told Emily all about his brand new book Best Foot Forward. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rob Beckett | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890105/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily goes out with comedian Rob Beckett and Goose, a dachshund who was rehomed via the Dog’s Trust. Rob chats about growing up in South East London and takes Emily for a stroll past his childhood home, they also talk about the family atmosphere that sparked his comedy career, and the importance of mindfulness. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rob Brydon | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890106/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890106/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily goes out for a walk with Rob Brydon and Patience, a golden retriever from The Dog’s Trust. They talk about Rob’s childhood in Wales, his friendship with Steve Coogan, his extraordinarily successful career and he gives Emily a burst of his Hugh Grant, his Anthony Hopkins and of course, his Tom Jones. He also tells Emily all about his new movie Swimming with Men!
Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Sara Pascoe | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890107/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily takes her Shih-Tzu Raymond out for a stroll with comic Sara Pascoe. They talk about growing up in Essex and dreaming of running away with Take That, her thoughts on love and family and her friendship with Katherine Ryan who named a cat in her honour. She also chats about going on the road for her upcoming 2018 tour LadsLadsLads. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>David Gandy | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890108/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890108/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily goes out for a walk with model and fashion icon David Gandy and his dog Dora who was adopted from Battersea Dogs and Cats Home. They chat about shyness, going to number 10 Downing Street in the wrong clothes, and disasters with dog poo bags! David also takes Emily to meet some of the dogs at Battersea and talks about his role as ambassador for the charity battersea.</description></item><item><title>Frank Skinner | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890109/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890109/</guid><description>Podcast Description For the start of a brand new series Emily goes out for a walk with legendary comic Frank Skinner and Peanut - a Terrier Cross who was successfully re-homed by the Dog’s Trust a few years ago. Frank talks about his childhood dogs Shep and Cal, his early years in comedy, the first time he met a young fellow comic called David Baddiel and his more recent adventures in parenthood.</description></item><item><title>David Baddiel | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890110/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890110/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Emily goes out with comic, writer and confirmed cat lover David Baddiel who tries out his dog compatibility with Jimmy, a rescue greyhound from The Dogs Trust. They discuss fame, his brilliant partnership with Frank Skinner, the extraordinary family David grew up in as well as his current tour and becoming a hugely successful children’s author - also featuring David’s brother who calls him halfway through! Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Dynamo | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890111/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily goes for a walk and a talk with magician Dynamo and his Newfoundland puppy Bunty - they chat about the challenges he faced growing up, the magical great-grandfather who kick started his career, the woman who keeps him grounded and they bump into a fellow celebrity dog walker on their travels! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best Bits | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890112/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily revisits some of the highlights of all of her walks with celebrity pals and their dogs this year - and brings you some incredibly funny, revealing and touching off duty moments. A stroll with Gary Lineker and his Labrador Snoop, a wander through the woods with Alan Carr and his English setters, a ramble on Hampstead Heath with Jonathan Ross and his French bulldog Snowball as well as a long walk and talk with Sarah Millican and her dog Tuvok.</description></item><item><title>Lee Mack | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890113/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily goes out to Bushy Park in London with comic Lee Mack and a rescue dog from The Dog’s Trust - a beautiful 3 year old collie cross called Livvy. Lee talks about growing up in a pub, meeting his wife Tara, becoming a comic, having ADHD and his first job as a stable boy for Red Rum. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Russell Howard | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890114/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily goes out for a walk with comic Russell Howard and his Parson Jack Russell terrier, Archie. They talk about the thing that really makes him angry, why he can never wear a suit, inventing a voice for his dog, why he stopped working out and that time he tried therapy. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Matt Lucas | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890115/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily goes out for a stroll with comedian Matt Lucas and his two Labradors Milo and Hob - they talk about Matt’s childhood and the moment he realised he was going to be a comic, coming out, avoiding the red carpet, and why he’s not a fan of dogs on the bed! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Larry and George Lamb | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890116/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 22:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily goes out for a walk on Hampstead Heath with her Shih-Tzu puppy Raymond and guests Larry Lamb and his son George Lamb. They talk about the secret to being a good dad, the power of therapy, Jeremy Corbyn, what it feels like when you&amp;rsquo;re told you&amp;rsquo;re handsome, and George&amp;rsquo;s secret message to Larry when he was in I&amp;rsquo;m a Celebrity Get Me Out of Here.
Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Sarah Millican | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890117/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily goes out for a stroll in the park with comic Sarah Millican and her Schnoodle, Commander Tuvok. The pair discuss the power of starting your life over, why it&amp;rsquo;s good to have a little cry, the importance of therapy and Sarah&amp;rsquo;s brilliantly bizarre childhood imaginary dog! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jimmy Carr | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890118/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2017 22:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily heads out for a summer stroll in north London with Jimmy Carr and his super-cute Yorkshire Terrier. The pair discuss the comedian&amp;rsquo;s early family life, his thoughts on fame, and the secret to happiness. We also discover that when it comes to shoes, Jimmy knows his Louboutins from his Miu Miu&amp;rsquo;s. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jonathan Ross | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890119/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 22:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily goes out for a stroll on Hampstead Heath with Jonathan Ross and his French bulldog Professor Snowball. The pair discuss the joys and pitfalls of being dog owners, what it&amp;rsquo;s like growing up in a large family, the realities of fame, and accepting compliments. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Adam Buxton | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890120/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 22:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily visits comedian, actor and certified podcast royalty Adam Buxton at his home in Norfolk to take his whippet poodle cross, Rosie, out for a walk.He talks about dealing with criticism and insecurities, an embarrassing incident back in the &amp;rsquo;90s, the changing dynamic of his partnership with Joe Cornish, and he and Emily do their best Louis Theroux impressions. Dog tip: Dogs do speak but only to those who know how to listen.</description></item><item><title>Gary Lineker | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890121/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 05:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily visits England legend, TV supremo and all round national treasure Gary Lineker at his home in London to take his Yellow Labrador Snoop out for a walk. He talks about what makes him cry, why he doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to go on Question Time, his friendship with ex-wife Danielle and what it really feels like to take a penalty for England. Dog tip: be the person your dog thinks you are.</description></item><item><title>Katherine Ryan | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890122/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2017 00:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890122/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Walking the Dog Emily goes out for a stroll with comic Katherine Ryan and her dogs Dolly, Megan and Manny. They talk about dating, female role models and a lovely doggy coincidence in their lives. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>John Bradley | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890123/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily takes her Shih-Tzu puppy Ray out with Game of Thrones star John Bradley to help him conquer his dog fear. They talk about starring in one of the most successful TV shows ever made, why he doesn’t drink, and a plane journey with David Beckham. They also have an encounter with some hungry pugs. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Russell Kane | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890124/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890124/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we head to Manchester for a walk with comedian Russell Kane and his pug Colin. Russell tells us how he found love in the front row of one of his shows, reveals why he’s finally coming clean about his age and explains why dogs never sleep on the bed. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Gabby Logan | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890125/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890125/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Gabby Logan takes Emily on a walk with her Boxer Milo and Labradoodle Maggie. They chat about being a footballer (Terry Yorath)’s daughter, 90’s ladettes, falling in love with her husband Kenny and her very famous next door neighbour. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ross Noble | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890126/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2017 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily takes a walk around Ross Noble’s country pile with his two labradoodles Baxter and Baguette. They chat about falling in love, how a comic burns off excess energy, and reality shows. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Alan Carr | Walking The Dog with Emily Dean</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7954890127/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2017 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7954890127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily Dean talks to Alan Carr and his partner Paul, while walking their dogs. They talk about Alan&amp;rsquo;s upbringing, the unreality of fame and their relationship. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>