<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>The History of English Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-history-of-english-podcast/</link>
        <description>Recent content in The History of English Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 23:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-history-of-english-podcast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Episode 30 The Celtic Legacy</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800032/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800032/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the History of English podcast, a podcast about the history of the English
language.
This is episode 30, The Celtic Legacy.
In this episode, we&amp;rsquo;re going to explore the impact of the Celtic languages on modern English,
and we&amp;rsquo;re going to look at the ultimate fate of the native Britons when they encountered
the Anglo-Saxons.
Now this may seem like a straightforward topic, but actually it&amp;rsquo;s a topic that&amp;rsquo;s perplexed</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Episode 29 The Anglo-Saxon Invasion</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800031/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800031/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the History of English podcast, a podcast about the history of the English
language.
This is episode 29, the Anglo-Saxon invasion.
In this episode, we&amp;rsquo;re going to explore the invasion of Britain by the Anglo-Saxons.
And specifically, we&amp;rsquo;re going to look at the period from around the year 410, when
the Roman Empire abandoned Britain, until around the year 600.
These two centuries are sometimes called the lost centuries of British history because</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Episode 28 Angles, Saxons, Jutes and Frisians</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800030/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800030/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the History of English podcast, a podcast about the history of the English
language.
This is episode 28, Angles, Saxons, Jutes, and Frisians.
This time, we&amp;rsquo;re going to turn our attention northward, to the peoples of Northern Europe
who spoke the Germanic dialects which became Old English.
These were the Angles, Saxons, and Jutes, and we can probably add in the Frisians, as
well as some Franks.
All of these people spoke closely related West Germanic languages, and they all lived</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Episode 27 Broken Empire and Fractured Languages</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800029/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800029/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the History of English podcast, a podcast about the history of the English
language.
This is episode 27, Broken Empire and Fractured Languages.
This time, we&amp;rsquo;re going to look at the final years of the Western Roman Empire and the
rise of new Germanic kingdoms in its place.
And these political events coincided with the division of Latin and the Germanic languages
into new dialects and languages.
And these newly emerging languages evolved into many of the languages of modern Western</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Episode 26 Imperial Crisis and the Goths</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800028/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800028/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the History of English podcast, a podcast about the history of the English
language.
This is episode 26, Imperial Crisis and the Goths.
This time, we&amp;rsquo;re going to explore a period of Roman history which is sometimes called
the Imperial Crisis, and this period coincides with the rise of a group of Germanic tribes
who invaded Rome during the same time frame.
These tribes included the ancient Goths, and the Goths are particularly important to us</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Episode 25 Germanic Markings and the Runes</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800027/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800027/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the History of English podcast, a podcast about the history of the English
language.
This is episode 25, Germanic Markings and the Runes.
In this episode, we&amp;rsquo;re going to continue to look at the early Germanic tribes, but this
time around we&amp;rsquo;re going to focus on events in southern Germania.
We&amp;rsquo;re going to look at the southward migration of Germanic tribes to the Danube region, where
they met the Romans and eventually met the alphabet.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Episode 24 Germanic Mythology</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800026/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800026/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the History of English podcast, a podcast about the history of the English
language.
This is episode 24, Germanic Mythology.
The last time I looked at the writings of the Roman historian Tacitus, and I used his
book Germania to explore early Germanic society.
In this episode, I&amp;rsquo;m going to continue exploring Germanic culture, but this time I want to
focus on Germanic mythology and religion, and the impact that Germanic mythology has</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Episode 23 Tacitus and Germanic Society</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800025/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800025/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the History of English podcast, a podcast about the history of the English
language.
This is episode 23, Tacitus and Germanic Society.
In this episode, we&amp;rsquo;re going to explore the social, legal, and political culture of the
early Germanic tribes, and I&amp;rsquo;m going to do that by using the writings of the Roman historian
Tacitus, who provided us with the first detailed look at the early Germanic tribes.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Episode 22 Early Germanic Grammar</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800024/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800024/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the History of English podcast, a podcast about the history of the English
language.
This is episode 22, Early Germanic Grammar.
In this episode, we&amp;rsquo;re going to continue our look at the earliest Germanic language.
Specifically, we&amp;rsquo;re going to focus on the grammar of the early Germanic tribes.
But before I begin, let me thank all of you who&amp;rsquo;ve purchased the History of the Alphabet
series.
That series is still available through iTunes and Amazon.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Episode 21 Early Germanic Words</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800023/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800023/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the History of English podcast, a podcast about the history of the English
language.
This is episode 21, Early Germanic Words.
In this episode, we&amp;rsquo;re going to look at the first evidence of Germanic writing, and
we&amp;rsquo;re going to begin looking at the original Germanic language by focusing on the vocabulary
which they used.
But before I begin, let me remind you that the History of the Alphabet series or audiobook</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Bonus Episode 2 History of the Alphabet</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800022/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800022/</guid>
        <description>Hi, everyone. Welcome to this bonus episode of the History of English podcast.
Unfortunately, I don&amp;rsquo;t have a new episode of the podcast ready this week.
I hope to have one ready next week.
But the reason I don&amp;rsquo;t have a new episode ready is because I finally committed myself to finishing that alphabet series,
which I&amp;rsquo;ve been mentioning from time to time.
And I&amp;rsquo;m happy to report that that series is finally ready.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Episode 20: The Early Germanic Tribes</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800021/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800021/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the History of English podcast, a podcast about the history of the English
language.
This is episode 20, The Early Germanic Tribes.
In this episode, I&amp;rsquo;m going to look at the emergence of the first Germanic tribes in
Northern Europe.
So, we&amp;rsquo;ll be looking at the peoples and the languages which gave birth to English.
That means that from this point forward in the podcast, we&amp;rsquo;ll be establishing a continuum</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Episode 19: The Romanization of Britain</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800020/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800020/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the History of English podcast, a podcast about the history of the English
language.
This is episode 19, The Romanization of Britain.
In this episode, I&amp;rsquo;m going to look at the emergence of the Roman Empire following the
death of Julius Caesar.
And then I&amp;rsquo;m going to look at what happened when the Romans decided to make another attempt
to conquer Britain.
As you probably already know, the Romans had more luck this second time around.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Episode 18: Keeping Time With The Romans</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800019/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800019/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the History of English podcast, a podcast about the history of the English
language.
This is episode 18, Keeping Time with the Romans.
The last time we looked at the emergence of the ancient Celts who once dominated much
of Central and Western Europe, and we looked at the defeat of those same Celts by the Romans
in the region known as Gaul, which is basically modern day France.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Episode 17: Ancient Celts and the Latin Invasion of Gaul</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800018/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800018/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the History of English podcast, a podcast about the history of the English
language.
This is episode 17, Ancient Celts and the Latin Invasion of Gaul.
In this episode, we&amp;rsquo;re going to look at the ancient Celts, the people who once dominated
much of Europe.
And we&amp;rsquo;ll look at the spread of Rome and Latin into many of the territories where the
Romance languages are being spoken today.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Episode 16 The Rise of Rome – and Latin</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800017/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800017/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the History of English podcast, a podcast about the history of the English
language.
This is episode 16, The Rise of Rome and Latin.
In this episode, we&amp;rsquo;re going to look at the emergence of Rome from a small city near the
western coast of Italy to the dominant political and military power of the Mediterranean.
And this will set the stage for the expansion of Latin throughout the western world.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Episode 15: Etruscans, Romans and a Modified Alphabet</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800016/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800016/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the History of English podcast, a podcast about the history of the English
language.
This is episode 15, Etruscans, Romans, and a Modified Alphabet.
In this episode, we&amp;rsquo;re going to turn our attention from the Eastern Mediterranean to the West,
specifically to Italy.
In the past few episodes, I&amp;rsquo;ve discussed the significant influence of Greek on English.
Now we start to look at the tremendous influence of Latin.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Episode 14 The Greek Word Horde</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800015/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800015/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the History of English podcast, a podcast about the history of the English
language.
This time we&amp;rsquo;re going to look at the vast horde of Greek words which have found their
way into modern English.
Now I&amp;rsquo;m not going to look at all the Greek words which have come into English, that would
probably take several episodes, but I am going to give you a heavy dose of Greek words to</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Episode 13 Greece, Phoenicia and the Alphabet</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800014/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800014/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the History of English podcast, a podcast about the history of the English
language.
This time I&amp;rsquo;m going to explore the beginning of the Greek alphabet, which is ultimately
the same alphabet we use today.
But before I begin, let me mention a couple of things about the alphabet in this podcast
series.
Obviously, the story of the alphabet is part of the story of English, and my general approach</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Episode 12: Early Greek, Hittite and the Trojan War (Extended Version)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800013/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800013/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the History of English podcast, a podcast about the history of the English
language.
This is Episode 12, Early Greek, Hittite, and the Trojan War.
Over the last few episodes, we&amp;rsquo;ve looked at the migration of the original Indo-European
from the Eurasian steppes to the areas where the modern Indo-European languages are located.
We will now begin to look at each of the individual Indo-European languages which have directly</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Bonus Episode 1</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800012/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800012/</guid>
        <description>Hi everyone, this is Kevin Stroud from the History of English podcast.
This is a bonus episode, I just wanted to use this opportunity to give you a quick couple
of updates related to the podcast and also answer a few questions that I&amp;rsquo;ve been receiving.
This is not a regular episode and that&amp;rsquo;s why it&amp;rsquo;s not numbered in sequence, but I thought
this would probably be the best way to address a few little quick issues with you.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Episode 11: Germanic Ancestors</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800011/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800011/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the History of English podcast, a podcast about the history of the English
language. In this episode, we&amp;rsquo;re going to look at the emergence of the Germanic tribes,
the early Greek speakers, the first Latin-speaking tribes in Italy, and the Celtic tribes in
Central and Western Europe. So we&amp;rsquo;re going to begin a shift from the original Indo-Europeans
to the various daughter languages, which directly influenced the development of English.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Episode 10: Early Indo-European Migrations</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800010/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800010/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the History of English podcast, a podcast about the history of the English
language.
Over the last few episodes, we&amp;rsquo;ve focused on the oldest known ancestor of English, the
ancient Indo-European language.
And in the last episode, I look at the evidence to determine when and where these ancient
Indo-Europeans lived.
Now I want to try to put all the pieces together to explore the emergence of the ancient Indo-Europeans</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Episode 9 Who Were the Indo-Europeans</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800009/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800009/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the History of English podcast, a podcast about the history of the English
language and the people who contributed to that history.
Over the last few episodes, we&amp;rsquo;ve looked at the oldest known ancestor of English, the
ancient Indo-European language called Proto-Indo-European Bilingualist.
We looked at how the language was discovered, and then how it was reconstructed.
We also looked at some of the reconstructed words and the connection many of those words</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Episode 8: Indo-European Grammar (Where have all the inflexions gone?)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800008/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800008/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the History of English podcast, a podcast about the history of the English
language.
So far in this podcast, we&amp;rsquo;ve looked at the oldest ancestor of English, the ancient
Indo-European language.
And in the last couple of episodes, I looked at some of the words that have been reconstructed
in that language.
Remember that the original Indo-European language was not written down.
It existed long before the alphabet, and there is no evidence of a written form of the original</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Episode 7 More Indo-European Words</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800007/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800007/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the History of English podcast, a podcast about the history of the English
language.
In the last episode, we began to look at some of the specific words used by the original
Indo-Europeans, many of which are still found in various forms in modern English.
In this episode, I want to continue looking at some of the original Indo-European words.
Many of the words in this episode relate to the society and culture of the Indo-Europeans,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Episode 6 Indo-European Words</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800006/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800006/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the History of English podcast, a podcast about the history of the English
language.
First of all, let me thank all of you who have been kind enough to leave feedback and
ratings for this podcast on iTunes.
As I&amp;rsquo;ve said before, the feedback is very helpful, and I continue to welcome your comments
there.
Now, as we look at this week&amp;rsquo;s episode, I want to continue to look at the original Indo-European</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Episode 5 Centum, Satem and the Letter C</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800005/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800005/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the History of English podcast, a podcast about the history of the English
language and the people who contributed to that history.
In the last episode, we looked at how Jacob Grimm and other early linguists discovered
a very specific set of rules to identify the way in which ancient Indo-European words became
Germanic words.
That included a set of specific sound changes which also permit linguists to reconstruct</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Episode 4: A Grimm Brother Resurrects the Dead (…language)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800004/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800004/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the History of English podcast, a podcast about the history of the English
language.
In this episode, we&amp;rsquo;re going to look at how a fairy tale collector helped to resurrect
a dead language, specifically the Indo-European language.
In the last couple of episodes, we&amp;rsquo;ve looked at William Jones&amp;rsquo; discovery that almost
all the languages of Europe, as well as several languages of Central Asia, were all descended
from an ancient common ancestor.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Episode 3 The Indo-European Family Tree</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800003/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800003/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the History of English podcast, a podcast about the history of the English
language and the people who contributed to that history.
In the last episode, we looked at how a British judge in India helped to discover the oldest
known ancestor of English, the ancient Indo-European language.
In this episode, we&amp;rsquo;ll look more closely at the Indo-European family of languages and
how English fits into that family.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Episode 2: The Indo-European Discovery</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800002/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800002/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to Episode 2 of the History of English podcast.
In this episode, we&amp;rsquo;re going to look at the oldest known ancestor of English, the
ancient language known as Indo-European, or technically speaking, the Proto-Indo-European
language.
This is the story of the discovery of that language, and the man who is credited for
that discovery, Sir William Jones.
In presenting a history of English, I believe that it&amp;rsquo;s important to begin at this point.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The History of English Podcast - Episode 1: Introduction</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307800001/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307800001/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the first episode of the History of English podcast.
My name is Kevin Stroud, your host for this podcast which will explore the history of
the English language.
In this introductory episode, I want to lay the groundwork for the series of episodes
which will follow.
Let me begin by noting that this is ultimately a history podcast.
The topic happens to be English, but this is not a podcast about the technical aspects</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
