<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Murder They Wrote with Laura Whitmore and Iain Stirling on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/murder-they-wrote-with-laura-whitmore-and-iain-stirling/</link><description>Recent content in Murder They Wrote with Laura Whitmore and Iain Stirling on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 06:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/murder-they-wrote-with-laura-whitmore-and-iain-stirling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>S1.7: The Maple Syrup Heist | Murder They Wrote with Laura Whitmore and Iain Stirling</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9378380008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9378380008/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re in the countdown to Christmas – a time to overindulge on sweet treats and sugary goodness. With that in mind, Iain has a maple-syrup-themed story he’s diving into this week. Get ready to hear all about an outlandish, multi-million-dollar heist that comes to a particularly sticky end.
Murder They Wrote with Laura Whitmore and Iain Stirling is available weekly on BBC Sounds. Subscribe now so you never miss an episode.</description></item><item><title>S1.6: A Corpse In The Kitchen | Murder They Wrote with Laura Whitmore and Iain Stirling</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9378380007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9378380007/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, we’re in Victorian England as Laura dives into the case of Frederick and Maria Manning. This is a story of duplicitous desperation and deadly dinner invites. And it even has an appearance from a world-famous author.
Murder They Wrote with Laura Whitmore and Iain Stirling is available weekly on BBC Sounds. Subscribe now so you never miss an episode. Email us at lauraandiain@bbc.co.uk and join the conversation using the hashtag #lauraiainpodcast.</description></item><item><title>S1.5: A Killer Cuppa | Murder They Wrote with Laura Whitmore and Iain Stirling</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9378380006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9378380006/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Iain looks at the case of Caroline Grills, an elderly lady with a killer instinct when it comes to making tea. It’s 1947 in Sydney, Australia, when members of Caroline’s family begin to fall ill with a sudden and mysterious ailment. No one can understand what’s going on – until Caroline’s nephew reads a newspaper article that blows the case wide open.
Murder They Wrote with Laura Whitmore and Iain Stirling is available weekly on BBC Sounds.</description></item><item><title>S1.4: Dr Hazzard's Sanatorium | Murder They Wrote with Laura Whitmore and Iain Stirling</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9378380005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9378380005/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Laura is looking at the case of Dr Hazzard, a so-called wellness practitioner with some seriously suspicious methods. When two wealthy sisters fall prey to Dr Hazzard’s persuasive spiel, it’s up to their former nanny, Margaret Conway, to spring them out of the remote sanatorium. Murder They Wrote with Laura Whitmore and Iain Stirling is available weekly on BBC Sounds. Subscribe now so you never miss an episode.</description></item><item><title>S1.3: The Hitman Dentist | Murder They Wrote with Laura Whitmore and Iain Stirling</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9378380004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9378380004/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Iain dives into the case of Glennon Engleman – aka ‘The Hitman Dentist’. It’s 1958 in St Louis, Missouri, when Glennon finds himself drowning in debt. His solution? A murder-for-profit scheme that flies under the radar from police for more than two decades. Along the way, Glennon leaves a trail of destruction in his wake. That is until he makes a crucial error that leads investigators straight to his door.</description></item><item><title>S1.2: The Coffin Kidnapper | Murder They Wrote with Laura Whitmore and Iain Stirling</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9378380003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9378380003/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s Laura’s turn this week and she’s looking at the 1992 kidnapping of Stephanie Slater, an estate agent in Birmingham. Stephanie was abducted by a man posing as a prospective house buyer wanting to look around a property. She was driven to a remote location and, once there, things became even more terrifying. But, along with the chilling details of this case, is a story of true resilience, with Stephanie fighting for her freedom every step of the way.</description></item><item><title>S1.1: A Deadly Honeymoon | Murder They Wrote with Laura Whitmore and Iain Stirling</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9378380002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9378380002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Laura and Iain dive into their first ever case. For the premiere episode of Murder They Wrote with Laura Whitmore and Iain Stirling, Iain is leading – and he’s taking us to location very close to his heart: Edinburgh!
When Ernest Domoulin and Helga Konrad elope to the Scottish capital, it looks like they have a bright future ahead of them. That is, until the night of their wedding.</description></item><item><title>Introducing... Murder They Wrote with Laura Whitmore and Iain Stirling | Murder They Wrote with Laura Whitmore and Iain Stirling</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9378380001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 11:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9378380001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Laura Whitmore and Iain Stirling are almost ready to open up the criminal case files for their brand-new True Crime podcast! Starting with one of their own… Well, kind of.
Listen and laugh along as Laura and Iain discuss how they would pull off an imaginary high-stakes heist and disappear under all new identities.
Subscribe now so you never miss an episode.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>