<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Musicland Stories on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/musicland-stories/</link><description>Recent content in Musicland Stories on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:17:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/musicland-stories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Intergalactic 2 | Moe Than We Expected | Musicland Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1476390001/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1476390001/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Arkestra has been without a drummer for years, since their original drummer disappeared, leaving his sticks behind. When Moe auditions her skills for the Arkestra, the sticks glow in her hands, a clear sign that she has what it takes. The Arkestra gives Moe three days to say goodbye to her friends and family before embarking on an intergalactic tour… But The Conductor has a couple tricky detours in store.</description></item><item><title>Intergalactic 1 | Cosmic Jazz | Musicland Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1476390002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1476390002/</guid><description>Podcast Description On a planet where everyone has two hearts that beat constantly out of sync, there’s one child, Moe, whose heart hammers out a unique rhythm unlike anyone else. An intergalactically famous cosmic jazz band, The Arkestra Obscura, visits the planet in search of a new drummer… Will Moe show the Arkestra what she’s made of? Want more kids podcasts for the whole family? Grown-ups, subscribe to Starglow+ here Learn more about Starglow Media here Follow Starglow on Instagram, Facebook, and YouTube</description></item><item><title>Coming Soon: Musicland Stories | Musicland Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1476390003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 04:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1476390003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey there, Cosmic Cats! Welcome to MUSICLAND STORIES, the origin point for all music and adventure stories. Each week The Conductor comes to you live from the Musicland Concert Hall with an original story. Join us for an immersive and educational journey that orbits around the magic that music brings to the world. MUSICLAND STORIES premieres on Tuesday, December 12th, wherever you get your podcasts. Tune in with your kids every week while you’re in the car, winding down after school, beginning bedtime, and everything in between.</description></item></channel></rss>