<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>The Deck on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-deck/</link>
        <description>Recent content in The Deck on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-deck/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>The Deck - Aaron &#34;Peanut&#34; Lamont Smalls (Ace of Spades, Virginia)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700068/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700068/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Aaron Lamont Smalls,
the Ace of Spades from Virginia.
When Aaron was found shot to death in 2001,
investigators dug through piles of tips
and several key pieces of evidence
to try and find his killer.
But each lead seemed to dry up quicker than the last,
and the case eventually went cold.
Now, more than 20 years later,
investigators are still hopeful
that they can uncover the truth for his family</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Keyru Lolo (Queens of Hearts, Colorado)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700067/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700067/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is K. Rue Lolo, the Queen of Hearts from Colorado.
As I&amp;rsquo;m sure you&amp;rsquo;ve already noticed, this is the second episode we&amp;rsquo;re releasing today.
It&amp;rsquo;s a bonus mini episode, a little shorter than a normal one, because there isn&amp;rsquo;t a ton
of information, but we knew that this was a case that still had to be told.
Cases like this are often hard for us to tell because there&amp;rsquo;s not always a lot to the investigation</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - James Walker III (King of Clubs, Kansas)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700066/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700066/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is James Walker III, the King of Clubs from Kansas.
When James was shot to death at a house party in 2017, local police kicked off an investigation
to find the people responsible.
But they were soon met with obstacles left and right, from lack of physical evidence
to witnesses refusing to cooperate.
Today, both investigators and James&amp;rsquo; family believe the case could be solved if just one</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Sherry Black (9 of Hearts, Utah) Part 2</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700065/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700065/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Sherry Black, the Nine of Hearts from Utah.
This is part two of her story.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t yet, go back and listen to the previous episode because in that I told
you about the start of the investigation into a horrifying murder that rocked the community
of South Salt Lake in Utah.
When we left off, it had been more than a year since the murder.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Sherry Black (9 of Hearts, Utah) Part 1</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700064/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700064/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Sherry Black, the Nine of Hearts from Utah.
In November of 2010, the community of South Salt Lake was shocked by the vicious murder
of a beloved great-grandmother.
Investigators chased leads and interviewed suspects, utilizing every resource at their
disposal to learn who could have committed such a brutal crime and why.
But those answers and justice would remain elusive for nearly a decade, until a dogged</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - NEW SHOW: The Deck Investigates</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700063/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700063/</guid>
        <description>Our card today is Darlene Hulse, the Four of Hearts from Indiana.
In 1984, mother of three Darlene was brutally attacked in her own home.
Nearly 40 years later, her daughters are still seeking answers,
and there are still new details to uncover.
So, we took our normal reporting one step further.
You&amp;rsquo;ll see what I mean.
A little over two years ago, I came across an old news article.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Deana Patnode (4 of Diamonds, Minnesota)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700062/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700062/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Deanna Patnode, the Four of Diamonds from Minnesota.
In 1982, 23-year-old Deanna disappeared without a trace from a bar in South St. Paul, Minnesota.
Decades later, a deck of cards would lead to some closure for her family, but ultimately
leave everyone with more questions than answers.
I&amp;rsquo;m Ashley Flowers, and this is The Deck.
In February of 2006, Jim Warren was taking on one of his first assignments after being</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Joseph Pellicci (Jack of Hearts, Connecticut)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700061/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700061/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Joseph Polici, the Jack of Hearts from Connecticut.
Joe was a father of three and a successful restaurateur when he was abducted and shot
to death in 1973.
Everyone in Stanford seems to know who&amp;rsquo;s responsible.
The real mystery is, why hasn&amp;rsquo;t anyone ever been charged with Joe&amp;rsquo;s murder?
I&amp;rsquo;m Ashley Flowers, and this is The Deck.
It was early afternoon on Sunday, February 4, 1973, and in Stanford, Connecticut, a young</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Cassandra Jones (Queen of Clubs, Kansas)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700060/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700060/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Cassandra Jones, the Queen of Clubs from Kansas.
In 1998, 20-year-old Cassandra vanished from the home
that she and her mother shared in Wichita, Kansas,
only to be found months later, her body discarded on the side of the road.
For the past two decades, investigators have thrown everything they can think of
at her case, trying to untangle the twisted web of mysteries
that her killer left behind.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Desiree Michaud (Queen of Clubs, Connecticut)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700059/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700059/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Desiree Michaud, the Queen of Clubs from Connecticut.
In 1984, 18-year-old Desiree was violently killed in a motel room in southeastern Connecticut.
For nearly 40 years, her murder has haunted the community and stumped investigators as
they&amp;rsquo;ve chased down every promising lead that&amp;rsquo;s come knocking on their door.
But they have yet to find the answers they need to crack this case.
As many of you know, I&amp;rsquo;m on the road this week, bringing my investigation of a deck</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Kyle Byrtus (8 of Hearts, Florida)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700058/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700058/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Kyle Burtis, the Eight of Hearts from Florida.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode is a special one to me for two reasons.
One, because Kyle&amp;rsquo;s mom, Lynn, actually reached out to us about covering her son&amp;rsquo;s
case.
And two, because I&amp;rsquo;m going to tell you his story differently than I typically do.
Today we&amp;rsquo;re going to walk through Kyle&amp;rsquo;s case the way Lynn had to, remaining in the</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Oakey &#34;Al&#34; Kite (9 of Hearts, Colorado) Part 2</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700057/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700057/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Oki Al Kite, The Nine of Hearts from Colorado.
This is part two.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t listened to part one, pause here and go back so you can follow along.
In part one, we unpack the beginning of the investigation into the murder of Oki Al Kite
in Aurora, Colorado.
Al was tortured and murdered in 2004, shaking that quiet community to its core.
But early on, detectives had a suspect, Robert Cooper, a man who had rented out Al&amp;rsquo;s basement</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Oakey &#34;Al&#34; Kite (9 of Hearts, Colorado) Part 1</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700056/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700056/</guid>
        <description>Hey, listeners, before I get into today&amp;rsquo;s story, I just want to give a massive thank
you to all of you because today marks the one-year anniversary of The Deck.
Thank you for your support of this podcast as we dive every week into a new cold case.
And what I love most is that you all don&amp;rsquo;t just listen to these cases.
You are taking action, like with that letter-writing campaign we did for Awachiki Osceola that</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Jennifer Wilson (9 of Diamonds, Kansas)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700055/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700055/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Jennifer Wilson, the Nine of Diamonds from Kansas.
In 2002, 29-year-old Jennifer vanished without a trace
after getting into a heated argument with her living girlfriend.
For over two decades, Jennifer&amp;rsquo;s disappearance has puzzled the community.
Because even though investigators think they know who&amp;rsquo;s responsible,
they&amp;rsquo;ve struggled to come up with the answers
to the two remaining questions in her case.
What happened, and where is Jennifer?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Timothy Blair (5 of Clubs, Kentucky)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700054/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700054/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Timothy Blair, the five of clubs from Kentucky.
When Timothy&amp;rsquo;s body was found on the side of the road in 2005, investigators launched
into action to find his killer, but their investigation quickly turned cold despite
the discovery of DNA evidence and the cooperation of his family.
Seventeen years later, Timothy&amp;rsquo;s mother persists in her search for justice, even with
the investigation being put on hold and overshadowed by a whirlwind of rumors that have only led</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Willie Troy Price Sr. (King of Diamonds, South Carolina)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700053/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700053/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Willie Troy Price Sr., the King of Diamonds from South Carolina.
You may have already looked at your feed and noticed, but today I&amp;rsquo;m dropping two episodes
instead of just one.
The stories that you&amp;rsquo;ll hear aren&amp;rsquo;t connected, but they do have something in common.
They&amp;rsquo;re both being investigated as possible cases of mistaken identity.
Cases like these are hard to tell because oftentimes there&amp;rsquo;s just not a lot to the</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Jermaine Johnson (2 of Spades, Arizona)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700052/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700052/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Jermaine Johnson, the Two of Spades from Arizona.
In 2006, Central Phoenix was shaken after a beloved member of the community was killed
while he was minding his own business, hanging out with his friends.
For 16 years, Phoenix police have attempted to hunt down the killers, only to hit dead
ends at every turn.
But they have far from given up hope because they know there are people in the community</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Maggie Long (4 of Spades, Colorado)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700051/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700051/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Maggie Long, the Four of Spades from Colorado.
In 2017, 17-year-old Maggie went missing in rural Park County, Colorado, only to be found
hours later as the victim of the most brutal murder the area had ever seen.
For the past five years, Maggie&amp;rsquo;s horrific murder has weighed on law enforcement in the
small community, as they&amp;rsquo;ve struggled to get any answers to the nagging questions surrounding</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Catherine Sjoberg (8 of Hearts, Wisconsin)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700050/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700050/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Katherine Sjoberg, the aid of hearts from Wisconsin.
In June 1974, 17-year-old Kathy was enjoying all the festivities of prom night when a heated
argument with her boyfriend at the post-prom dance sent her storming off into the cool
summer night, never to be seen or heard from again.
For nearly 50 years, law enforcement in Jefferson County, Wisconsin, have been haunted by Kathy&amp;rsquo;s
as they&amp;rsquo;ve tried to find answers to the nagging questions still weighing on the community</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Donna Ingersoll (10 of Clubs, Minnesota)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700049/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700049/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Donna Ingersoll, the Ten of Clubs from Minnesota.
On a snowy December night in 1990, 25-year-old Donna stormed outside and disappeared into
the night after a heated argument with her boyfriend,
leaving behind several important belongings and a twisted web of mysteries that investigators
have spent decades trying to untangle.
But some recent developments have present-day investigators questioning everything they
thought they knew about the case, and believing that they&amp;rsquo;re closer than ever to cracking</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Dale Williams (Jack of Hearts, Colorado)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700048/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700048/</guid>
        <description>Before we jump into the episode, I have a quick announcement to make.
I know it&amp;rsquo;s hard to believe, but we&amp;rsquo;re actually coming up on the one-year anniversary
of The Deck.
And I&amp;rsquo;ve been kind of working on something kind of in secret in the background.
You see, in the middle of investigating all of these cases that we&amp;rsquo;ve told you over
the last year, our reporter Emily and I stumbled across a case right here in Indiana that was</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Kellie Poppleton (9 of Hearts, California)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700047/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700047/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Kelly Poppleton, the Nine of Hearts from California.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been looking forward to sharing Kelly&amp;rsquo;s case with you all because it is so close,
and I mean like investigative inches away from finally being solved.
And after almost 40 years of her case going unsolved,
detectives are now ready to share new information
that has never been released to the public.
Information that, with your help, could get Kelly&amp;rsquo;s family the answer to the question</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Viola Pendergrass (Wild Card, North Carolina)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700046/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700046/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Viola Pendergrass, a wild card from North Carolina.
I felt compelled to tell you Viola&amp;rsquo;s story even though she&amp;rsquo;s not featured on a cold
case deck because she was the matriarch of not just her sprawling family, but also those
at the apartment complex where she&amp;rsquo;d lived for two decades.
Residents there even called her Ma.
That is, until one winter morning in 1992 when someone came into her home and viciously</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Rachel Hurley (9 of Hearts, Florida)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700045/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700045/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Rachel Hurley, the Nine of Hearts from Florida.
On St. Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Day 1990, in the picturesque beach town of Jupiter, 14-year-old Rachel
joined a group of friends for an afternoon of boating.
After the teens disembarked a few hours later, Rachel was supposed to meet her mom at their
pickup point, but she never made it.
That night, the middle schooler&amp;rsquo;s body was found in some woods nearby.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Joyce &#34;Tina&#34; Gallegos (7 of Spades, Utah) &amp; Gabrielle DiStefano (3 of Spades, Utah)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700044/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700044/</guid>
        <description>Our cards this week are Joyce Tina Gallegos and Gabrielle DeStefano, the seven and three
of spades from Utah.
In 1982, Tina and Gabby mysteriously disappeared from the same northern Utah city only days
apart.
When their bodies were found just miles from each other, many people took notice of the
similarities in their cases, and a recent development in the case has permanently linked
their two murders.
For 40 years, their cases have been unsolved, but police are still hopeful the right person</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Valincio Hill (Ace of Hearts, Kansas)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700043/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700043/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Valencio Hill, the Ace of Hearts from Kansas.
In September 2020, the 17-year-old high school basketball player was standing on his front
porch in Wichita, Kansas, hanging out with his family, when he was suddenly gunned down.
For the past two years, Valencio&amp;rsquo;s murder has haunted the community of Wichita as police
try to get information from the few people who may have the answers they need, including</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Brian Sullivan (3 of Spades, New York)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700042/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700042/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Brian Sullivan, the Three of Spades from New York.
In 2007, 19-year-old Brian was enjoying his summer, hanging out and making music with
friends when one July day he vanished without a trace.
Over the past 15 years, law enforcement&amp;rsquo;s investigation has yielded answers to many
of the questions surrounding his disappearance, but not the one still weighing on his friends
and family daily.
Where is Brian?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Dana Ramm (Jack of Hearts, California)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700041/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700041/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Dana Ram, the Jack of Hearts from California.
Just shy of New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve in 1986, 20-year-old Dana Ram vanished from a gas station parking
lot in a small California town.
When her body was found the morning after she disappeared, her friends and family were
heartbroken, but they helped police piece together the last moments of Dana&amp;rsquo;s life.
Without any tips generated for decades, police are now turning to the public for help identifying</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Roberta Johnson (10 of Diamonds, Florida)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700040/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700040/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Roberta Johnson, the Ten of Diamonds from Florida.
In the spring of 1999, 38-year-old Roberta Johnson had a lot to look forward to.
The U.S. Army veteran had a job that she loved, working with at-risk children at a local school.
She was also nine months pregnant and would soon welcome a baby boy into the world.
And she was doing all of this while her teenage daughter was set to graduate high school in</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - James Winston III (9 of Clubs, Kansas)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700039/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700039/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is James Winston the third, the nine of clubs from Kansas.
In February 2020, James was sitting in his Wichita, Kansas apartment when suddenly two
people barged in in the dead of night, shot him and fled, leaving behind a heartbroken
family.
Investigators think they know the motive behind James&amp;rsquo;s murder, but their investigation has
been frustrated by a lack of cooperation from the very people that they think hold</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - James Rowe, John Spivey &amp; Nancy Spivey (Jack of Spades, Florida)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700038/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700038/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is James Rowe and John and Nancy Spivey, the Jack of Spades from
Florida.
On a cool January evening in 1991, the three roommates hosted a small group of friends
in their St. Petersburg apartment for a night of drinks and card games.
But exactly what happened next that night has baffled investigators for three decades.
I&amp;rsquo;m Ashley Flowers, and this is The Deck.
On January 10th, 1991, during the pre-dawn hours in the Tampa Bay area, a man, who we&amp;rsquo;re</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Irving Shuman (5 of Diamonds, Arizona)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700037/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700037/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Irving Schumann, the Five of Diamonds from Arizona.
On a September afternoon in 2008, 84-year-old Irving, a well-known Phoenix real estate developer
and Jewish philanthropist, was firing off some work emails alone in his office when
an intruder burst in.
Irving tried to fight off his attacker in an intense struggle, leaving behind a horrific
crime scene and a mystery that has endured for nearly 15 years.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Mary &#34;Frankie&#34; Harvey (Jack of Hearts, Massachusetts)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700036/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700036/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Mary Frankie Harvey, the Jack of Hearts from Massachusetts.
Forty-two years have passed since Frankie was left for dead in a southeastern Massachusetts
gravel pit.
Frankie&amp;rsquo;s case is unique in a lot of ways, but one reason is because her story straddles
the state line of Rhode Island, where she was last seen alive, and Massachusetts, where
her body was found, which complicated the investigation from the get-go.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Jenny Lin (Queen of Hearts, California) Part 2</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700035/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700035/</guid>
        <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re just tuning in, go back and listen to part one because we unpacked a lot in the
last episode.
I told you about the investigation into the murder of 14-year-old Jenny Lynn, whose brutal
killing in 1994 shook the quiet community of Castro Valley, California, and it has left
investigators searching for her killer for 28 years.
When we left off last time, police were four months into their investigation and struggling</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Jenny Lin (Queen of Hearts, California) Part 1</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700034/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700034/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Jennifer Lynn, the Queen of Hearts from California.
In 1994, the brutal murder of 14-year-old Jenny inside her parents&amp;rsquo; safe suburban
house left a community shaken to its core, because not only had a bright and talented
life been suddenly snuffed out, but police struggled to find a motive.
And the more clues they uncovered, the more investigators realized the nightmare they
were dealing with.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Marjorie Sue Fithian (Wild Card, Colorado)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700033/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700033/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Marjorie Fithian, a wild card from Colorado.
It broke my heart when I first heard about what happened to Marjorie and her son,
so even though they&amp;rsquo;re not featured on a cold case card in Colorado,
I knew we had to tell you their story.
And not just because it is so devastating,
but because nearly 50 years have gone by since Marjorie&amp;rsquo;s murder,
and some of the stories surrounding her death are as confusing today as they were back then.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Donna Tattersall (Queens of Spades, Rhode Island)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700032/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700032/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Donna Tattersall, the Queen of Spades from Rhode Island.
In 1979, 24-year-old Donna was found dead behind a bar,
a bar that she was seen alone at just hours earlier.
Thanks to eyewitnesses, police quickly zeroed in on a promising suspect.
But when the case went to trial, they learned things weren&amp;rsquo;t as straightforward as they
seemed.
For more than 40 years, the sexual assault and murder of Donna Tattersall has haunted</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Rachael Runyan (5 of Clubs, Utah)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700031/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700031/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Rachel Runyon, the five of clubs from Utah.
In the early 80s, a small town&amp;rsquo;s illusion of safety was shattered when one of its youngest
residents was kidnapped just steps away from her backyard.
And her abduction, along with some strange happenings that unfolded after, has haunted
the residents of Sunset, Utah for the last 40 years.
I&amp;rsquo;m Ashley Flowers, and this is The Deck.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Melissa Mason &amp; Nicole Glass (6 of Hearts, Arizona)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700030/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700030/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Melissa Mason and Nicole Glass, the Six of Hearts from Arizona.
Life was good for the 27-year-old best friends and roommates who had big plans on the horizon.
Until one day in the winter of 2010 when someone went into their suburban Phoenix home and
committed a heinous crime.
One that&amp;rsquo;s left their loved ones and police perplexed for over a decade.
I&amp;rsquo;m Ashley Flowers and this is The Deck.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Darwin Vest (King of Hearts, Idaho)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700029/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700029/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Darwin Vest, the King of Hearts from Idaho.
On a summer night in 1999, Darwin, a quirky intellectual
who was obsessed with studying spiders,
decided to go out to the bars with some friends
because he had just gotten some amazing news.
But after his final nightcap, Darwin wandered out the side door of a bar
and into a dark alley, triggering a mystery
that no one in 23 years has been able to solve.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Anthony Adams (Ace of Hearts, Utah)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700028/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700028/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Anthony Tony Adams, the Ace of Hearts from Utah.
Tony was a rising star in Salt Lake City who had nothing but a bright future ahead of him
in politics.
Until one night in 1978 when someone entered his apartment and viciously attacked him,
leaving behind a still unsolved mystery and complicated questions of motive.
Was Tony&amp;rsquo;s murder a political assassination, a hate crime, or a random attack?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Shannon Michelle Aumock (6 of Clubs, Arizona)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700027/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700027/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Shannon Amok, the 6th of Clubs from Arizona.
In February 2011, the Phoenix Police Department finally ID&amp;rsquo;d a Jane Doe whose case they&amp;rsquo;d
been working for nearly two decades.
But learning who their victim was was only half the battle.
Investigators have spent the last 11 years since determined to solve her murder.
And their work has led to major breakthroughs in recent years.
And now, some speculate that her tragic ending is connected to three similar crimes.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Nicole Silvers (5 of Diamonds, Colorado)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700026/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700026/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Nicole Silvers, the Five of Diamonds from Colorado.
Nicole, who her friends all called Nikki, was a happy, free-spirited teenager juggling
a part-time job, high school classes, and a busy social life, when one day in the spring
of 2014, she vanished.
We sent our reporting team to her hometown in Colorado to speak with investigators currently
working her case, about why her story is so unique, and why the circumstances surrounding</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Mary Beth &#34;Pixie&#34; Grismore (10 of Spades, Indiana)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700025/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700025/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Mary Beth Pixie Grismore, the Ten of Spades from Indiana.
In 1978, Pixie was a young newlywed excited about moving from Indiana back to her home
state of Iowa to be with her new husband.
That&amp;rsquo;s when she vanished from her own home in the middle of the night, leaving behind
few clues and a chilling mystery that&amp;rsquo;s been unsolved for more than four decades.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Dorothy Kajpust (4 of Diamonds, Idaho)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700024/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700024/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Dorothy Kapust, the Four of Diamonds from Idaho.
In August 2004, 54-year-old Dorothy was crashing at a friend&amp;rsquo;s house in eastern Idaho when
suddenly, in the middle of the night, someone entered the house and brutally beat her, leaving
her for dead.
Dorothy&amp;rsquo;s case is still just as puzzling for detectives today as it was 18 years ago.
What could have possibly been the motive behind one of the most brutal beatings police have</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - David Comparetto (King of Hearts, Florida)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700023/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700023/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is David Camperetto, the King of Hearts from Florida.
David was 30 years old in the early 1990s, had multiple jobs that earned him a steady
income, had a loving family to go home to, and was someone who kept a smile on his face
every day.
But on October 16th, 1993, all of that changed.
David vanished, only to be found burned inside his car right outside of his hometown.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Kétie Memory Jones (5 of Clubs, North Carolina)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700022/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700022/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Katie Memory Jones, the five of clubs from North Carolina.
In 2016, Katie was walking home from a night out with friends enjoying one of the last
warm nights of the year when something bad happened that has haunted her friends and
family for years and has left investigators puzzled to this day.
Now law enforcement is providing new details about Katie&amp;rsquo;s case, hoping that someone</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Bobby Joe Fritz (5 of Spades, Wisconsin)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700021/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700021/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Bobby Joe Fritz,
the five of spades from Wisconsin.
When five-year-old Bobby Joe vanished
one afternoon in the early 80s,
no one suspected right away that he&amp;rsquo;d been abducted
because stuff like that just didn&amp;rsquo;t happen
in his tiny hometown.
But as days went by without any sign of the little boy,
the clues started to point to a worst case scenario
and revealed something much more sinister going on</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Owachige Osceola (8 of Diamonds, Oklahoma)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700020/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700020/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Awachagee Osceola,
the Eight of Diamonds from Oklahoma.
Even though Awachagee called for help
on the morning her killer broke in,
what actually happened inside her apartment
is still a mystery.
And while evidence supports police&amp;rsquo;s theory
about who killed her,
one huge hurdle still stands in the way of justice.
I&amp;rsquo;m Ashley Flowers, and this is The Deck.
On
September 25th, 2013,
Toni Brown was hanging out at home in Anadarko, Oklahoma,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - COUNTERCLOCK The Death of John Welles</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700019/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700019/</guid>
        <description>How did a 17-year-old boy turn up dead on his family&amp;rsquo;s farm in rural South Florida?
That&amp;rsquo;s the question investigative journalist Delia D&amp;rsquo;Ambra is trying to answer on the
newest season of CounterClock.
Follow Delia as she treks through the swamps and orange groves of Arcadia, Florida and
goes toe-to-toe with the most powerful government agencies in the Sunshine State to discover
if John Wells really died from a tragic drowning, or was something far more sinister going on?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Dail Dinwiddie (9 of Diamonds, South Carolina)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700018/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700018/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Dale Dinwiddie, the Nine of Diamonds from South Carolina.
In 1992, Dale was a 23-year-old woman enjoying a night out with friends when suddenly she
vanished from a crowded club, never to be seen again.
Maybe the right person listening to this episode will change that.
I&amp;rsquo;m Ashley Flowers, and this is The Deck.
On September 24th, 1992, at 6.15 in the morning, Dan Dinwiddie was just getting out of bed.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - BONUS: James Foote (7 of Clubs, Florida) featuring Tommy Ray</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700017/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700017/</guid>
        <description>Our card today is James Foote, the Seven of Clubs from Florida.
And James&amp;rsquo; story is unlike any that I&amp;rsquo;ve told you since we launched the deck earlier
this year.
With this bonus episode, I want to tell you a story that shows the power of what these
decks can do.
So you&amp;rsquo;re going to hear from the guy who invented the decks, about what inspired it,
and how they&amp;rsquo;re changing cold cases.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Leah Ulbrich (3 of Clubs, Connecticut)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700016/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700016/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Leah Ulbrich, the Three of Clubs from Connecticut.
For months now, I&amp;rsquo;ve anticipated the release of this episode for a few reasons.
One is because the investigation is still very active and new discoveries were made
while our team was reporting on Leah&amp;rsquo;s case.
Actual breakthroughs that could lead to her murder getting solved.
And the second reason is because Leah&amp;rsquo;s family,
who&amp;rsquo;s been waiting nearly 30 years for answers, talked to us for this episode.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Randall Leach (4 of Hearts, Idaho)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700015/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700015/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Randy Leach, the Four of Hearts from Idaho.
When Randy was 20 years old, he decided to take a break from college and hitchhike through
the American West.
What was supposed to be a journey of self-discovery turned into a mystery that 42 years later
remains unsolved.
I&amp;rsquo;m Ashley Flowers, and this is The Deck.
On November 26th, 1980, Marjorie and Richard Leach were at home in northern Wisconsin preparing</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Cindy Elias (6 of Diamonds, Minnesota)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700014/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700014/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Cindy Elias, the Six of Diamonds from Minnesota.
Cindy was a 19-year-old college student enjoying a night out with friends when she made the
decision to get into someone&amp;rsquo;s car, a decision that would change the course of her life and
leave homicide detectives in Minnesota searching for answers for 45 years.
To this day, her story remains the oldest unsolved case in the state, but efforts to</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Shelton Sanders (Wild Card, South Carolina)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700013/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700013/</guid>
        <description>This is a special episode of The Deck, because the story I want to tell you today is about
a man whose face is not in a cold case card deck.
But we found the case so compelling that we&amp;rsquo;ve decided to bring you his story in what we&amp;rsquo;re
going to call a wildcard episode.
There will be other wildcard episodes throughout this year, mostly because when our reporters
travel to do an interview, sometimes they come across other cases that aren&amp;rsquo;t featured</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Ann Kline (8 of Hearts, Indiana)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700012/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700012/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Anne Klein, the aid of hearts from Indiana.
Anne was a loving wife and devoted teacher who was well on her way to earning a master&amp;rsquo;s
degree, when one winter afternoon in 1973, she was viciously attacked outside her classroom.
This episode is a special one because I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to tell Anne&amp;rsquo;s story ever since I
first heard about it years ago, long before we ever started this show.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Eddie and Frances Cizauskas (3 of Clubs, Wisconsin)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700011/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700011/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Eddie and Francis Sazauskas,
the three of clubs from Wisconsin.
Eddie and Francis were in their mid-70s
and still working hard as successful scrap metal dealers,
when one day, a monster showed up in their junkyard,
leaving behind a mystery
that has lasted for more than three decades.
I&amp;rsquo;m Ashley Flowers, and this is The Deck.
I&amp;rsquo;m Ashley Flowers, and this is The Deck.
A little after 9 o&amp;rsquo;clock on Wednesday, November 30th, 1988,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Natasha Warren (4 of Hearts, South Carolina)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700010/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700010/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Natasha Warren, the four of hearts from South Carolina.
In 2008, Natasha was a young mother of two who was working two jobs to provide for her
family, when one night, on a dark stretch of road, a stranger came across her path and
forever changed her life.
That person has gone unnamed and unknown for 14 years, and now, law enforcement is opening
up, hoping justice can finally be served.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Donna Lemon (7 of Spades, Idaho)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700009/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700009/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Donna Lemon, the Seven of Spades from Idaho. Donna was a young woman
working as a nurse and had a hopeful future, but her life was cut far too short. And her
death has been clouded in mystery for almost 50 years. But all of that could change very
soon. I&amp;rsquo;m Ashley Flowers, and this is The Deck.
On July 5th, 1973, in a beautiful area of Montana known as Gallatin Canyon, Sherry Pierce</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - LeeAnna Warner (Ace of Hearts, Minnesota)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700008/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700008/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Leanna Warner, the Ace of Hearts from Minnesota.
Leanna&amp;rsquo;s case is one of those that once you&amp;rsquo;ve heard about it, you will never forget
about it.
She was just five years old and not even two blocks away from her family&amp;rsquo;s house when
she disappeared in the middle of the day.
The mystery has haunted Leanna&amp;rsquo;s family and hometown for 18 years.
I&amp;rsquo;m Ashley Flowers, and this is The Deck.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Kelly Dee Wilson (10 of Spades, Ohio)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700007/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700007/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Kelly D. Wilson, the Ten of Spades from Ohio.
Kelly D. Wilson was a young woman whose life and career as a rising star on radio was tragically
cut short, with few clues left behind to piece together the mystery.
What happened to Kelly at the start of the new millennium shocked her fans, it horrified
her family, and it left detectives baffled to this very day.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Rebecca Harvey (Queen of Clubs, Indiana) &amp; Steven Hendricks (8 of Hearts, Indiana)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700006/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700006/</guid>
        <description>Our cards this week are Rebecca Harvey and Stephen Hendricks, the Queen of Clubs, and
the Eight of Hearts from Indiana.
In this episode, I&amp;rsquo;m going to tell you everything our reporting team could find out about Rebecca&amp;rsquo;s
horrific death in 1988, and how it&amp;rsquo;s connected to Stephen, who is still missing today.
For years, there hasn&amp;rsquo;t been much out there on Rebecca&amp;rsquo;s murder or Stephen&amp;rsquo;s disappearance.
That&amp;rsquo;s because their case is a lesser-known unsolved mystery from right here in my home</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Silene Eaddy (3 of Diamonds, South Carolina)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700005/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700005/</guid>
        <description>Our card this week is Selene Eadie, the Three of Diamonds from South Carolina.
Selene Eadie was a friendly 15-year-old girl whose budding teenage years were cut horrifically
short in the spring of 2004.
Law enforcement investigators in Columbia, South Carolina have been trying to solve this
case for 18 years.
So to help us understand the ins and outs of this story and learn more about what happened
Detectives took our reporter, Emily, to the scene of the crime, which means we&amp;rsquo;re taking</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Stewart Simmons and Margaret Walden (Ace of Diamonds and Ace of Hearts, Colorado)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700004/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700004/</guid>
        <description>Our cards this week are Stuart Simmons and Margaret Walden,
the Ace of Diamonds and the Ace of Hearts from Colorado.
With the help from the lead detective,
I&amp;rsquo;m gonna tell you the bizarre tale about these two people
who were murdered in the 80s
and went unidentified for almost 30 years.
And now, law enforcement needs your help to find their killer.
I&amp;rsquo;m Ashley Flowers, and this is The Deck.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - The Deck Mission Statement</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700003/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700003/</guid>
        <description>Hi everyone, I&amp;rsquo;m Ashley Flowers, host of The Deck.
And I want you to take a moment and think about why you listen to true crime podcasts,
what makes you interested and what keeps you coming back for more.
If you&amp;rsquo;re a regular Audiocheck listener, then you already know that we bring you stories
each week, not just to entertain you, but to try and make a difference in the cases</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Raquel Ramirez (7 of Diamonds, Connecticut)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700002/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700002/</guid>
        <description>This series is something that&amp;rsquo;s been a long time coming,
an idea I&amp;rsquo;ve had for years, and over the last year at AudioChuck,
we&amp;rsquo;ve been putting together the right team of people
to make this show a reality.
Those of you who are deep in the true crime community
might know about cold case playing card decks.
Some law enforcement agencies have replaced
the faces of traditional playing cards
with images of missing and murdered people.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck - Linda Smith (9 of Hearts, Idaho)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308700001/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308700001/</guid>
        <description>This series is something that&amp;rsquo;s been a long time coming,
an idea I&amp;rsquo;ve had for years, and over the last year at AudioChuck
we&amp;rsquo;ve been putting together the right team of people
to make this show a reality.
Those of you who are deep in the true crime community
might know about cold case playing card decks.
Some law enforcement agencies have replaced the faces
of traditional playing cards with images of missing</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
