<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Vanishing Point on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-vanishing-point/</link><description>Recent content in The Vanishing Point on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 08:02:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-vanishing-point/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bonus: Advocates &amp; Survivors | The Vanishing Point</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5208500008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 08:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5208500008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our team travels to Hoopa and Covelo to speak to Native women who are on the frontline in the fight against violence. They are using their voices to advocate, educate and support victims of violence and their families.
Explore more at https://upandvanished.com/vanishingpoint/. Follow the show at @thevanishingpointpod.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Agency Road | The Vanishing Point</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5208500007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 08:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5208500007/</guid><description>Podcast Description A death bed confession leads investigators to Agency Road, a rural road that twists and turns into the woods. Will this tip lead to answers and, if not, what can we do to support the efforts to find Khadijah, Emmilee, Virgil, Andrea, Sumi, and other missing Indigenous people in this area?
Explore more at https://upandvanished.com/vanishingpoint/. Subscribe to Tenderfoot+ for ad-free listening and an exclusive binge at tenderfootplus.com. Follow the show at @thevanishingpointpod.</description></item><item><title>Covelo | The Vanishing Point</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5208500006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 08:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5208500006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Located approximately 200 miles south of Hoopa is Covelo, California; home of the Round Valley Tribe. This quaint town with a population of less than 1500 has a violent crime rate higher than the average U.S. city. Our team travels to Covelo to look into the case of Khadijah Britton, a 25 year old woman who was last seen being forced into a car at gunpoint in 2018.</description></item><item><title>Off the Highway | The Vanishing Point</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5208500005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 08:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5208500005/</guid><description>Podcast Description The rural roads and highways leading in and out of the reservation provide the perfect backdrop for someone to vanish. We explore the cases of 52 year old Virgil Bussell Jr. and 22 year old Andrea “Chick” White. White’s case dates back 30 years.
Explore more at https://upandvanished.com/vanishingpoint/. Subscribe to Tenderfoot+ for ad-free listening and an exclusive binge at tenderfootplus.com. Follow the show at @thevanishingpointpod.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>The Wild West | The Vanishing Point</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5208500001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 07:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5208500001/</guid><description>Podcast Description The TFTV team looks into more cases of missing Indigenous people in Humboldt County and hears recurring themes… substance abuse, mental health and lawlessness. Is Humboldt County “The Wild West”?
Explore more at https://upandvanished.com/vanishingpoint/. Subscribe to Tenderfoot+ for ad-free listening and an exclusive binge at tenderfootplus.com. Follow the show at @thevanishingpointpod.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>End of the Road | The Vanishing Point</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5208500002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 07:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5208500002/</guid><description>Podcast Description The last confirmed sighting of 35 year old Emmilee Risling’s was on a cold Autumn day in October 2021. She was standing on Pecwan bridge but several reports place her at “the end of the road”; a remote area on the Yurok reservation. Our team travels to the end of the road to speak to the man some say knows more about Emmilee’s disappearance than he leads on.</description></item><item><title>Hoopa Valley | The Vanishing Point</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5208500003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 07:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5208500003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hoopa Valley is located in the Pacific Northwest. It is a beautiful place with a rich history and culture but this land holds a dark secret, the high rate of missing and murdered Indigenous people. The Tenderfoot TV team heads to Hoopa to investigate why this tribal community is vulnerable to these issues and to hear the stories that have been ignored for so long.
Explore more at https://upandvanished.</description></item><item><title>The Vanishing Point | The Vanishing Point</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5208500004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 16:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5208500004/</guid><description>Podcast Description From the creators of Up and Vanished, this new series explores the last known location shared by multiple individuals. What makes this tribal land, known as the Hoopa Valley, a vanishing point for so many Indigenous people? Coming October 25th.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>