<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>OverDrive on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/overdrive/</link><description>Recent content in OverDrive on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:47:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/overdrive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Applebaum on the recap of the 2023 PGA Tour season, PGA-PIF's discussions and the RBC Canadian Open's developments | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360101/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:47:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Golf Canada CEO Laurence Applebaum joined OverDrive to recap the season across the PGA Tour, the state of the tour moving forward, LIV Golf and the PIF&amp;rsquo;s role, RBC Canadian Open&amp;rsquo;s changes and honouring Nick Taylor with the tournament logo and the Golf Canada Holiday Auction.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 18, 2023 - Hour 3 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360102/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:22:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 3 to close out the Monday edition with Bryan Hayes and Frank Corrado. TSN Hockey Analyst and OverDrive co-host Jamie McLennan stops by from Arizona to discuss the Senators dismissing D.J. Smith, Jacques Martin taking over on an interim basis, Ottawa trying to create a new dynamic, his impressions of Martin Jones and his tenure with the Leafs and self-driving cars in Arizona. Then, CEO of Golf Canada Laurence Applebaum joins the show to recap the PGA Tour season, the changes across the country for golf, RBC Canadian Open additions and the honour of Nick Taylor in the logo, the view of LIV Golf when constructing a tournament and the Golf Canada Holiday Auction, and Best Bets powered by FanDuel SportsBook.</description></item><item><title>Willson on the Monday Night Football matchup, the Bills gaining steam and O'Win Willson's selection | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360103/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 23:29:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360103/</guid><description>Podcast Description TSN NFL Analyst Luke Willson joined OverDrive to preview the Monday Night Football matchup between the Eagles and Seahawks, the Bills&amp;rsquo; impressive beatdown against the Cowboys and their stance in the AFC East, O-Dog and Al&amp;rsquo;s Brother make an surprise appearance for O&amp;rsquo;Win Willson&amp;rsquo;s MNF selection.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Johnston on Smith's dismissal in Ottawa, the coaching carousel in Canada and Dubas' first season in Pittsburgh | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360104/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 22:20:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360104/</guid><description>Podcast Description TSN Hockey Insider Chris Johnston joined OverDrive to discuss the Senators&amp;rsquo; dismissal of D.J. Smith, the reasoning of cleaning house in Ottawa and the next steps for the franchise, the coaching carousel around the Canadian markets, Kyle Dubas&amp;rsquo; first season in Pittsburgh and how the Penguins are on track of significant changes.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 18, 2023 - Hour 1 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360105/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 22:15:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 1 to kick off the week with Bryan Hayes and Frank Corrado as they discuss the Senators&amp;rsquo; cleaning house dismissing D.J. Smith and hiring Jacques Martin as their interim head coach, what led to the decision, Ottawa&amp;rsquo;s underwhelming season in the Eastern Conference, the next steps for the Senators and the Leafs&amp;rsquo; taking down the Penguins in Kyle Dubas&amp;rsquo; return to Toronto. Then, TSN Hockey Insider Chris Johnston stops by to give the latest on the Senators&amp;rsquo; coaching changes, Ottawa&amp;rsquo;s opportunity for a resurgence, the coaching carousel across Canada, Kyle Dubas&amp;rsquo; first season in Pittsburgh and how the Penguins&amp;rsquo; lacklustre start.</description></item><item><title>OverDrive NFL Picks - Week 15 w/ Luke Willson and Al's Brother | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360001/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 00:26:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360001/</guid><description>Podcast Description TSN NFL Analyst Luke Willson and Al&amp;rsquo;s Brother join to make selections for Week 15 in the NFL.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 15, 2023 - Hour 3 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360002/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 00:14:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 3 on a busy Mail it in Friday with Bryan Hayes, Kara Wagland and Frank Corrado. TSN NFL Analyst Luke Willson stops by to breakdown the Thursday Night Football matchup, the Raiders&amp;rsquo; significant victory over the Chargers, Brandon Staley&amp;rsquo;s dismissal and a pivotal weekend of OverDrive&amp;rsquo;s NFL Picks with Al&amp;rsquo;s Brother for Week 15. Then, they play Dear Hayesy-B to give fans of the show their best advice.</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 15, 2023 - Hour 2 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360003/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 23:21:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 2 on Mail it in Friday with Bryan Hayes, Kara Wagland and Frank Corrado. TSN Hockey Analyst Mike Johnson stops by to give his impressions on the Leafs third period comeback and defeat to the Blue Jackets, Ilya Samsonov&amp;rsquo;s lacklustre performances, Martin Jones&amp;rsquo; larger opportunity, Kyle Dubas&amp;rsquo; return to Toronto on Saturday, the Senators&amp;rsquo; expectations, D.J. Smith&amp;rsquo;s job security and the Canucks&amp;rsquo; ceiling in the Western Conference. Then, Kara walks into the show late, and Hayes, Frank and Kara debate at who&amp;rsquo;s at fault and the genuine reasoning for the lateness, the Pistons&amp;rsquo; historic losing skid and the Raptors&amp;rsquo; roster expectations.</description></item><item><title>Johnson on the Leafs' wild comeback defeat, Dubas' return to Toronto and Samsonov's roller coaster season | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360004/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 22:49:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360004/</guid><description>Podcast Description TSN Hockey Analyst Mike Johnson joined OverDrive to recap the Maple Leafs&amp;rsquo; third period large comeback and defeat against the Blue Jackets, Ilya Samsonov&amp;rsquo;s shaky performances, Kyle Dubas&amp;rsquo; return to Toronto on Saturday, the Senators&amp;rsquo; lacklustre season continuing, D.J.&amp;rsquo;s Smith&amp;rsquo;s job security, the Canucks&amp;rsquo; ceiling and more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 15, 2023 - Hour 1 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360005/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 22:14:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 1 on a Mail it in Friday with Bryan Hayes, Kara Wagland and Frank Corrado as they discuss the Leafs&amp;rsquo; 5-goal comeback and falling short in an overtime loss against the Columbus Blue Jackets, Auston Matthews&amp;rsquo; significant impact and if he should be considered in the Hart Trophy conversation, Ilya Samsonov&amp;rsquo;s ongoing issues, if Martin Jones makes his way into the crease against the Penguins, the Raiders&amp;rsquo; scoring a franchise record 63 points in win over the Chargers, Brandon Staley dismissed as the Chargers&amp;rsquo; head coach, Bill Belichick&amp;rsquo;s future in New England and Jordan Kyrou&amp;rsquo;s emotional comments over fan&amp;rsquo;s response.</description></item><item><title>Graziano on the Staley's dismissal from the Chargers, Belichick's future in New England and the Bills' grand opportunity | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360006/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 22:07:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360006/</guid><description>Podcast Description ESPN NFL Insider Dan Graziano joined OverDrive to discuss Brandon Staley&amp;rsquo;s dismissal from the Chargers and Los Angeles&amp;rsquo; downward season, Bill Belichick&amp;rsquo;s tenure in New England concluding, Jerod Mayo as a candidate for the Patriots, the Chiefs&amp;rsquo; up-and-down season, the Bills&amp;rsquo; opportunity for a turnaround and Tommy DeVito&amp;rsquo;s interest around the league
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Willson on the Thursday Night Football matchup, Belichick's future in New England and Hayes and Bro's selection | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360007/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:35:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360007/</guid><description>Podcast Description TSN NFL Analyst Luke Willson joined OverDrive to give his opinion on Al&amp;rsquo;s Brother&amp;rsquo;s In-Season Tournament pitch, Hayes and Bro&amp;rsquo;s selection for the Thursday Night Football matchup, the expectations for the Chargers and Raiders in the battle of the backup quarterbacks, the speculation around Bill Belichick in New England and more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 14, 2023 - Hour 3 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360008/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:26:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 3 to wrap up the Thursday edition with Bryan Hayes, Jonas Siegel and Michael DiStefano. TSN Hockey Analyst Dave Poulin joins to go across the hockey world to discuss Auston Matthews&amp;rsquo; goal-scoring hot streak, the Leafs&amp;rsquo; additions report card, the Eastern Conference&amp;rsquo;s competition, teams to watch and the Senators&amp;rsquo; puzzling start. Then, TSN NFL Analyst Luke Willson joins the show to preview the Thursday Night Football matchup, Bill Belichick&amp;rsquo;s tenure in New England, Hayes and Bro&amp;rsquo;s selection for the game and Best Bets powered by FanDuel SportsBook.</description></item><item><title>Poulin on Matthews' goal-scoring excellence, Leafs' additions report card and the Eastern Conference's competition | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 23:50:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360009/</guid><description>Podcast Description TSN Hockey Analyst Dave Poulin joined OverDrive to discuss his impressions on the Leafs&amp;rsquo; consistency, the report card for Brad Treliving&amp;rsquo;s additions, Auston Matthews&amp;rsquo; sizzling goal-scoring and his chase for the Rocket Richard Trophy, the Eastern Conference&amp;rsquo;s possible playoff teams to watch and the Senators&amp;rsquo; puzzling season
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 14, 2023 - Hour 2 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 23:12:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 2 on the Thursday edition with Bryan Hayes, Jonas Siegel and Michael DiStefano. TSN Hockey Insider Pierre LeBrun stops by to discuss the buzz around Chris Tanev, why the Maple Leafs are a suitor, the price point for Tanev, Roberto Luongo joining the Canucks&amp;rsquo; Ring of Honour, Craig Berube&amp;rsquo;s dismissal and the Capitals&amp;rsquo; potential arena move to Virginia. Then, Hayes, Siegel and Al&amp;rsquo;s Brother breakdown Auston Matthews&amp;rsquo; impressive goal scoring this season and his opportunity to win the Rocket Richard , where he sits on the all-time list for the Leafs, what quantifies the status of being the greatest in a franchise and Toronto&amp;rsquo;s most notable athletes.</description></item><item><title>LeBrun on Tanev's price point and why Toronto is a suitor, Luongo joining the Canucks' Ring of Honour and the Capitals' potential arena move | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 22:39:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360011/</guid><description>Podcast Description TSN Hockey Insider Pierre LeBrun joined OverDrive to discuss the buzz around Chris Tanev, the price point for Tanev, why the Maple Leafs are a suitor in the sweepstakes, the Capitals&amp;rsquo; potential arena move to Virginia, the dismissal of Craig Berube and the next steps for the Blues, Roberto Luongo joining the Canucks Ring of Honour and more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 14, 2023 - Hour 1 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 22:10:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 1 to kick-start the Thursday edition with Bryan Hayes, Jonas Siegel and Michael DiStefano as they breakdown the Raptors&amp;rsquo; victory over the Hawks, Pascal Siakam and Scottie Barnes as a duo, Draymond Green&amp;rsquo;s indefinite suspension from the NBA, Giannis Antetokounmpo&amp;rsquo;s antics in the chaos against the Indiana Pacers and the Leafs returning home to take on the Blue Jackets following their New York road trip. ESPN NBA Front Office Insider Bobby Marks stops by to discuss the Raptors&amp;rsquo; possible paths for Pascal Siakam and his future in Toronto, Draymond Green&amp;rsquo;s indefinite suspension, the Warriors dubious future, Giannis Antetokounmpo&amp;rsquo;s anger against the Indiana for the game ball.</description></item><item><title>Marks on the Raptors' routes for Siakam, Green's indefinite suspension and Antetokounmpo's antics | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 21:55:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360013/</guid><description>Podcast Description ESPN NBA Front Office Insider Bobby Marks joined OverDrive to discuss Giannis Antetokounmpo&amp;rsquo;s anger and chaos over the game ball against the Pacers, Draymond Green&amp;rsquo;s indefinite suspension and the unproven path for the Warriors, the Raptors&amp;rsquo; ceiling in the Eastern Conference, Pascal Siakam&amp;rsquo;s high value and if Toronto decides to keep him on board long-term
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 13, 2023 - Hour 3 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360014/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:17:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join Bryan Hayes and Frank Corrado for the final hour of OverDrive! The guys kick off the hour by welcoming TSN Hockey Insider Darren Dreger to discuss the latest news from around the NHL before bringing you another edition of Role Play Level of Concern. Bryan and Frankie close out the show by bringing you their Best Bets powered by Fan Duel.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best Bets powered by FanDuel - December 13th, 2023 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:11:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Best Bets powered by FanDuel - December 13th, 2023
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dreger on Blues parting ways with Berube, pressure mounting for Senators as underwhelming season continues, and Capitals’ plans for new arena | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:02:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360016/</guid><description>Podcast Description TSN Hockey Insider Darren Dreger joins OverDrive to discuss the latest news from around the NHL. Dreger shares his thoughts on the St.Louis Blues opting to dismiss former head coach Craig Berube, whether DJ Smith’s job status is in danger as the Ottawa Senators continue to underwhelm, the Washington Capitals announcing plans to move their arena location from downtown D.C to Virginia, and more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>McDaniel on where Blue Jays go after missing out on Ohtani, Dodgers’ all-in approach, and where Yamamoto might land | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 23:34:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360017/</guid><description>Podcast Description ESPN MLB Analyst Kiley McDaniel joins OverDrive to discuss the latest news from the Hot Stove season. McDaniel shares his thoughts on where the Blue Jays go now after missing out on Shohei Ohtani, where he is expecting Yoshinobu Yamamoto to land as he gets set to choose a North American team, the Dodgers all-in approach after landing Ohtani in free agency, and more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 13th, 2023 - Hour 2 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 23:15:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join Bryan Hayes and Frankie Corrado for the second hour of OverDrive! The guys kick off the hour by welcoming Columbus Blue Jackets&amp;rsquo; Defenceman Zach Werenski to look ahead to tomorrow&amp;rsquo;s game against the Toronto Maple Leafs. Bryan and Frankie are then joined by ESPN MLB Insider Kiley McDaniel to discuss where the Toronto Blue Jays go from here after missing out on the Shohei Ohtani sweepstake and where prized Japanese free agent Yoshinobu Yamamoto might land.</description></item><item><title>Werenski on the rise of USA Hockey over the last decade, looking ahead to the 2026 Olmypics, and how Blue Jackets handled Babcock turmoil | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 23:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Columbus Blue Jackets Defenceman Zach Werenski joins OverDrive to look ahead to tomorrow’s game against the Toronto Maple Leafs. Werenski shares his thoughts on the rise of USA Hockey over the last decade, why he would be honoured to play for the American squad at the 2026 Olympics, how the Blue Jackets were able to handle the early-season turmoil surrounding the firing on Mike Babcock, and more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 13, 2023 - Hour 1 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 22:13:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join Bryan Hayes and Frankie Corrado for the opening hour of OverDrive! The guys kick off the show by recapping the Toronto Maple Leafs&amp;rsquo; dominant win against the New York Rangers last night before discussing why the Los Angeles Dodgers might not be done spending even after handing Shohei Ohtani a record-setting contract and Draymond Green landing in hot water yet again.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 12, 2023 - Hour 3 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:17:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 3 to wrap up the Tuesday edition with Bryan Hayes, Andi Petrillo and Dave Feschuk. TSN Basketball Analyst Leo Rautins stops by to chat about the Raptors&amp;rsquo; losing streak and the team underperforming, the team searching for improvements and if an addition is essential, Shai Gilgeous-Alexander winning the Northern Star Award and his ceiling in his career in the NBA. Hayes, Petrillo and Feschuk give their opinions on John Herdman&amp;rsquo;s comments surrounding his departure with Canada Soccer and Co-Host of the Chasin&amp;rsquo; It Podcast and The 33rd Team Contributor Trey Wingo joined to discuss the Tommy DeVito show for the Giants, the concerns for the Packers, Patrick Mahomes backtracking on his outburst against the Bills and the identity of the Dolphins following the Titans&amp;rsquo; comeback win and Best Bets powered by FanDuel SportsBook.</description></item><item><title>Wingo on the Dolphins' undetermined identity, Mahomes circling back on his outburst and the DeVito show | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:05:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Co-Host of the Chasin&amp;rsquo; It Podcast and The 33rd Team Contributor Trey Wingo joined OverDrive to discuss the Tommy DeVito&amp;rsquo;s show for the Giants, the Packers&amp;rsquo; roller coaster season, Patrick Mahomes backtracking on his outburst against the Bills and the Chiefs not performing to full standards, the true identity of the Dolphins and more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rautins on the Raptors' culpability, Toronto scavenging for improvements and Gilgeous-Alexander winning the Northern Star Award | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 23:46:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360023/</guid><description>Podcast Description TSN Basketball Analyst Leo Rautins joined OverDrive to discuss the Raptors&amp;rsquo; losing streak continuing after defeat against the Knicks, Darko Rajakovic&amp;rsquo;s schemes with their starting lineup, the team&amp;rsquo;s underwhelming start and spiralling three-point percentages, Shai Gilgeous-Alexander winning the Northern Star Award and the ceiling in his skilled career
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 12, 2023 - Hour 2 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360024/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 23:15:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 2 on the Tuesday edition with Bryan Hayes, Andi Petrillo and Dave Feschuk. They are joined by Former NHL Coach and NHL Network Analyst Bruce Boudreau stops by to discuss John Tavares reaching the 1000 point mark, his legacy in both markets, the Islanders&amp;rsquo; crowd response, Connor McDavid vs. Connor Bedard&amp;rsquo;s first instalment, Mikko Rantanen&amp;rsquo;s heated comments around his own teammate, Alex Ovechkin&amp;rsquo;s slow start and goal chase to break Wayne Gretzky&amp;rsquo;s record.</description></item><item><title>Boudreau on Tavares eclipsing the 1000 point mark, Ovechkin's goal chase and McDavid vs. Bedard | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360025/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 22:35:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former NHL Coach and NHL Network Analyst Bruce Boudreau joined OverDrive to discuss John Tavares reaching the 1000 point mark and his legacy across the league, the Islanders fans bringing out the boo birds, dad&amp;rsquo;s trip stories, Mikko Rantanen&amp;rsquo;s comments around Artturi Lehkonen, Connor McDavid vs. Connor Bedard&amp;rsquo;s first matchup and Alex Ovechkin&amp;rsquo;s goal chase
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 12, 2023 - Hour 1 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360026/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 22:08:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 1 to start-up the Tuesday edition with Bryan Hayes, Andi Petrillo and Dave Feschuk as they discuss Maple Leafs&amp;rsquo; captain John Tavares reaching the 1000 point mark against his former team of the Islanders, his legacy in both markets, the harsh response from the New York crowd, tee up of the matchup against the Rangers, the ceiling of the Maple Leafs as the season progresses, the Raptors&amp;rsquo; losing streak continuing and Darko Rajakovic&amp;rsquo;s agreement for the roster.</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 11, 2023 - Hour 3 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360027/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:30:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 3 on the jam-packed Monday show with Bryan Hayes, Jamie McLennan and Dave Feschuk. TSN Hockey Insider Chris Johnston stops by to discuss the increase of physical altercations in the league and if the NHL will change rules, Ilya Samsonov in a larger role with Joseph Woll&amp;rsquo;s injury and John Tavares closely reaching the one thousand point mark and the Penguins&amp;rsquo; troubling season. Then, Canadian businessman, investor and television host Robert Herjavec joins to discuss the extraordinary plane tracking, being mistaken for Shohei Ohtani and his opinion on the otherworldly fan conspiracy theories and Best Bets powered by FanDuel SportsBook.</description></item><item><title>Johnston on the recent rash of altercations, Samsonov's loftier role and Tavares' milestone watch | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360028/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:20:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360028/</guid><description>Podcast Description TSN Hockey Insider Chris Johnston joined OverDrive to discuss the busy weekend across the league. Johnston gave his opinion the league&amp;rsquo;s uptick in physical altercations and brawls, Ilya Samsonov&amp;rsquo;s higher role with Joseph Woll&amp;rsquo;s injury, John Tavares nearing the one thousand point mark, the Oilers&amp;rsquo; turning heads during winning streak and more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Herjavec on the famous tracked plane, experience on the flight and the fan conspiracy theories | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360029/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 23:57:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Canadian businessman, investor and television personality Robert Herjavec joined OverDrive to discuss his point-of-view on the tracked flight, his flight being mistaken with Shohei Ohtani, the fan conspiracy theories, having no involvement in the scenarios, the reaction from Blue Jays fans and more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 11, 2023 - Hour 2 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360030/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 23:12:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 2 as the Monday edition continues with Bryan Hayes, Jamie McLennan and Dave Feschuk. TSN NFL Analyst Luke Willson stops by ahead of the doubleheader on Monday Night Football, Dak Prescott&amp;rsquo;s monumental case for the NFL MVP, the Cowboys&amp;rsquo; robust route to the top of the NFC and their dominance against the Eagles, Patrick Mahomes&amp;rsquo; unconventional outburst, displeasure of referees against the Bills, Buffalo&amp;rsquo;s recapturing momentum and Hayes and Bro and O&amp;rsquo;Win Willson&amp;rsquo;s picks.</description></item><item><title>Willson on the Prescott's significant case for MVP, Mahomes' uncharacteristic outburst and Week 14 MNF picks | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360031/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 22:44:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360031/</guid><description>Podcast Description TSN NFL Analyst Luke Willson joined OverDrive to discuss Patrick Mahomes&amp;rsquo; outburst, uncharacteristic anger displeasure for the referees, Kadarius Toney&amp;rsquo;s offside call, the Bills regaining a playoff opportunity, the Cowboys&amp;rsquo; persistent dominance and Dak Prescott&amp;rsquo;s MVP-caliber season and Al&amp;rsquo;s Brother joins to make selections for MNF for Week 14
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 11, 2023 - Hour 1 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360032/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 22:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 1 to start-up the week with Bryan Hayes, Jamie McLennan and Dave Feschuk as the Shohei Ohtani circus across Canada has completed, Ohtani signing a record-setting deal with the Dodgers, the next steps with the Blue Jays, an athlete&amp;rsquo;s perspective of playing in Toronto and the importance of drafting and developing in a franchise. Then, MLB.com Blue Jays Reporter Keegan Matheson joins to unwrap the Blue Jays coming up short on Ohtani, the opportunity to move into Plan B, why the team should focus on the trade market, Vladimir Guerrero Jr&amp;rsquo;s stardom and the likelihood of the team taking a step.</description></item><item><title>Matheson on the Blue Jays falling short on Ohtani, pivoting to Plan B and Guerrero Jr.'s essential limelight | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360033/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 21:50:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360033/</guid><description>Podcast Description MLB.com Blue Jays Reporter Keegan Matheson joined OverDrive to discuss the saga around Shohei Ohtani, the circus and build up around the deal, Ohtani&amp;rsquo;s record-setting contract with the Dodgers, the team moving towards Plan B and the benefits of the skyrocketing into the trade market and Vladimir Guerrero Jr.&amp;rsquo;s opportunity to become a bigger star.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 8, 2023 - Hour 3 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360034/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 00:22:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 3 on Mail it in Friday brought to you by Boston Pizza with Bryan Hayes, Jeff O&amp;rsquo;Neill and Jamie McLennan. NHL Network Analyst and Former NHL Brian Boyle joins to give his opinion on the Leafs&amp;rsquo; season and level in the challenging Atlantic Division, the Bruins remaining a contender, the Penguins closed-door meeting and how they navigate through their power play concerns and how the physical game has changed since he&amp;rsquo;s played in the league.</description></item><item><title>Boyle on the Leafs' controlling their own destiny, the Penguins' roller coaster start and Bruins remaining pertinent | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360035/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 00:14:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360035/</guid><description>Podcast Description NHL Network Analyst and Former NHLer Brian Boyle joined OverDrive to discuss his impressions on the Leafs&amp;rsquo; constructed lineup, the Bruins rising to the top, the Penguins&amp;rsquo; underwhelming season, the physicality importance, how Tom Wilson&amp;rsquo;s force is evident and more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Phillips on the outlandish Ohtani watch, the Blue Jays' elevated interest and role in the sweepstakes | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360036/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 23:50:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360036/</guid><description>Podcast Description TSN MLB Insider Steve Phillips joined OverDrive amidst of the Shohei Ohtani watch. Phillips discussed his impressions of the ongoing speculations, the reported flight to Toronto and the clarity of the news, his potential role with the Blue Jays and the team&amp;rsquo;s chances to facilitate a deal.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 8, 2023 - Hour 2 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360037/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 23:37:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 2 on Mail it in Friday brought to you by Boston Pizza with Bryan Hayes, Jeff O&amp;rsquo;Neill and Jamie McLennan continues with the acclaimed Shohei Ohtani watch across the city of Toronto. TSN MLB Insider Steve Phillips stops by to give his opinion on the buzz around Ohtani&amp;rsquo;s decisions, the Blue Jays reported interest in the superstar and how the team would implement him in the lineup. Then, TSN NFL Analyst Luke Willson and Al&amp;rsquo;s Brother join to make their selections for O&amp;rsquo;Win Willson and Hayes and Bro for Week 14.</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 8, 2023 - Hour 1 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360038/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 23:25:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 1 on Mail it in Friday brought to you by Boston Pizza with Bryan Hayes, Jeff O&amp;rsquo;Neill and Jamie McLennan as they give comprehensive coverages into the reports of Shohei Ohtani watch, the clarity of the superstar landing into the Toronto Pearson International Airport, where the private jet was headed, &amp;amp; Joseph Woll&amp;rsquo;s injury against the Senators.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Willson on the Thursday Night Football matchup, the Steelers and Patriots' impressive defensive teams and Lawrence's return | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360039/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:35:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360039/</guid><description>Podcast Description TSN NFL Analyst Luke Willson joined OverDrive ahead of the Thursday Night Football between the Patriots and Steelers, the high-octane defensive games and the expectation around the matchup, Trevor Lawrence&amp;rsquo;s return following ankle injury in the Monday Night Football matchup and more
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 7, 2023 - Hour 3 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360040/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:12:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 3 to wrap-up the Thursday edition with Bryan Hayes and Dave Feschuk. TSN Hockey Insider Pierre LeBrun joins the guys to discuss the Oilers&amp;rsquo; progressively improving and if they can claw their way back in the standings, the Senators&amp;rsquo; new additions across the front office, the Battle of Ontario and the Leafs&amp;rsquo; recent line changes and Patrick Kane making his awaited debut with the Red Wings. Then, TSN NFL Analyst Luke Willson stops by in-studio to lookahead to the Thursday Night Football matchup showcasing the Patriots and Steelers, the expectations around a low-scoring game, Trevor Lawrence&amp;rsquo;s return to the field and Al&amp;rsquo;s Brother hops on to make the pick for Hayes and Bro for the matchup.</description></item><item><title>LeBrun on the Oilers' sizzling streak, the Battle of Ontario and Kane making his debut with Detroit | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360041/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 23:57:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360041/</guid><description>Podcast Description TSN Hockey Insider Pierre LeBrun joined OverDrive to go across the world of hockey to discuss the Battle of Ontario, the Senators making coaching staff additions and how Ottawa could boost through adversity, the Oilers&amp;rsquo; turning the corner in the Pacific Division and Patrick Kane making his acclaimed debut with Detroit
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 7, 2023 - Hour 2 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360042/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 23:18:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 2 as the Thursday edition continues with Bryan Hayes and Dave Feschuk. OverDrive Host and TSN Hockey Analyst Jeff O&amp;rsquo;Neill joins from Ottawa to discuss the Battle of Ontario, how the Leafs&amp;rsquo; can kickstart winning ways following an extended break, the Oilers&amp;rsquo; hot streak and Jon Rahm joining LIV Golf in a departure from the PGA Tour. Then, MLB Network Analyst and Host of Off The Mound Ryan Dempster stops by to discuss the ongoing Shohei Ohtani sweepstakes and his gradual return to the mound, if the Blue Jays can input him into the outfield and act as a relief pitcher, Juan Soto traded to the Yankees and how he fits in superior lineup in The Bronx.</description></item><item><title>Dempster on Ohtani's all-around stature, his gradual returning to the mound and Soto heading to The Bronx | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360043/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 23:06:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360043/</guid><description>Podcast Description MLB Network Analyst and Host of Off The Mound Ryan Dempster joined OverDrive to discuss the ongoing Shohei Ohtani sweepstakes, how Toronto could orchestrate an impending deal, if Ohtani will return to normal pitching form, the Yankees&amp;rsquo; landing Juan Soto in a blockbuster deal and the prominent lineup in New York and more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>O'Neill on the Battle of Ontario, the Leafs' return after an extended break and Rahm joining LIV Golf | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360044/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 22:32:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360044/</guid><description>Podcast Description OverDrive Host and TSN Hockey Analyst Jeff O&amp;rsquo;Neill joined the show ahead of the Leafs&amp;rsquo; matchup against the Senators in the Battle of Ontario, Toronto&amp;rsquo;s opportunity to take advantage in the Atlantic Division, the Oilers&amp;rsquo; heating up, the Penguins&amp;rsquo; closed-door meeting and Jon Rahm departing from the PGA Tour joining LIV Golf
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 7, 2023 - Hour 1 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360045/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 22:15:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 1 to start-up the Thursday edition with Bryan Hayes and Dave Feschuk. Hayes and Feschuk hand out their opinions on the continuous watch for Shohei Ohtani&amp;rsquo;s next team decision, the extended wait and how he&amp;rsquo;ll present a deal, how the Blue Jays have played their cards during the process and the lack of clarity around Ohtani&amp;rsquo;s choice. Then, Senior NBA Insider for The Athletic and Stadium, and co-host of Run It Back on FanDuel TV Shams Charania to discuss the league&amp;rsquo;s interest around the Raptors&amp;rsquo; roster, the eyes on Pascal Siakam and OG Anunoby, the trade that fell through between the Hawks and Raptors for Siakam, Scottie Barnes as an untouchable asset, the positivity and next steps around the NBA in-season tournament.</description></item><item><title>Charania on the league's interest in the Raptors' roster, Barnes being an untouchable asset and the positivity around the NBA in-season tournament | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360046/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 22:01:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Senior NBA Insider for The Athletic and Stadium, and co-host of Run It Back on FanDuel TV Shams Charania joined OverDrive to discuss the league&amp;rsquo;s interest around the Raptors&amp;rsquo; roster, Scottie Barnes&amp;rsquo; being an untouchable aspect on the team, the Hawks&amp;rsquo; nearly reaching trade deal with Pascal Siakam and the next steps for the NBA in-season tournament
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 6, 2023 - Hour 3 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360047/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:21:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 3 to wrap up the mid-week edition with Bryan Hayes, Jeff O&amp;rsquo;Neill and Jamie McLennan as they discuss Juan Soto reportedly traded to the Yankees, how this will shape the AL East and the Blue Jays out of a deal to prioritize Shohei Ohtani in free agency. The guys revisit the conversation with Maple Leafs&amp;rsquo; general manager Brad Treliving discussing the Leafs&amp;rsquo; season through the quarter mark, if the team is in the place to make a deal, William Nylander&amp;rsquo;s desire to remain with the team and the contract talk continuing, John Klingberg&amp;rsquo;s season-ending injury, Joseph Woll&amp;rsquo;s impressive role in the crease, working alongside Sheldon Keefe and more.</description></item><item><title>Mitchell on the Raptors' seesaw performances, Siakam and Barnes' contrasts and Lowry planning of retiring in Toronto | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360048/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:05:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360048/</guid><description>Podcast Description TSN Basketball Analyst Sam Mitchell joined OverDrive to discuss the Raptors&amp;rsquo; medium start of the season, Darko Rajakovic&amp;rsquo;s approach to a new roster, the contrast between Pascal Siakam and Scottie Barnes&amp;rsquo; leadership, Kyle Lowry&amp;rsquo;s longevity and his decision to retire in Toronto, positives around the NBA In-Season Tournament and more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 6, 2023 - Hour 2 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360049/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 23:26:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 2 as the Wednesday edition continues with Bryan Hayes, Jeff O&amp;rsquo;Neill and Jamie McLennan. Former NHLer and NHL on TNT Analyst Ed Olczyk hops on to discuss his impressions on the Leafs through the first set of the schedule, the competition around the league and biggest surprises in the NHL, Patrick Kane making his debut in Detroit on Thursday and his legacy with the Chicago Blackhawks. Then, Gerry makes an appearance to go across the sporting world in the latest edition of &amp;lsquo;Gerry&amp;rsquo;s Percentages&amp;rsquo;.</description></item><item><title>Olczyk on the Leafs' stance in the Atlantic Division, Kane debuting in Detroit and his long-lasting legacy in Chicago | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360050/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 23:19:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former NHLer and NHL on TNT Analyst Ed Olczyk joined OverDrive to wraparound the latest headlines across the NHL to discuss his impressions of the Leafs and the Atlantic Division&amp;rsquo;s competition, Patrick Kane making his debut with the Red Wings, Kane&amp;rsquo;s legacy with the Blackhawks and more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 6, 2023 - Hour 1 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360051/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 22:26:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 1 to open the mid-week edition of OverDrive with Bryan Hayes, Jeff O&amp;rsquo;Neill and Jamie McLennan as they discuss the ongoing free agency watch for Shohei Ohtani&amp;rsquo;s decision, the league-altering impact across the MLB Winter Meetings, Juan Soto a potential trade partner with the Yankees and Kyle Lowry candidly stating he&amp;rsquo;ll be retire as a member of the Raptors. Toronto Maple Leafs General Manager Brad Treliving joined the show to discuss the Leafs&amp;rsquo; season through the quarter mark, the team&amp;rsquo;s interest in exploring the market, William Nylander&amp;rsquo;s ongoing negotiations and his desire to stay in Toronto, John Klingberg&amp;rsquo;s season-ending injury, his experience with Sheldon Keefe and if the team wants to make a deal.</description></item><item><title>Treliving on the Leafs' interest in exploring the market, Nylander's ongoing negotiations and Klingberg's season-ending injury | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360052/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 22:02:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Toronto Maple Leafs General Manager Brad Treliving joined OverDrive to discuss the impact of monumental signings, the ongoing negotiations William Nylander and the continuous goal of extending his contract, experiences with Sheldon Keefe, John Klingberg&amp;rsquo;s season-ending injury, the interest of exploring the market and more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 5, 2023 - Hour 3 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360053/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 3 to close out the Tuesday edition with Bryan Hayes, Jeff O&amp;rsquo;Neill and Jamie McLennan. MLB.com Blue Jays Reporter Keegan Matheson stops by from the MLB Winter Meetings to dive into the Shohei Ohtani sweepstakes, the Blue Jays &amp;rsquo;legitimate&amp;rsquo; interest, his potential role in Toronto, Ross Atkins&amp;rsquo; approach and the timeline of a deal. TSN Soccer Reporter Claire Hanna joins the show from Vancouver to preview Christine Sinclair&amp;rsquo;s farewell match with Canada Soccer in friendly against Australia, hanging up the cleats and her remarkable legacy on the pitch.</description></item><item><title>Hanna on Sinclair hanging up the cleats, her farewell with Canada Soccer and her illustrious legacy | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360054/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 23:55:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360054/</guid><description>Podcast Description TSN Soccer Reporter Claire Hanna joined OverDrive ahead of Canada Soccer&amp;rsquo;s friendly against Australia to discuss Christine Sinclair&amp;rsquo;s retirement, her farewell playing for the nation, her remarkable legacy on the pitch and powerful influence for women&amp;rsquo;s sports, her future with the program and more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Matheson on the Blue Jays' interest in Ohtani, the legitimate opportunity to sign him and his potential fit in Toronto | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360055/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 23:32:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360055/</guid><description>Podcast Description MLB.com Blue Jays Reporter Keegan Matheson joined OverDrive to discuss the Shohei Ohtani sweepstakes, Toronto&amp;rsquo;s serious interest, Ohtani&amp;rsquo;s reported visit in Dunedin, Ross Atkins&amp;rsquo; approach during the process, management not commenting on the discussions with the free agent, his potential role on the roster and more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 5, 2023 - Hour 2 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360056/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 23:07:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 2 as the Tuesday edition continues with Bryan Hayes, Jeff O&amp;rsquo;Neill and Jamie McLennan. TSN Hockey Analyst Mike Johnson stops by to discuss the concerns for the Senators, the team&amp;rsquo;s underachieving first quarter of the season, the Hughes&amp;rsquo; brothers in the spotlight, which Hughes brother has the capabilities to lead a franchise, Cale Makar&amp;rsquo;s skillset and Sidney Crosby&amp;rsquo;s longevity. They play &amp;lsquo;Confirm or Deny&amp;rsquo; to wraparound the world of sports with the Shohei Ohtani watch, Ryan Reaves&amp;rsquo; tenure in Toronto, the Arizona Coyotes&amp;rsquo; hot streak and more.</description></item><item><title>Johnson on Crosby's longevity, the Hughes' brothers in the spotlight and the Senators' concerns | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360057/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 22:39:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360057/</guid><description>Podcast Description TSN Hockey Analyst Mike Johnson joined OverDrive to discuss the concern around the Ottawa Senators, the underachieving recent performances, the leadership in the nation&amp;rsquo;s capital, the Hughes&amp;rsquo; brothers in the spotlight and the differences between Jack and Quinn, Sidney Crosby&amp;rsquo;s longevity and more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 5, 2023 - Hour 1 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360058/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 22:12:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 1 to start-up the Tuesday edition with Bryan Hayes, Jeff O&amp;rsquo;Neill and Jamie McLennan as they chat about the Shohei Ohtani sweepstakes, his reported visit to the Dunedin at the Player Development Complex, the Dodgers chipping into the talks around Dave Roberts&amp;rsquo; comments, the Hughes brothers&amp;rsquo; headlining Tuesday&amp;rsquo;s NHL schedule and Joseph Woll stepping into the starter&amp;rsquo;s net for the Leafs. Former MLB GM and MLB Network Radio Host Jim Duquette stopped by from the MLB Winter Meetings to give the latest on the Ohtani watch, the Blue Jays and Dodgers meeting with him, the timeline of the signing and the Giants emerging as a favourite in the sweepstakes.</description></item><item><title>Duquette on the league-altering Ohtani watch, the Blue Jays' notable interest and the timeline of the signing | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360059/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 21:55:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360059/</guid><description>Podcast Description MLB Network Radio Host and Former MLB Executive Jim Duquette joined OverDrive from the MLB Winter Meetings from Nashville to discuss the Shohei Ohtani watch, the notes around the Blue Jays&amp;rsquo; meeting with the free agent, the Dodgers and Dave Roberts&amp;rsquo; transparent comments and the Giants emerging as a candidate in the sweepstakes
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 4, 2023 - Hour 3 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360060/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:18:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 3 to close out Monday&amp;rsquo;s edition with Bryan Hayes, Jeff O&amp;rsquo;Neill and Jamie McLennan. TSN Hockey Insider Chris Johnston hops on from Seattle for the NHL Board of Governors meetings to discuss William Nylander&amp;rsquo;s contract discussions and if a trade would be mentioned, Christopher Tanev linked to Toronto and how he&amp;rsquo;d fit the Leafs&amp;rsquo; blue line and the latest from the meetings. TSN MLB Insider Steve Phillips also joined the show from the MLB Winter Meetings in Nashville to discuss the Shohei Ohtani sweepstakes, why Blue Jays GM Ross Atkins conducted a virtual meeting, the likelihood of Ohtani and Juan Soto landing on the team, Alek Manoah&amp;rsquo;s name swirling in deals and more.</description></item><item><title>Phillips on the MLB Winter Meetings, Ohtani's sweepstakes in Toronto and Atkins' comments | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360061/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360061/</guid><description>Podcast Description TSN MLB Insider Steve Phillips joined OverDrive from the MLB Winter Meetings in Nashville to discuss the Shohei Ohtani sweepstakes and where talks have advanced, Ross Atkins&amp;rsquo; media availability and his comments from a managerial perspective, Juan Soto being linked to the team, Vladimir Guerrero Jr. and Bo Bichette&amp;rsquo;s future with the team and more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Johnston on the NHL Board of Governor meetings, Nylander's high value and Tanev linked to the Leafs | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360062/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:44:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360062/</guid><description>Podcast Description TSN Hockey Insider Chris Johnston joined OverDrive from Seattle at the NHL Board of Governor meetings. Johnston discussed William Nylander&amp;rsquo;s continuous contract talks in Toronto and if a potential trade would be on the table, Christopher Tanev&amp;rsquo;s name connected to the Leafs, the trade market across the league gaining steam and more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 4, 2023 - Hour 2 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360063/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:12:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 2 on the Monday edition with Bryan Hayes, Jeff O&amp;rsquo;Neill and Jamie McLennan. They are joined for a spirited conversation with Luke Willson to discuss the Monday Night Football matchup featuring the Bengals and Jaguars, the NFL&amp;rsquo;s officiating missed calls and the evident decisions on SNF, Jordan Love making a solid impression, Bill Belichick and the Patriots stock continuously falling, Hayes and Al&amp;rsquo;s Brother getting dressed as Batman and Robin and O&amp;rsquo;Win Willson&amp;rsquo;s pick and William Nylander&amp;rsquo;s contract discussions being a noteworthy buzz at the NHL Board of Governors meetings.</description></item><item><title>Willson on Monday Night Football, the NFL officiating conundrum and Love's rise to stardom | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360064/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:01:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360064/</guid><description>Podcast Description TSN NFL Analyst Luke Willson joined OverDrive to discuss the Monday Night Football matchup between the Bengals and Jaguars, the NFL officiating missed calls and the affect in the SNF matchup, Jordan Love&amp;rsquo;s notable performance against Kansas City, O&amp;rsquo;Win Willson&amp;rsquo;s pick and much more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 4, 2023 - Hour 1 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360065/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:14:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 1 to kick off the week with Bryan Hayes, Jeff O&amp;rsquo;Neill and Jamie McLennan as they dive into &amp;lsquo;Something to Chew On&amp;rsquo; brought to you Boston Pizza around the Blue Jays and what they could pitch to Shohei Ohtani in the decision-making of signing a contract and the MLB Winter Meetings kicking off from Nashville. Then, the guys discuss the Leafs&amp;rsquo; overtime defeat against the Bruins, Toronto&amp;rsquo;s struggles to win in regulation and circle across the league as the winners through the quarter mark of the season.</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 1, 2023 - Hour 3 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360066/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:18:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 3 to wrap up the show on a Mail it in Friday with Bryan Hayes, Jeff O&amp;rsquo;Neill and Jonas Siegel. Senior Managing Editor James Mirtle stops by to discuss the Leafs through the first quarter, their up-and-down offensive roles, Auston Matthews looking to break through cold streak and the biggest rivalry for the team and Canadian comedian and host Gerry Dee joins the show to preview his upcoming stand-up comedy tour &amp;lsquo;Funny You Should Say That&amp;rsquo; across Ontario from March to May and Best Bets powered by FanDuel SportsBook.</description></item><item><title>Gerry Dee on his stand-up comedy tour 'Funny You Should Say That' | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360067/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 23:56:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Canadian Actor and Comedian Gerry Dee joined OverDrive to discuss his new stand-up comedy tour across the province of Ontario with the &amp;lsquo;Funny You Should Say That&amp;rsquo; tour
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mirtle on the Leafs' offensive inconsistencies, Matthews' goalless run and Woll's heroic role | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360068/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 23:38:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Senior Managing Editor of The Athletic James Mirtle joined OverDrive to discuss Auston Matthews braving frozen goalless streak, the offensive unsteadiness through the first quarter of the season, Joseph Woll&amp;rsquo;s valiant role, the Leafs&amp;rsquo; first quarter of the season, the team&amp;rsquo;s needs on the blue line and more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive NFL Picks - O'Win Willson vs. Hayes and Bro - Week 13 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360069/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 23:10:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Luke Willson and Al&amp;rsquo;s Brother join Hayes, O-Dog and Jonas Siegel to make selections for Week 13 between O&amp;rsquo;Win Willson and Hayes and Bro
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 1, 2023 - Hour 2 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360070/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 23:09:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 2 on the jam-packed Mail it in Friday edition with Bryan Hayes, Jeff O&amp;rsquo;Neill and Jonas Siegel. They are joined by TSN Hockey Analyst Mike Johnson to discuss the Leafs&amp;rsquo; shootout victory over the Kraken, Auston Matthews&amp;rsquo; cold snap a preview to Toronto&amp;rsquo;s matchup against the Bruins and Nikita Zadorov&amp;rsquo;s deal to the Canucks. TSN NFL Analyst Luke Willson and Al&amp;rsquo;s Brother stop by to make their selections for Week 13 for OverDrive NFL picks between O&amp;rsquo;Win Willson and Hayes and Bro.</description></item><item><title>Johnson on the Leafs and Bruins preview on Saturday, Matthews' scoring drought and Zadorov dealt to Vancouver | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360071/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 22:36:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360071/</guid><description>Podcast Description TSN Hockey Analyst Mike Johnson joined OverDrive to discuss his assessment of the Leafs through the quarter mark of the season, Auston Matthews&amp;rsquo; cold streak, the upcoming matchup against the Bruins and the potential of retaliation, Nikita Zadorov traded to the Canucks and more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - December 1, 2023 - Hour 1 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360072/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 22:11:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 1 to kick off the Mail it in Friday edition with Bryan Hayes, Jeff O&amp;rsquo;Neill and Jonas Siegel as they discussed the Leafs&amp;rsquo; shootout victory over the Kraken, Toronto&amp;rsquo;s lack of regulation wins, if it has become a concern for the team and if the 2023-24 is better than the 2022-23 . Then, Siegel came up with a list of positives from the current Maple Leafs roster and if Brad Treliving has led up to early expectations with the Leafs, the reports of the Blue Jays in the Shohei Ohtani sweepstakes and where they expect him to land.</description></item><item><title>Willson on the Thursday Night Football matchup, Rodgers' gradual return and O'Win Willson's pick | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360073/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:37:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360073/</guid><description>Podcast Description TSN NFL Analyst Luke Willson joined OverDrive to discuss the Thursday Night Football matchup, his faith in Geno Smith and the Seahawks&amp;rsquo; offence, Aaron Rodgers&amp;rsquo; return with the Jets and if he expects him on the field this season, the Bills&amp;rsquo; reeling playoffs odds and Al&amp;rsquo;s Brother joins the show
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - November 30, 2023 - Hour 3 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360074/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:20:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 3 to wrap up the First Up edition on OverDrive with Aaron Korolnek, Carlo Colaiacovo and Frank Corrado. Maple Leafs voices Joe Bowen and Jim Ralph joined the show to discuss the Leafs injury-riddled blue line, their grades of the team at the quarter mark of the season and where the team can to add to bolster the lineup. Then, Seattle Kraken Executive VP and General Manager Ron Francis hops on ahead of the matchup against the Leafs, Matty Beniers and the team continuing to bloom and how a manager views trades around the league, and Best Bets powered by FanDuel SportsBook.</description></item><item><title>Bowen and Ralph on Zadorov landing in Vancouver, the Leafs' injury-riddled blue line and matchup against Kraken | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360075/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:08:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Maple Leafs voices Joe Bowen and Jim Ralph joined OverDrive to discuss the trade of Nikita Zadorov to the Vancouver Canucks and their opinion on the deal, the Leafs&amp;rsquo; defensive depth, if a trade is on the horizon to bolster the blue line and the matchup against the Kraken
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Francis on the Kraken's blooming roster, Beniers' leadership role and the managerial view of trades | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360076/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 23:47:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Seattle Kraken Executive VP and General Manager Ron Francis joined OverDrive ahead of the matchup against the Maple Leafs matchup, the Kraken bolstering early in their process, Matty Beniers&amp;rsquo; leadership, a GM&amp;rsquo;s view of a trade and the defensemen market across the league
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - November 30, 2023 - Hour 2 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360077/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 23:35:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 2 on the eventful edition with Aaron Korolnek, Carlo Colaiacovo and Frank Corrado. They are joined by TSN NFL Analyst to discuss the Thursday Night Football matchup between the Seahawks and Cowboys, the outlook for the Buffalo Bills and if Aaron Rodgers finds his way back to the field following his Achilles injury, and Al&amp;rsquo;s Brother storms in to battle pack O&amp;rsquo;Win Willson&amp;rsquo;s pick. Then, the guys go full First Up playing show staple &amp;lsquo;Pigeon or Peacock&amp;rsquo; and discuss the ongoing speculations around Shohei Ohtani playing with the Toronto Blue Jays.</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - November 30, 2023 - Hour 1 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360078/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 22:13:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 1 to kick off the Thursday edition with Aaron Korolnek, Carlo Colaiacovo and Frank Corrado as they preview the Leafs&amp;rsquo; matchup against the Kraken, the injury-plagued blue line and the essential need of adding a defensemen and their assessment of the team through the first quarter of the season. TSN Host James Duthie hops on to discuss the Leafs on TSN panel, the OverDrive takeover and what to expect and the guys examine Drake&amp;rsquo;s postgame speech following the Raptors&amp;rsquo; victory over the Suns and the popularity level around the Leafs.</description></item><item><title>Duthie on the Leafs on TSN panel, the preparation for the broadcast and Woods return in The Bahamas | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360079/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 21:53:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360079/</guid><description>Podcast Description TSN Host James Duthie joined OverDrive to preview the Leafs on TSN panel featuring Hayes, Noodles and the O-Dog against the Kraken and his assessment of Tiger Woods&amp;rsquo; return in The Bahamas at the Hero World Challenge
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - November 29, 2023 - Hour 3 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360080/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 00:10:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 3 to wrap up the Wednesday edition with Bryan Hayes, Jeff O&amp;rsquo;Neill and Jamie McLennan. TSN Hockey Insider Darren Dreger joins the show to discuss the Leafs&amp;rsquo; double-tap review and being in the mix for a defensemen, D.J. Smith&amp;rsquo;s job security behind the bench in Ottawa and Jack Campbell&amp;rsquo;s possible promotion in Edmonton. Then, Golf Channel and NBC Commentator Steve Sands stops by from The Bahamas to chat about Tiger Woods&amp;rsquo; return to the course, his physical shape and the latest in the PGA Tour-PIF merger and Best Bets powered by FanDuel SportsBook.</description></item><item><title>Sands on Woods making his return in The Bahamas, his physical stature progression and the PGA Tour-PIF merger | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360081/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 00:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Golf Channel and NBC Commentator Steve Sands joined OverDrive to discuss Tiger Woods&amp;rsquo; return to the PGA Tour at the Hero World Challenge, his physical shape on the course, Woods&amp;rsquo; track record over previous years, his backing of the PGA Tour-PIF merger and the absence of stars in The Bahamas
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dreger on the Leafs in the mix for a defenseman, D.J. Smith's job security and the NHL's double-tap review | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360082/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 23:37:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360082/</guid><description>Podcast Description TSN Hockey Insider Darren Dreger joined OverDrive to discuss the latest headlines across the league including the Maple Leafs in the market for a defensemen and teams that are in the mix, D.J. Smith&amp;rsquo;s job security in Ottawa, Jack Campbell&amp;rsquo;s possible promotion, the Leafs&amp;rsquo; shootout victory from the Panthers&amp;rsquo; double-tap and more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - November 29, 2023 - Hour 2 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360083/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 23:04:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 2 as the mid-week edition of the show continues with Bryan Hayes, Jeff O&amp;rsquo;Neill and Jamie McLennan. Former NHLer and Got Yer Back Podcast Host Jason Strudwick stops by to discuss the Oilers finding their groove, Connor McDavid continuing his fiery streak, the chippy play between the Leafs and Panthers and memories of minor hockey playing days. Then, the guys play &amp;lsquo;Role Play Level of Concern&amp;rsquo; to discuss Alex Ovechkin&amp;rsquo;s goal chase, the Buffalo Bills&amp;rsquo; market and the Golden State Warriors&amp;rsquo; dynasty and much more.</description></item><item><title>Strudwick on the Oilers heating up, McDavid turning the corner and the Leafs' physical level | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360084/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 22:44:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Got Yer Back Podcast Host and Former NHLer Jason Strudwick joined OverDrive to discuss the Oilers triumphant streak, Connor McDavid starting to heat up, their opportunity to rise in the Pacific Division, the Leafs&amp;rsquo; playing chippy against the Panthers and memorable stories from the Ontario Hockey League
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Duthie on the announcement of OverDrive becoming the Leafs on TSN panel on Thursday | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360085/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 22:20:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360085/</guid><description>Podcast Description TSN Host James Duthie joined OverDrive to discuss the special announcement around the show as the guys hit the panel for the Leafs&amp;rsquo; matchup against the Kraken
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - November 29, 2023 - Hour 1 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360086/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 22:14:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 1 to kick off the mid-week edition with Bryan Hayes, Jeff O&amp;rsquo;Neill and Jamie McLennan discussing the Leafs&amp;rsquo; shootout victory over the Panthers, the double-tap goal overturned, their assessment of the stars&amp;rsquo; performances in the game and their impressions of the Leafs at the quarter mark of the season. Then, TSN Hockey Host James Duthie joins to discuss the special announcement of the collaboration of OverDrive and TSN Hockey as the guys hit the panel on Thursday and his impressions of the Leafs&amp;rsquo; shootout victory over the Panthers.</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - November 28, 2023 - Hour 3 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360087/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 00:28:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 3 of the Tuesday edition with Bryan Hayes and Jamie McLennan. ESPN and SiriusXM NBA Radio Host Frank Isola stops by to discuss the Raptors wrapping up their In-Season Tournament action against the Nets, LeBron James&amp;rsquo; interesting choice of individualistic words, Klay Thompson&amp;rsquo;s future and seeking a contract in Golden State. Then, Hayes and Noodles played &amp;lsquo;Confirm or Deny&amp;rsquo;, previewed the Panthers and Leafs rematch and the line combinations for the blue and white</description></item><item><title>Isola on the Raptors' wrapping their In-Season Tournament, James individualistic comments and Thompson's future in Golden State | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360088/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 23:56:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360088/</guid><description>Podcast Description ESPN NBA Analyst and SiriusXM NBA Radio Host Frank Isola joined OverDrive ahead of the Raptors and Nets&amp;rsquo; In-Season Tournament matchup, the ceiling of the Raptors, the foundation built around Scottie Barnes, LeBron James&amp;rsquo; individual comments and Klay Thompson&amp;rsquo;s future in Golden State
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - November 28, 2023 - Hour 2 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360089/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 23:29:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 2 on the jam-packed edition with Bryan Hayes, Jeff O&amp;rsquo;Neill and Jamie McLennan. They are joined by TSN Hockey Analyst Mike Johnson to discuss the Blackhawks terminating Corey Perry&amp;rsquo;s contract, the Leafs and Panthers meeting in a rematch from the Stanley Cup Playoffs and Patrick Kane representing the Detroit Red Wings. Hayes and Noodles discuss Ross Atkins&amp;rsquo; press conference in Toronto, the comments circulating around Shohei Ohtani, Vladimir Guerrero Jr.</description></item><item><title>Johnson on the Blackhawks terminating Perry's contract, the Leafs and Panthers rematch and Kane's new role in Detroit | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360090/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 22:59:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360090/</guid><description>Podcast Description TSN Hockey Analyst Mike Johnson joined OverDrive ahead of the Leafs&amp;rsquo; rematch against the Panthers, Toronto&amp;rsquo;s lineup changes with Mitch Marner and William Nylander swapping lines, the Blackhawks&amp;rsquo; terminating Corey Perry&amp;rsquo;s contract and Patrick Kane landing with the Red Wings
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Upshall on Kane landing in Detroit, the Red Wings' boost and the Leafs' consistency | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360091/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 22:32:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former NHLer and Co-Host of Missin Curfew Scottie Upshall joined OverDrive to discuss the heated brawls between the Panthers and Senators, his impressions on the roster construction of the Leafs, Patrick Kane signing with the Red Wings, his role on the roster and reuniting with Alex DeBrincat
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - November 28, 2023 - Hour 1 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360092/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 22:12:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 1 to start up the Tuesday edition with Bryan Hayes, Jeff O&amp;rsquo;Neill and Jamie McLennan to dive into Patrick Kane signing with the Detroit Red Wings the Chicago Blackhawks placing Corey Perry on unconditional waivers and the termination of his contract. Then, Former NHLer and Co-Host of the Missin Curfew Podcast Scottie Upshall hops on to discuss the fiery brawl between the Panthers and Senators, his impressions of the blue and white and Kane landing in Motor City, and the guys dive into the Blue Jays fielding trade calls for Vladimir Guerrero Jr.</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - November 27, 2023 - Hour 3 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360093/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 00:18:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 3 to wrap up the Monday edition with Bryan Hayes, Jeff O&amp;rsquo;Neill and Jamie McLennan. They are joined by Maple Leafs legend Wendel Clark to discuss the Pros Talk Prostate campaign, his role in the community and to rewind on his favourite memories in Toronto. Then, TSN MLB Insider Steve Phillips stops by to discuss the latest around Shohei Ohtani, the Blue Jays&amp;rsquo; reported interest in the superstar, how a potential deal could affect Vladimir Guerrero Jr.</description></item><item><title>Clark on the Pros Talk Prostate awareness campaign, his role representing the community and rewind on his Leafs' memories | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360094/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 00:05:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Maple Leafs Legend Wendel Clark joined OverDrive to discuss the Pros Talk Prostate awareness campaign teaming up with Novartis, the importance of the campaign, his role representing the community, his opinion on the current Leafs roster and a rewind on his memories in Toronto
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Phillips on the Blue Jays' interest in Ohtani, his potential role in Toronto and contract negotiations around a deal | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360095/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 23:55:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360095/</guid><description>Podcast Description TSN MLB Insider Steve Phillips joined OverDrive to discuss the Blue Jays&amp;rsquo; high interest in Shohei Ohtani, his potential role on the roster, the financial outlook for Toronto, if a deal limits the future of Vladimir Guerrero Jr. and Bo Bichette, teams involved in the sweepstakes and more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - November 27, 2023 - Hour 2 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360096/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 23:32:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 2 on the jam-packed edition with Bryan Hayes, Jeff O&amp;rsquo;Neill and Jamie McLennan. They are joined by TSN NFL Analyst Luke Willson ahead of the Monday Night Football matchup, the Buffalo Bills playoff chances slimming, if Russell Wilson is capable of bringing the Denver Broncos Al&amp;rsquo;s Brother stops by to make the selections with Hayes and Bro for the game. Then, they react to the Minnesota Wild cleaning house dismissing Dean Evason, hiring John Hynes as head coach and the Wild&amp;rsquo;s persistent struggles this season.</description></item><item><title>Willson on the Monday Night Football matchup, Hayes and Bro's selection and the Bills' downward spiral | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360097/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 22:56:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360097/</guid><description>Podcast Description TSN NFL Analyst Luke Willson joined OverDrive ahead of the Monday Night Football matchup featuring the Bears and Vikings, the Buffalo Bills&amp;rsquo; downturn of a season, their slim playoff chances, and Al&amp;rsquo;s Brother joins the show to make the selection
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - November 27, 2023 - Hour 1 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360098/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 22:13:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 1 to kick off the week with Bryan Hayes, Jeff O&amp;rsquo;Neill and Jamie McLennan. They dive into the weekend for the Leafs, the line shuffles involving Mitch Marner and William Nylander and the short slump for the blue and white and O&amp;rsquo;Win Willson taking a major lead over Hayes and Bro. TSN Hockey Insider Chris Johnston joins to discuss Brad Treliving&amp;rsquo;s comments at the first quarter mark, the Leafs&amp;rsquo; high interest, the Flames&amp;rsquo; potentially cleaning house and Jacob Trouba&amp;rsquo;s illegal high-stick.</description></item><item><title>Johnston on the Leafs' line shuffles, Treliving's first quarter comments and Trouba's illegal high-stick on Frederic | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360099/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 22:08:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360099/</guid><description>Podcast Description TSN Hockey Insider Chris Johnston joined OverDrive to discuss the Leafs&amp;rsquo; recent line shuffles with Mitch Marner and William Nylander, Brad Treliving&amp;rsquo;s comments around John Klingberg&amp;rsquo;s status and high interest with William Nylander, the Flames&amp;rsquo; potentially cleaning house, the Oilers budding upturn, Jacob Trouba&amp;rsquo;s illegal high-stick on Trent Frederic and more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OverDrive - November 24, 2023 - Hour 2 | OverDrive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9036360100/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 00:14:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9036360100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hour 2 to wrap up the Mail it in Friday edition with Bryan Hayes and Frank Corrado. They circle around the world of sports playing &amp;lsquo;Buy or Sell&amp;rsquo; on Black Friday. Then, TSN Raptors Analyst Jack Armstrong joins ahead of the Raptors&amp;rsquo; NBA In-Season Tournament matchup in DeMar DeRozan&amp;rsquo;s return to Toronto, Scottie Barnes&amp;rsquo; high ceiling and how the team can improve on slower starts and FanDuel Best Bets across Week 12 in the NFL.</description></item></channel></rss>