<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>What Now? with Trevor Noah on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/what-now-with-trevor-noah/</link><description>Recent content in What Now? with Trevor Noah on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 05:49:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/what-now-with-trevor-noah/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Janelle Monáe | What Now? with Trevor Noah</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5492570008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 05:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5492570008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trevor is joined by genre-defying artist and performer, Janelle Monáe, whose 2023 album, The Age of Pleasure, was recently nominated for two GRAMMYs, including Album of the Year. Janelle shares her reaction to that honor, her rebellious youth, and why she used to be scared of mentor Prince and Grace Jones. Trevor also shares an exclusive GRAMMY update of his own, and his theory on why Beyoncé was late to the last one.</description></item><item><title>Sam Altman [VIDEO] | What Now? with Trevor Noah</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5492570007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 10:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5492570007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trevor has a candid and revealing conversation with Sam Altman, who was ousted and then reinstated as CEO of OpenAI just 12 days ago. Sam recounts where he was when he received the brutal phone call, how it all really went down, and its emotional toll. Trevor and Sam also discuss ChatGPT’s explosive release last year, Sam&amp;rsquo;s hopes for AI to better humankind, as well as its potential for evil if not governed properly.</description></item><item><title>DaBaby [VIDEO] | What Now? with Trevor Noah</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5492570006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 05:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5492570006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trevor sits down with Grammy-nominated rapper DaBaby, who just a few years ago was the face of hip-hop with multiple hit singles to his name. Then a controversial moment at the Rolling Loud festival in 2021 changed everything. Trevor and DaBaby face that moment head-on, as well as DaBaby’s challenging upbringing in North Carolina, how he understands his own role as a father, and whether he has any regrets.</description></item><item><title>Bill Gates | What Now? with Trevor Noah</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5492570005/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 05:02:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5492570005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trevor is joined by Bill Gates, the co-founder of Microsoft and one of the world’s foremost philanthropists. The two talk about how he and Paul Allen schemed to get computer time as teens, the dangers AI may play in our future, what it’s like to be at the center of so many conspiracy theories, Bill’s love of pickleball, and more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description></item><item><title>Kerry Washington | What Now? with Trevor Noah</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5492570003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5492570003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trevor is joined by actress/producer/author Kerry Washington. The good friends unpack the end of the Hollywood strikes, the shocking family secret Kerry shares in her newly published memoir, the responsibility of being first on the call sheet, why James Corden is concerned for Kerry, and the one feature Trevor inherited from his family. Trevor also catches up with friend Christiana Mbakwe Medina about their different life choices and the reason she wants Trevor to marry and have kids.</description></item><item><title>Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson [VIDEO] | What Now? with Trevor Noah</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5492570001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5492570001/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the series premiere episode, Trevor is joined by Dwayne &amp;ldquo;The Rock&amp;rdquo; Johnson — &amp;ldquo;The People&amp;rsquo;s Champion&amp;rdquo; in the wrestling world, one of the hardest working actors in Hollywood, and a bonafide Girl Dad. Trevor and Dwayne get real — discussing everything from Dwayne&amp;rsquo;s troubled youth and his lifelong struggles with depression, to Dwayne listening, understanding and responding to public feedback surrounding the launch of his fund following the Maui fires and whether he&amp;rsquo;d ever consider running for President of the United States.</description></item><item><title>INTRODUCING “What Now? with Trevor Noah” Coming November 9 | What Now? with Trevor Noah</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5492570002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5492570002/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is Trevor Noah up to Now? Well, he’s back with a new podcast. Join Trevor and special guests for authentic, candid and necessarily messy conversations. This show is all about conversations without limits. Trevor and his guests will be real and vulnerable. They might even say the wrong thing. And once that happens there’s only one question left to ask: What Now? Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item></channel></rss>