<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>What Now? with Trevor Noah on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/tags/what-now-with-trevor-noah/</link>
        <description>Recent content in What Now? with Trevor Noah on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/what-now-with-trevor-noah/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Kerry Washington | What Now? with Trevor Noah</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/5492570003/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/5492570003/</guid>
        <description>Podcast Description Trevor is joined by actress/producer/author Kerry Washington. The good friends unpack the end of the Hollywood strikes, the shocking family secret Kerry shares in her newly published memoir, the responsibility of being first on the call sheet, why James Corden is concerned for Kerry, and the one feature Trevor inherited from his family. Trevor also catches up with friend Christiana Mbakwe Medina about their different life choices and the reason she wants Trevor to marry and have kids.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Dwayne &#34;The Rock&#34; Johnson [VIDEO] | What Now? with Trevor Noah</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/5492570001/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/5492570001/</guid>
        <description>Podcast Description In the series premiere episode, Trevor is joined by Dwayne &amp;ldquo;The Rock&amp;rdquo; Johnson — &amp;ldquo;The People&amp;rsquo;s Champion&amp;rdquo; in the wrestling world, one of the hardest working actors in Hollywood, and a bonafide Girl Dad. Trevor and Dwayne get real — discussing everything from Dwayne&amp;rsquo;s troubled youth and his lifelong struggles with depression, to Dwayne listening, understanding and responding to public feedback surrounding the launch of his fund following the Maui fires and whether he&amp;rsquo;d ever consider running for President of the United States.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>INTRODUCING “What Now? with Trevor Noah” Coming November 9 | What Now? with Trevor Noah</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/5492570002/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/5492570002/</guid>
        <description>Podcast Description What is Trevor Noah up to Now? Well, he’s back with a new podcast. Join Trevor and special guests for authentic, candid and necessarily messy conversations. This show is all about conversations without limits. Trevor and his guests will be real and vulnerable. They might even say the wrong thing. And once that happens there’s only one question left to ask: What Now? Learn more about your ad choices.</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
