<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>My Mate's A Footballer on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/my-mates-a-footballer/</link><description>Recent content in My Mate's A Footballer on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 06:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/my-mates-a-footballer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Joe on MOTD and Other Landmark Footballing Moments | My Mate's A Footballer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4164410001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4164410001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Patrick begins this episode with a bone to pick with Joe regarding his footballing ability. Kalvin Phillips gets in touch with Joe who starts planning a celebration for when he scores his first professional goal. Plus they discuss the career-defining moments that all players experience on their journey to becoming a Premier League footballer.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Moving to Chelsea on Transfer Deadline Day | My Mate's A Footballer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4164410002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4164410002/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re back on track in this episode about transfers where Pat discusses how his move to Chelsea came out of the blue and gives Joe insight into the power dynamic between a club and a player during the transfer window. Joe discusses what was going on in his life at the same age Pat was moving to the Premier League giants and they discover there’s a lot more in common between the pair than they first imagined.</description></item><item><title>Patrick Bamford’s 5-a-side Clinic | My Mate's A Footballer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4164410003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4164410003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joe slightly derails this episode in order to utilise the time he spends with his professional footballer co-host. After a crushing defeat, he wants to know what things he can add to his game to become a better player at the tender age of 48. Pat obliges with a couple of tips and tricks and we also learn something that Joe could never have imagined about the world of professional football, which only helps their friendship become stronger.</description></item><item><title>How Much Impact Can a New Manager Really Have? | My Mate's A Footballer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4164410004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4164410004/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a confident start to Joe’s attempt of making Patrick his friend, discussion turns to the various things a new manager can change at a club. Having recently gone through the experience with Daniel Farke at Leeds, Pat reveals the rules the German gaffer has brought in, how Sam Allardyce chose to communicate with the squad and how well a team would cope if the players were left to rule on their own.</description></item><item><title>Can Joe Wilkinson become Best Friends with Patrick Bamford | My Mate's A Footballer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4164410005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 06:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4164410005/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this first episode of the pod, Joe reveals his plan of how he will become best mates with a professional footballer. The pair discuss the importance of friendship and Patrick reveals who the most popular man in football is and whether it’s possible for Aaron Ramsdale to be friends with David Raya at Arsenal.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Welcome to My Mate's a Footballer | My Mate's A Footballer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4164410006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4164410006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joe Wilkinson wants to make footballer Patrick Bamford become his new best mate.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>