<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>MrBallen’s Medical Mysteries on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/tags/mrballens-medical-mysteries/</link>
        <description>Recent content in MrBallen’s Medical Mysteries on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 07:04:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/mrballens-medical-mysteries/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Sanju’s Belly/One by One | 4 | MrBallen’s Medical Mysteries</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/2587833073/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 07:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/2587833073/</guid>
        <description>Podcast Description “Sanju’s Belly”
For decades, a 36-year-old Indian man has been plagued by a mysterious swelling in his belly. He refuses to see a doctor, until one day, he’s rushed to the hospital with breathing problems. When doctors operate, what they find inside him is horrific.
“One by One”
A family in 1860s London is struck by a mysterious illness that claims three of their children. When the city’s finest physician is brought in to treat the family&#39;s last surviving child, a three-year-old girl, he is baffled by her symptoms.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A Change in Fortune | 3 | MrBallen’s Medical Mysteries</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/2587833074/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 07:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/2587833074/</guid>
        <description>Podcast Description On a hot September day in 1986, a family in Goiania, Brazil, suddenly begin feeling sick after a celebration. The symptoms are horrific: vomiting, diarrhea, and bleeding. But one family member suspects something far worse. Her hunch soon leads to a devastating discovery.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Tigers on the Ceiling | 2 | MrBallen’s Medical Mysteries</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/2587833075/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 07:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/2587833075/</guid>
        <description>Podcast Description In 1951, dozens of people in the small French town of Pont St. Esprit fall ill with nausea, chills, and stomach pains. At first, the local doctor suspects food poisoning, but when the symptoms turn into hallucinations, violence, and even suicide, he realizes that something much more sinister is at play.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Ashes to Ashes | 1 | MrBallen’s Medical Mysteries</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/2587833076/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/2587833076/</guid>
        <description>Podcast Description In the Spring of 1986, a man discovers that his elderly father has been trapped inside his home that was devastated by a fire. But no one can figure out what caused the fire – or what exactly happened to the man’s father. When medical science can’t explain it, one investigator turns to a strange phenomenon to find answers.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Introducing: MrBallen&#39;s Medical Mysteries | MrBallen’s Medical Mysteries</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/2587833077/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/2587833077/</guid>
        <description>Podcast Description Follow MrBallen’s Medical Mysteries wherever you get your podcasts. You can binge the first 8 episodes, early and ad-free on Amazon Music. Download the Amazon Music app today.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
