<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Who shat on the floor at my wedding? on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/who-shat-on-the-floor-at-my-wedding/</link><description>Recent content in Who shat on the floor at my wedding? on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 08:47:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/who-shat-on-the-floor-at-my-wedding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>E13 - The Finale | Who shat on the floor at my wedding?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7990550001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 08:47:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7990550001/</guid><description>Podcast Description The team pull out all the stops to find out what really happened on the night of 11th August 2018.
Can a real lie detector test, a code breaker and a psychic shed any light on who shat on the floor at Helen and Karen’s wedding?
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>E12 - Let's get ready to fumble | Who shat on the floor at my wedding?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7990550002/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 09:52:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7990550002/</guid><description>Podcast Description A former boss with a chip on her shoulder&amp;hellip;. a bridesmaid who left town immediately after the wedding&amp;hellip;. a heavily pregnant woman overwhelmed with hormones&amp;hellip; and an alarming frisson between two unexpected guests…. Welcome to Episode 12. Hold onto your hats, you’re in for quite a ride as Detective Lauren Kilby goes on a rampage to unearth all final suspects in this case.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>E11 - Bad cop | Who shat on the floor at my wedding?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7990550003/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 08:12:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7990550003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Feeling like she was too lenient on Henk in Episode 6, Detective Lauren Kilby decides it’s time for BAD COP to come out. The man who was in the ladies bathroom for 4 hours is dragged back into the interrogation chambers for a second grilling, and it’s not pretty. Having run out of other options, the team starts to explore the idea of torture as a means to get a confession.</description></item><item><title>E10 - Size of a small fist | Who shat on the floor at my wedding?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7990550004/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 09:25:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7990550004/</guid><description>Podcast Description A brand new witness comes forward with some alarming new information. In light of this new worrying lead, the team seeks the expertise of someone with very high security clearance.&amp;nbsp; Is Detective Lauren Kilby investigating the right crime or was there something even more criminal that occurred during Helen and Karen’s wedding? Is this crime even a crime?
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>E9 - On his knees | Who shat on the floor at my wedding?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7990550005/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 10:46:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7990550005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Feeling the wool was pulled over her eyes in the previous episode, Detective Lauren Kilby turns on Karen - the very bride who brought her on to investigate this case. Is Karen the genuine victim of this crime? Or is she hiding something? What happens if a client becomes a suspect?
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>E8 - The Entertainer | Who shat on the floor at my wedding?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7990550006/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 08:23:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7990550006/</guid><description>Podcast Description The team unearth an important piece of evidence which brings a new sinister suspect to light. Forensic scientist Jo Millington comes on board to offer her expert opinion and opens up a new focus for the investigation: the animal kingdom. Detective Lauren Kilby and bride Karen feel they have no choice but to go to the zoo to assess possible suspects.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>E7 - File number 8653 | Who shat on the floor at my wedding?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7990550007/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 10:01:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7990550007/</guid><description>Podcast Description The team send a survey around to all guests, the results of which are alarming. Fingers are pointed at new suspects, the mother of the bride is interrogated and some new evidence comes forward that changes the direction of the whole investigation.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>E6 - Four hours in the bathroom | Who shat on the floor at my wedding?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7990550008/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 09:43:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7990550008/</guid><description>Podcast Description The team finally interrogate Henk - the MAN who was reported to have spent 4 hours in the LADIES bathroom during the wedding and who was found at the scene of the crime cleaning up the turd. Was Henk a hero or was there another reason why he was motivated to clean up that poo?
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>E5 - Comedy joke shop turd | Who shat on the floor at my wedding?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7990550009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 17:41:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7990550009/</guid><description>Podcast Description The team grill another key witness in their interrogation chambers, and grow increasingly uneasy as they discover that this week’s witness statement contradicts the story they heard in Episode 2. Who is lying and who is telling the truth? In an act of desperation the detective attempts to use unorthodox methods to force a confession.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>E4 - Solid as a rock | Who shat on the floor at my wedding?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7990550010/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 08:11:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7990550010/</guid><description>Podcast Description The team goes on a road trip back to the scene of the crime to see if they can unearth some important clues. Detective Lauren Kilby dazzles the brides with her innovative - never seen before - forensic examination techniques and they uncover something very surprising in a secret cupboard.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>E3 - Straight, straight, straight, lesbian | Who shat on the floor at my wedding?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7990550011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 18:35:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7990550011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Forensic psychologist Mike Berry gives the team some solid advice. They head to the red light district of Amsterdam and confront an ex lover who attended the wedding. Was this a crime of passion?
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>E2 - Three nuggets | Who shat on the floor at my wedding?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7990550012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 14:20:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7990550012/</guid><description>Podcast Description The team puts the USB ‘Police Edition’ polygraph test v2.0 through its paces and hook up bridesmaid / key witness, Emma, to obtain information. The test results give the trio something more than they bargained for as the investigation takes a surprising turn. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>E1 - A crime was committed | Who shat on the floor at my wedding?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7990550013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 10:38:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7990550013/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this very first episode we delve into the details of a crime that took place at a lesbian wedding in 2018. Join the brides, Helen and Karen, and ‘Detective’ Lauren Kilby as the trio explore possible motives and show you what tricks they have up their sleeves to crack this case. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trailer | Who shat on the floor at my wedding?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7990550014/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 15:25:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7990550014/</guid><description>Podcast Description A true story involving two brides and one turd. What do you do if someone defecates on the floor at your wedding? Re-evaluate your friends and family? No, you launch an investigation to find who did it. Join the brides, Helen Mclaughlin and Karen Whitehouse, and the extremely under-qualified “Detective” Lauren Kilby, as they interrogate wedding guests, hook bridesmaids up to polygraph machines and speak with top forensic experts in an attempt to crack the case.</description></item></channel></rss>