<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Nothing To Wear on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/nothing-to-wear/</link><description>Recent content in Nothing To Wear on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/nothing-to-wear/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Inside Mia Freedman's Wardrobe | Nothing To Wear</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5554600001/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5554600001/</guid><description>Podcast Description 7 Things I’d dress Mia Freedman In (if she let me).
Mia Freedman is known for her wardrobe full of colour, sequins and clashing prints. This episode, Leigh goes inside Mia’s insta-babble worthy closet (actually it’s a whole room) to ask all the questions you’ve wondered about Mia’s signature looks.
Mia shares her experience shopping with ADHD, how her style has evolved in her 40's and 50's and finally talks about whether or not she would start her own label.</description></item><item><title>11 Items Every Woman In Paris Is Wearing Right Now | Nothing To Wear</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5554600002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5554600002/</guid><description>Podcast Description 11 Things To Buy Now (that you'll wear all of 2024)
The French know just about everything when it comes fashion. So in honour of Leigh Campbell's recent trip to Paris, she's giving us all a sneak peak at what all the women are wearing on the Parisian streets.
Leigh will be joined by journalist and fashion icon Jacqui Felgate, to share tops, bottoms, shoes, fabric and colours you MUST get around for 2024.</description></item><item><title>Shopping Hacks To Save Money | Nothing To Wear</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5554600003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5554600003/</guid><description>Podcast Description 9 wardrobe classics under $150.
Tina Abeysekara is the founder of Trash To Treasure, a self described impulse shopper turned expert stylist and she might just be THE fashion hack oracle.
Get ready to learn acronyms like TOAG, three Cs and 2B2. Whilst they may not sound like fashion things, they are the key to saving you big dollars!
Plus, Leigh and Tina talk how to go from desk to dinner, affordable fashion and the perfect timeless pieces</description></item><item><title>Trinny Woodall on the Biggest Fashion Mistake Women Make | Nothing To Wear</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5554600004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5554600004/</guid><description>Podcast Description 7 pieces of clothing that won't make you feel invisible
There’s a theory that after a certain age, a woman gives up on her wardrobe.
This week Leigh Campbell, Mia Freedman and Trinny Woodall inspire women to find their style into their 40s and beyond. Sequins, colour and clothing confidence is always in season.
Plus, a group exorcism of the word mutton.
THE END BITS
Subscribe to Mamamia</description></item><item><title>BONUS: Meet The Woman Behind Quay Australia Sunglasses | Nothing To Wear</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5554600005/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5554600005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Recently we got the chance to interview Linda Hammond… now you may not know the name but I can bet that you might have heard about her internationally known brand - Quay Australia Sunnies.
She was interviewed by Elfy Scott on our Lady Startup Stories podcast and dished all about her journey working in fashion, growing her empire, being one of the first influencer-led fashion powerhouses, rubbing shoulders with the Kardashians and SO much more.</description></item><item><title>The Pair Of Jeans Every Woman Should Own | Nothing To Wear</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5554600006/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5554600006/</guid><description>Podcast Description 9 of the best wide-leg jeans money can buy.
With fashion changing so quickly, this week's episode is here to tell you what jeans are always IN. Leigh Campbell and personal shopper Fifi Milne take us through denim 101, breaking down: high waisted, wide leg, skinny, Mum and low rise jeans and how to wear them. As well as answering the age old question, is there a pair of jeans that works in the corporate world?</description></item><item><title>Kate Wasley Explains How To Enjoy Fashion At Every Size | Nothing To Wear</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5554600007/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5554600007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Model Kate Wasley on the best plus-size pieces to invest in right now
On todays episode Leigh Campbell is joined by plus size model Kate Wasley to talk about the importance of size inclusivity, how it feels to go shopping as a plus size woman in Australia AND of course, some of the best online shopping tips with brands that have caught up to size inclusivity!
Brands mentioned in this episode:</description></item><item><title>Summer Trends To Get Your Head Around | Nothing To Wear</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5554600008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5554600008/</guid><description>Podcast Description 10 throw-on shirts for easy summer dressing
It’s getting hot in here *cue Nelly song* and whilst we may want to take off all our clothes, on this weeks episode we are here to help you dress for the warmer months.
Fashion expert Leonie Barlow and Leigh Campbell discuss their favourite summer outfits as well as the Australian brands you need to know about. Get ready to learn that sun safety is the new sexy!</description></item><item><title>Dressy Outfits Every Woman Can Wear | Nothing To Wear</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5554600009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5554600009/</guid><description>Podcast Description 9 Slip Dresses That Will Take You Literally Anywhere
What is the difference between elevated cocktail and resort cocktail? Formal and black tie? And should you wear heels or ballet flats?
This episode Paula Joye breaks down all things evening wear. Spoiler, smart casual is cancelled.
Plus, Leigh gives us a sneak peek of the looks on and off the runway at Melbourne Fashion Week.
Products mentioned in this episode:</description></item><item><title>The 8 Bras &amp; Undies Every Woman Needs | Nothing To Wear</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5554600010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5554600010/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Best Bras For Big Boobs
Get ready to hack your underwear draw… we are diving into the world of bras and undies.
In this episode Leigh Campbell’s is joined by model and writer Jessica Vander Leahy who busts the myth of the t-shirt bra, prepare to be shocked! Plus how to dress your boobs for your cycle and how to find a bed bra (yes they exist)!</description></item><item><title>How To Wear Sneakers With Anything | Nothing To Wear</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5554600011/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5554600011/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 5 best sneaker trends to shop right now
Prefer comfort over fashion? Well lucky for you sneakers are a hot trend that is here to stay. In this episode, host Leigh Campbell and the queen of sneakers herself, Mia Freedman, unpack the key trends this season and how to style them in your current wardrobe. Whether it's to the office, to dinner or every day, learn how to wear sneakers confidently.</description></item><item><title>6 Trends To Instantly Upgrade Your Style | Nothing To Wear</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5554600012/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5554600012/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's time to figure out your summer wardrobe and we're here to help.
In this episode, host Leigh Campbell and fashion expert Leonie Barlow, unpack the 6 trends that are worth adding to your wardrobe this summer. Trends that make you feel your best self and maybe encourage you to take a risk or two while you're at it.
Products mentioned in this episode:
Commonry Oversized Shirt
Crochet Trend From Seed Heritage
Zara Pointy Toe Kitten Heels
Zara Metallic Denim Jacket
H&amp;amp;M Resort Sets
Sass &amp;amp; Bide Slip Dress Thrills Slip Dresses
Camilla &amp;amp; Marcs Set LMND The Chiara Shirt
THE END BITS</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Nothing To Wear | Nothing To Wear</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5554600013/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 05:33:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5554600013/</guid><description>Podcast Description The right outfit can transform your mood and lift your confidence. Nothing To Wear is the new weekly fashion podcast that helps all women, no matter their size, age or style.
Hosted by Leigh Campbell, with the help of the style collective who know best.
Listen to Nothing To Wear: Launching Wednesday 4th October.
Mamamia acknowledges the Traditional Owners of the Land we have recorded this podcast on, the Gadigal people of the Eora Nation.</description></item></channel></rss>