<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Burden of Guilt on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/burden-of-guilt/</link><description>Recent content in Burden of Guilt on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/burden-of-guilt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Burden of Guilt: Bonus Episode 1 – Let's Go Back to 1974 | Burden of Guilt</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5108380010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5108380010/</guid><description>Podcast Description If this case happened after 1974, would there have been a different outcome? In this bonus episode, we explore that question with some background on the groundbreaking legislation known as CAPTA (Child Abuse Prevention and Treatment Act). We also look at the history of people’s understanding and perception of child abuse.
If you would like to reach out to the Burden of Guilt Team, email us at burdenofguiltpod@gmail.com If you or someone you know is a victim of domestic abuse, please reach out and call the National Domestic Violence Hotline at 1-800-799-7233.</description></item><item><title>Burden of Guilt: Ep 8 - The Last Word | Burden of Guilt</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5108380009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5108380009/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the season finale of Burden of Guilt, Nancy and Tracyraquel discuss what this podcast journey has been like for her and clear up some unanswered questions with new details revealed in the series. We also sit down with the people closest to Tracyraquel and hear how her strength, bravery, and compassion have impacted them for the better. If you would like to reach out to the Burden of Guilt Team, email us at burdenofguiltpod@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Burden of Guilt: Ep 7 - Are You Kidding Me? | Burden of Guilt</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5108380008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5108380008/</guid><description>Podcast Description The jury from Jan Barry Sandlin’s second trial returns a verdict. When it seems like Tracyraquel would finally find justice for Matthew, the defense comes back with a new strategy. A new advocate steps in for Jan Barry Sandlin. Tracyraquel shares more about the two souls she feels are connected to her story. If you would like to reach out to the Burden of Guilt Team, email us at burdenofguiltpod@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Burden of Guilt: Ep 6 - Battlefield | Burden of Guilt</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5108380007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5108380007/</guid><description>Podcast Description After Judge Fuller declared a mistrial, the Prosecution must once again set out to prove that Tracyraquel’s father, Jan Barry Sandlin killed her baby brother. As the second trial begins, the Defense comes prepared with an entirely new strategy. Would trial 2 be the time justice is finally served for Matthew? If you would like to reach out to the Burden of Guilt Team, email us at burdenofguiltpod@gmail.com If you or someone you know is a victim of domestic abuse, please reach out and call the National Domestic Violence Hotline at 1-800-799-7233.</description></item><item><title>Burden of Guilt: Ep 5 - Game On | Burden of Guilt</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5108380006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5108380006/</guid><description>Podcast Description With Jan Barry Sandlin’s murder trial approaching, Prosecutors unearth new evidence that change their entire understanding of the case. As the trial begins, Tracyraquel confronts one of her toughest challenges yet; coming face to face with Jan Barry Sandlin in the courtroom. This is the first time Tracyraquel has been in the same room with her father since she was a little girl. The trial and the long road to justice for baby Matthew begins.</description></item><item><title>Burden of Guilt: Ep 4 - The Body Keeps the Score | Burden of Guilt</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5108380005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5108380005/</guid><description>Podcast Description With Jan Barry Sandlin’s murder trial approaching, Prosecutors unearth new evidence that changes their entire understanding of the case. As the trial begins, Tracyraquel confronts one of her toughest challenges yet; coming face to face with Jan Barry Sandlin in the courtroom. This is the first time Tracyraquel has been in the same room with her father since she was a little girl. The trial and the long road to justice for baby Matthew begins.</description></item><item><title>Burden of Guilt: Ep 3 - Ashes to Ashes | Burden of Guilt</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5108380001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 04:06:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5108380001/</guid><description>Podcast Description With Jan’s upcoming parole hearing, Tracyraquel was in a race against time to keep her father behind bars. So Tracyraquel pressed her mother for any information that would keep him in prison. After a fateful phone call, her mother’s admission about the day Matthew died was shocking. But it also led investigators to do something nobody could imagine 27 years later. If you would like to reach out to the Burden of Guilt Team, email us at burdenofguiltpod@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Burden of Guilt: Ep 2 - Physics | Burden of Guilt</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5108380002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 04:06:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5108380002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tracyraquel was always unsure how her baby brother died. When she finally got access to the official medical report, it felt suspicious and incomplete. But the more questions she asked, the more people dismissed her...except for one person. His shocking revelation and a simple lesson in physics pushed Tracyraquel to get law enforcement involved. Together, they’d go to war to expose the truth. If you would like to reach out to the Burden of Guilt Team, email us at burdenofguiltpod@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Burden of Guilt: Ep 1 - Age of Innocence | Burden of Guilt</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5108380003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5108380003/</guid><description>Podcast Description The loss of her baby brother has haunted Tracyraquel Berns ever since she was 2 years old. Growing up, her questions about her brother’s death were met with beatings from her father. As an adult, Tracyraquel did her own investigation and what she discovered would change everything. It caused a burden that she would carry with her for the rest of her life. That burden of guilt coupled with a nagging suspicion that there was more to the story, led Tracyraquel to revisit her abusive and dysfunctional childhood in a quest for the whole truth.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Burden of Guilt | Burden of Guilt</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5108380004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5108380004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Burden of Guilt is an emotionally harrowing audio docu-series that tells the story of Tracyraquel Berns, a woman who has spent four decades at the center of one of the most bizarre and disturbing criminal cases in American History – surrounding the devastating and mysterious death of her baby brother. This podcast explores Tracyraquel’s pursuit for justice and her journey to confront the burden of guilt she has carried with her for the majority of her life.</description></item></channel></rss>