<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bang On on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/bang-on/</link><description>Recent content in Bang On on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 16:52:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/bang-on/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>#273: Bang Fam Bang Back | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960001/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s our final episode for 2023 and Myf and Zan are handing over the reins of Bang On to you, Bang Fam, for an epic Bang Back.
We love this episode, not just cos we get to hear from our beautiful community of Bang Fam, but also cos you gift us with an epic list of summer recommends. Books, TV shows, podcasts, even beanies get a look in.</description></item><item><title>#272: Rizz, Taylor’s TIME, Year in Review | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960002/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s December! And that means we’re wrapping everything (including presents) to see out another big year. It’s official, the Oxford Dictionary has got the charisma, or the Rizz, as their Word of the Year would have it. Taylor Swift has been named TIME mag’s Person of the Year, and Mariah has been knocked off the Christmas Tree by a fellow icon. We’re stoked.
And as everyone wraps their Best Of lists for the year, Myf and Zan cast their pop culture eyes and ears back across our fave moments with the Bang Fam.</description></item><item><title>#271: Dolly Cheerleader, Word of the Year, Spinal Tap Sequel | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hello Bang Fam! It’s almost December, and if that doesn’t make your head spin then this past week in music, art, life, and stuff, will.
Dolly Parton continues to slay, performing at the Thanksgiving Halftime Show in a cheerleader outfit for the NRL, but some people (a dude) ain’t having it. We’re living for the responses to his opinion that a 77 year old woman should “dress her age”.</description></item><item><title>#270: Ghost Diana, Andre 3000’s flute album, Saltburn | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960004/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a veritable smorgasbord of pop culture this week, and yes we’re kicking off with the slide into soap opera for The Crown. It’s final season is upon us and oh boy, it’s a bit cooked. Zan is watching it all.
Nat Bass has revealed she’s in a loving relationship with a woman; how good is good news? And it’s Marie Claire’s turn with their Women of the Year issue, and it’s all about the Tillies.</description></item><item><title>#269: ARIAs goss, Jared Leto’s climb, Towel skirt | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960005/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re fresh from the ARIAs and have all the behind the scenes chat to dish for you. Troye Sivan dominated, and he’s had a bit of a week aye? Being parodied by Timothee Chalamet, and being nominated for a Grammy. But the Grammy’s are being dominated by women overall, and we love to see them finally reflecting the culture.
Jared Leto has climbed one of the most famous buildings in the world, and we want to know why.</description></item><item><title>#268: Nipple bra, 1989, Not Hot Halloween | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are back and there’s a lot to catch up on. Like actively choosing to celebrate the headlights being on. Yep, we’re discussing Kimmy K’s nipple bra.
Dolly Parton is reportedly going to be presenting an award at the ARIA’s and with both of us heading along we’re wondering if this is our moment. And with Taylor Swift’s “1989” re-recording out, a great long read remembering that time Ryan Adams covered us has us thinking about how women’s pop music is digested differently to men’s singer-songwriter approach.</description></item><item><title>See you next week! | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey Bang Fam! We'll be back next week with a big episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#267: Britney Spears, Goatees, AI is a thirst trap | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960008/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s finally here, Britney Spears highly anticipated memoir “The Woman In Me” is out, and Zan has read it all in one hit. We go in with all you need to know, as Britney reclaims her story. It’s been a big week for Beyonce too, as we mark 10 years since she visited Brunswick, and she releases a new perfume to mark the occasion. Maybe not related, but we’ll say they are.</description></item><item><title>#266: Britney’s Memoir, Jada’s Revelations, Nicolas Cage’s Shopping | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960009/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s raining memoirs, and we’ve got the dish on Britney Spear’s forthcoming tell all, and Jada Pinkett-Smith’s mic drop revelations in her just released “Worthy”. Dolly is lobbing in too, she loves a good book, and we’re here for it.
Nicholas Cage is shooting a movie in south-west WA and we’re living for the reportage around his local spottings. And on the East Coast, the Dugong is being pitched as the perfect Olympic mascot.</description></item><item><title>#265: Beckham, Gaffa Banana, Silent Walking | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960010/</guid><description>Podcast Description #265: Beckham, Gaffa Banana, Silent Walking
It’s been a full on week, and we’re here to give you a little reprieve if you need it. Fat Bear Week is here to help us, we have a winner, she is amazing, and we celebrate Grazer. Meanwhile Bang Fam are rallying around the Peregrine Falcons after their fortunes took a turn.
The conceptual art piece “Comedian” (a banana gaffa taped to a wall) is coming to Melbourne for the NGV’s Triennial, so it’s time for Myf’s critical art eye.</description></item><item><title>#264: Beyoncé’s Renaissance film, U2’s Sphere, Stevie Nicks’ Barbie | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are frothing at the news that Beyoncé will bring her Renaissance tour to the big screen; we share what we know so far. In Vegas, U2 are putting on their own show. In a sphere. We review it (without having seen it).
Stevie Nicks is being immortalised as a Barbie, and it’s “goodbye girl boss, hello snail girl” as some women switch their priorities from hustle to hammock.</description></item><item><title>#263: Bears, Drew Barrymore, Russell Brand | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 15:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are back after a break and catching up on the last two weeks of music, art, life and stuff. A lot has happened. Split ups, bears in Japan, brush-turkeys at Myf’s house…
The writers strike has ended too, but one star broke early and the backlash against Drew Barrymore’s decision to return to work has been sizeable. Meanwhile Rolling Stone co-founder Jann Wenner has decided that if you’re not male or white you’re not a master, and all those covers and Rock and Roll Hall of Fame history is starting to make sense.</description></item><item><title>#262: Kylie and Timothée, Burning Man, Bird Sniffer | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wow, what a week. We really do cover it all on Bang On and partake in a healthy amount of googling, too. Yep, Myf and Zan are back to make sense of the week that was; music, art, life, and birds.
Kylie Jenner and Timothée Chalamet’s rumoured dating has been publicly confirmed in the VIP tower at Beyonce’s LA show. Smooching and smoking was just the pressie she wanted.</description></item><item><title>#261: The forcible kiss, Cat Person film, …And Just Like That finale | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960014/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 15:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960014/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a big week for Bang On, and a lot can happen in seven days. Last ep the revolt against Spanish Football Federation President Luis Rubiales was just kicking off, since then there have been calls for his dismissal, rallies in the street, hunger strikes, and a fair dose of blokes claiming victim hood. We catch up on it, and an excellent piece by Annabel Crabb that explains and eviscerates it all.</description></item><item><title>#260: Matildas legacy, AFL closet, Britney &amp; Sam | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf’s made her road trip north and has all the news from life on the road with Vyv. There’s heaps to catch up on too, as Myf and Zan reunite to reflect on the Matildas wins and how they celebrated. There’s a lot of talk of legacy too, and the changes being made in women’s sport overall.
One thing that hasn’t changed is inappropriate behaviour at the workplace: Spanish Football Federation boss, we’re looking at you.</description></item><item><title>#259: Matildas, Before Smartphones, Only Murders | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960016/</guid><description>Podcast Description The nation is screaming “goooooooooooooal!” as the Matildas bring in the numbers and we froth over football in the Women’s World Cup. Myf and Zan are revelling in it all, and what this moment will do for girls in the future.
If you’re always being told you’re wasting your time on your phone, get ready for a hot take from The Atlantic that has us shoot. Were we always wasting our time?</description></item><item><title>#258: Logies, Doja Cat, John Farnham | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan went to the Logies and we have goss. The wild red carpet, the neverending awards ceremony, and which celebs Zan pulled a netball manoeuvre on.
Meanwhile Doja Cat has been going off on one on socials, we dig into why – and how parasocial relationships are changing the invisible contract between artist and fan. But was there one in the first place?
Have you ever put deodorant on your face?</description></item><item><title>#257: Sinead, Greta makes history, Cocaine shark | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960018/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan wake to the sad news of Sinead O’Connor’s death, and reflect on her power, her protest, and her extraordinary voice which lifted us and gave a voice to so many without one.
Barbie has made history at the box office, with Greta Gerwig pulling in the biggest opening weekend by a female film director ever. But some conservative are in an absolute tizz about it.</description></item><item><title>#256: Barbenheimer, Actors Strike, Selling Out | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960019/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a huge episode this week, as Myf and Zan finally see the Barbie film and we’ll give you our (spoiler free) thoughts. Zan backed it up with Oppenheimer too, so dig into that movie sandwich.
Both films squeezed in their premieres just before American actors joined their writer colleagues in a strike; we unpack what it all means for the people who create all the stuff we bang on about every week, and the future of the industry (and what will be on on our screens in a year’s time).</description></item><item><title>#255: Jonah Hill, “Girl Dinner”, Wham! | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 15:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960020/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been a big week for showing the receipts. If you’re catching up on what is going on with Jonah Hill and his ex GF Sarah Brady, we’ll fill in the blanks. But will we be talking about it in Threads? A week in from Zuckerberg’s take on Twitter and we’re wondering what it’ll be and how much time we have for more social media apps.
Speaking of which, a TikTok food trend “girl dinner” has a lot of people talking, and Britney Spears’ highly anticipated tell-all memoir has been given its release date.</description></item><item><title>#254: Mattel movies, Adele dares you, Beige-fluencers | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are back and Zan has the goss from the Barbie press conference in Bondi last week. It’s the first film to come from Mattel’s film arm, but it certainly won’t be the last. We discover the plans for Polly Pocket, He-Man, and some toys you never imagine could be movies.
People are throwing more unhinged stuff on stage, and we try to understand this cultural “moment”, meanwhile women can finally wear non-white undies at Wimbledon.</description></item><item><title>#253: Glastonbury, And Just Like That, Barbie Dreamhouse | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960022/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been a huge weekend at Glastonbury with all kinds of wild things going down. We wrap it all; from Tilda Swinton and Cate Blanchett’s cameos, to Lana and Lewis singalongs. Not to mention Rina Sawayama’s pointed take down of Matty Healy.
While we’re talking live music, people seem to be throwing stuff at musicians of late. Notably, phones. Why? And we’ve watched the first two eps of “And Just Like That”, we’ll share our thoughts.</description></item><item><title>#252: Indiana Jones, Microscopic Handbag, Pharrell at LV | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 13:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960023/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a treat for the eyeballs this week, as Zan gets a preview of the new Indiana Jones film. You’ll hear her take, and what Phoebe Waller-Bridge does for the franchise. The trailer for Sophia Coppola’s “Priscilla” movie just dropped too, and we are ready, Taft in hand.
An Australian lolly is about to be discontinued, and Myf has some hot takes on the chewy classic, and with the Sussex’s Spotify deal coming to an end, we wonder if the ex-Royals will ever be able to move forward if people only ever want them to look back?</description></item><item><title>#251: The Idol, Jennifer Coolidge at Vivid, Beatles AI song | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960024/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960024/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been another bumper week, and we’re here to unpack it all with you. Zan saw Jennifer Coolidge and Mike White in convo with an 8000 strong crowd of high end gays, and gives you the highlights of a life affirming conversation.
The Idol has been getting attention for all the wrong reasons, specifically one of the worst sex scenes in TV history. We bring in a special guest to unpack it.</description></item><item><title>#250: Padam Padam, Apple Vision Pro, Succession | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960025/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960025/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s our 250th episode and a bumper Bang! A very Padam to you all, yep we’ll chat about the epic career of Kylie who continues to hit the charts. Danni is doing pretty well too, while we’re here.
Given it’s a special occasion, a special guest and member of the Bang Fam is dropping by. Virginia Trioli (AKA DJ Trigger) shares her thoughts on Sex and the City, female friendships, ghosting, all of it.</description></item><item><title>#249: Alone, Taylor and Matty, Hipster turns 20 | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960026/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960026/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been a big week of finales, and we celebrate the iconic winner of Alone Australia and those moments following the reveal. Succession and Ted Lasso have wound up too, but don’t be scared; Myf is still catching up on Succession, and Zan on Lasso, so no spoilers here for now.
As we hit record, breaking news about Samantha AKA Kim Cattrall’s appearance on the Sex In the City reboot has us shook (and jazzed).</description></item><item><title>#248: Tina Turner, Beyoncé, Jury Duty | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Just hours after we hear the news, Myf and Zan pay tribute to Tina Turner; an icon of music, a survivor who became a Queen, and an inspiration to so many. From our personal recollections, to chatting with her collaborators about working with her, it’s all about Tina as we reunite for Bang On this week.
Beyoncé has also been living large this week, after Zan caught her incredible set on Saturday night in Edinburgh.</description></item><item><title>#247: Eurovision, Coronation, Dolly Parton’s Rockstar | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960028/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960028/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a UK Hun, I mean, BANG! Myf is in Liverpool in the thick of Eurovision 2023 and has the kind of access we’ve come to know and love. Come for the gossip, stay for Croatia’s entry.
We take the temperature on the ground and online after the King’s Coronation. That was weird. In more exciting news, an attendee at the LA Philharmonic is having a euphoric time out and about.</description></item><item><title>#246: And Just Like That, Rom-Coms, Life Coach Cult | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960029/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960029/</guid><description>Podcast Description As we hit record, the official trailer for S02 of “And Just Like That” (aka the Sex and the City reboot) has dropped. Do we care? Of course we do. Next door on HBO, a new Harry Potter series is brewing with some changes afoot.
The death of Barry Humphries has drawn different reactions from all corners. Sammy J captures the complexities of farewelling the comic who said some crook stuff in his final years.</description></item><item><title>#245: Mischa Barton, Frank Ocean, Beef | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960030/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960030/</guid><description>Podcast Description The world of pop culture really delivered this week. If you’re confused, we got you. Kicking off with why Mischa Barton (yes, of The OC) is coming to Erinsborough. Yep, the Neighbours reboot just got bigger.
With the coronation of King Charles on the horizon, and commemorative dish has been announced, but Myf is not impressed. Meanwhile in the States, the Coachella Music Festival’s first weekend had some highs and lows, with everyone talking about Frank Ocean’s headline set.</description></item><item><title>#244: Therapy Speak, Alone Australia, Succession S04 E03 | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960031/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are back with you and relocated, with Myf setting up shop in a new city once again. Can you feel a paddle steamer bang on coming?
Tupperware’s future is uncertain, with the legendary air-tight product experiencing a downfall in the modern day. We dig into their legacy, and what it means for our beloved spew bowls. And speaking of the olden days, a journo switching off streaming and switching back on free to air TV has interesting results.</description></item><item><title>#243: Barbie, Fatphobia, Stealth Wealth | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960032/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960032/</guid><description>Podcast Description #243: Barbie, Fatphobia, Stealth Wealth
It’s another wild week and we’re here to make sense of it, support donkeys in tow. The new trailer for the Barbie movie has dropped and we are salivating at the pink plastic universe coming our way. Rod Stewart has been making trips to Bunnings while in town, we explain why.
With Ozempics, The Whale, and the Kardashians new looks, writer Rebecca Shaw senses the noughties fatphobia is making a comeback.</description></item><item><title>#242: Succession, Eurythmics Nepo Baby, Pope’s Puffer | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960033/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are back to wrap the week that was, including Myf’s debut on the big screen and some ch-ch-changes in Zan’s world. It’s looking certain that White Lotus S03 will be set in Thailand, while in New York City the Roys are back for Succession’s final season. We discuss all we know so far.
Gwyneth Paltrow is the gift that keeps giving, and her civil trial for a skiing mishap has been one of the most entertaining and ridiculous stories of the week.</description></item><item><title>#241: Sofia Coppola’s daughter, Gwyneth’s rectal ozone therapy, Courtney Love on Hall of Fame | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960034/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Well it’s certainly been a time online. Sofia Coppola and Thomas Mars’ daughter was grounded, got bored, and inadvertently launched her filmmaking career on TikTok. Confused? We’ll explain it all. Meanwhile TikTok is going absolutely off chops after Gwyneth’s appearance on a wellness podcast has her espousing some questionable health approaches. What is rectal ozone therapy? Again, we got you.
The nominations for 2023’s Rock n’ Roll Hall of Fame have drawn an excellent op-ed from Courtney Love.</description></item><item><title>#240: Oscars, Hugh Grant, Meg White | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960035/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960035/</guid><description>Podcast Description #240: Oscars, Hugh Grant, Meg White
Ooh it’s a big one this week, as we unpack THE awards ceremony of every year, the Oscars. From the champagne (beige) carpet, to what Hugh Grant said on it. Little donkeys and Cocaine Bear’s. We celebrate the reason for the season too, the incredible and historic wins in a year dominated by Everything Everywhere All At Once.
The Oscars gift bags get a look in too, for better and worse.</description></item><item><title>#239: IWD, Circumboob, Jamie Lee Curtis | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960036/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960036/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been another big week for Myf and Zan, in private and public, and we catch up on Bjerth, missing cues on the Rocky Horror stage, and meeting the guy who wrote “I Want It That Way”. It’s also 6 years to the day that Bang On first popped into your podcast feed! Oh yes, we go back to the tapes…
We were chatting International Women’s Day then, and still are now.</description></item><item><title>#238: Jennifer Coolidge, Subjective Age, Queerstralia | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960037/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are catching up on the week that was, and whether Harry is still doing shoey’s. W Magazine has just unveiled a phenomenal cover shoot with woman of the moment Jennifer Coolidge, as crafted by Directors of the moment “Daniels”. Yep, the people who put together Everything Everywhere All At Once have made a magical world for J Cool and it’s as good as it sounds.</description></item><item><title>Bang On is Back ! Cocaine Bear, Big Red Boot, Cunk On Earth | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960038/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960038/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re back, and 2023 is already as wild as we imagined it would be. Myf and Zan catch up on what’s gone down since we last banged on; notably Myf is now best friends with Jason Donovan.
Zan watched Cocaine Bear and lets you know whether it’s worth the ticket, and Harry Styles is continuing the strange and disgusting “tradition” of drinking from his own shoe while in Australia.</description></item><item><title>Bang On: back soon | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf Warhurst and Zan Rowe are getting ready to get back in the ring and wrap-up your week in art, life, music, faaaarshun and everything in between.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#236: Bang Back: We cap off 2022 with our Bang Fam’s recommends! | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960040/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960040/</guid><description>Podcast Description What a bloody year. Well done, you made it! And for our final episode, we’re throwing Bang On over to you – our beautiful Bang Fam – for some excellent summer recommends.
Myf and Zan will wrap our favourite (and most cooked) moments of the year too, and ask the question we posed at the start of 2022: has the vibe actually shifted? Yes, that was this year.</description></item><item><title>#235: Goblin Mode immortalised, Balenciaga BDSM, Cocaine Bear | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960041/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960041/</guid><description>Podcast Description White Lotus is winding up and we’re on the edge of our seats, but importantly – which character would we most like to take back to our fancy hotel room? Myf and Zan are digging into a brilliant thinkpiece on just that. A couple of weeks ago we got the Macquarie Word of the Year, now it’s Oxford’s turn and the results prove that dictionaries are Bang Fam.</description></item><item><title>#234: Bang On Live in the Barossa | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960042/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 13:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan bring Bang On live to the Bang Fam for the first time in 3 years! As a part of the Grapes of Mirth festival, we head to the Barossa Valley in South Australia for some woine time, with special guests Tom Gleeson and Geraldine Hickey.
Did you know Tom is Bang Fam? Believe. And wait till you hear what Gez is Banging Back about. Join us for a big love in, in the Barrel Room of a vineyard, as we reunite with our Bang Fam.</description></item><item><title>#233: Kath &amp; Kim, Dolly Inducted, Clitoris Mascot | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960043/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are back and oh boy, there’s a lot to catch up on. We’ve been glued to the telly with the Kath &amp;amp; Kim specials, news of Neighbours returning (what?), and the promise of even more White Lotus.
The Macquarie Dictionary are offering up their contenders for word/phrase of the year and there are some Bang On classics in the mix. And speaking of Bachelor’s Handbags, there’s more bird talk this week.</description></item><item><title>#232: Chicken Guy, Heroin Chic, Goop Gift Guide | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960044/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are back to flick through the week that was and explain WTF happened. A man in Philly has eaten 40 rotisserie chickens in 40 days, there’s that. Speaking of birds, Myf has an important update on her beloved Collins St Peregrine Falcons. Meanwhile Twitter’s “imminent demise” has a few people switching to the Mastodon social platform, we explain what it is.
If you’ve noticed that celebs have flipped back to the “heroin chic” look of the 90’s, you’re not alone.</description></item><item><title>#231: Heidi’s Worm, Elon’s Twitter, Coming Out | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960045/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960045/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s Halloween and you know what that means: celebs dressing up in hot costumes.
Not so with Heidi Klum, Halloween’s biggest fan, who has topped all of her previous efforts by dressing up as a giant earthworm. We talk about why this slimy turd is so compelling.
Speaking of scary, several lions escaped from their enclosure in Taronga Zoo this week, and we’re wondering what they were looking for.</description></item><item><title>#230: Björk, Beyoncé, Breaking up with Ye | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960046/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960046/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been another headline filled week, but never fear – Myf and Zan are your cliff notes, and making sense of it all.
It’s been a big week in music too, with Björk announcing her first live performances in Australia since 2008! Taylor Swift dropped an album, ICYMI, and Tina Knowles-Lawson is once again leaking all the good stuff re: her daughter on her socials, including a Beyoncé World Tour.</description></item><item><title>#229: Bad Sisters, Olivia Wilde’s salad, Hot chook handbag | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960047/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are back and oh boy there’s a lot to catch up on.
Much of it food related, weirdly; from roast chicken handbags as art, to butter boards (wtaf), and Olivia Wilde’s “special salad dressing”. James Cordern is being banned from eating out, for good measure.
More locally, the Bureau of Meteorology caused it’s own storm with an attempt at rebranding this week. And artists across the globe are cancelling tours and speaking out against rising costs, unsustainable touring wages, and the mental health impacts of working in an industry that is so demanding.</description></item><item><title>#228: Funeral Spider, Nick Cave’s Pottery, Mariah's Grunge | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960048/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yeah look it’s a bit of a weird one this week. All good, Myf Warhurst and Zan Rowe make sense of it for you as per.
The Queen’s funeral has taken place and in amongst the meticulously planned ceremony, some outlier events have all of us talking. Yes, we’re referring to the spider, and that bit of paper on the ground. The end of this long period of mourning, respect, and reflection has been felt in different ways across different communities.</description></item><item><title>#227: The Emmys, The Little Mermaid, The Monarchy | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960049/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan make sense of a week dominated by one news event, but with plenty of pop culture tugging at our attention.
The Emmy’s provided plenty of reminders of TV we loved, missed, or clean forgot that we watched in the first place, and a rare magical TV moment as Sheryl Lee Ralph took to the stage. Staying with the screen, the trailer for Disney’s live action remake of The Little Mermaid got a whole lot of attention, but we’re mostly here for the real time reacs from young black girls at the Ariel reveal.</description></item><item><title>#226: Don’t Worry Darling, Teenage Dirtbags, The Bear | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960050/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960050/</guid><description>Podcast Description What a smorgasbord this week has been. Grab the popcorn, Myf Warhurst and Zan Rowe are going in.
If you’re confused about all the hullabaloo around Olivia Wilde’s new film Don’t Worry Darling, don’t worry – we were too. We explain it all, and debrief on what’s driving this ferocious hunger for gossip.
A Reddit thread on sex soundtracks has the internet heaving, while Kim Kardashian’s bum makes the front page again.</description></item><item><title>#225: Britney Spears, Taylor Swift impersonations, Doggy Parton | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960051/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf’s back from Bali and she and Zan have a lot to bang on about.
Pool times, hanging with the PM, all of it. It’s been a big week for Britney too, with the release of her new Elton John collab, and a 22 minute audio recording detailing her conservatorship.
We debrief on the MTV VMA’s too (WTF), and the biggest mic drop of the night; Taylor Swift’s announcement of her new album.</description></item><item><title>#224: Freya, Tommy Lee, Music in your 30’s | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960052/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are back to make sense of the week that was, and mourn the unnecessary loss of Freya the 600kg walrus. The Bang Box has been overflowing with your sweet emails, and also some nice surprises from young nudists.
Speaking of getting your gear off, Tommy Lee did, but who asked for it? We dissect the double standards of Instagram censorship. And an editorial on our connection to music as we age has us thinking about our own musical journeys.</description></item><item><title>#223: Olivia Newton-John, Malcolm Gladwell, Nudists | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960053/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are here to make sense of the week that was in all its lows and highs.
We’ve lost some icons of late, and we pay tribute and show thanks. Meanwhile Malcolm Gladwell reckons we need to get back to the office which is frankly a BIT RICH coming from him, Mr Laptop on the Couch.
Naturism, or getting in the nuddy, is making a comeback in these pandemic times and we investigate why.</description></item><item><title>#222: Neighbours finale, Beyonce’s Renaissance, Got the Ick? | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960054/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are back and absolutely champing at the bit to bang on this week.
Which is a perfect horse reference for Beyoncé’s Renaissance album (see: cover art). We go in deep on all facets of this instant club classic, and some of the backlash it’s received. We also dip into a larger discussion around releasing, then changing an album. Is an album, as a “finished” piece of art, much more malleable in the digital age?</description></item><item><title>#221: Vabbing, Hathahate, Joni Mitchell | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960055/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960055/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is one of those weeks where Bang On truly has it all.
Myf and Zan start with a 600kg sun-loving walrus, and end with vagina perfume.
In between, we wrap the week that was, including the solving of the mysterious Somerton Man (Zan wants to rewind to when he was a mystery). A teaser for the new Black Panther movie has us in a tizz, particularly cos one of our faves is in it.</description></item><item><title>#220: Bennifer Wedding, Performative charity, Reclaiming HOT | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960056/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 16:01:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Zan and Myf are back and have lots to catch you up on! It’s a time of celebration too, with J Lo and Ben Affleck hitting Vegas for a quickie wedding (20 years in the making).
Meanwhile on the streets of Melbourne an act of “kindness” has gone viral for two very different reasons, and we’re digging into our reactions to performative charity and who it targets. And a piece on the “end of ambition” has us thinking about the cumulative effect of everything that’s hit us over the past two years, and how it’s shifted us, across generations, forever.</description></item><item><title>#219: Barbie, Thor, Looking Black | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960057/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 17:47:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960057/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been a whirlwind coupla weeks and Myf and Zan have heaps to catch up on. TV adventures as the ABC celebrates 90, book deadlines, and what it’s like to be in a trigger ban state when Roe V Wade is overturned. In more joyful news, Rihanna has become the youngest female billionaire, and Only Murders in the Building is back (with a helluva guest cast).
The internet is frothing at images emerging from the Barbie movie shoot, and we catch you up on everything you need to know.</description></item><item><title>#218: Beyoncé, Logies, Messy Millennial Women | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960058/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960058/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s the return of Queen B, and we are bouncin’ to her new single and how perfectly it captures the moment.
Like all things Beyoncé, there are layers and layers, and we dig in.
Myf has been hitting the red carpet for the Logies, so we catch up on all the goss from TV’s night of nights.
An opinion piece on the popularity of “messy millennial women” on TV has caught our eye; is it becoming a trope?</description></item><item><title>#217: Rebel Wilson, Britney marries, Lizzo | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960059/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ooh it’s been a big week. Britney got hitched (a dream wedding with a dream reception guestlist), while Lizzo’s new single features a word we weren’t expecting to hear in 2022.
The outing of Rebel Wilson by a gossip columnist has dominated discussion; and made for some hot shoe shuffles and stumbles in the apology department. Meanwhile the dress Kim Kardashian wore to the Met Gala has been returned to the museum, but Marilyn’s iconic sheer frock is looking a little different.</description></item><item><title>#216: Platty Jubes, Madonna, Top Gun Maverick | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960060/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 14:30:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan continue to celebrate Kate Bush’s resurgence into popular consciousness, and rejoice in the discovery of her official website.
The iceberg lettuce shortage has us talking leaf, while on the other side of the pond the Platty Jubes is trying to shore up support for the monarchy.
Meanwhile the European Union has stepped in to decree that there should only be one charger for all devices (hallelujah), and Julia Garner is set to portray Madonna in a new biopic written and directed by Madge herself.</description></item><item><title>#215: Kate Bush, Swedish Dinner, Gaslit | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960061/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 17:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960061/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Zoomers have discovered Kate Bush and while everyone Gen X and older cries “where have you been?!”, we’re revelling in the celebration of one of music’s great icons.
The ruling for the Johnny Depp v Amber Heard defamation trial has just been handed down, and we debrief on what it all means. And the internet is shook by the news that Swedish people don’t feed their guests? Myf and Zan are here to investigate.</description></item><item><title>#214: Women vote, Kravis wed, Ru Paul’s All Stars | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960062/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 15:05:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960062/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a new day and a new government in Australia, as Myf and Zan emerge post election. The rise of women’s voices has been heard, and we debrief on the seismic shift in the electorate.
Meanwhile new PM Anthony Albanese's dog Toto is getting roasted online, and Kourtney Kardashian has wed Travis Barker but what was served at the reception?
A new app called BeReal promises to cure us of our social media obsessions, while we’re all obsessed with the lewk of Balenciaga’s new runway show.</description></item><item><title>#213: Eurovision debrief, Kendall’s cucumber, Meme culture | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960063/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 13:25:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf has literally just landed, and is back to spill the tea on what went down at Eurovision.
Kendall Jenner’s cucumber cutting technique has the internet agog, and speaking of online pile ons we take a look at the bizarre meme-ing of the Amber Heard and Johnny Depp defamation trial.
It’s been a busy travel time for Myf and Zan, but of course we’ve made time for consuming culture!</description></item><item><title>#212: Met Gala, Female “juniors”, Balldo | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960064/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 14:55:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960064/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s fashun Christmas! And we’re real time reacting to the red carpet at the Met Gala as the “gilded age” is revealed. Who nailed it? Who phoned it in? And who wore puffa??
A timely biography on Anna Wintour has us reflecting on her power too, and recommending one helluva fashion doco.
Women are increasingly naming their kids after themselves, a la “junior” boys, and a great piece on the patriarchal conventions of names has us thinking.</description></item><item><title>#211: Elon Musk, Cynthia Plaster Caster, Jonathan Franzen | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960065/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 16:12:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960065/</guid><description>Podcast Description We're back after a couple of weeks of adventures, some less pungent than others. And in the time since we last met, Elon Musk has bought Twitter for US$44 billion. We unpack what it might mean for the site, and who benefits from the free speech he touts.
A short read on the (hopeful) death of the handshake has us thinking about what we learned and what we’ve left behind in the pandemic.</description></item><item><title>#210: Britney Baby, Bieber’s Balenciaga, Life &amp; Beth | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960066/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 10:30:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960066/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s an election free zone, as we wrap our loving arms around you and talk shit about the week that was. Britney has some joy to share too, with the announcement of her pregnancy. And we debrief on the most talked about fashun of the Grammy’s; Justin Bieber’s oversized suit and Balenciaga Crocs.
In sad music news, we reflect on the legacy of Chris Bailey of The Saints, and Big Day Out founder Ken West, who both touched our lives in different ways.</description></item><item><title>#209: Oscars hot takes, Oscars fashun, Vulva Spacecraft | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960067/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 14:56:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Well it has been a big week for hot takes. Our heads are spinning, but we’re making sense of all the ways the world reacted to “the slap” at this year’s Oscar ceremony. If you’re wondering what else happened on the night, good news; plenty of good stuff. We’ll wrap on the big highlights and most moving moments. And debrief on the best lewks on the red carpet. The Academy Awards has sucked up a lot of time this week, but don’t worry we’ve found a corner to chat about the Vulva Spacecraft.</description></item><item><title>#208: Women’s Network Logo, Goblin Mode, Stolen Focus | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960068/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 18:10:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960068/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you don’t laugh you’ll cry right? And other things we find to say about the ill thought out logo for the government’s Women’s Network. Myf and Zan are weeding through the week to debrief on the most talked about stuff… and we’ve watched all of Byron Baes. We have thoughts. We’re also deeply connected with going full goblin mode. What is goblin mode? Let us explain. Meanwhile a dog performing Swan Lake is about the best thing you could hope for online, and we’re banging on about Johann Hari’s book Stolen Focus, and Jessica Stanley’s novel A Great Hope.</description></item><item><title>#207: Byron Baes, IWD, Severance | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960069/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 18:27:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960069/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s finally here, Netflix’s first locally commissioned show whose mere existence was already divisive. What do Myf and Zan make of Byron Baes? It’s quite the time for reality on Netflix – however that’s constructed – and we’re curious about what it says about us. Are we being wilfully scammed at every turn? International Women’s Day was this week, and a piece on whose voices are being amplified in Australia has cut right through.</description></item><item><title>#206: The word is CAP, Decline of the Girl Boss, Jon Ronson | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960070/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 17:53:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960070/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been a brutal week, and Myf and Zan are finding the light wherever we can. A viral tweet on a Wheel of Fortune FAIL helps a lot, as does one of the funniest and heartfelt fine dining restaurant reviews we’ve ever read. Meanwhile as we continue the march towards equality through the now 4th wave of feminism, a piece on the decline of the “Girl Boss” has us thinking: are we just doing the heavy lifting again?</description></item><item><title>#205: Vibe Shift, Baz’s Elvis, The Making of Mariah | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960071/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 17:22:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Everyone is talking about the “vibe shift” and Myf explains what it is, when it’s happening, and if we’re doing it right. Following our conversation last episode about romantic love not being all it’s cracked up to be, some more think pieces on Platonic Life Partnerships have popped up; is this the bond you see yourself committing to? Meanwhile the first trailer for Baz Luhrmann’s “Elvis” has dropped and we are all in, and casting has begun for an Australian version of ALONE; lockdown city citizens should feel well placed to pitch for this.</description></item><item><title>#204: Romantic Love, Super Bowl, Post Languishing | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960072/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 17:00:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960072/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s post Valentines Day and Myf and Zan are catching up on what we did, and thinking about what maybe we should do instead. The ideas of romantic love have long been flawed and out of date, is it time to rethink the stories we tell ourselves? The start of this week also kicked off with a history making moment for hip-hop and culture, as the Super Bowl half time show celebrated the world’s biggest genre for the first time.</description></item><item><title>#203: Brittany &amp; Grace, The Tinder Swindler, Pam &amp; Tommy | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960073/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 11:02:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are breathless, and fired up, following Brittany Higgins and Grace Tame’s incredible National Press Club address. We unpack how and why these two women continue to floor us with their strength, as they keep their foot on the pedal and empower us to do the same.
Everyone is watching the new Netflix doco The Tinder Swindler, and frankly we have more questions than answers.
The news that Neighbours could be coming to an end has us reflecting back on a show we literally grew up with, and the Oscar nominations have been revealed (we have some catching up to do).</description></item><item><title>#202: Rihanna's baby, Spotify Boycott, Chippendales | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960074/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 14:54:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are beside themselves with joy at the news Rihanna is pregnant with A$AP Rocky’s baby, and in conniptions over the big reveal.
The wholesome backstory of Wordle has taken on another context, with the news that the NY Times has purchased the word game for a figure “in the low 7’s”.
And Neil Young’s protest against Spotify’s housing of Joe Rogan’s podcast is gathering steam, we dig into the how’s, why’s, and what next of it all.</description></item><item><title>#201: Grace Tame’s honesty, Damon’s mistake, Kanye’s double denim | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960075/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 20:40:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are back after their summer break, and we’re rolling off the pool noodles and into 2022 with our Wordles sorted.
And Just Like That... has settled in over the break too, and we catch up on how the Sex &amp;amp; the City reboot is traveling.
Grace Tame has wound up her epic stint as Australian of the Year, but not before being slammed by some media by how she engaged with the PM.</description></item><item><title>#200: And Just Like That we hit 200 episodes | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960076/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 17:44:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Whoosh, Bang On has hit the big 200, and what a ride it’s been! It’s a massive Bang Back on big lessons from our beautiful Bang Fam this week. PSA: there will be tears. After an extraordinary 21 months, we asked you to share the lessons you’ve learned and good lawd you delivered. It’s been a huge week on telly too; don’t worry we’re debriefing on the highly anticipated Sex and the City reboot and savouring the (actual) finale of Succession’s third season.</description></item><item><title>#199: Kendall Roy, Kenny G, Chanel Advent Calendar | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960077/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 18:23:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960077/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s Listmas with everyone revealing their bests of the year, and we’re reflecting back on the best TV shows of 2021. One of them wrapped it’s third season this week; perfect timing for the New Yorker to publish a quite intense profile of it’s main star. While filming Succession, where does Jeremy Strong end and Kendall Roy begin? We already know what will be Myf’s fave of the year, after seeing the trailer for a new doco on Kenny G.</description></item><item><title>#198: Las Vegas, Jenkins Review, Dopesick | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960078/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960078/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Adele hits keep coming with her announcement of a Vegas residency in 2022 WHAAAAAAAT? C U THERE. If Omicron doesn’t screw things up.
In the final week of Parliament sitting, Kate Jenkins’ report into workplace culture at Parliament House has been released, and it’s even more shocking than some imagined.
Comedian and writer Nina Oyama has written a brutally honest account of comedy and misogyny and self belief, and we’re watching a brilliant doco on the late David Gulpilil, and a compelling new series on America’s opioid crisis ‘Dopesick’.</description></item><item><title>#197: Adele, Word of the Year, Grace Under Fire | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960079/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 20:45:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960079/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s all about Adele this week; the launch, the teacher moment, the Spotify hustle, and that interview, or non-interview… we dig in. Macquarie Australian English Dictionary are putting forth their picks for the word of the year, and we have more questions than answers. And a message from one of our Bang Fam has us thinking about the complexities and exhaustion of pushing for change. Meanwhile we’re both jazzed about The Beatles “Get Back” doco coming to Disney +, while Myf is watching the incredible Australian Story on Grace Tame, and Zan is reading Insomniac City.</description></item><item><title>#196: Britney Freed, Marilyn Manson, Daniel Johns | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960080/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 17:29:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960080/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s Britney, bitch! Yes it is, and she’s finally free. We revel in hearing her voice truly for the first time in years, and the voice she’s giving to others. Taylor Swift’s re-recording of Red has broken records and provided a platform too, it’s pretty awesome to see two pop stars shining a light on power imbalances we didn’t really understand, before. Speaking of which, a Rolling Stone investigation 9 months in the making tells the harrowing stories behind the allegations against Marilyn Manson, and again has us questioning the industry that has let it slide.</description></item><item><title>#195: 007, Travis Scott, Roadrunner | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960081/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960081/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re sifting through and making sense of the week that was, while looking with our eyes and listening with our ears.
No Time to Die has finally opened, and Zan has her spoiler-free hot takes on the new James Bond (and what phone he’s using).
The tragic death of eight people at Travis Scott’s ‘Astroworld’ festival raises questions about how why it happened, and if the artist holds the ultimate responsibility in keeping punters safe.</description></item><item><title>#194: Sally Rooney, Metaverse, Frayed | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960082/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 17:55:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960082/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re coming off a weekend of moving house and not moving much, and there’s plenty to chat about. Zan finally finished the latest Sally Rooney book, and has some thoughts. Meanwhile chatter about the “Great Resignation” happening in the States makes us wonder if it’ll happen here, and we once again embrace our new found roles as careers counsellors. Reality is getting a reboot, as is Facebook, with the launch of the “Metaverse”… What is going on with those videos?</description></item><item><title>#193: Josh Cavallo, TipTop, Maid | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960083/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 18:05:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Zan and Myf are back to wrap the week that was, and oh boy it went all over the place. Adelaide United football player Josh Cavallo came out publicly; a rare event in Australian sport and we couldn’t be more stoked. TipTop bread is trending on Twitter but why? And a brilliant piece exploring different people’s inner voices has us wondering about the scenes going on in our own heads.</description></item><item><title>#192: Succession, Dark Side of Wellness, The Bachelorette | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960084/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 18:08:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960084/</guid><description>Podcast Description One of the best shows ever is back, and we’re digging into the visceral one-liners, the power, the politics, all of it, as Succession returns. A well rounded read on the crossover of the wellness industry and conspiracy theorists has us thinking about what leads us (all of us) to different ways of thinking. And as lockdown lifts in Melbourne, and greater freedoms are felt all over Australia, we’re reflecting back on how we’re feeling coming out of the cave.</description></item><item><title>#191: 4 Corners, Megan Fox &amp; Machine Gun Kelly, Vigil | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960085/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 18:43:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last week’s discussion of work and worth got a big response from the Bang Fam, and this week we’re digging deeper into how we spend our lives and how to become time millionaires. It’s a thing. A 4 Corners story investigating allegations of toxic work culture and abuse within Sony Music Australia reignites conversations around what’s next. And a GQ feature on Megan Fox and Machine Gun Kelly’s love affair has everything we crave: dramz, quotes, and fashun.</description></item><item><title>#190: Bad Art Friend, Self-Objectification, Summer of Soul | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960086/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 20:02:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960086/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Gouldian Finch is holding strong in the final moments of Bird of the Year; will this rainbow pom pom take the crown? Tweets have definitely been louder this week, that’s for sure, after Facebook, Instagram and Whatsapp went offline for hours, leaving people to flock to Twitter. What did the outage say about our daily habits and addictions? Meanwhile an epic long read about a Bad Art Friend has the internet in a tizz, but if you’re seeing it and CBF reading it don’t worry, we got you.</description></item><item><title>#189: Birds, Bingeing, Morning Wars | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960087/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 18:55:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bird of the Year is back and the twitchers in us are absolutely frothing. Will the Ibis rise (from the bin) to claim the crown? The humble Magpie? What about the Tawny Frogmouth? Myf and Zan will reveal who they’re backing and why we love this annual poll of winged creatures. When we’re not bird watching, we’re binge viewing. But many streaming services are turning away from the mass dump of series in one go.</description></item><item><title>#188: Met Gala, The Activist, Alone | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960088/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 18:18:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fashun is back! And we are kids in the candy store of the Met Gala. The lewks, the themes, the references, all of it unpacked in this week’s ep. Away from the red carpet, a new reality show has activists pitted against one another but is it as bad as it sounds? And we’re back in New York for a new show which teams Steve Martin and Martin Short together once again, and in the woods where we’re all Alone.</description></item><item><title>#187: Women’s Summit, Kmart Plates, The Chair | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960089/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 19:06:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960089/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been a heck of a week for words and actions, with the Women’s Summit in Canberra being met with a lot of criticism. Next door, Minister Alan Tudge wants the curriculum to view history more favourably, and we look at who indeed that favours, and why. Thankfully $1.50 Kmart plates have provided welcome relief, a true sign that we have run out of things to talk about. And we’re banging on about a new Netflix show with Sandra Oh, and a page turner called The Midnight Library.</description></item><item><title>#186: DONDA, Dr Luke, Pandemic Dating | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960090/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 17:58:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kanye’s long awaited new album is finally out, and launched with his most provocative live streaming event so far. What does DONDA say about him as an artist, and the art he’s communicating to the world? Meanwhile, a longread on pop producer Dr Luke is a thorough case study on how the music industry is broken, and what we need to do to fix it. But also a discussion on how we as fans make ethical choices about the music we enjoy.</description></item><item><title>#185: Existential Pop Stardom, Dopamine, Coffee Towels | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960091/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 17:43:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960091/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s another wild week and we’re keeping our heads above water making sense of it all with the Bang Fam. Qantas have made a big push for us to get vaccinated, and subsequently have us bawling. A brilliant piece on the unbearable nature of being a female pop star nails it, meanwhile we’re questioning our own addictions in a new look at dopamine and digital media. And there are claims that ‘tea towel’ is not a uniform term.</description></item><item><title>#184: Coping, Bathing, Mike White | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960092/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 18:01:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are throwing a big bear hug around the Bang Fam with our best coping techniques in a rough time. Some choice words from Nick Cave have us high-fiving the prince of darkness, and a debrief with White Lotus writer/creator Mike White answers a lot of questions and begs a few more. Alex Lahey’s impassioned plea to the PM to keep our music industry alive hits hard, while the conversation around celebrities bathing habits opens an absolute can of worms.</description></item><item><title>#183: White Lotus, Amanda Knox, Census | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960093/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 18:03:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Everyone’s frothing on the social satire White Lotus and frankly we don’t want it to end. Myf and Zan share some good news for fellow fans, and an insight into the music that makes the show. Meanwhile Dolly is telling more stories with the news of her debut novel; we’re ready to tear into it. A new film based on the story of Amanda Knox’s conviction and acquittal is about to come out, and the woman herself has thoughts on who gets to tell her story.</description></item><item><title>#182: Simone Biles, Fashion Forecasting, This Way Up | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960094/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 18:46:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960094/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s the final week of the Olympics, and Myf and Zan are blown away by the strength, vulnerability, and power of Simone Biles.
Her decision to step back from competing in several events is the latest in a time where athletes are speaking out about the importance of protecting their mental health. Meanwhile a piece on how to forecast fashion in a pandemic confirms that this and every other industry is being turned on it’s head.</description></item><item><title>#181: Olympics, Kanye, Ted Lasso | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960095/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 18:41:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Any naysaying about the Olympics has totally dissolved, the Games are here and we are here for them! Myf and Zan commentate on the highs and lows of Tokyo 2020(21); the fashion, the ceremony, the sports we forgot existed and are 100% invested in. Stadiums are a big theme of the week too, with the news that Kanye has allegedly moved into one to finish his DONDA album. Meanwhile a doco on Anthony Bourdain and it’s use of AI voices has us discussing where the line lies in documentary film.</description></item><item><title>#180 Bang Back with the Bang Fam | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960096/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 08:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960096/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re banging back! And for our 180th episode we’re doing a full 180, spinning the mic around to you, the Bang Fam, for more of YOUR brilliant recommendations.
Big thanks to Annie, Ruth, Stevie, Alisha, Tilly, Lucinda, Melissa, Nellie, Deb, Angus, Steph, Kate, the other Kate, Viv, Joh, Sally, Hannah, Emma, Dominique, Bonnie and Ramonda in New Zealand for contributing to this excellent mid-winter list!
Show notes:
Shrill https://www.</description></item><item><title>#179: Emmy Noms, Ms Represented, Toilet Roll Orientation | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960097/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 16:45:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960097/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Emmy nominations have been revealed! HBO lead the pack with some of our favourite TV of the last year but it seems that Emily in Paris is still a thing. Why?
A great VOX read explores how trends have dissolved in this age of individualised media and expression and asks the question, are we cool anymore?
Annabel Crabb’s new TV series Ms Represented couldn’t have come at a more perfect time and we’ve binged it all.</description></item><item><title>#178: Sex/Life, Meditation Apps, Firestarter | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960098/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 15:15:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960098/</guid><description>Podcast Description We want you to Bang back! Have you watched, read or heard something that you want to tell the Bang Fam about? Let us know via the email address below. Succession season 3 has finally been announced, and Myf and Zan are jazzed about watching the worst people on earth fight with one another, as well as Cousin Greg.
Meanwhile Myf is hate watching Sex/Life on Netflix, while Zan has watched 7 essential seconds of it.</description></item><item><title>#177: Crime Stoppers, Lookism, Vagina Tunnels | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960099/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960099/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s another bin fire of a week, but rest assured we’re here to help! Myf and Zan read all the stuff so you don’t have to, and hopefully give you a good laugh along the way.
Someone called Crime Stoppers on Barnaby Joyce (and we want to meet them), while IKEA are celebrating Pride Month with some very unique Loveseats.
An editorial on “lookism” has us intrigued; can a symmetrical face get you further in life?</description></item><item><title>#176 Britney, Sony, Starstruck | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960100/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 18:10:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960100/</guid><description>Podcast Description As we hit record, Britney Spears has just spoken publicly for the first time on her conservatorship and it’s effects on her. It’s a lot, and we dig in.
Meanwhile a toxic working environment at Sony Music Australia begs the question; has the reckoning we’ve been waiting for, begun?
A new edition of a masked dating show has us absolutely razzed, but not as much as Rose Matafeo’s new comedy series Starstruck which Myf has literally gone without sleep, to watch.</description></item><item><title>#175: Wasabi, Australia Club, Cruella | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960101/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 18:45:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wow it’s been a week aye! A man was swallowed by a whale AND did a Reddit AMA about it. Then the Westminster Dog Show is back and Wasabi the Pekingese is not the only winner.
Meanwhile Batman apparently doesn’t go downtown. We have questions.
An old boys club wants to keep it that way; should the Australia Club and other networking organisations be able to discriminate against half the population?</description></item><item><title>#174: Lorde, Hacks, Mare of Easttown Finale | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960102/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 16:30:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960102/</guid><description>Podcast Description The meme machine has been in overdrive this week, with Lorde dropping new visual clues on her new music, and Gladys pretending to watch the rugby. It’s what we need in these lockdown times, thank you, the internet.
A beautiful piece on senior singles has us contemplating the importance of different kinds of relationships with others, and ourselves.
And a long read on the absence of women in visual art has got us finding our own black spot of understanding.</description></item><item><title>#173: Naomi Osaka, Bo Burnham, Channel 9 | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960103/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 16:10:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960103/</guid><description>Podcast Description A tennis champion’s decision to not partake in press conferences has got everyone talking, and it raises questions again about old ways falling, and respecting mental health, rising.
Channel 9’s vaccination push has hit a bung note for everyone who doesn’t have straight blonde hair, and the internet is ablaze with millennial Bo Burnham’s new Netflix special, shot through the pandemic last year.
Meanwhile as Myf and Zan continue Lockdown 4.</description></item><item><title>#172: Taika’s Thruple, Bisexual Bachelorette, Sinead’s Rememberings | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960104/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 16:31:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Well what a week it’s been. An all night party at Taika Waititi’s Sydney pad has tongues wagging, meanwhile the Bachelorette is Bi, and men and women will battle it out for her affections.
Reconciliation Week has kicked off, and we reflect on the fight for Indigenous recognition and non-Indigenous Australia’s responsibilities in moving forward.
Sinéad O’Connor has penned a memoir, and spoken with the New York Times about how she saw everything unfold in the early part of her career.</description></item><item><title>#171: Pam and Tommy, Defending Keanu, Puffa | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960105/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 16:20:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960105/</guid><description>Podcast Description A new TV series on Pamela Anderson and Tommy Lee’s whirlwind romance has Courtney Love calling bullshit, and us thinking about how we witness other people’s trauma as entertainment.
The Israeli-Palestinian conflict continues, but it feels as though more people are publicly speaking out about it. We think about what has changed.
A spirited defence of Keanu Reeves has us fist pumping, especially Myf who has had a front row seat to this screen angel’s chill vibe.</description></item><item><title>#170: Bennifer, Australian Music’s #MeToo, Girls5eva | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960106/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 16:42:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960106/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re making sense of the world around us once again, including why Matt Damon is hanging out at a TAB, and whether Ben Affleck and J-Lo are having a red hot go at it again.
There’s a Cheugy update and it relates to NFT’s. Don’t worry, we’ll explain.
Extensive research into the harassment, assault, and disrespect of women in Australia’s music industry is in the news again, and while it feels like the volume is being turned up we wonder if and when the reckoning will happen in our local scene.</description></item><item><title>#169 Cheugy, Billie Eilish, Drag Race Down Under | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960107/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 16:15:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960107/</guid><description>Podcast Description We have a new word and we’re not afraid to use, or be it. Are you a little bit cheugy too?
Everyone has an opinion on Billie Eilish’s transformation (including us it seems), and we’re loving the arrival of Ru Paul’s Drag Race Down Under. Especially the swears!
Britney Spears has spoken directly to her followers about those documentaries, and Ben Affleck is being ghosted online.
Meanwhile the Bang Box overfloweth with suggestions for us to check out a very particular dress, and we’re banging on about a new SBS series on domestic abuse, and Kate Winslet’s incredible turn in Mare of Easttown.</description></item><item><title>#168: Oscars, Languishing, The End of Kimye | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960108/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 17:10:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960108/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s the big Kahuna of award shows and we unpack everything about a very different Oscars: the historic wins, the notable absences, the Glenn Close moment, and of course the farshun.
There’s some serious Black Mirror shizz happening in China, as a Russian contestant on a reality TV gets trapped inside the machine.
And a short read on the space between flourishing and depression has resonated with us hugely in this pandemic marathon.</description></item><item><title>#167: Milkshake Consent Video, Byron Baes, Canadian Tuxedo | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960109/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 15:05:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960109/</guid><description>Podcast Description An educational video about consent has us more confused than before we pressed play, and we’re not alone. Myf and Zan unpack the 1950’s world of milkshakes and Moving the Line. Byron Bay locals are boycotting the filming of a Netflix series about their town and it’s people, prompting the question “if you build it, they will come?” We’ve got some breaking screen updates from France and Italy, and anywhere Adam Driver is.</description></item><item><title>#166: Digital Footprints, Sex Discrimination Act, Upside Down Bikinis | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960110/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 17:25:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960110/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re max relaxed after a long weekend down the beach, and ready to dissect the week with you. An editorial on women’s pasts and how they are weaponised against us in the halls of power, resonates and has us reflecting on our digital footprints.
Meanwhile the reckoning continues, all of it; the discussions, the anger, and importantly the change. A shift in the definition of the Sex Discrimination act has us cheering and yelling “whut?</description></item><item><title>#165: Go Down South, Lil Nas X, Big Boat | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960111/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 16:01:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960111/</guid><description>Podcast Description What a wild week. A South Australian (alleged) tourism ad has everyone talking. With their mouths.
Lil Nas X is feeding and fighting the conservatives with his excellent new video, and serving satanic sass on his social media.
And Parliament is still doing it’s thing. When will “it’s thing” change?
Thankfully we have big boat to save us, and remind us of the simplicity of having one thing the world can get behind (and push).</description></item><item><title>#164: Michael Gudinski Memorial, Dark Mofo, 2000s Fashion | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960112/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 18:25:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960112/</guid><description>Podcast Description A state memorial for Australian music’s biggest legend has taken place in Melbourne, Myf and Zan were there and reflect on the epic night.
The foot is staying on the pedal in the fight against sexism and sexual abuse, and we catch up on the conversations and head shaking reactions of the past week.
Meanwhile the Dark Mofo festival has commissioned, then cancelled an offensive art commission, but is an apology enough?</description></item><item><title>#163: March4Justice, Elliot Page, Croc Undies | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960113/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 15:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960113/</guid><description>Podcast Description 100,000 people marched against sexism and sexual assault this week, and Myf was one of them. We unpack the March4Justice rallies, which voices are being amplified, and what happens next.
Elliot Page has made history as the first trans man on the cover of TIME magazine, telling his story to a huge audience.
And “Croc Undies” are two words which should frankly be illegal when paired, but here we are.</description></item><item><title>#162: Meghan and Harry, Cocaine Bear, WFH Pyjamas | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960114/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 15:10:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960114/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s one big story in pop culture this week, and we are all in. The revelations, the racism, Piers, Oprah, the Empire, and Myf’s always sizzling takes on the Royal Family. We’re here for you
Elsewhere, a film called Cocaine Bear has been greenlit, and if that piqued your interest then wait till you hear what else we know about said bear.
A perfect pair of pyjama’s has been designed in Japan, and we’re banging on about some great reads (short and long form) from food writer Claire Dent and futurist musician David Byrne.</description></item><item><title>#161: Incandescent Rage, Grace Tame, Nomadland | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960115/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 16:03:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960115/</guid><description>Podcast Description The events of the past week have us angry, frustrated, and exhausted. We sit with that, and with the knowledge that it’s been happening for a long time. But also that this very public reckoning means things are different, the conversation is shifting.
As our leaders offer statements that diminish the experiences of survivors, Australian of the Year Grace Tame’s speech at the National Press Club is a hopeful and rallying call, and huge call out on how we discuss and deal with sexual abuse.</description></item><item><title>#160: Daft Punk, Will TV Confront COVID?, Obama &amp; Springsteen | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960116/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 15:23:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two boomers have started a podcast, and we’re very interested in their home recording setup. Another duo have called it a day, and we reflect back on the soundtrack Daft Punk have given our lives. As big TV shows like Sex &amp;amp; the City, Succession, and Curb Your Enthusiasm go back into production, the question of COVID as a storyline is front of mind. Should TV reflect, or escape reality?</description></item><item><title>#159: Facebook News, Brittany Higgins, Those Jeans | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960117/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960117/</guid><description>Podcast Description We woke to a Facebook devoid of Australian news content, and so much more. Myf and Zan talk about how the social media giant is playing poker with the Australian government and frustrating it’s millions of local users and communities. Brittany Higgins’ allegations of rape within Parliament House have caused shockwaves across the country, and differing responses from our leaders. How do we value the women in our lives?</description></item><item><title>#158: The Weeknd, Framing Britney Spears, Clubhouse | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960118/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 17:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960118/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s Super Bowl time which means (to us) a halftime show of high spectacle and lots of pyrotechnics. How did The Weeknd stack up against the legacy of roof jumps and left sharks? A New York Times doco on Britney Spears’ conservatorship has everyone talking, and us reflecting on our own judgements as we watched her rise and fall. An English parish meeting on Zoom has gone viral for all the right reasons, while Grand Slam tennis is providing the fashun hit we need.</description></item><item><title>#157: Golden Globes, Marilyn Manson, Promising Young Woman | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960119/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 16:30:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960119/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s awards season! And the hit and miss nature of the Golden Globes never fails to disappoint. We analyse the nominations. Dolly Parton has had another big week of sweet scents and stinkers, while Myf is exploring the world of casual friendships and how important “weak ties” are to us and our human ecology. Allegations of abuse and coercion against Marilyn Manson raise a lot of questions around the concept of consent, and we’re banging on about brilliant watches on screens – big and small - including Promising Young Woman.</description></item><item><title>#156: January 26, The Honours System, It’s a Sin | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960120/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 17:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960120/</guid><description>Podcast Description The conversation around how, when, and if to mark January 26 as "Australia Day" continues, and Myf and Zan talk about how circular it’s becoming. The honours system is under scrutiny, as we question the people given the highest awards for service in Australia, and who decides it. Cardi B has made Hottest 100 history with Myf’s anthem of 2020. And pandemic fashion continues to influence the latest trends (Zan is ready to invest), while Myf’s Tupperware spew bowl chat has “brought up” some memories for Bang Fam.</description></item><item><title>#155: Inauguration Day, Phil Spector, Sapiens | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960121/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 17:15:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hours after US President Biden is sworn in we’re giving our hot takes on the important moments of Inauguration Day: the brooch, the coats, and Melania's kaftan. Speaking of fashion, US Vogue has been criticised over its cover image choice of history making VP Kamala Harris. We dig into the discussion around it. And convicted murderer and known abuser Phil Spector has died; we reflect on the “lone genius” myth, and the industry that allows certain men to make others suffer for their art.</description></item><item><title>#154: Sex and the City, Bridgerton, 2021 goals | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960122/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 18:25:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960122/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re back for another year of Bangin’ On, and with plenty to sink our teeth into. Sex and the City is back too, but in what form and why? Kim and Kanye are reportedly on the rocks; we do what we can with the information at hand. And sea shanties have gone viral on TikTok, which is frankly joyful, but also speaks to a larger instinct towards community. A new year is an opportunity for taking stock and setting some 2021 goals, but how do you do that when there’s so much uncertainty in the world?</description></item><item><title>#153: It’s Bangmas! Our end of year wrap | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960123/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 21:40:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Well we’ve come to the end of a year, and while everyone does their 2020 wrap we give this bin fire our own Bang On spin. Plenty to love (and suddenly remember) about it; from WAP to Dreams, hyper realistic cakes and hyper ugly Crocs. Fashion didn’t sleep, but did resemble a waste bag, and Dolly saved us all. It was a year of challenges too; in some cases good ones, and we reflect on the reckonings we’ve felt, in this tumultuous 12 months.</description></item><item><title>#152: Bang Back with the Bang Fam | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960124/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 14:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960124/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s over to you Bang Fam, as you share your recommendations for summer in a bumper Bang Back special episode. We laugh, we cry, and we now have a big list of all kinds of joyful, funny, enlightening, and ridiculous things to dig into over the summer break. Show notes:
Dionne Warwick: https://twitter.com/_DionneWarwick/status/1336005472910864385
Nigella pronouncing microwave: https://twitter.com/EtceteraWithEst/status/1336287775390396417
The Weekend: https://www.charlottewood.com.au/the-weekend.html
Breath: https://www.penguin.com.au/books/breath-9780241289082
The Big Film Buffet: https://podcasts.apple.com/au/podcast/the-big-film-buffet/id1532358360
The Undoing: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#151: Elliot Page, COVID resets, Wedgie shorts | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960125/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 16:15:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960125/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a big week for trans awareness, with actor Elliot Page coming out and highlighting the realities of many others in the trans community. A great piece in the Washington Post on how COVID has changed arts criticism has us thinking more broadly about the ways we’re shifting for good, including in live gig accessibility. It’s quite a time for butts in fashion too, and of course we have many thoughts.</description></item><item><title>#150: Music Awards, Meghan Markle, Toast | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960126/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 15:20:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960126/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been a big week for music statues, with the ARIA Awards going down, and the Grammy nominations going up. Diversity on both fronts is on the rise, but The Weeknd ain’t happy. A great read on a new generation’s viewing of Diana’s “princess story” has us also reflecting on the shifting stories around cultural institutions, while an op-ed penned by The Duchess of Sussex shows she continues to do things her way.</description></item><item><title>#149: Dolly's Vaccine, The Crown, Pete Evans | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960127/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 20:50:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dolly Parton cured Coronavirus! ABC Fact Check: not quite, but how wonderful that her $1 million donation towards the development of a vaccine is reaping dividends; we celebrate the Queen. Speaking of monarchies, the new season of The Crown has dropped and everyone is googling whether or not Diana dressed as a tree. But has artistic licence been taken too far? The success of double screen friendly shows like Emily in Paris has us looking into the concept of “ambient tv”, while we’re grateful that Channel 10 has decided to keep Pete Evans OFF the box.</description></item><item><title>#148: Manterrupting, Indigenous place names, Four Seasons | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960128/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 16:15:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960128/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been a week for finding, and figuring out women’s place in power in 2020. An ABC 4 Corners expose on the power imbalance between men and women in Canberra has been seamlessly followed by a political press conference confirming the point. Meanwhile a statue erected to pay tribute to a feminist hero has many confused and outraged about the gaze it was sculpted in. Australia Post has backed a campaign to include Indigenous place names on letters and packages, which has us reflecting on the every day inclusion of traditional country names in all walks of life.</description></item><item><title>#147: Beyonce’s beehives, Johnny Depp’s decline, Goop gift guide | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960129/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 17:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan bang on about Johnny Depp, Beyonce's 80,000 bees, the ridiculous Goop gift guide, The Vow, and Meg Mason's new book Sorrow and Bliss.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#146: Kim’s Birthday, Fashion at 40, Seduced | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960130/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 16:55:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960130/</guid><description>Podcast Description After 2 weeks of multiple health screens and asking everyone to quarantine, I surprised my closest inner circle with a trip to a private island where we could pretend things were normal just for a brief moment in time. Joking! We just emerged from months of lockdown to record Bang On face to face, IRL! And it’s like one million private island birthdays rolled into one. We talk about the tone deaf socials post from KKW that has the world’s meme machine ticking over.</description></item><item><title>#145: Giuliani &amp; Borat, Friendship, Honeybee | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960131/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 16:15:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960131/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been a week for blokes with their hands down their pants! Rudy Giuliani has been caught in some compromising shots in the new Borat film, while US journalist Jeremy Toobin has dissolved the boundaries of working from home, in a Zoom meeting. Why are so many men coming to his defence? A beautiful long read on how we value our friendships has us reflecting on our own lifelong bonds, and NASA has landed on an asteroid this week.</description></item><item><title>#144: The Crown, Rihanna, Billie Eilish and Zadie Smith | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960132/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 18:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960132/</guid><description>Podcast Description The trailer for season 4 of The Crown is out and we are absolutely frothing for it. A new Crocs x Bieber collab has the internet ablaze again, and while younger folks have been behind the plastic clog for a while now, it feels as though the multi-generational tipping point is here. Meanwhile Rihanna has drawn attention to male body image with her brilliant inclusion of 2XL model Steven G in her latest undies campaign, while Billie Eilish’s appearance is being dissected once again (she’s having none of it).</description></item><item><title>#143: Claudia Conway, Fleetwood Mac, David Attenborough | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960133/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 18:15:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960133/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been a big week in American politics and frankly, we gotta dive in. Love overtakes #ProudBoys, while a fifteen year old on TikTok becomes the voice of honesty out of the White House. An Idaho fella with a penchant for cranberry juice wins everyone over, including Mick Fleetwood. And Myf is binge watching Issa Rae's TV show Insecure, and hate-watching Emily in Paris. Meanwhile Zan discovers Myf has never seen an Attenborough nature doco, when she bangs on about his latest, "</description></item><item><title>#142: Helen Reddy, Lizzo, Michaela &amp; Donald | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960134/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 16:50:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960134/</guid><description>Podcast Description The death of a feminist icon has us reflecting on the power of song, and the impact her anthem had on the highest office in the land. Lizzo has made history on the cover of Vogue, and there’s a lot of feedback. We're also in awe of an incredible conversation between Michaela Coel and Donald Glover. In between we talk about puppet haute couture and a famous wood nymph celebrates her birthday in an eye opening way.</description></item><item><title>#141: Emmys 2020, Rolling Stone 500, RBG Tributes | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960135/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 17:45:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960135/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Emmy Awards happened on Zoom and we watched the highlights, how very 2020. We wrap the winners, the ground breakers, and the list of awards that – if anything – remind us of shows we might have missed. Not sure about Schitt's Creek yet? Myf explains why they took home the most gongs. Speaking of which, Rolling Stone have just updated their lengthy list of the 500 Best Albums of All Time.</description></item><item><title>#140: The Social Dilemma, Kanye vs Universal, Freeman | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960136/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 15:45:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960136/</guid><description>Podcast Description The crossover of the wellness industry and conspiracy theorists is real (#DoYourResearch), and we explore why. Speaking of Venn diagrams, a new doco on Netflix has everyone talking about the power and intentions of social media. Kanye’s latest tweet-rant resonates, and a doco on Cathy Freeman’s iconic Olympic gold has us crying, and reflecting on what has and hasn’t changed in the past 20 years.
Show notes:
The wellness realm has fallen into conspiritualism: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#139: The Kardashians, AI, I Hate Suzie | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960137/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 16:40:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960137/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s the end of an era as Keeping Up With The Kardashians calls time. We reflect back on the empire (and wealth) this family has built, and why now is the right time to finish. An op-ed penned by robot AI has the human world in a tizz, meanwhile a phenomenon around bookstores and toilets has us oversharing. And everyone is talking about Billie Piper’s incredible performance in I Hate Suzie.</description></item><item><title>#138: Human connection, Pop Music, I May Destroy You | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960138/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 18:20:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960138/</guid><description>Podcast Description The pandemic is proving to us how much we need to connect with one another. Luckily ingenuity + the internet is here to help this week. A longread on Katy Perry’s music has us digging into the shifting landscape of pop, artistic authenticity, social media, and more. And Michaela Coel’s acclaimed TV series has a surprise landing on Australian screens, finally!
Show notes:
The Joys of Looking Outside a Strangers Window: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Back Next Week | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960139/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 23:30:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey Bang Fam. No episode this week. We're fine, don't worry! We'll be back to bang on with you next week. Can't wait to catch up then. Much love, Myf and Zan x
Don't forget you can email us: bangon.podcast@abc.net.au
Bang On is produced by Double J. it is recorded on the lands of the Wurundjeri people of the Kulin nation. We pay our respects to elders past, present, and emerging.</description></item><item><title>#137 Dolly speaks out, Cher goes postal, Media diversity disappoints | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960140/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 17:20:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960140/</guid><description>Podcast Description The normally apolitical Ms Dolly Parton has spoken out in support of Black Lives Matter, which has us looking back at the Dolly Parton’s America podcast and thinking about the theme of “unity” that is dominating US politics this week. Cardi B has interviewed Joe Biden, and Cher is VOLUNTEERING (all caps) at her local post office. 2020, you’re a wild time! And a report auditing diversity on Australian broadcast news and current affairs has us shocked but not surprised.</description></item><item><title>#136: WAP, Nick Cave, Phil Collins Reactions | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960141/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 16:50:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cardi B and Megan Thee Stallion have caused a ruckus online following the release of their sex positive collab “WAP”, but the reactions to it’s message are divided, and the hot takes are multiplying. We dive in. Meanwhile Nick Cave has weighed in on the cancel culture debate, and a couple of twins in Indiana are bringing us joy with their reactions to songs we thought everyone had heard.</description></item><item><title>#135: Ellen, Black is King, Dog Poo Bag | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960142/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960142/</guid><description>Podcast Description The rise and (possible) fall of Ellen DeGeneres has been filling the feeds, and we’re deciphering what it all means. Beyoncé has dropped her new visual album "Black is King", and Myf has managed to find a Disney+ login to watch it. And even though there are no runways, we've found a fashion accessory to keep us going in this lockdown. To the dog park.
Show notes:
Ellen DeGeneres: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#134: Challenge Accepted, Taylor’s folklore, KFC Crocs | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960143/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 17:20:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Black and white selfies of “women supporting women” have been flooding our feeds this week, but why? Alexandria Ocasia-Cortez’s speech on the floor of US Congress has us fist pumping, while Taylor Swift’s surprise album has the music world reviewing. We give our take, somewhat fearfully, due to Swiftie stans. And as it is written, so it shall be done; the KFC Crocs collab is finally here. Plus, Zan is in awe of Julia Baird's book Phosphorescence and Myf takes a journey with Miriam Margolyes.</description></item><item><title>#133: Kanye, Netflix Cancel Culture, Q Mag | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960144/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 16:40:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960144/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been a turbulent week for Kanye West, and the responses to his breakdowns has us again discussing the understanding and compassion towards mental health in celebrity culture. Netflix’s 3 seasons and you’re out policy prompts us to take a bigger look at the legacy of great television series, and how streaming services are disrupting the game. Plus, fashion face masks and what does the demise of Q Mag mean for long form music journalism?</description></item><item><title>#132 Ausmusic's Me Too Moment, Cutting Cakes and Free Britney | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960145/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 17:40:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960145/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Australian music industry is experiencing its first public #MeToo moment and we’re wondering what it will take to create real systemic change, in this small scene. Meanwhile, an exceptional feature on Thandie Newton has us pumped up, and people cutting cakes that look like things that are not cakes has us confused. The Free Britney movement is rising again, giving new context to her social media posts. And a new look wetsuit has Myf absolutely jazzed.</description></item><item><title>#131 Hamilton, High Fidelity, Harpers | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960146/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 16:15:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960146/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s open season on open letters denouncing cancellation culture. But are the people calling the call outs just replicating what they’re fighting against? Yeezy season is well and truly upon us, with Kanye running for President. And we’re digging into the latest adaptation of High Fidelity, and what do we make of Hamilton on the small screen? Show Notes
SMH Open Letter: https://www.smh.com.au/culture/movies/something-dangerously-askew-with-the-way-we-re-talking-about-race-and-the-arts-20200706-p559bz.html
Harpers Open Letter: https://harpers.org/a-letter-on-justice-and-open-debate/
Kanye in Forbes: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#130: Kanye, The Nest Boyfriend, Eurovision Movie | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960147/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 17:10:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960147/</guid><description>Podcast Description By popular demand, Eurovision host and expert Myf weighs in on Will Ferrell’s Eurovision movie "The Story of Fire Saga". While Zan bangs on about Mrs America. Kanye and Kim have had a big week of music, fashion, and Freesian horses, and we’re here for it. All of it. And a “Ken and Karen” of Missouri are the pin ups of white privilege, and the source of many a meme.</description></item><item><title>#129: Dyson Heydon, Barbie Quarantine, Sashay Away Segway | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960148/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 17:30:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960148/</guid><description>Podcast Description An investigation into sexual harassment at the highest levels of Australian law has us talking about the systemic abuse of power that women are subjected to every day. It’s the end of the road for the Segway, and the start of a new project by Beyonce. And an American comedian has made our week with her Barbie Quarantine Dreamhouse.
Show Notes:
Myf’s Sovereign Hill Deb dress: https://twitter.com/MyfWarhurst/status/1275675671176663055
Zan’s “anti-Deb” dress: https://twitter.</description></item><item><title>#128: Callout Culture or Accountability, 1997 Fashion, Debutante | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960149/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 16:50:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can callout culture create actionable change? The removing and recontextualising of past problematic art is one thing, but we’re reminded to keep our foot on the pedal when there are some big issues at stake. A piece on 1997 fashion is a stretch (but of course we’ll take it), and a new podcast on Debutante Balls has us looking at this old tradition through a new lens.
Show Notes</description></item><item><title>#127 A Reckoning, A Rowling, A Rousing | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960150/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 18:30:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960150/</guid><description>Podcast Description The world is responding to call outs for change, with major publications, streaming services, and organisations taking responsibility for past practices and platforming, and also reassessing how they work differently into the future. TV shows are buried, statues of slave traders are toppled, while some are only just learning that Tom Morello’s rage isn’t against his dishwasher. JK Rowling has doubled down on her stance on trans women, causing Potterheads (not least recent fan Zan) to question their connection to her books.</description></item><item><title>#126 The Return, Blackout Tuesday, COVID Farshun | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960151/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 16:05:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960151/</guid><description>Podcast Description The world is a very different place to where we left you more than eight months ago! And we’re catching up on what we’ve learned in this new “normal”. Following the killing of George Floyd, and protests in both America and Australia on racial injustice, the music industry this week responded with a blackout. But the confused messaging on social media has people wondering if these conversation will continue beyond the news cycle.</description></item><item><title>It is happening | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960152/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 12:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960152/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's a Tiger King free zone, but there is so much that Myf and Zan have watched, read and heard that they can't wait to discuss with you. Yes, Bang On is back THIS WEEK. You won't have to wait long Bang Fam. They will be at a safe distance but no topic is safe - farshun, hot takes &amp;amp; convos about music, art, life and stuff are all back on the table.</description></item><item><title>Hello, is this thing on? | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960153/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 16:15:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960153/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are back! After 9 months away they're almost ready to bang on again. Are YOU ready Bang Fam? Stay tuned...
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#125: Greta Thunberg, JVN, Unbelievable | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960154/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2019 17:11:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are reunited and catching up on another massive week. On the east coast of America, Greta Thunberg is making waves with her impassioned fight for climate change action but a certain type of man is bent on bringing her down. Meanwhile on the west, the Emmys are on and we’re dissecting the farshun on ground. Jonathan Van Ness is absent, but in the news for other reasons: a revealing interview with the New York Times.</description></item><item><title>#124: Hannah Gadsby, Muting Trolls, Berghain | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960155/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 17:36:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf wakes Zan up at a ridiculous hour in Germany, where she’s been busy trying to get into all the coolest clubs, before she begins her judging duties for the ANCHOR – Reeperbahn Festival International Music Award. We celebrate Hannah Gadsby’s Emmy win while questioning how Beyonce missed out on six awards. As well, suggested new rules for dealing with trolls have us thinking about the best way to deal with nastiness online.</description></item><item><title>#123: Parma, Caroline Calloway, Snowball | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960156/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 16:42:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are dealing with another bad take by a repeat offender, and going in to bat for the chicken parma. A long read in The Cut has the internet ablaze, but why are we so thirsty for watching public take downs? And the unveiling of a statue of AFLW player Tayla Harris speaks for more than just one woman. We’re banging on about a gripping new podcast, and there’s some big Bang news to share with the Bang Fam too.</description></item><item><title>#122: Flume, Taylor vs Tool, Unwanted Kisses | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960157/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 17:49:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960157/</guid><description>Podcast Description #122: Flume, Taylor vs Tool, Unwanted Kisses
Myf and Zan sink their teeth into another big week, and it’s a real peach. Flume has been setting the internet on fire with his antics at Burning Man, Taylor Swift fans don’t know or understand Tool and it’s a vibe. Meanwhile an unwanted kiss at a charity event sparks a conversation around the different greetings men and women receive, and the earliest invasions of personal space.</description></item><item><title>#121: Missy Elliott, Pizzadilla, G7 wives | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960158/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 16:48:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960158/</guid><description>Podcast Description What a smorgasbord of hot topics Myf and Zan have this week. The MTV VMA’s have given us eye candy for days, and peaked with two killer performances from legends, new and old. Someone has mapped and analysed Taylor Swift’s journey “London Boy”, and we’re here for it (and how much it’d cost), and a food video has taken things too far. Meanwhile the G7 is on, and the tenets of sexism are on full display with the leaders wives.</description></item><item><title>#120: Billie Eilish, Branded Podcasts, Convict Slang | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960159/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 17:26:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan start their week with a story about dogs watching musicals, and go from there. A piece on how podcasts are pitching products has us thinking about the creative (and sometimes insidious) ways brands are selling. And a conversation between Pharrell Williams and Billie Eilish has us punching our fists in the air for the present. Meanwhile the 200th anniversary of a dictionary strikes a chord, and Myf is banging on about ponies (up there with Paddle Steamers).</description></item><item><title>#119: BTS, Art &amp; Instagram, Succession | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960160/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 16:32:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960160/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are back from Brisbane and still flying high after a Bang Fam reunion in the sunshine state. South Korea’s most famous boy band is taking a breather, and it marks a shift in how the industry treats it’s biggest stars. A piece on art feeding your soul in the age of social media has us jazzed… How can art touch your soul when your soul is busy posing on Instagram?</description></item><item><title>#118: Bang On Live in Brisbane | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960161/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 17:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960161/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan finally make the pilgrimage to Brisvegas, for a special live recording of Bang On and boy howdy, do the Bang Fam show up! It’s our first date with Brissie so, with some help from the Guardian, we make all the right choices about etiquette. Tarantino’s latest epic hasn’t come out yet but – much like the internet – we’re here to dish some hot takes without having seen it.</description></item><item><title>#117: Queer Eye, Millennial Disney, Meghan Vogue | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960162/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 17:49:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960162/</guid><description>Podcast Description With a new season of Queer Eye out, Myf and Zan are digging in and noticing shifts in the Fab Five’s approach to makeovers. A rant online about who should and shouldn’t be at Disneyworld has Zan worked up (and planning her next visit). Meanwhile the September issue of British Vogue has a guest editor who’s turning the focus on others. And we’re banging on about two Australian docos that have us reflecting back on who we are.</description></item><item><title>#116: Masterchef, Cats, World Music | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960163/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 17:55:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960163/</guid><description>Podcast Description You’re hot then you’re cold but you’re always bang on. It’s the end of an era for our Masterchef judges and we have some spicy takes on Matt, George, and Gary’s departure. We’re calling into question a “definitive list” of the best bikkies, and have more than a few queries about the movie trailer for Cats. And in 2019, do we really need the category of “world music”? Ahead of WOMAD in the UK, a great opinion piece sparks the convo once again.</description></item><item><title>#115: Princess Di, 007, Chernobyl | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960164/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 17:21:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960164/</guid><description>Podcast Description #115: Princess Di, 007, Chernobyl
Myf and Zan are reunited after their respective Bali sojourns, and there is a LOT to catch up on. David Campbell truly believes his son is Princess Di reincarnated so there’s that. Meanwhile the internet is buzzing with a new 007 in town, and Lil Nas X checking in with Keanu and Dolly. We’re in front of the box too, banging on about tv shows hyped and hidden online.</description></item><item><title>#114: Women’s World Cup, Jeffrey Epstein, Influencers | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960165/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 17:47:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Zan invites Jan Fran back into the Bang Fam this week, while Myf is on hols. The victory of the US Women’s Team in the World Cup has everyone talking, particularly about the pay gap. Jeffrey Epstein is having his day of reckoning, sparking a discussion around complicity, connection, and whether the structures that protect abusers are shifting in the wake of #MeToo. And a brilliant long read in Vanity Fair about linen loving Byron Bay babes has us digging into the social media sell once again.</description></item><item><title>#113: Logies, Taylor Vs Scooter, Michael Hutchence | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960166/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 17:31:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960166/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf’s away so Clare Bowditch is coming to play as a special guest Banger! It’s been a juicy week too, with the Gold Logie going to Gleeson. Should we / do we care about the Logies? Taylor Swift’s public fight for her master recordings gets an explanation from Clare, as we ponder the power of the artist. And Celine Dion is in Paris for Couture Fashion Week. Enough said.</description></item><item><title>#112: Being Beyonce’s Assistant, Body Makeup, Rethinking Productivity | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960167/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 16:54:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960167/</guid><description>Podcast Description While Zan’s away Myf and Meshel Laurie play - and boy, are they hopeless at the new choose your own adventure twitter game, Being Beyonce’s Assistant For The Day. As well, we have ALL the thoughts on Kim Kardashian’s new makeup range for the body - and while we’re at it, we do some deep reflection on how to live our lives in a post social media age.</description></item><item><title>#111: Garlic, Gay Anthems, Gender bans | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960168/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 17:10:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960168/</guid><description>Podcast Description The internet has gifted Myf and Zan this week, with shortcuts to cooking glory and cat filters for days. Pride Month in America is sparking lots of conversations about queer subcultures becoming the mainstream, and we’re digging into all the hot takes. And over in the UK big organisations are taking affirmative action on gender equality. Beryl pops by too. God love her.
Show notes:
Pakistani politician’s cat filter: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#110: Handmaid's Jenner, Cool to be Alone, Big Little Lies | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960169/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are capturing the week that was including birthday parties and OH BOY Kylie Jenner came up with a clanger of a theme for one of hers. An opinion piece on society’s view of singledom resonates deeply with us, while we’re planning our Golden Girls retirement and – for Myf at least – it’ll be on a boat. And the return of an HBO series has Zan absolutely razzed for the sport of watching Streep actor the shit out of it.</description></item><item><title>#109: Helicopter Woman, Rich Musicians, DNA Travel | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960170/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 16:13:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are spinning you right round baby, right round. Oh boy. Thank you internet. A helicopter rescue has us in tears, meanwhile it’s raining money in Jay-Z and Rihanna’s world but music isn’t necessarily the maker. A strange collab between Ancestry and commerce seems very on the nose, but Myf is consoling herself with Digestives, so we’re all good.
Show notes:
Helicopter Woman: https://junkee.com/helicopter-woman/208658
Jay-Z billionaire: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#108: Bong On, CWA, Fleabag | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960171/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 16:47:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960171/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are reunited, but reflecting back on a lot of things for good reason this week. A listening-at-half-speed mistake in the Bang Fam has us on the floor, while the CWA is proving that women who band together and fight the good fight, rule. There’s more updates on Moby and Yiayia, while we’re devouring TV shows like nobody's business. And in Breaking Bang, we’re bringing Bang On Live to Brissie for the first time!</description></item><item><title>#107: Moby, Cardi B, Celine Carpool Karaoke | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960172/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 16:52:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf is dialling in from Rome, in the days following Eurovision, cos she can. A new Moby biography detailing the women he “tried to date” has the internet abuzz and we have thoughts. Oh we have thoughts. Cardi B is proving why her social media rants are always ripe for remixing, and Celine Dion has just won Carpool Karaoke. Meanwhile Myf is sitting down to Wine Country and we’re all moving the Bang Fam to Italy.</description></item><item><title>#106: Eurovision, Socks n’ Sandals, Spritz | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960173/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 17:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960173/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are looking at the endless drone of election campaigning, and dark news out of Alabama and sending back a reprieve of light and fluffy fodder for our Bang Fam. With Eurovision in full swing, Myf joins you from bed in Tel Aviv where the sun is just coming up. All the goss from the world’s biggest song competition awaits. Meanwhile fashion has gone a bit State School Science Teacher, but Myf is one step ahead of the curve, and a hot take on Aperol Spritz has the internet abuzz.</description></item><item><title>#105: Met Gala, #MyMum, Yiayia Next Door | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960174/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 16:42:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960174/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s farshun Christmas with the annual Met Gala on show. So many thoughts. So many hot takes. So much to dissect. The Daily Telegraph’s attack on a politician misses the mark on the realities of women’s sacrifice, but the internet restores the balance, and we’re ready to hand over cold hard cash for a unique Madonna meet 'n’ greet. Meanwhile, Yiayia next door is bringing Zan much joy, while Russian spies have got Myf razzed.</description></item><item><title>#104: Taylor Swift, Slacker Culture, Sally Rooney | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960175/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 16:34:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960175/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are in their pastels and digesting the week in pop culture. Tay Tay has been accused of ripping off Bey, but we’re wise to it. A great article about the pendulum swinging back towards slacker culture has us ready for the revival, and the darkness of the latest Game of Thrones was intentional, but not helpful for most of the world’s viewers. Don’t worry, it’s a spoiler free zone.</description></item><item><title>#103: Sri Lanka, Chill Music, Adele | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960176/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 16:35:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960176/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan’s conversations around the differing values of culture in the wake of tragedy rises again, this time following the horrific terrorist attacks in Sri Lanka. On a completely other tip, an article on the rise of chill music has us divided, and the public ownership of pop stars in a time of personal pain, leaves a bad taste in our mouths. In a week of darkness, discrimination of the astrological kind in a share house gives us some light relief.</description></item><item><title>#102: Notre Dame, Beyonce, Game of Thrones | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960177/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 17:29:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960177/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are digesting another big week, and talking about the significance of Notre Dame. The fire in this iconic Parisian building caused a global reaction, but what of the other monuments that receive less attention? Is our value of culture firmly rooted in western traditions? We’ve watched Beyonce’s “Homecoming” film with you, and have plenty of thoughts buzzing in our Beyhive. Game of Thrones has returned for it’s swansong, and we’re diving into some hot takes from it’s debut.</description></item><item><title>#101: Black Holes, Death of Genre, Alan Partridge | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960178/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 16:36:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960178/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are razzed about the photographic evidence of a supermassive black hole, although it’s fair to say Myf is somewhat critical of the quality of the snap. A chart topping, genre defining song has us questioning the value of traditional gatekeepers to everyday music fans. And an article about poo gives us the opportunity to talk about poo. Plus in another world first (soz Black Hole, you’re not the only news today), we’re going Instagram Live for the very first time for a group Bang Fam viewing of the Beyonce doco “Homecoming” on Netflix.</description></item><item><title>#100: April Fools, Rock n Roll Hall of Fame, The Century | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960179/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 16:16:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan mark 100 episodes of Bang On! Holy hell, where did that time go? April Fools has rolled around, but the foolin’ has made way for the hard sell and we’re more than a little cynical of it all. A red carpet moment from Robert Smith of The Cure has sparked a bigger conversation around entitlement, and an article about reality TV has Myf vindicated. Plus we mark the century with a few memories, and it wouldn’t be an occasion if Beryl didn’t drop by.</description></item><item><title>#99: Jagged Little Pill, Mel &amp; Geri, Jundies | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960180/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 16:32:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan have found 2019’s first bad take, and we’re digging in. NASA have neglected to sort out spacesuits for a history making spacewalk and we’re facepalming, and news of a Spice Girls romp has us cynical for why we’re hearing it now. Plus there’s a double fashion update, with Myf here for all of it.
Show notes:
NASA Astronauts: https://www.abc.net.au/news/2019-03-26/nasa-cancels-first-all-female-spacewalk-no-fitting-suits/10942166?pfmredir=sm
Make-up kit shuttle: https://airandspace.si.edu/collection-objects/make-kit-shuttle
Jagged Little Pill is Actually Very Bad?</description></item><item><title>#98: Jacinda’s Leadership, Janet’s Glasto, Car Koala | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960181/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 16:34:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan find strength in the compassion and empathy of Jacinda Ardern, and reflect on how differently Australian politicians and media reacted to the Christchurch terrorist attack. Egg Boy has been a beacon of hope in a dark week, but has the focus on him come at the expense of a much harder conversation? Meanwhile Glastonbury has been announced and Janet Jackson has gone the ol’ cut and paste on the poster, and the sweet relief of good news has come in the form of a hitchhiking koala.</description></item><item><title>#97: Michael Jackson, Cancellation Culture, 90s Websites | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960182/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 16:59:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960182/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s another heavy week but thank dog we have each other to debrief with. Myf and Zan have watched the Leaving Neverland documentary, and unpack the way the story was told and the stories we told ourselves. In the wake of the latest allegations, is it possible to cancel a cultural giant? Is it right? And what does it mean for the conversations that are silenced, with it? On a (blessedly) lighter note, an archive of websites from the dawn of the world wide web has us reminiscing about the golden age of fonts, and a college admissions scandal in the States sadly confirms everything we already knew.</description></item><item><title>#96: Luke Perry, R Kelly, Flat Earthers | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960183/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 18:26:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960183/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan digest another, quite frankly, heavy week. After our 90210 reboot chat last week, it was a shock to hear the news of Luke Perry’s sudden death. In the same 24 hours, Keith Flint of The Prodigy also passed. We reflect on what they meant to us, in our formative years. An intense interview between Gayle King and R Kelly has everyone talking, and a tiny farshun update is quite frankly, the release we need this week.</description></item><item><title>#95: Oscars, Fat Rat, 90210 | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960184/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 16:51:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960184/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan relive their favourite moments from the Oscars, and dig into that performance from Lady Gaga and Bradley Cooper. A fat rat trapped in a manhole in Germany has brought the world great joy, while a reported reboot of Beverly Hills 90210 isn’t quite what you think it is. And we’re banging on about some heavy stories that need to be told.
Show notes:
Shallow at the Oscars: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#94: Lagerfeld, Zip Jeans, Dirty John | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960185/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 17:28:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960185/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan reflect on designer Karl Lagerfeld’s legacy, good and bad, in the wake of public reaction to his passing. A story from an Air France flight has us squealing, and our DM’s have been flooded with notifications after Alexander Wang released some very special jeans. And the adaptation of a podcast to the small screen has us completely hooked.
Show notes:
Anti-Condolences for Lagerfeld: https://wearyourvoicemag.com/culture/anti-condolences-karl-lagerfeld
Jameela Jamil on Lagerfeld: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#93: Grammys, Ryan Adams, Russian Doll | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960186/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 17:18:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960186/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan have all eyes on farshun at the Grammy Awards cos that’s what it’s all about, right? A New York Times article on Ryan Adams has us thinking about abuse of power, and the music industry’s day of reckoning. Myf is quizzing Zan on whether her apartment is a man repeller, and we’re shredding through a couple of brilliant Netflix series.
Show notes:
Eurovision: https://www.sbs.com.au/programs/eurovision
Grammys farshun: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#92: Superbowl, Hottest 100 Revote, Black Saturday | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960187/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960187/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are bored shitless by the Superbowl Halftime Show, but the absence of a real headliner has more to say about the power of protest than the lack of Levine’s clothing. A Hottest 100 revote reveals that you shouldn’t mess with history, and confirms that songs can triumph as emotional memory above all else. We’ve got the latest Fyre Festival update, and Myf is overjoyed at a new season of Call My Agent, while Zan is compelled by a brilliant account of an Australian tragedy.</description></item><item><title>#91: Hottest 100, KAK + Yumi, Eggshell Skull | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960188/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 17:22:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960188/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are unpacking what is, on record, the slowest tempo Hottest 100 in history and what it means. The many discussions around Kerri-Anne Kennerly and Yumi Stynes on Studio 10 have us diving in too, while Oscar noms are bringing joy to a certain Brit. The Fyre Fest flow-on online spirals us into interesting new territory, and Zan is saying Konbanwa to the new Terrace House season, while Myf is flicking the pages of a brilliant new Australian book.</description></item><item><title>#90: ICYMI, Fyre, Bros | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960189/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 18:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960189/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are back and banging into 2019! We catch up on the important stuff we missed over the break; from Kondo to Cardi B, to the 10 Year Challenge. And in the wake of two excellent docos on the failed Fyre Festival, we unpack the bigger story it tells of where we are right now. There’s farshun, we’re banging on, and most of all we're stoked to be back with the Bang Fam.</description></item><item><title>Bonus ep: Year in Review! | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960190/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 12:02:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960190/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan have a Christmas gift for you! A couple of months back, you may have heard a special Bang On live from the Thornbury Theatre in Melbourne. There was part of that live show that wasn't included in the podcast - but it's here for you now!
It’s the Bang On YEAR IN REVIEW! Bang On will be back in your feeds at the end of Jan.</description></item><item><title>#89: Goop Gift Guide, Post Malone Crocs, Listmas | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960191/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 17:02:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960191/</guid><description>Podcast Description ‘Tis the season! Myf and Zan wind up Bang On for the year by going shopping with Gwyneth, while Myf has Zan’s stocking stuffed with some limited edition Crocs. End of Year lists have Zan seeing what she missed, and we’re wrapping the year with some of the best shows, podcasts and books to binge over summer. Happy Festivus! Show notes:
How many fries to eat: https://www.news.com.au/lifestyle/health/diet/this-is-exactly-how-may-fries-you-can-eat-in-one-serve/news-story/b6cf2a573683babf862b12949d20fb7cGoop Gift Guide: https://goop.</description></item><item><title>#88: Victoria's Secrets, The Bad Sex Awards, Goat Yoga | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960192/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 15:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960192/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan discuss the Victoria's Secret show and wonder if it still has a place in 2018 as it is, Zan does a call out to designers urging them to create 'fancy evening wear' for people with curves and Myf is here for the new [potential] craze of Goat Yoga. Plus, it's that time of the year again - The Bad Sex Awards are back!
Show notes:</description></item><item><title>#87: ARIAs, Knickers, Lena Dunham | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960193/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 17:34:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960193/</guid><description>Podcast Description Zan backs up after the ARIA Awards with minimal sleep but maximal stories about Australian music’s night of nights. Knickers the giant cow has everyone talking and we’re here for it. And a long long read about Lena Dunham has us questioning our own reactions to this divisive creator. Meanwhile Melania Trump has decked the halls once again and oh boy, it’s gonna be a bloody Christmas. Show notes:</description></item><item><title>#86: Iceberg, Pamela, House of Cards | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960194/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 17:21:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960194/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan wrap the week of music, art, life and lettuce much like an iceberg wraps it’s perfect self in it’s own glad wrap. We discuss the bogan leaf and it’s comeback, while on telly we’re watching the reactions of different men to Scott Morrison’s comments about Pamela Anderson. The plotline for the doomed Sex and the City 3 movie has been revealed and explains everything about the aforementioned doom, and Myf gets Zan on the couch for some deep therapy in her television choices.</description></item><item><title>#85: Pellegrini’s, Peach + Boss, Victim or Vixen | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960195/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 17:04:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960195/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan wrap the week that was, highs and lows, and farewell a Melbourne icon who welcomed all. Madonna has made an incredible self-aware SIX MINUTE ad for her facial roller and we’re here for it. Channel 10 have rebranded with some unfortunately gendered channel names, in 2018. And in a week of frustrating stories being told by men, of women’s experiences, a piece on Monica Lewinsky has us thinking about who gets to live in victimville.</description></item><item><title>#84: Spice Girls, Homesteading, The Good Place | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960196/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960196/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are ready to spice up your life with another week that was. The rumoured reunion has finally been confirmed, but where’s Posh and why is she posing that way? Myf is hankering for a simpler life and considering joining the Homesteading Movement, and we’ve found a website that lists all the words that became words the year you were born. Hours of fun. Meanwhile we’re banging on about books and TV and singing a bit too.</description></item><item><title>#83: Halloween, Horror, Bodyguard | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960197/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 17:06:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960197/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan and Beyonce are celebrating Halloween in our own little ways, while a timely take on the changing social commentary within horror movies has us thinking. Prince's family are trying to trademark the colour purple (no jokes) and we're a bit flummoxed by that. And we're both a little worn out so watching heaps of Netflix in bed at home. Show notes:
Beyonce Halloween: https://www.instagram.com/p/BpkdLlZHH_5/?hl=en&amp;amp;taken-by=beyonceHorror movies with a social conscience: https://junkee.</description></item><item><title>#82: Bang On Live in Melbourne | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960198/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 16:41:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960198/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan bring Bang On to a sold out crowd for the first time ever in Melbs. With homemade badges in hand, they capture the week that was, with the Bang Fam. Rihanna has reportedly turned down the Superbowl Halftime Show in solidarity with quarterback Colin Kaepernick, but does it signal a shift in broadcast power as well? One of the biggest films of the year has opened, and we’re wondering if A Star Is Born pits pop music against “authenticity”.</description></item><item><title>#81: Royals, COSMO, Bohemian Rhapsody | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960199/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 17:16:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960199/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are sussing out the Duke and Duchess of Sussex’s royal visit, and saying farewell to the last women’s mag, on the news of COSMO’s closure. The Banksy art shred gets new life in fashion, as Myf’s curatorial brain gets to work on the meaning behind it all. And we’re gearing up for our own #Farshun parade, with only a few more sleeps till Bang On live in Melbourne.</description></item><item><title>#80: Taylor’s politics, Madonna massager, Cher | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960200/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 17:45:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960200/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are digesting some big news from all corners of the pop sphere. Taylor Swift has broken a career long silence on her politics, making us wonder the why’s, when’s and what for’s of it all. Madonna’s foray into the skin care world has unearthed a pragmatic tool, and Myf has found her magic tickets again to be front row for Cher. Believe. Plus we’re pleading with you to get behind an elaborate hashtag.</description></item><item><title>#79: Tampons, Kavanaugh, Kanye | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960201/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 17:48:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960201/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are celebrating a tax free flow from here on in, with the removal (finally) of the GST on sanitary products. The Kavanaugh-Ford hearings, and reactions, feel like yet another tipping point in the conversation around entitlement, assault and respect. We’re watching closely. And Ye is back at it again, and shredding friends by the second. Meanwhile, preparations for our upcoming Bang On Live event in Melbourne require your participation.</description></item><item><title>#78: Plane etiquette, Lily + MIA, Killing Eve | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960202/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 17:12:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960202/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are connecting deeply with a plane passenger who opened the door of a cockpit looking for a place to charge his phone. An excellent editorial on Lily Allen and MIA staying loud in a world that silences women has us thinking, and a triple breasted fashion show has us not [thinking]. And we’re glued to the laptop screen watching crime (fact and fiction). Show notes:</description></item><item><title>#77: Trioli, Qantas, Bert &amp; Ernie | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960203/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 17:36:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960203/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan connect deeply to an excellent speech Virginia Trioli gave this week on the strength of self and self belief. Qantas has decided to remove music from many flights, and we ponder the responsibilities of our national carrier. And the ARE THEY OR AREN’T THEY question about Bert &amp;amp; Ernie has finally been answered, but it’s Sesame Street’s official response that has us reacting.
Show notes:Virginia Trioli speech: http://www.</description></item><item><title>#76: Serena, NYFW, The Yoko Effect | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960204/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960204/</guid><description>Podcast Description Well, what a week. Zan and Myf digest the event at the Women’s Final of the US Open, the many think-pieces following it, and then that cartoon. New York Fashion Week has Myf glued to her screen for an iconic collection, and in the wake of Mac Miller’s death we look at the backlash against his ex partner Ariana Grande. Why are women demonized in toxic relationships? Oh and we have BIG news for our Bang Fam in Melbourne.</description></item><item><title>#75: Neighbours, The Music Canon, Jameela Jamil | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960205/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 18:22:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960205/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are back in the Bang Fam again, and celebrating the first same sex marriage on Australian screens since marriage equality. An editorial on the death of the traditional music canon has us frothing for the future, and actor/activist Jameela Jamil is calling into question the Kardashians, and breaking the spell.
Show notes:
Neighbours: https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2018/sep/04/neighbours-first-same-sex-wedding-reflects-australias-glorious-new-realityBland on Blonde: https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/aug/29/why-the-old-pop-music-canon-is-finished-greatest-albums-digital-ageJameela Jamil: https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2018/sep/03/jameela-jamil-is-right-the-kardashians-are-double-agents-for-the-patriarchyTonightly: https://www.facebook.com/tonightlyCrazy Rich Asians: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZQ-YX-5bAs0
Email us: bangon.</description></item><item><title>#74: Tennis, ASMR, Louis C.K. | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960206/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 17:08:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960206/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jan Fran sits in for Myf this week, and the US Open has us talking about more than the tennis with female players being penalised for their uniform approach. A new video of Janet Jackson doing ASMR has us both in a tizz, for very different reasons. And Louis C.K. has returned to stand up, ten months after admitting to sexual misconduct, sparking the question of choice and who gets the power to hold it?</description></item><item><title>#73: Aretha, Crazy Rich Asians, Parliament | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960207/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 17:08:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960207/</guid><description>Podcast Description Zan and Myf declare Bang On a politics free zone, except if they decide to run for PM. Watch this space. We recognise the legacy of the Queen of Soul, and digest a brilliant editorial from writer Michelle Law about Asian-Australian representation on screen.
Show notes:
The Party Room: http://www.abc.net.au/radionational/programs/partyroom/podcasts/
Aretha Franklin’s Respect: https://www.vox.com/2018/8/17/17699170/aretha-franklin-2018-respect-song-otis-redding-feminism-civil-rights
Why it’s important to see Asian-Australians on screen: https://junkee.com/asian-representation-australia/171514
Happily Never After: https://scribepublications.com.au/books-authors/books/happy-never-after
Foreign Correspondent: https://iview.</description></item><item><title>#72: Bananas in Pyjamas, Gay Disney, Crocs | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960208/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 17:08:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960208/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan have been jumping all over Australia together, culminating in their annual hang out with B1 and B2 in Canberra. We say Happy Birthday to an icon, and respond to the news that Disney’s first ever openly gay character will be played by a straight actor. There’s breaking farshun news, and one of the worst hot takes of the week. We got you.
Show notes:
B1 and B2 Bang On: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#71: Oscars, Beyonce's Vogue, Heathers | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960209/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 17:20:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960209/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are in Darwin in their finest Helen Bidou sarongs, and ready to Bang On in the Top End. The Oscars have announced a new category but why? Beyonce has complete control over Vogue's biggest issue of the year, and she's using her platform once again. And the 30th birthday of Heathers has Zan thinking about the hero that was Veronica Sawyer. Show notes: Oscars: https://news.avclub.com/oscars-add-best-popular-film-category-for-the-uncultu-1828194090Beyonce: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#70: Lee Lin, Celine, Bluesfest | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960210/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 16:33:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960210/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan pay tribute to a KWEEN, on the announcement of a legendary newsreader and cultural icon. Zan recounts the transformative experience of Celine Dion live, while the 30th birthday announcement of Bluesfest seems to be missing something. There’s a farshun update that has us hitting the shops (finally), and Myf is banging on about a show that’s described as Breaking Bad meets Steel Magnolia’s. Meanwhile Zan is glued to a compelling new podcast.</description></item><item><title>#69: Pilot Week, Splendour, Whitney | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960211/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 17:56:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960211/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are celebrating an episode milestone this week, but it’s unlikely they’ll make a big deal out of it. Meanwhile Channel 10 has let us know that there are plenty of funny men to watch on screen, and off the back of Splendour In the Grass, Zan is wondering whether it’s more about the headlines than the headliners. The power of all the senses is explored in a brilliant piece on restaurant music, and we’re banging on about two excellent doco’s about incredible women.</description></item><item><title>#68: Queen’s brooches, Madonna, You Can’t Ask That | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960212/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 17:14:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960212/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf is back in her Thai fisherman’s pants from holidays, and joining Zan to dissect the incredible trolling via brooch that Queen Elizabeth just unleashed. A great editorial on Madonna’s life-changing influence on a young gay fella has us again praising the power of platform, and Zan is binging TV while Myf is banging on about books.
Show notes:
Queen’s Brooch Troll: https://www.thepoke.co.uk/2018/07/17/queen-trolled-donald-trump-brooch-best-thing-youll-read-today/2/Matt Cain on Madonna: https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/jul/15/matt-cain-on-madonna-homophobic-interviewers-gay-culture?CMP=fb_guViv Albertine: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#67: NAIDOC, Drake, Dog Ice Creams | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960213/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960213/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf is still living the island lyfe, so Brooke Boney joins Zan to bang on about 'Black Christmas'. Drake is searching for legitimacy, but is he making the art to justify it? And a viral video of a dog and it’s owner sharing an ice cream has us pondering our own sharesies. And Zan is seeing farshun on screen, while BB has a thinkpiece to recommend.
Show notes:</description></item><item><title>#66: Logies, Leyonheljm, Overly Woke | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960214/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 18:17:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960214/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf is in the tropics, so Zan invites Jan Fran from The Feed to join the Bang Fam. Jan attended the Logies, so of course Zan grills her about that. Senator Leyonheljm’s comments about a fellow senator has the internet ablaze, and arguments around free-speech and slut-shaming are front and centre once again. And Zan is enjoying some Tracey Ullman gold while Jan has a podcast to share. Show notes:</description></item><item><title>#65: BDE, The Notebook, The Staircase | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960215/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 16:44:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960215/</guid><description>Podcast Description Zan is back from holidays and just in time for the internet to gift us with some Big Dick Energy. It makes sense once you listen. Myf catches up on Zan’s Greek Island adventures, and finds out which tv shows and movies she cried to on the plane. And a new Netflix show has everyone talking.
Show notes:
Milos: http://www.cntraveller.com/gallery/milos-greeceBig Dick Energy: https://www.thecut.com/2018/06/pete-davidson-ariana-grande-big-dick-energy.htmlOn The Run II: https://www.beyonce.com/The Staircase: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#64: Whoppers, The Carters, The Nanny | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960216/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 17:42:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960216/</guid><description>Podcast Description Zan is away on her final week of holidays, so Monique Bowley is back in the Bang Gang. Myf and Mon dissect Beyonce and Jay-Z's latest masterpiece, discuss whether The Handmaid's Tale is getting too hard to watch, plus - are we looking forward to a potential Nanny reboot?!
Show Notes:
Burger King in Russia: https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/worldviews/wp/2018/06/20/sorry-you-no-longer-get-a-free-burger-king-whopper-if-you-have-a-world-cup-stars-baby/?utm_term=.78e954d6c472 Handmaid's Tale: https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2018/jun/16/handmaids-tale-season-2-elisabeth-moss-margaret-atwood
The Carters: https://www.newyorker.com/culture/culture-desk/what-it-means-when-beyonce-and-jay-z-take-over-the-louvre
The Nanny: https://www.news.com.au/entertainment/tv/flashback/fran-drescher-confirms-shes-in-talks-to-reboot-the-nanny/news-story/9564a4ec9450b81ec50ed7562fcdf87a
Farshun: http://junkee.com/kath-kim-runway-models/164157
Queer Eye: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#63: Family Feud, Bourdain, Haim | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960217/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 17:02:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960217/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf is joined again this week by Monique Bowley, where they discuss Anthony Bourdain’s impact on food journalism and his role as an ally of the #metoo movement, dissect Haim’s bold pay parity move AND marvel at the Kardashian-West family’s uncharacteristic ugg boot and tracksuit pant moment: appearing on Family Feud! Show notes:
Kardasian-Wests on Family Feud: https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/arts-and-entertainment/wp/2018/06/11/no-one-has-ever-been-as-happy-as-kanye-west-on-celebrity-family-feud
Anthony Bourdain dies: http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-06-08/anthony-bourdain-dies-aged-61-cnn-says/9851840
Confessions of journalists covering celebrity deaths: https://digiday.</description></item><item><title>#62: Queer Eye in Yass, SATC, Miss America Swimsuits | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960218/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 17:27:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960218/</guid><description>Podcast Description Zan’s away but the Bang Gang still plays and this week we welcome Monique Bowley into the Bang Fam. Myf and Monique reassess Sex And The City through woke eyes on its 20th anniversary, discover what the Queer Eye crew were really doing in Yass and mull over Miss America ditching the togs for clogs.
Show Notes:
Queer Eye in Yass: https://twitter.com/NetflixANZ/status/1004452348423360512
Why do today's feminists hate Sex And The City: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#61: Roseanne, Kim K and Trump, Wild Wild Country | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960219/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 18:38:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960219/</guid><description>Podcast Description The star of TV’s biggest comeback has just been brought back down to earth, but how much of a surprise is her social media demise? The strangest pic on Trump’s twitter feed has us in a tizz, and there’s a #Farshun update that contains no denim but all style. Meanwhile Myf is watching docos on cults, while Zan is dipping into music industry history.
Show notes:
Roseanne: https://www.theguardian.com/culture/2018/may/29/roseanne-cancelled-what-happened-tweets-rise-fall-tv-biggest-showTrump and Kimmy K: https://twitter.</description></item><item><title>#60: Reverend Curry, Arrested Development, Westworld | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960220/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 17:45:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960220/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan debrief on the epic sermon from Reverend Michael Curry at the Royal Wedding, and ponder the power of that speech. Ahead of the recut new season of Arrested Development, a New York Times interview with the cast has done more harm than good. And Beyonce bought a church. Cos she’s Beyonce.
Show notes:
Michael Curry’s speech will go down in history: https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/may/20/bishop-michael-curry-sermon-history-harry-meghan-weddingMaxine Beneba Clarke’s Twitter thread: https://twitter.</description></item><item><title>#59: Spotify, The Americans, Jeggings | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960221/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960221/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf’s dedication to the Bang Fam knows no bounds as she joins Zan from the London airport lounge to talk post Eurovision goss and the buffet spread highlights. A new Spotify policy has us once again considering the conversation around the separation of art and the artist. Zan has been devouring The Americans final season, why Myf is finding time on planes to read debut novels by Australian musicians.</description></item><item><title>#58: Eurovision, Met Gala, Childish Gambino | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960222/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 18:04:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960222/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf is in Lisbon but nothing stops her from joining the Bang Fam for a gossip about the world of glitter, high drama and musical diplomacy. The Met Gala was a treat for the eyes, but was the theme a bit on the nose? And Childish Gambino’s new video (and song) is peak think-piece fodder, for good reason. Show notes:
Eurovision: https://www.sbs.com.au/programs/eurovisionMet Gala: https://www.vogue.com/tag/event/met-galaChildish Gambino: https://www.nytimes.com/2018/05/08/arts/music/childish-gambino-this-is-america-roundup.htmlI’m Not Black, I’m Kanye: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#57: Michelle Wolf, Janelle Monae, The Handmaids Tale | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960223/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 17:27:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960223/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan have been diving into the many reviews and think-pieces following the White House Correspondent’s dinner monologue by comedian Michelle Wolf. Meanwhile Janelle Monae has released one of the albums of the year, with an “emotion picture” to boot. And the fate of a band’s album was once in the hands of Pitchfork reviews, but does it still have the power to make or break? There’s a bonus pre-bang too, cos we love our Bang Fam (and want to warn you against bad decisions).</description></item><item><title>#56: Royal baby, Avicii, Paddlesteamers | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960224/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 17:23:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960224/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan and every other woman in the world are surprised about the time between childbirth and royal presentation of the new Prince, and have thoughts on that. The death of Avicii causes us to ponder the duty of care in not-so-traditional work environments, and Shania Twain has been copping heat for her perceived support of Trump. Meanwhile, Zan has been in Moscow, while Myf is on the Murray and we’re good with both.</description></item><item><title>#55: Kanye, Kendrick, Beyoncé | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960225/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 18:11:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960225/</guid><description>Podcast Description What a week. Myf and Zan are stoked to see Kanye back on Twitter, and unveiling his book of philosophy in real time. Kendrick Lamar has made history as the first rapper to win the Pulitzer Prize for Music. And we invite special guest Nkechi Anele into the Bang Fam Beyhive to unwrap the enormity that was Beychella. Kanye tweets: https://twitter.com/kanyewestKendrick Lamar Pulitzer: https://www.nytimes.com/2018/04/17/arts/music/kendrick-lamar-music-pulitzer-prize-damn.htmlDaily Fail: http://junkee.com/daily-mail-bachelor-vapid/154733Beychella: https://www.nytimes.com/2018/04/15/arts/music/beyonce-coachella-review.htmlThe Pin: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#54: Yo-Yo’s, Janelle Monae, The Breakfast Club revisited | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960226/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 17:29:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960226/</guid><description>Podcast Description Zan asks a question about Yo Yo biscuits that gets way out of hand, and we could have an early winner of 2018 farshun with the release of Janelle Monae’s new videoclip. Molly Ringwald has been watching her own films again and seeing them in a new light, while Myf has been hanging out with Helen Bidou.
Show notes:
Yo-Yo’s: http://vanillawings.blogspot.com.au/2011/05/melting-moments-yo-yos.htmlJanelle Monae: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PaYvlVR_BEcWhat About The Breakfast Club?: https://www.newyorker.com/culture/personal-history/what-about-the-breakfast-club-molly-ringwald-metoo-john-hughes-pretty-in-pinkThe Death of Stalin: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#53: Opening Ceremonies, Men Write Women, Russell Crowe | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960227/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 17:41:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960227/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan recap the confusing and wonderful and very Surfers Paradise Commonwealth Games Opening Ceremony, while catching up on some fine representations of women in literature. Russell Crowe’s divorce auction has us saving our pennies, and we sing again. Why not eh?
Show notes:
Opening Ceremony: http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-04-04/commonwealth-games-2018-opening-ceremony-gold-coast-live-blog/9619078Men Write Women: https://www.theguardian.com/books/booksblog/2018/apr/03/male-authors-write-female-characters-twitterRussell Crowe’s Divorce Auction: http://junkee.com/russell-crowe-divorce-auction/150533Bluesfest: http://doublej.net.au/news/features/13-unforgettable-moments-of-bluesfest-2018-The Trauma Cleaner: https://www.textpublishing.com.au/books/the-trauma-cleaner-one-woman-s-extraordinary-life-in-death-decay-disasterEmail us: bangon.podcast@abc.net.au
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#52: Bang On bangs back | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960228/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960228/</guid><description>Podcast Description We reach out to the Bang Fam for tips on what you’ve been loving or loathing, and you deliver once again! Emma tells you about a new all female Western on Netflix, Holly riffs on Party Hard legend Andrew W.K.’s first new music in yonks, and Erin goes where many others have feared to tread; to Darren Aronofsky’s “Mother!”. Godless: https://www.netflix.com/au/title/80097141Andrew W.K.: http://andrewwk.com/news/new-album-out-now-andrew-wk-releases-youre-not-alone#disqus_threadMother! https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XpICoc65uh0Email us: bangon.podcast@abc.net.au
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#51: Detroit House, Facebook, RIP Keyboard Cat | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960229/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 18:09:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960229/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan discover their dream home in Detroit and start saving for it. The Cambridge Analytica story has us thinking again about how much we allow Facebook into our lives, and Cynthia Nixon’s run for NY Governor has us pondering the celebrity politician. And it’s a sad farewell to Bento, the Keyboard Cat, with his stiff little arms bringing the world so much joy. Show notes:
Detroit House: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#50: 1970’s food, Honey Bachelor, The Long Read | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960230/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 17:01:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960230/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan ponder over the hideousness of 1970’s food, as Zan plans for a themed dinner party. Nick Cummins AKA The Honey Badger has been announced as the next Bachelor and of course we have thoughts. And an online piece that everyone is talking about has us wondering, is the long form read making a comeback?
Show notes:
1970’s Dinner Party: https://twitter.com/70s_partyNick Cummins is The Bachelor: https://thefix.nine.com.au/2018/03/15/05/08/nick-cummins-confirmed-as-the-bachelor-2018Worst Roommate Ever: http://nymag.</description></item><item><title>#49: Mardi Gras, Oscars, NME | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960231/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 18:01:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960231/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan debrief on their Mardi Gras parties, and dig into the insane goodie bags that Oscars attendees receive. The NME is calling it a day in print form, which has Myf reflecting on the beating heart of music journalism as a fan, and emerging writer. And we’re celebrating International Women’s Day. That’s every day, in our world tbh.
Show notes:
Mardi Gras 2018: https://www.sbs.com.au/ondemand/video/1164538947938/Sydney-Gay-and-Lesbian-Mardi-Gras-2018Oscars goodie bag: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#48: Perth, 50/50 Festivals, Dolce Drones | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960232/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 17:13:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960232/</guid><description>Podcast Description Zan is in Perth and very excited about music and stadiums, while Myf is reminding us of Zan’s Perth past. Music Festivals in the UK are pledging gender equality by 2022, in the same week an Australian festival announces an entirely male line-up, and it’s time for another Farshun update. Isn’t every week Farshun Week on Bang On?
Show notes:
Perth Stadium: https://www.youtube.com/watch?time_continue=2&amp;amp;v=sjBjuvyAUTEGender equality at music festivals: http://www.bbc.com/news/entertainment-arts-43196414Dolce &amp;amp; Gabbana Drones: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#47: Xenophon Rap, Black Panther, #MAFS | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960233/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 17:27:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960233/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan get sucked into a seasoned politicians stutter rap, and bask in the glory (and many think-pieces) around the latest Marvel blockbuster. Myf is viewing Married At First Sight in “omnibus” form and explains what that, and the show, means to Zan. And in between we’re on another planet, forgive us, Bang Fam.
Show notes:
Xenophon Rap: https://www.sbs.com.au/news/a-rapping-and-dancing-xenophon-courts-sa-voters-in-campaign-adBlack Panther Round Up: https://www.nytimes.com/2018/02/20/watching/black-panther-movie-roundup.html?smid=fb-nytimes&amp;amp;smtyp=curMarried At First Sight: https://www.9now.com.au/married-at-first-sight/season-5Hunger: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#46: Queer Eye, Obama Portrait, Lady Bird | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960234/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 16:36:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960234/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan have been soaking up the reboot of Queer Eye, and wading through the internet’s hot takes on it’s relevance in 2018. There’s another face app kicking around, so of course we’ve given it a burl, and the world of political portraiture is changing and we’re here for it. Plus we’ve found a cross section between the Winter Olympics and farshun. Gold medal podcast, tbh.
Show notes:</description></item><item><title>#45: Quincy Jones, Super Bowl, Elon Musk | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960235/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 17:27:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960235/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are thanking the internet angels for a Q&amp;amp;A with Quincy that is giving us life. The Super Bowl halftime show fell a little flat except for one saving grace, and Zan is very excited about rockets and space while Myf is devouring books on creativity. Oh and there’s a Farshun update. Show notes:
Quincy Jones in Conversation: http://www.vulture.com/2018/02/quincy-jones-in-conversation.htmlSelfie Kid: http://time.com/5133184/selfie-kid-justin-timberlake-super-bowl-halftime-show/Falcon Heavy: http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-02-07/spacex-rocket-takes-sports-car-into-space/9403618Farshun: https://www.teenvogue.com/story/unravel-project-debuts-denim-belt-for-dollar400?mbid=social_twitterGoing Greyscale: https://www.nytimes.com/2018/01/12/technology/grayscale-phone.htmlBig Magic: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#44: Shania, Lorde, IKEA | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960236/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 18:11:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960236/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan get excited about big tours coming, and Michael Bolton on a Tuesday. The founder of IKEA has died but left a flatpack legacy that has become the cornerstone of all relationships. And Lorde is gone but not forgotten from the Grammy stage and we have thoughts on that. Show notes:
Michael Bolton Tuesdays: https://www.instagram.com/p/BekZ7Z9ACtB/?taken-by=zanroweShania Twain Touring: http://www.smh.com.au/entertainment/music/shania-twain-announces-first-australian-tour-in-almost-two-decades-20180131-h0rl61.htmlIKEA Founder Dies: https://thenewdaily.com.au/news/people/2018/01/29/ikea-founder-ingvar-kamprad-dies/Lorde (not) at Grammys: http://variety.com/2018/music/news/why-isnt-lorde-performing-at-the-grammys-sources-explain-1202679146/Parliament House: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#43: ICYMI, Google Arts and Culture App, I, Tonya | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960237/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 17:40:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960237/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are back after summer break and speed rounding their way around the summer. A new app taps into art and narcissism and we love it, and more tech giant founders are talking about the addictions we’re lured into, with our smart phones. And we’ve been busy watching depictions of real people on screen, high and low brow alike.
Show notes:
Google Arts and Culture App: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Bang On Recommends: The Real Thing | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960238/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 17:30:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960238/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Real Thing celebrates unique Australian characters.
On this episode: Meet Lizzy Gardiner. Her early life included minimal supervision, late nights at the Dubbo drive-in and a stint in Papua New Guinea. Lizzy's unusual experiences made her a perfect fit for the turbulent film industry, where she won an Oscar for the costumes in Priscilla, Queen of the Desert. But she never thought a bold decision to wear a dress made out of credit cards would be part of her legacy.</description></item><item><title>Bang On Recommends: How Do You Sleep At Night? | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960239/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 17:28:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960239/</guid><description>Podcast Description How Do You Sleep At Night? is a new podcast hosted by Hack’s Sarah McVeigh. It’s about people who live their lives in the face of judgement.
On this episode: Charlie stabbed and killed two innocent men on a night out in Brisbane in the '90s. Retrace the night he took their lives, meet his mum and discover how he lives with himself. And a warning — there’s very strong language in this episode.</description></item><item><title>#42: Bonus Bang On | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960240/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960240/</guid><description>Podcast Description A special treat from Bang On Live, Myf &amp;amp; Zan give out awards for Artist Of The Year, Bang Backer Of The Year and of course, the greatest moment in #farshun Transcript</description></item><item><title>#41: Cat Person, MeNoMore, Vegemite Icy Poles | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960241/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960241/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan talk about the short story every else has been talking about this week, and reflect on the huge year of uprising in the wake of Harvey Weinstein. It’s been epic. A refresher in the form of Vegemite icy poles has one of us excited, and with holidays on the horizon we’re banging on about stuff one last time. Thanks for being the best Bang Fam a coupla women could dream for.</description></item><item><title>#40: Job swaps, Paul McCartney, Sia | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960242/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960242/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been a huge week for Myf and Zan, and we talk about all the ch-ch-ch-changes in our working and creative worlds in 2018. Zan has been hanging out with Paul McCartney, so lets you know what went down when the microphones weren’t on, and Sia’s rejection of fame has been called into question in her use of Maddie Ziegler as her public face. Show notes:
Zan’s new gig: http://www.</description></item><item><title>#39: ARIAs, Bad Sex Awards, Harry and Meghan | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960243/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960243/</guid><description>Podcast Description Zan gives the goss on what happened backstage at the ARIA Awards when she was wearing Myf’s clothes (creep), and the annual Bad Sex Awards for literature have begun again! We’re talking Royal Family news and how “woke” the Windsors are becoming, and banging on about banging. Kind of. It’s been a big week.
Show notes:
Backstage at the ARIAs: https://www.instagram.com/p/BcCBONHAxIh/?taken-by=zanroweMeghan Markle’s lineage: http://www.newsweek.com/prince-harrys-fiancee-meghan-markle-related-william-shakespeare-and-winston-726068Bad Sex in Literature shortlist: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#38: Bird of the Year, Emo’s problem with women, Nanette | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960244/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960244/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan are all in on The Guardian’s bird poll, and casting our votes. Allegations of sexual misconduct have been made against the lead singer of Brand New, unleashing more than a couple of think-pieces on mid 00’s emo music’s problem with women. And Zan has been reading from the paper of a 10 year old journalist, while Myf is floored by Hannah Gadsby’s swan song. Show notes:</description></item><item><title>#37: Bang On Live at Giant Dwarf for Yack Festival | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960245/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 17:00:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960245/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan bang on in front of a sold out crowd of Bang Fam, in Sydney. Former Facebook President Sean Parker has called out the social media giant for their exploitation of human vulnerability, while Zan wonders if Taylor’s new media strategy is doing the same. We actively choose to watch Bad Moms Christmas and have many thoughts on that, and it’s interesting how salty we can get when we have a crowd cheering us on.</description></item><item><title>#36: Sia Nudes, Britney Spears art, Noel Gallagher's scissors solo | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960246/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960246/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan rejoice at Sia taking control of her leaked naked photo, celebrate Britney Spears’ unleashing of her inner Monet with her foray into visual art and applaud Noel Gallagher’s crafty use of scissors as a musical instrument. Show notes:
Sia nude fightback - https://www.theguardian.com/media/shortcuts/2017/nov/07/how-to-style-out-a-naked-photo-leak-sias-approach-is-just-one-of-a-few-options Britney is an artist now - https://www.vanityfair.com/style/2017/11/britney-spears-art-sold-for-ten-thousand-dollars
RIP Paddles - https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/nov/08/paddles-first-cat-of-new-zealand-dies-hit-by-car-jacinda-ardern
Noel Gallagher’s scissors solo - http://www.nme.com/blogs/nme-blogs/noel-had-someone-playing-scissors-last-night-and-people-are-confused-2155344
Diddy is Love - https://www.usmagazine.com/celebrity-news/news/diddy-i-was-only-joking-about-that-name-change/</description></item><item><title>#35: Lion King remake, Butter Shortage, Highly Vaginal Album Art | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960247/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 18:06:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960247/</guid><description>Podcast Description Zan is stoked about the cast announcement for The Lion King but Myf seems more keen to talk about the impending butter shortage worldwide. The sexual harassment house of cards continues to fall in Hollywood, while airlines are filling aisles with live music. And Bjork’s highly vaginal artwork has us googling inappropriate things at work. Again.
Lion King cast announced: http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-11-02/the-lion-king-beyonce-to-star-as-nala/9111180
Hollywood’s house of cards: http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-11-02/hollywood-sex-accusations-now-levelled-at-ratner-hoffman/9110048
Butter crisis: http://www.</description></item><item><title>#34: Stu or Jarrod, Kate Nash, Dirty John | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960248/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960248/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan can’t / don’t want to predict The Bachelorette finale, meanwhile hungry “hot content” creators are dismissing artists willy-nilly. There’s a farshun update from Tokyo Farshun week, and we’ve been devouring other podcasts about people who do bad things.
Malcolm Turnbull's Dog Blog: https://www.malcolmturnbull.com.au/dog-blog
Bang On Live: https://giantdwarf.com.au/events/bang-on-yack/The Bachelorette Penultimate Power Ranking: http://junkee.com/bachelorette-power-ranking-straitjacket/132468Kate Nash hits back: http://www.nme.com/news/music/kate-nash-buzzfeed-article-no-longer-exists-2152998The Jong: http://www.news.com.au/lifestyle/fashion/fashion-trends/thong-jeans-bizarre-designer-denim-trend-puts-your-entire-bum-on-display/news-story/f3a64517bf5305f902133abf08063813How Do You Sleep At Night? http://www.abc.net.au/radio/programs/how-do-you-sleep-at-night/Dirty John: http://www.</description></item><item><title>#33: Lisa Wilkinson, CD Collections, Molto Bene | Bang On</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5054960249/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 18:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5054960249/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myf and Zan catch up where wages don’t, on parity. An article about keeping or turfing their CD collections has them pondering the past again, and they bond over high school Italian for no reason whatsoever.
Show notes:
Lisa Wilkinson and the gender pay gap: http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-10-19/lisa-wilkinson-gender-pay-gap-your-stories/9063812Is It Time To Get Rid of Your CD Collection: http://doublej.net.au/news/features/that-cd-collection-youve-got-time-to-sellTheir Grotesque Indifference: https://meanjin.com.au/blog/their-grotesque-indifference/Pretty For An Aboriginal: https://itunes.apple.com/gb/podcast/pretty-for-an-aboriginal/id1282132573?mt=2
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>