<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/nerdwallets-smart-money-podcast/</link><description>Recent content in NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/nerdwallets-smart-money-podcast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Year-End Money Tasks to Thrive in 2024 and How to Choose a Budgeting App | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720326/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720326/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn about practical money management tasks to set yourself up for success in 2024 and tips for choosing a budgeting app.
01:11 This Week in Your Money: Hosts Sean Pyles and Sara Rathner propose three money tasks to tackle this winter. The first is a task to do this week, the next is something to do over the course of a month, and the last is something you can do over the whole winter season.</description></item><item><title>How Your Feedback Shapes Our Podcast: Listener Messages from 2023 | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720325/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 08:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720325/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of NerdWallet&amp;rsquo;s Smart Money Podcast, hosts Sean Pyles and Sara Rathner share feedback and constructive criticism from listeners over the past year. They discuss topics such as the need for more representation minority groups in financial discussions, the importance of highlighting issues related to race and gender, the coverage of alternative healthcare in insurance plans, and the challenges of discussing controversial topics from a financial perspective.</description></item><item><title>Using AI to Budget and Save and Debit vs. Credit Card Pros and Cons | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720324/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 08:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720324/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn how to use AI for help with budgeting and saving money, then learn whether credit cards or debit cards are safer. 01:30 This Week in Your Money: NerdWallet banking writer Chanelle Bessette joins hosts Sean Pyles and Sara Rathner to discuss how AI can be used to help with budgeting and saving money. They explore how AI chatbots can assist in creating a budget and setting savings goals, why it’s important to double check chatbots’ math and consider seeking official financial advice for more risky decisions.</description></item><item><title>Financial Success Stories: Learn from Listener Wins in 2023 | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720323/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 08:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720323/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of the Smart Money podcast, hosts Sean Pyles and Sara Rathner share the best money moves made by their listeners in 2023. Some of the wins include listeners who moved their Roth IRA account away from a pricey financial advisor, one who paid off their student loans and started a business, and another who successfully managed their money with ADHD. In their conversation, the Nerds discuss: Roth IRAs, credit scores, student loans, estate planning, home buying, credit cards, financial advisors, high-yield savings accounts, paying off cars, money market accounts, 401ks, and HSAs.</description></item><item><title>Money News: Ticketmaster Trouble, Alaska Airlines Merger, GDP Updates and More | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720322/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720322/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn how the Department of Justice is tackling the ticketing industry — and what it could mean for buyers and sellers. Before focusing on Congress’ latest ticketing industry crackdown, hosts Sean Pyles and Anna Helhoski discuss the IRS&amp;rsquo; delayed online seller rule, a revision to Q3 GDP figures, a new survey on money and happiness, the merger between Alaska Airlines and Hawaiian Airlines, and self-serve airplane snacks. Get ready for an episode that dissects the struggle for fair ticket prices and the potential consequences of a ticketing market in need of change.</description></item><item><title>Avoiding Financial Scams and Changing Your Money Mindset | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720321/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 08:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720321/</guid><description>Podcast Description Protect yourself from sophisticated holiday shopping scams and explore the psychology behind changing your money mindset. 01:07 This Week in Your Money: Hosts Sean Pyles and Sara Rathner discuss tactics for avoiding three common money scams, including social media ad scams, charity scams, and gift card scams. 10:08 Today’s Money Question: Sean and Sara answer a listener’s question about how to change your money mindset. They discuss methods you can use to understand your current attitudes and behaviors towards money, the emotional connection to money and the stories we tell ourselves about our finances.</description></item><item><title>Using Your Financial Anxiety to Make Better Decisions | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720320/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 08:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720320/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to NerdWallet’s Smart Money podcast, where we answer real-world money questions. In this episode: Nerds Sean Pyles and Kimberly Palmer speak with Farnoosh Torabi, author of the new book, “A Healthy State of Panic.” She explains how we can use our fears as a superpower to make better decisions when it comes to finances, career and life. Torabi is a personal finance expert and host of the “So Money” podcast.</description></item><item><title>Is Your Personal Finance Indecision Costing You? Plus, How to Shop for a New Bank | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720319/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 08:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720319/</guid><description>Podcast Description Uncover the true cost of making financial decisions (and financial indecision) and get tips for shopping for a new bank. 01:19 This Week in Your Money: Explore the concept of financial opportunity cost and the trade-offs we make with our money with hosts Sean Pyles and Sara Rathner. They discuss the risks associated with sticking with the status quo, the importance of periodically reassessing your financial decisions, the potential pitfalls of always relying on automatic payments, and the benefits of switching banks and taking advantage of sign-up bonuses.</description></item><item><title>Money News: Where to Save Money on Falling Prices from Deflation | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720318/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720318/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn which prices are slowing down—or even dropping—as a result of deflation, including your Thanksgiving feast.
Before focusing on price deflation, hosts Sean Pyles and Anna Helhoski explore recent financial updates, including the rising income among first-time homebuyers, the United Autoworkers Union (UAW) ratifying new contracts with the Big Three automakers, and Black Friday and Cyber Monday sales trends.
Then, Sean and Anna explain what’s happening behind recent price deflation.</description></item><item><title>Money and Happiness: What's Happiness Really Worth? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720317/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720317/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you really need money to be happy? Or is money the reason you’re unhappy? Either way, chances are your relationship to money and happiness is a little, well, messy. To kick off this Nerdy deep dive into money and happiness, Sean talks with happiness experts Gretchen Rubin and Robert Puff to understand what happiness really means. Then Sean talks with Morgan Housel, author of “The Psychology of Money,” about where money and happiness intersect.</description></item><item><title>Your Guide to Budgeting, Credit and Debt Management Strategies | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720315/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 08:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720315/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn tactics to make and manage a budget, understand credit scores, and manage debt to improve your financial health. 02:02 Budgeting Basics: Personal Finance Nerd Elizabeth Ayoola discusses how you can create and stick to a budget. She explains how to use the 50-30-20 method to allocate your income, gives tips on how to adjust your budget to fit your needs, and methods for budgeting and stretching your paycheck when it arrives at different intervals, like monthly or biweekly.</description></item><item><title>Money News: Latest Stock Market News, New IRS Tax Brackets, Tipping Trends | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720314/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720314/</guid><description>Podcast Description Delve into recent stock market developments. Plus, tax bracket adjustments.
Before taking an in-depth look at what’s going on in the stock and bond markets, hosts Sean Pyles and Anna Helhoski delve into the recent developments in personal finance news. They start by breaking down the latest inflation numbers. Then, they discuss the concerning increase in credit card delinquencies, shedding light on rising balances and the generational shift in credit card usage before offering smart tips on managing credit balances in a high-interest rate environment.</description></item><item><title>Plan Your Black Friday Shopping Strategy and Should You Wait to Buy a Home? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720313/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 08:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720313/</guid><description>Podcast Description Craft your holiday shopping plan with Black Friday insights, then understand options for buying a home in today’s market. 01:24 This Week in Your Money: Unlock the secrets of savvy shopping by learning about the biggest sales events of the year. Hosts Sean Pyles and Sara Rathner discuss the holiday shopping season with Personal Finance Nerd Tommy Tindall, who talks about the value of shopping on Black Friday versus other annual sales events like Cyber Monday, the best days of the season to find deals in certain categories like big ticket electronics and winter clothing, and helpful tips for how to budget for your holiday shopping list.</description></item><item><title>Maximizing Your Benefits: A Guide to Employer-Provided Perks | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 08:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Understand employer-provided benefits, from dental and vision coverage to more unique perks like legal assistance. In the third and final episode of our special series on open enrollment, hosts Sean Pyles and Liz Weston discuss the various benefits that employers offer during open enrollment season aside from health insurance. Liz speaks with Amber Clayton (Society for Human Resource Management) about dental and vision coverage, long-term care insurance, pet insurance, legal assistance, adoption assistance, gym memberships, mental health benefits, and more.</description></item><item><title>Money News: Lawsuit Could Change How Houses are Sold; Also, a $23.5K Payout … in Coins | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn how recent headlines could impact your finances, including a federal real estate ruling and new employment figures. Hosts Sean Pyles and Anna Helhoski start by dissecting the latest monthly jobs report and its potential impact on the Federal Reserve&amp;rsquo;s interest rate policies, then explain how a recent federal jury&amp;rsquo;s decision on real estate agent commissions could reshape the way homes are bought and sold in the United States.</description></item><item><title>2 Ways to Improve Your Credit Score, Budgeting Tips, and Investing 403b and 529 Plans | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn about two quick credit tips, 403b and 529 plans, delinquencies on old loans, and budgeting when you only get paid once a month. 01:11 This Week in Your Money: Hosts Sean Pyles and Sara Rathner provide two quick tips for improving credit scores. The first tip involves credit utilization, which is the amount of available credit that you&amp;rsquo;re using. They also discuss the option of asking for an increased credit card limit.</description></item><item><title>Choosing the Right Insurance Policy to Protect Your Income: Life Insurance, Disability Insurance, and More | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Explore coverage options to protect your income in worst-case scenarios, such as life insurance and disability insurance. Hosts Sean Pyles and Liz Weston discuss the importance of insurance coverage, highlighting statistics around how many people are underinsured or lack adequate coverage. To dive deeper into different types of coverage, Liz welcomes Insurance Nerd Ryan Brady and John Ryan, founder and CEO of Ryan Insurance Strategy Consultants, to explain various types of insurance.</description></item><item><title>Money News: Should You Rent or Buy Amid Rising Interest Rates? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Understand the costs of renting versus buying a home. Plus: the UAW strike, GDP growth, debit card fees, and AI policy.
Before discussing housing affordability, hosts Sean Pyles and Anna Helhoski review noteworthy financial headlines, including an update on the UAW strike against major US automakers, the latest Commerce Department numbers on GDP growth, debit card merchant fees, and the White House’s wide-ranging executive order pertaining to artificial intelligence.</description></item><item><title>Options for Paying Off Credit Card Debt: Hardship Programs, Balance Transfer Cards, Loans and More | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720006/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hear Nerds’ “financial horror stories” and explore solutions for paying credit card debt, from 401k loans to bankruptcy. 01:20 This Week in Your Money: Hosts Sean Pyles and Sara Rathner share their personal “financial horror” stories, including Sean’s rejected credit card application and what happened to some of Sara’s retirement account funds. They’re cautionary tales that will help you make sure you’re getting the most out of your money.</description></item><item><title>Choosing a Healthcare Plan via Open Enrollment (HMO, PPO, FSA, HSA, HDHP and More) | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Expert Nerds talk through the complexities of open enrollment, starting with ways to assess healthcare plans and costs. This episode takes a deep dive into specific terminology and scenarios relevant to choosing health insurance coverage. Hosts Sean Pyles and Liz Weston start with an overview of open enrollment period timelines for November and December 2023 before welcoming guest Nerd Kate Ashford to explain deductibles, premiums, HMOs, PPOs and HDHPs.</description></item><item><title>Money News: Save Money on Commuting Costs in a Changing Economy | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn practical financial tips to save on rising commuting costs as workers increasingly return to the office.
Before discussing the rising costs of commuting, hosts Sean Pyles and Anna Helhoski review noteworthy financial headlines, including the Federal Reserve&amp;rsquo;s influence on interest rates, the latest Commerce Department report on retail sales, the Mercer CFA Institute’s Global Pension Index ranking of 47 different kinds of retirement systems from around the world, and the IRS&amp;rsquo;s pilot program for free tax preparation software called Direct File.</description></item><item><title>Money Saving Tips On Car &amp; Home Insurance, plus Budgeting for Conventions and Hobbies @ Comic Con | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720009/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get budgeting tips for conventions and hobbies straight from New York Comic Con, then learn about money saving strategies for car and home insurance. 01:20 This Week in Your Money: Having just returned from New York Comic Con, host Sean Pyles discusses what he learned about budgeting for conventions, hobbies and cosplay outfits. He also shares an interview with Kayden Phoenix, a Los Angeles-based comic book writer known for her Latina superheroes.</description></item><item><title>HIV Prevention and Gender-Affirming Care: Costs, Solutions and Legalities of LGBTQ+ Health Care | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Understand the financial and legal challenges in LGBTQ+ health care, including HIV treatment and gender-affirming surgery. NerdWallet’s Sean Pyles and Sam Taube delve into the intricate financial and legal issues faced by the LGBTQ+ community regarding their health care. They start by exploring the struggle to prevent and treat HIV, focusing on the effectiveness and financial burden related to pre-exposure prophylaxis (PrEP) and highly effective antiretroviral treatment (HEART). Sam speaks with Tim Horn, a director of the public health systems team at the National Alliance of State and Territorial AIDS Directors, or NASTAD, about these drugs and available resources for those dealing with these expenses.</description></item><item><title>Money News: Cracking Down on Junk Fees: Bidenomics in Action | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Transcript</description></item><item><title>Retirement Planning Guide: Estate Planning, Social Security, Long-Term Care and Medicare Explained | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn how to plan for the golden years with a deep dive into long-term care, Social Security, Medicare and estate planning. 3:23 Long-Term Care Insurance: Kate Ashford, a certified senior advisor specializing in Medicare and retirement topics, discusses the intricacies of long-term care insurance, including exactly what Medicare covers in terms of long-term care costs. Kate also discusses alternative options to long-term care insurance such as hybrid policies that combine permanent life insurance with a long-term care rider.</description></item><item><title>Your Guide to Reproductive Health Care Costs, Options and Economic Implications | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Understand recent and upcoming changes in costs and access to reproductive care, as well as resources to manage them. This episode delves into the complex and ever-changing landscape of reproductive care costs. Hosts Sean Pyles and Sam Taube discuss the financial implications of recent high-profile court cases, including the overturning of Roe v. Wade and the Burwell v. Hobby Lobby decision, which significantly transformed insurance coverage for birth control.</description></item><item><title>Money News: CFPB Removes Medical Debt from Credit Reports | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn how removing medical debt from credit reports will protect consumers. Plus: rising interest rates and falling stock prices.
Before discussing news from the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau (CFPB) that could reshape the way medical debt impacts your credit score, hosts Sean Pyles and Anna Helhoski discuss the latest news around student loan forgiveness, rising auto and mortgage rates, and recent losses in the stock market. They then turn their attention to the benefits of omitting medical debts and collection information from credit reports.</description></item><item><title>If You’re Traveling for the Holidays, Start Planning Now | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn why it’s a good time to check your credit card interest rates, and why to start planning your holiday travel now. 01:03 This Week in Your Money: NerdWallet’s Rosalie Murphy joins host Sean Pyles to discuss rising credit card interest rates and how they can impact debt repayment. They offer tips on adapting to higher interest rates and how you may be able to negotiate a lower rate or payment plan with your credit card issuer if you&amp;rsquo;re struggling to make repayments.</description></item><item><title>Behind the Rising Health Care Costs of Bodily Autonomy | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Understand how legal restrictions and policies are increasing health care costs, especially for marginalized communities. This episode explores rising health care prices at the intersection of law, policy and personal health decisions. Investing Nerd Sam Taube interviews Vina Smith-Ramakrishnan, a senior policy associate on the health care equity and reform team at the Century Foundation, about the systemic barriers to accessing health care faced by the LGBTQ+ community, people of color, and low-income individuals.</description></item><item><title>Money News: What to Know About Student Loan Repayments, Gas Prices, SkyMiles and Other Financial News Stories | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn about federal student loan payments resuming, alongside an analysis of this week’s biggest financial stories.
Before discussing this week’s resumption of federal student loan payments after a three-and-a-half-year pause due to the pandemic, hosts Sean Pyles and Anna Helhoski break down this week’s most relevant financial headlines. The discuss the recently averted government shutdown, the impact of crude oil costs on gas prices, an update on Delta’s SkyMiles program, and a new Pew Research Center survey looking at the share of women in top leadership positions at US companies.</description></item><item><title>Understand Your Options for Buying and Selling Cars | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Understand how to avoid “dark patterns” companies use to trick you, then learn different financial approaches for buying a car. 01:11 This Week in Your Money: Dark patterns are manipulative tactics used by companies to influence customer decisions, often to the consumer’s detriment. To start the show, hosts Sean Pyles and Liz Weston explain how you can spot dark patterns, which are not exclusive to sketchy websites. Sean and Liz also discuss confirmshaming, a tactic companies use that could make it difficult for you to cancel paid subscriptions.</description></item><item><title>Money News: Why The Fed Paused Interest Rates, The CFPB, and “Dumb Money” | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn why the Fed paused interest rates. Plus: the Supreme Court&amp;rsquo;s CFPB hearing, NFT prices, and a new GameStop movie.
Join hosts Sean Pyles and Anna Helhoski as they break down the latest headlines in the world of personal finance. They explain the Supreme Court&amp;rsquo;s upcoming hearing on the constitutionality of the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau&amp;rsquo;s funding structure, the risks of investing in &amp;ldquo;dumb money&amp;rdquo; like the Powerball lottery and NFTs, and the new movie &amp;ldquo;Dumb Money,&amp;rdquo; which tells the story of the GameStop stock-buying phenomenon.</description></item><item><title>How to Approach Wedding Costs and Gift-Giving Budgets | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn methods for planning a wedding that makes sense for your budget, then hear how the Nerds think about gift-giving etiquette. 01:12 This Week in Your Money: Get an inside look at the latest trends in wedding planning, as Zola.com Director of Communications Emily Forrest joins host Sean Pyles to discuss findings from a recent survey of more than 2,000 American adults. They discuss the financial challenges many engaged couples face during the wedding planning process, ways to prevent money matters from being overlooked in pre-wedding conversations, and tips for initiating these critical financial conversations.</description></item><item><title>How Millennial Money Woes Are Reshaping the American Dream | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Experts discuss how millennials are redefining the American dream and finding ways to thrive despite hard economic times. Have you ever wondered how younger generations are maneuvering around traditional milestones in the face of mounting financial hurdles? That’s what Personal Finance Nerd Tiffany Curtis discusses with Dr. Jatali Bellaton, a neuropsychologist and the founder of Brilliant Minds Unite, a youth and adult financial literacy movement. She dives into the daunting financial realities of skyrocketing home prices and crippling student loans, and the impact these have on the dreams and aspirations of millennials and Gen Zers.</description></item><item><title>Money News: How a Government Shutdown Could Impact Your Finances | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 14:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn how a government shutdown would impact your finances. Plus: updates on inflation, retail sales and Delta SkyMiles.
In this financial news roundup, hosts Sean Pyles and Anna Helhoski touch on key headlines such as what the latest Consumer Price Index tells us about inflation, the reason why retail sales are surging, and controversial changes to Delta Airlines&amp;rsquo; SkyMiles program. They then take a close look at the looming threat of a government shutdown in Congress, particularly in the House of Representatives.</description></item><item><title>International Budget Travel, and Firing Financial Advisors | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn how to travel abroad on a budget and how to part ways with a financial advisor whose services are unsatisfactory. 1:15 This Week in Your Money: It’s possible to travel abroad on a budget, according to NerdWallet Travel editor Meghan Coyle. She joins hosts Sean Pyles and Liz Weston to discuss the pros and cons of using budget airlines for international travel. She discusses the overall change in flight prices over the last few years, how reliable budget airlines are when compared with other larger airlines, and what to look for in terms of hidden fees and terms so you’re not surprised by unexpected costs.</description></item><item><title>Navigating Generational Financial Trauma in a Digital World | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720024/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Explore the impact of generational financial trauma on millennials, how social media amplifies it and ideas for healing. Personal Finance Nerd Tiffany Curtis delves into the complex topic of generational financial trauma, particularly its impact on millennials, with two special guests: Aja Evans and Rahkim Sabree. Aja Evans is a licensed mental health counselor and financial therapist, and Rahkim Sabree is a certified financial education instructor and author. Together, they explore how past financial landscapes can shape our current financial behaviors, the double-edged sword of social media in shaping financial perspectives, and the importance of understanding these impacts, especially for marginalized groups.</description></item><item><title>Money News: How UAW Strike Could Affect Workers — and Car Costs | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nerds explain this week’s personal finance news, with a focus on labor unrest as the United Auto Workers union prepares to strike.
In Smart Money’s new weekly personal finance news roundup, hosts Sean Pyles and Anna Helhoski take a look at recent developments in the world of money and then go in-depth on an issue that could be important to your life — and your bottom line. Today’s topics include rising home prices, the latest statistics on household wealth and debt, the rise in poverty from 2021 and 2022, and high-yield savings accounts.</description></item><item><title>Important Job Interview Questions and Travel Insurance Tips | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720026/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ace your next job interview with questions you may not have considered asking, then learn how travel insurance works. 01:13 This Week in Your Money: Before you head into your next job interview, consider asking yourself some questions suggested by hosts Sean Pyles and Liz Weston. They share specific questions you can ask in an interview to gain valuable insights into the position and the organization. They also suggest things you may want to ask yourself before jumping into a new role.</description></item><item><title>Overcoming Millennial Money Problems for Financial Wellness | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Discover how global events molded millennial finances, and hear ideas for addressing economic challenges and financial trauma. In this Nerdy deep dive, personal finance Nerd Tiffany Curtis joins host Sean Pyles to discuss millennial money woes, from generational financial trauma to structural challenges that have made financial life more difficult for Americans between 27 and 42 years old. They discuss the changing ways that generations are studied and explore how world events such as the financial crisis and the COVID-19 pandemic have shaped people’s financial attitudes.</description></item><item><title>Are CDs Worth It, and Managing a Life-Changing Windfall | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720028/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720028/</guid><description>Podcast Description The rates on certificates of deposit have shot up over the past year. But are CDs really a good option, especially when high-yield savings accounts are offering similar yields? Sean Pyles and Sara Rathner discuss. Then Sean and Liz Weston talk with a listener about how to manage a life-changing financial windfall. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Employee Stock Purchase Plans and AI Travel Planning | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720029/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Explore how AI can help with personalized travel planning, then learn about Employee Stock Purchase Plans (ESPPs). 01:08 This Week in Your Money: Travel Nerd Sam Kemmis discusses the surprising benefits of using artificial intelligence for personalized travel planning. He joins hosts Sean Pyles and Liz Weston to share his experiences with AI tools like Google&amp;rsquo;s Bard and ChatGPT, including tips for guiding AI and validating creative suggestions before committing to a travel itinerary.</description></item><item><title>Alternative Investments and Speculation in Your Portfolio | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720030/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Discover how alternative investments could help you diversify your portfolio. Have you ever wondered about the potential of alternative investments in your financial portfolio? NerdWallet’s Andy Rosen sits down with certified financial planner James Lee to uncover the world of untraditional investments, including real estate, commodities, cryptocurrency and collectibles. They discuss a recent survey indicating a shift in financial advisors&amp;rsquo; perspectives toward alternative investments and unpack the nuances of speculative investing.</description></item><item><title>Overcoming Financial Fears, and Appliance Repair Tips | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720031/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn why a broken appliance doesn’t have to drain your savings, and how to fight financial fears to enjoy your money. 1:13 This Week in Your Money: Should you repair your appliance instead of replacing it? Hosts Sean Pyles and Liz Weston delve into the latest data from Consumer Reports and share handy tips that could end up saving you money and reducing electronic waste. They also discuss the “right to repair” movement and what it could mean for appliance owners in the future.</description></item><item><title>Options Trading, Short Sales and Derivatives: A Nerdy Guide | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720032/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Explore the risks and rewards of options trading, short selling and margin trading in this nerdy derivatives deep dive. Hosts Sean Pyles and Andy Rosen explain the concept behind derivatives trading before investing Nerd Sam Taube joins the show for a closer look at the ins and outs of specific types of derivatives. Sam explains the speculative and protective reasons for derivatives trading — and the average retail trader’s chances of finding success.</description></item><item><title>When and How to Talk to Your Parents About Their Finances | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720033/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn how to have crucial financial discussions with your aging parents while preserving their dignity and security. In this Nerdy Book Club episode, personal finance Nerd Kim Palmer talks with journalist Cameron Huddleston about insights from her book “Mom and Dad, We Need to Talk: How to Have Essential Conversations With Your Parents About Their Finances.” In their discussion, Cameron shares her personal journey of stepping up to manage her mother&amp;rsquo;s finances after an Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s diagnosis and offers guidance on how to have critical discussions about money matters with parents.</description></item><item><title>Seasonal Housing Market Trends and Travel Credit Card Tips | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720034/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn how to take advantage of seasonal housing market trends and enjoy travel credit card rewards — even in small cities. 1:03 This Week in Your Money: Seasonal housing market trends can have a big impact on homebuying (or selling!), which is why NerdWallet data writer Liz Renter joins today’s episode to discuss the latest patterns. She talks with hosts Sean Pyles and Liz Weston about the fluctuating trends of home prices, inventory and sales, with a focus on how they’ve shifted over the past few years — including with the impact of the pandemic.</description></item><item><title>Day Trading Highs and Lows: A Nerdy Guide to Calculating Risk | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720035/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get an inside look into strategies and pitfalls of the high-risk, high-reward world of day trading. Hosts Sean Pyles and Andy Rosen discuss the high-stakes world of day trading and shed some light on your statistical chances of finding success. Then, Andy welcomes seasoned traders Sierra Smith and Michael Sincere to the podcast to share their perspectives. They pull back the curtain on Sierra&amp;rsquo;s typical trading morning, break down concepts like options trading, and highlight the rollercoaster ride of market highs and lows.</description></item><item><title>Student Loan Repayments and a Nerdy Midyear Money Review | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720036/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 14:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Uncover actionable tips for ensuring your money is working for you, and how to plan for resuming student loan payments. 01:28 This Week in Your Money: Learn how to conduct a midyear financial check-in with help from hosts Sean Pyles and Liz Weston, who offer practical advice for reassessing your financial situation and getting back on track. They discuss strategies to save on car insurance and cell phone plans and stress the importance of securing the best rates for savings accounts.</description></item><item><title>Smart Strategies for Advanced Investing and Active Trading | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720037/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Discover the risks and rewards of active investing, and when to consider calling in professionals for trading decisions. If you’re ready to take your investing game to the next level, then listen as NerdWallet’s Sean Pyles and Andy Rosen discuss the ins and outs of advanced investing strategies. They tackle the topic of autonomy over your investments, examining the rewards and risks that come with managing your own portfolio.</description></item><item><title>Smart Saving Tips for Disney Trips, and Self-Employed Retirement | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720038/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn Nerdy tips to plan a Disney vacation without going broke, and how to choose a retirement plan when self-employed. 01:08 This Week in Your Money: Unlock the magic of making your next Disney vacation more affordable with insider tips from travel Nerd Sally French. She joins hosts Sean Pyles and Liz Weston to unveil the secrets behind experiencing Disneyland and Disney World on a budget, from strategic hotel choices to the types of tickets you might want to avoid.</description></item><item><title>Smart Credit Building and Saving for a Secure Retirement | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720039/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 16:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Understand the implications of adding authorized users to credit cards, and how to plan retirement so your money lasts. 01:40 Today’s first Money Question: A listener asks whether it’s a good idea to help a friend or family member build credit by adding them as an authorized user on your credit card. Credit expert Bev O’Shea joins Sean Pyles and Liz Weston to discuss the risks and benefits of adding authorized users, including the impact it can have on a person’s credit profile, the conditions under which it might be unfavorable and how many people a credit card holder can add as authorized users.</description></item><item><title>Outsmart Student Loan Scams, and Child Care Budgeting Tips | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720040/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Keep your money safe by spotting student loan scams, then learn how to cover child care costs without going into debt. 01:02 This Week in Your Money: Hear a student loan scammer’s actual voicemail, which hosts Sean Pyles and Liz Weston dissect line by line to give you a better understanding of scammers’ manipulative strategies and pressure tactics. Sean and Liz will also share practical advice about how to safeguard yourself and your loved ones against these scams and tips for how to plan your budget for when student loan payments resume later in 2023.</description></item><item><title>Smart Ways to Get Out of Debt, and Pet Insurance Planning | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720041/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn ways to handle your debt, including some options you might not know about. And find out how pet insurance works, how much it costs and ways to budget for pet care. 01:14 Today’s first Money Question: Personal finance Nerd Tommy Tindall joins Sean Pyles and Liz Weston to discuss alternative ways to pay off debt when you can’t get a personal loan. The Nerds discuss credit counseling, debt management plans and when it may make sense to declare bankruptcy.</description></item><item><title>Social Media Shopping Tips, and Smart Spare Cash Investing | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720042/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn pro tips for shopping on social media so you don’t overspend, and smart strategies for investing your spare cash. 00:48 This Week in Your Money: Get equipped with practical tips to shop smart on social media platforms and stay vigilant against overspending. Personal finance Nerd Kimberly Palmer joins hosts Sean Pyles and Liz Weston for a Nerdy look at how your social media feed may be leading you to spend more money than you should.</description></item><item><title>Nerdy Guide to Brokerage Fees and Investment Advisors | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720043/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn how to avoid overspending on investing and brokerage fees, and get smart about how to choose a financial advisor. 01:55 Today’s First Money Question: Investing Nerd Alana Benson joins Sean Pyles and Liz Weston to demystify brokerage fees and explain how you can reduce the fees you’re paying on investment accounts. They discuss the types of brokerage fees and how they can impact your investments. 13:53 Today’s Second Money Question: The Nerds walk through the process of choosing the right financial advisor for your needs.</description></item><item><title>Human Longevity Literacy, and How Debt Impacts Credit Scores | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720044/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Improve your longevity literacy so you don’t retire too early (or late!), then learn how debt affects your credit score. 01:31 This Week in Your Money: Sean Pyles and Liz Weston delve into the significant yet often overlooked concept of longevity literacy. They discuss how understanding your life expectancy can greatly influence retirement planning, and they share a life expectancy calculator you can use to get a personalized estimate of your life expectancy.</description></item><item><title>Bill Disputes, Managing a Raise, and Smart Saving Early | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720045/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn how checking your bills can prevent you from overspending, how to manage a raise and how to build wealth early. 01:14 This Week in Your Money: Sean Pyles and Liz Weston discuss how you can prevent overspending by double-checking all your bills and share how doing so saved Sean more than $100 on just a single bill. They also discuss some surprising ways bills can demonstrate that you’re getting shortchanged.</description></item><item><title>When to Merge Finances — or Not | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720046/</guid><description>Podcast Description At a certain point in your relationship, merging your finances can feel like a natural step … or not. To start this episode, hosts Sean Pyles and Sara Rathner talk about why combining your finances with a partner isn’t always a great idea. Then Sean is joined by Nerds Liz Weston and Kim Palmer to answer a listener&amp;rsquo;s question about how to manage multiple credit card accounts when merging finances.</description></item><item><title>Student Loan Forgiveness Struck Down by Supreme Court. Now What? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720047/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 18:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720047/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Supreme Court has struck down President Biden’s student loan forgiveness plan. Sean and Anna discuss what this means for consumers — including when you can expect payments to resume. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Price of Parenthood: In Vitro Fertilization and the Future of Parenthood | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720048/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720048/</guid><description>Podcast Description In vitro Fertilization — or IVF — is an effective way to become pregnant. But is it only for the wealthy? In this final episode of our Nerdy Deep Dive into the price of parenthood, Sean and Ronita explore IVF and hear from a mother who went through the process. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.com. Like what you hear?</description></item><item><title>Nerdy Tips on Tipping, and Managing High Credit Card Annual Fees | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720049/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Feel less awkward about tipping with our Nerds’ tipping tips. Then learn about credit cards with high annual fees. 01:12 This Week in Your Money: Sean Pyles and Liz Weston discuss when to tip, when not to tip and how much you should tip — not just in restaurants but also in places where people haven’t historically tipped, like grocery stores and self-serve frozen yogurt places. They also talk about the broader economic implications of tipping and different tipping standards around the world.</description></item><item><title>The Price of Parenthood: How Egg Freezing Works | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720050/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Egg freezing lets would-be parents put their plans on ice. But is it a realistic option for everyone? In the third episode of our nerdy deep dive into the price of parenthood, Sean and Ronita explore when egg freezing is a good option for parents — and how much it really costs. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Nerdy Travel Tips, and Budgeting for a Non-Traditional Life | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720051/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Avoid costly travel mistakes with expert tips from our Nerds. Then, learn how to budget for a non-traditional lifestyle. You can help us improve our show! Please take our listener survey at: https://nerdwallet.com/podsurvey 01:00 This Week in Your Money: Summer travel costs are soaring this year — but that doesn’t mean your expenses have to. Sean Pyles and Liz Weston offer tips for planning ahead to decrease your costs, from capitalizing on credit card rewards points to scheduling your trips when airfares aren’t so high.</description></item><item><title>The Price of Parenthood: What It Takes to Adopt | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720052/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720052/</guid><description>Podcast Description The price of adoption can vary greatly — from under $1,000 to over $60,000. In this episode of our nerdy deep dive into the price of parenthood, Sean and Ronita explore the various avenues and expenses associated with adoption. A dad now in the adoption process shares his experiences, and a financial planner unpacks questions you should ask if you’re considering adoption. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Money Scams, and Renting Credit Card Tradelines for Cash | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720053/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn about how to avoid the latest money scams and whether it’s worth using your credit score to earn extra income. This Week in Your Money (00:00 - 08:06): Sean and Liz discuss the latest financial fraud to watch out for, including Google Voice scams and AI-generated voice spoofing, and provide insights and advice on how to stay safe and avoid becoming a victim. They also recommend resources for staying informed and where to go if you get defrauded.</description></item><item><title>The Price of Parenthood: What It Costs to Be a Parent | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720054/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Becoming a parent is unavoidably expensive. But this is a financial decision that’s about a lot more than just money. To kick off our nerdy deep dive into the price of parenthood, Sean Pyles and Ronita Choudhuri-Wade talk about how much it costs to have a child, including the cost of raising one to adulthood. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Making Hobbies Affordable, and Saving Money Priorities | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720055/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn how to make your hobbies more affordable. Plus, decide what to save for first: an emergency, a house or retirement. This Week In Your Money (0:00 - 12:03): Sean delves into the finer aspects of how you can plan ahead to make affordable gardening possible, including tips for sourcing tools and the surprising benefits of engaging with the gardening community. Liz then explains how you can enjoy your hobbies on a budget without sacrificing the fun factor by discussing how to avoid making some of the same mistakes she made when she got into her hobby of making miniatures.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720056/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 04:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720056/</guid><description>Podcast Description NerdWallet’s Smart Money Podcast will give you practical knowledge you can use to level up your finances. Every week, NerdWallet’s expert Nerds answer your money questions and break down the latest personal finance news. You’ll learn about different investment strategies; understand your credit score and your tax bills; get pro tips for organizing your expenses and putting more money into your savings; and a whole lot more. Whatever your money question, the Nerds will give you the info to make your money decisions with confidence.</description></item><item><title>Get Creative About Money With Paco de Leon | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720057/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720057/</guid><description>Podcast Description If traditional money advice doesn’t work for you, then you might want to consider a more creative approach. In this episode, personal finance Nerd Kim Palmer talks with Paco de Leon, author of the new personal finance book, “Finance for the People.” She is also an illustrator, musician and founder of a financial education firm and bookkeeping agency. De Leon shares how to take a visual and creative approach to budgeting and making money decisions, including why — and how — to write a letter to your own debt.</description></item><item><title>The Cost of Climate Change: Preparing for the Worst | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720058/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720058/</guid><description>Podcast Description How would you recover if your life was upended by a huge disaster — a fire, hurricane or flood? Getting your affairs in order before a disaster hits — and knowing what help is available afterward — can help you recover faster and more fully. In this episode of our nerdy deep dive into climate change and your money, we talk about how to rebuild your finances after the worst happens.</description></item><item><title>More Money Hot Takes, and When to Leave Your Job | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720059/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720059/</guid><description>Podcast Description A lot of influencers peddle classes with guarantees of helping you become rich and successful. But are they legit — or just another moneymaking scheme? Sean has strong feelings about these classes, and he shares them in another round of Money Hot Takes. Then Sean and Sara answer a listener’s question about when you should leave a job. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>The Cost of Climate Change: Investing (and Banking) for a Greener World | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720060/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720060/</guid><description>Podcast Description You really want to effect change around climate issues? Put your money to work for you. In this episode of our nerdy deep dive into how climate change affects your money, we discuss ways your banking and investing choices can reflect your climate goals — and how to avoid greenwashing. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.com. Like what you hear?</description></item><item><title>Top Consumer Complaints, and Car Shopping in 2023 | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720061/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720061/</guid><description>Podcast Description The car market has been a mess for … a while. Is now a better time to buy than a year ago? And how is the car market looking for the rest of the year? This episode, Sean and Sara answer a listener’s question about car buying in 2023. And to kick off this episode, Sean and Liz talk about the issues and providers that consumers are complaining about the most.</description></item><item><title>Why Moms Face a Pay Penalty — and What to Do About It | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720062/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Becoming a mother can transform your life: providing a new sense of purpose, expanding your family and, potentially, limiting your earning power. In this episode, Sean and NerdWallet writer Amanda Barroso dig into the motherhood pay gap, including what it is, where it comes from and how to fix it. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.com. Like what you hear?</description></item><item><title>The Cost of Climate Change: How to Protect Your Home From Disaster | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720063/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720063/</guid><description>Podcast Description If a natural disaster struck your home — whether you own or rent — would you be covered? Many consumers aren’t as protected as they might think. In this episode of our nerdy deep dive into how climate change affects your money, Sean and NerdWallet insurance editor Caitlin Constantine talk about how to really protect yourself when a big storm hits where you live. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>How to (Really) Save on Groceries | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720064/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eating a plant-based diet doesn’t have to be expensive — or boring. In this episode, Nerds Sean Pyles and Kimberly Palmer talk with Toni Okamoto, author of “Plant-Based on a Budget Quick &amp;amp; Easy,” about how to save money on your groceries by making healthy, vegan meals. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.com. Like what you hear?</description></item><item><title>The Future of College Debt, and Rent vs. Buy (With a Dog) | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720065/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Deciding whether to keep on renting or get serious about buying a house is rarely easy. But in an area where houses are expensive and many apartments aren’t amenable to your four-legged friend, the choice gets even more complicated. This episode, the Nerds talk with a listener about how she’s working through this predicament. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>The Cost of Climate Change: The Big Picture | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720066/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Climate change is going to have profound effects on our lives — including our money. To kick off this nerdy deep dive into climate change and finance, we explore how personal finances and economies could be affected by natural disasters. Then we talk about how to manage the emotional dread around climate change — and how to prevent it from bogging down your financial goals. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Your Social Security Benefits, and Tax Efficient Retirement Investing | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720067/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Knowing how much you could get from Social Security is a big part of retirement planning (and, yes, cynical listeners — you will be getting these benefits!). To kick off this episode, Sean and Liz talk about a new tool that can help you estimate your benefits. Then Sean and Sara answer a listener’s question about tax efficient investments for retirement accounts. Need help with a money question? Call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Money and Happiness: Building (and Buying) Your Happiness | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720068/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720068/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s here at last: This episode, the simple formula to your happier, more prosperous life will finally be revealed! Just kidding. Turns out, happiness is work. But you can take steps to improve your levels of happiness and the role money plays in shaping your happiness. To round out this Nerdy deep dive into money and happiness, Sean talks with Dan Harris of “Ten Percent Happier&amp;quot;; University of California, Berkeley professor and host of “The Science of Happiness” podcast Dacher Keltner; and financial therapist Ashley Agnew.</description></item><item><title>Money News: What’s the Deal With ‘Junk Fees’? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720069/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720069/</guid><description>Podcast Description You don’t have to be a Taylor Swift fan to feel like you’re being personally attacked by hidden fees and surcharges. These so-called junk fees can be unrelenting, but the tide may be changing. In this Money News episode, Sean talks with Anna Helhoski about the latest on junk fees and what you can do about them. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Neurodiverse Money, and Financial Infidelity | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720070/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720070/</guid><description>Podcast Description If your partner hid tens of thousands of dollars in credit card debt from you, would you bail — or help them pay it off? In this episode of the podcast, Sean and Sara tackle a listener’s question about financial infidelity. They also talk about managing money when you’re neurodiverse. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.com. Timestamps: This Week in Your Money segment: 0:00 - 7:31 Money Question segment: 7:32 - 27:02 Like what you hear?</description></item><item><title>Money and Happiness: Happiness for a Bargain | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720071/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Let’s wheel out the cliche “money can’t buy happiness.” In truth, we know that’s not really the case, right? Research shows that the more money you have, the more well-being you have. But you can find happiness without steadfast reliance on cash. In this episode of our deep dive into money and happiness, we explore how much money you really need to be happy — and what it’s like to create a happy life where money plays a less important role.</description></item><item><title>Making Your Big Money Reset, With Jill Schlesinger | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720072/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720072/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you wanted to dramatically upend your life overnight, you probably could — but it could have unintended consequences. You do have the power to transform your life, though, from your job, to where you live and how you manage your finances. In this episode, Sean and Sara talk with Jill Schlesinger — CBS business analyst, host of the “Jill on Money” podcast and author of “The Great Money Reset” — about how you can enact the changes you want in your life.</description></item><item><title>Money and Happiness: Uncover Your Money History | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720073/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720073/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is your first money memory? And how is it influencing your finances today? In this episode of our deep dive into money and happiness, Sean explores how you can dig into your financial history to build a happier — and more financially fruitful — future. Have questions about money and psychology? Share them with the Nerds! Call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.com. Like what you hear?</description></item><item><title>Recession Anxiety, and Retirement Savings vs. Mortgage Payoff | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720074/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720074/</guid><description>Podcast Description A recession is imminent. Or, maybe it isn’t? News stories about looming recession can feel incessant, only for the economic turmoil to never materialize. To start off this episode, Sean and Sara talk about how to cut through the noise and focus on improving your financial life. Then Sean and Sara talk with a listener, Lauren, who’s deciding whether to pull back from her retirement savings to pay down her mortgage faster.</description></item><item><title>Money and Happiness: What's Happiness Really Worth? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720075/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you really need money to be happy? Or is money the reason you’re unhappy? Either way, chances are your relationship to money and happiness is a little, well, messy. To kick off this Nerdy deep dive into money and happiness, Sean talks with happiness experts Gretchen Rubin and Robert Puff to understand what happiness really means. Then Sean talks with Morgan Housel, author of “The Psychology of Money,” about where money and happiness intersect.</description></item><item><title>Spring-Cleaning, and Paying Off Different Types of Debt | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720076/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720076/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s officially spring, which means it’s time to bust out the duster, broom — and your bank account logins. To start this episode, Sean and Sara talk about how you can do a little financial spring-cleaning. Then they answer a listener’s question about paying off different debts, like taxes and credit cards. Want the Nerds to answer your money question? Call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>‘This or That’: Lightning Round | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720077/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720077/</guid><description>Podcast Description The travel Nerds have all sorts of opinions on when to get to the airport ahead of a flight, what sorts of upgrades or perks are most valuable to them — and of course, whether to check or carry on a bag. In this episode of Smart Money, the travel Nerds answer some lightning-round questions on their takes.
To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Is Banking Stable, and Traditional vs. Online Banks | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720078/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720078/</guid><description>Podcast Description The banking system has been feeling less than stable lately. But how worried should you really be? To start this episode, Sean and Sara discuss the concern. Then Sean and Liz answer a listener question about how to choose between an online and a traditional bank. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.com. Timestamps: This Week in Your Money segment: 0:00 - 6:21 Money Question segment: 6:22 - 25:13 Like what you hear?</description></item><item><title>‘This or That’: Loyalty to One Travel Brand or Diversify? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720079/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720079/</guid><description>Podcast Description So you’re deep in the points game (or want to be). Are you better off focusing your points earning and spending efforts on one brand, or diversifying your points? This episode, Sean talks with travel Nerd Elina Geller about which is better and why. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.com. Like what you hear? Please leave us a review and tell a friend.</description></item><item><title>Are CDs Worth It, and Managing a Life-Changing Windfall | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720080/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720080/</guid><description>Podcast Description The rates on certificates of deposit have shot up over the past year. But are CDs really a good option, especially when high-yield savings accounts are offering similar yields? Sean Pyles and Sara Rathner discuss. Then Sean and Liz Weston talk with a listener about how to manage a life-changing financial windfall. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>‘This or That’: Travel Credit Card or Cash-Back Credit Card | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720081/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Travel credit cards can help you score the vacation of your dreams on points alone. But are they worth the hassle of playing the points game? In this episode of the “This or That” travel series, Sean talks with travel Nerd Sally French about why travel cards are worth the hype — and when a cash-back card might be the better option. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>How COVID Changed Our Finances — and Our Advice | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720082/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720082/</guid><description>Podcast Description The COVID-19 pandemic upended the world — and our finances. The tumult created a lot of opportunity and angst in its wake. In this episode, Sean hosts a roundtable discussion about how COVID-19 changed the way we manage and talk about money. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.com. Like what you hear? Please leave us a review and tell a friend.</description></item><item><title>‘This or That’: Booking With Points vs. Cash | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720083/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720083/</guid><description>Podcast Description You’ve got a trip coming up. Should you use cash or points to book your travel and lodging? In this episode, Sean Pyles talks with travel writer Meghan Coyle about when you might want to use cash — and when points are your best bet. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.com. Like what you hear? Please leave us a review and tell a friend.</description></item><item><title>How to Leverage Inflation for Your Benefit | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720084/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Inflation is affecting a lot more than the price of groceries. It’s also presenting financial opportunities — if you know where to look. In this episode, we share a discussion about how you can leverage inflation for your benefit while minimizing its negative effects on your finances. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.com. Like what you hear?</description></item><item><title>Money News: The Supreme Court Debates Student Debt Cancellation | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720085/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720085/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Supreme Court is getting closer to dashing or fulfilling folks’ dreams of student debt cancellation. This week, the justices heard arguments that will determine the fate of some 40 million student loan borrowers. In this Money News episode of the podcast, Sean Pyles and Anna Helhoski talk about what happened, which way the court might be leaning and what it means for you. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>‘This or That’: Airbnb vs. Hotel | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720086/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 20:44:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Airbnb used to be a go-to option for fun, one-of-a-kind lodging. Then the cleaning fees started stacking up. Are Airbnbs worth it anymore, or are hotels the better route to go? In this episode, host Sean Pyles talks with travel Nerd Sam Kemmis about how to decide between an Airbnb and a hotel. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>The Tax Episode 2023 | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720087/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tax season is in full swing. And this episode, we’re taking on popular questions, including when you’re fine filing on your own — and when you might want to hire help. We also discuss why so many Americans who are eligible to file their taxes for free end up paying anyway. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>When Your Family Steals Your Identity | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720088/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Being the victim of identity theft can be traumatic, especially when your own mother is the perpetrator. In this episode, personal finance Nerd Kimberly Palmer talks with Axton Betz-Hamilton, author of “The Less People Know About Us: A Mystery of Betrayal, Family Secrets, and Stolen Identity.” Betz-Hamilton talks about her experience being the victim of familial identity theft and shares tips on how to protect your identity — and how to recover if you are a victim.</description></item><item><title>Money Hot Takes, and Too Many Credit Cards | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720089/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720089/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s time for some money hot takes. To start off this episode, Sean and Liz share their (maybe unpopular) opinions about personal finance topics. Sean goes off about why buy now, pay later loans aren’t all they’re cracked up to be. And Liz shares her thoughts on how the credit bureaus can fix the way they handle your data. Then they answer a listener’s money question about when you might have too many credit cards — and what to do about it if you do.</description></item><item><title>‘The Color of Wealth’: Investing for Your Family's Future | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720090/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720090/</guid><description>Podcast Description There are many ways for Black women and mothers to invest to build wealth for their families. Choosing the one that fits best can be a challenge, especially when you have competing priorities. In this episode, we explore different methods to invest, including various retirement accounts and 529 college savings accounts, and how to decide whether to save for yourself or your children when money is tight. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>When to Merge Finances — or Not | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720091/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720091/</guid><description>Podcast Description At a certain point in your relationship, merging your finances can feel like a natural step … or not. To start this episode, hosts Sean Pyles and Sara Rathner talk about why combining your finances with a partner isn’t always a great idea. Then Sean is joined by Nerds Liz Weston and Kim Palmer to answer a listener&amp;rsquo;s question about how to manage multiple credit card accounts when merging finances.</description></item><item><title>‘The Color of Wealth’: The Emotional Trade-Offs of Wealth Building | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720092/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sometimes anger is the best response to finding out you’ve been deprived of an opportunity. The steps you take from there may require research – and trade-offs. In this episode of our “Color of Wealth” series, personal finance Nerd Elizabeth Ayoola talks with Dasha Kennedy, founder of the financial advocacy group The Broke Black Girl, about how to balance emotions and building wealth. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Money News: Student Debt Cancellation at the Supreme Court | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720093/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720093/</guid><description>Podcast Description This month the Supreme Court will hear cases to decide the fate of those hoping for federal student debt cancelation. In this Money News episode of the podcast, hosts Sean Pyles and Anna Helhoski give you the rundown on those cases — including whether debt cancellation is likely to be upheld and when you might have to restart payment on your student loans. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>ChatGPT vs. the Nerds, and Rental Properties | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720094/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Artificial intelligence tools like ChatGPT are making headlines — but can they be trusted to give personal finance advice? To kick off this episode, Sean Pyles and Liz Weston have ChatGPT answer some common money questions. Then Liz and regular Smart Money host Sara Rathner answer a listener’s question about how to make money from investment properties. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>‘The Color of Wealth’: Overcoming Structural Challenges | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720095/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Black women face distinct challenges when building wealth. So what can they do about it? To kick off this new series, “The Color of Wealth,” NerdWallet writer Elizabeth Ayoola talks with Washington Post personal finance columnist Michelle Singletary about what Black women and mothers can do individually to grow their wealth. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>No-Spend Month 2.0, and Recovering From Credit Damage | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720096/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720096/</guid><description>Podcast Description A no-spend month is a chance to retool your relationship with how you spend money — and tuck away some extra cash. To start this episode, Sean Pyles and Liz Weston talk about how they’re approaching the no-spend-month challenge this year. Then they answer a listener’s question about how to recover from damage to their credit, including how to land an apartment or get a car loan. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Your Money in 2023: Managing Uncertainty | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720097/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Uncertainty is the new normal. So, what can you do about it? In this episode, hosts Sean Pyles, Liz Weston and Sara Rathner talk about how to improve your financial resilience, including savings strategies, setting your mindset and leaning on your community. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.com. Like what you hear? Please leave us a review and tell a friend.</description></item><item><title>Data Breaches, and Catching Up on Retirement Savings | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720098/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720098/</guid><description>Podcast Description A number of high-profile companies have reported data breaches recently. That means we have to be extra vigilant to secure our information. To start this episode, Sean Pyles and Liz Weston talk about the breaches and how you can protect yourself. Then they answer a listener’s question about how to catch up on retirement contributions — including whether you can open an LLC to contribute with no limits. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Your Money in 2023: Homebuying and Selling | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720099/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720099/</guid><description>Podcast Description What can the housing market of 1981 teach us about 2023? A lot, apparently. In this episode, Sean Pyles and Liz Weston talk about what would-be home buyers and sellers should think about this year — including how the past can inform the present, whether a housing crash is imminent and how to navigate the new twists of the market in 2023. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>The Art of Complaining, and Saving for Your Kids’ Future | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720100/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Getting a hold of customer service representatives can be a nightmare. Working with them to actually solve your problems can be even less fun. To start this episode, Liz Weston and Sara Rathner talk about the art of complaining. Then Liz and regular Smart Money co-host Sean Pyles answer a listener’s question about how to save for your kids’ future — whether they go to college or not. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Your Money in 2023: Investing in the Stock Market | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720101/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720101/</guid><description>Podcast Description The stock market had a rough year in 2022. But for the savvy investor, the market downturn meant a big opportunity. And that good fortune could continue in 2023. In this episode, Sean Pyles and Liz Weston talk about investing in 2023, including the lessons of the past year, ideas for investing in a recession, and how to find the right investment tools for your financial goals. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Retirement Changes You May Have Missed | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720102/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Important changes are coming to how you can save for retirement — including one that will allow your student debt payments to count toward retirement contributions. In this episode, Sean Pyles and Anna Helhoski run through the retirement benefits that were passed by Congress at the end of last year and when those changes go into effect. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>January Money Moves, and Paying Off Your Mortgage Early | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720103/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720103/</guid><description>Podcast Description What are you doing to improve your money in the new year? If you’re not sure where to start, we have some ideas. To kick off this episode, Sean Pyles and Liz Weston talk through ways to start off the new year right financially. Then they answer a listener’s money question about whether they should pay off their mortgage early — or just go on more vacations. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Your Money in 2023: Use Your Values to Set Your Goals | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720104/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Setting money goals in the new year is a time-honored tradition. But ditching them after a month (or a week) is all too common. This year, use your values to guide your financial ambitions. In this episode, Sean Pyles and Liz Weston discuss how you can set goals you’ll actually keep in 2023 — and what to do if you still need ideas for your money this year. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Student Loans and the Cancellation Debate, Part 1 | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720105/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Student loans are a tool, as well as a dreaded financial reality, for most Americans who attend college. In this two-part Nerdy Deep Dive into student loans, Sean and student loans Nerd Anna Helhoski explore how taking on huge amounts of student debt has become the norm in America. They also discuss what’s shifting now in today’s student debt conversation. In Part 1, we trace the origins of student loan debt and how college got so expensive.</description></item><item><title>Single-Income Couples, and When to Use Your HSA and FSA | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720106/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Going from a two-income household to a one-income household is not solely a financial challenge. But this change also creates opportunities to strengthen your relationship and set clear expectations. To start off this episode, Sean and Liz discuss how to manage finances in a one-income household. Then Sean and Liz answer a listener’s money question about using HSAs and FSAs. Both can cover health care expenses, but only one can be used as an investment vehicle.</description></item><item><title>What We Learned About Our Money in 2022 | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720107/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720107/</guid><description>Podcast Description A lot can happen to your finances in a year. Raises, curveball expenses, luxurious vacations. Each step along your money journey in 2022 has its own lesson. And in this episode, Sean Pyles and Liz Weston look back at the year that was and celebrate what our listeners did with their money during the year — and what they’re most excited about in 2023. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Rising Interest Rates, and Budgeting With Apps | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720108/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720108/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Fed is poised to raise interest rates — again. To kick off this episode, Sean Pyles and Liz Weston talk about who’s actually hurt when the Fed raises rates and what you can do about it. Then they answer a listener’s question about which budgeting apps are the best and whether you might want to use multiple budgeting apps to track your money. Also, next year, the Smart Money team wants to talk with you, on the podcast, to answer your money questions.</description></item><item><title>How to Find the Humor in Money Management With Joe Saul-Sehy | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720109/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Talking about money doesn’t have to be boring. In this episode of our Nerdy Book Club series, NerdWallet writer Kimberly Palmer talks with former financial advisor Joe Saul-Sehy, co-author of “Stacked: Your Super-Serious Guide to Modern Money Management” and co-host of “The Stacking Benjamins Show” podcast, about setting money goals, recovering from big financial mistakes and how to have a good time while figuring out your finances. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Money News: What the Jobs Report and Recent Layoffs Mean for You | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720110/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720110/</guid><description>Podcast Description The job market is strong — but thousands of workers have been laid off in recent months. So, what’s happening? And what does this mean for the labor market in 2023? In this episode, Sean Pyles and Anna Helhoski talk about the latest jobs report with NerdWallet data writer Liz Renter, including why the job market is so weird right now and what it means for you. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>The End of Credit Card Rewards, and When to Cancel Luxury Credit Cards | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720111/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Credit card rewards programs might be on the chopping block in Congress. To start off this episode, Sean Pyles and Liz Weston talk with a credit card Nerd about what’s happening and what it might mean for your credit card rewards. Then Sean is joined by personal finance Nerd Kim Palmer to answer a listener’s question about when to cancel a luxury credit card. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Questioning the 50/30/20 Budget and Company Stock | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720112/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720112/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 50/30/20 budget is a simple way to organize your finances. But as rent prices soar and inflation impacts everything from gas to groceries, does this budget still make sense? To start this episode, Sean and Liz discuss the merits — and limits — of the 50/30/20 budget. Then they answer a few listeners’ questions about navigating company stock. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Crypto Crash, and Growing Money Fast | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720113/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shockwaves rippled through the crypto world with the collapse of the crypto exchange FTX. To start off this episode, Sean Pyles and Liz Weston discuss what happened — and what it might mean for your finances. Then Sean talks with personal finance Nerds Kim Palmer and Kate Wood about how to grow your money quickly ahead of home improvement projects. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Outsmart Scammers, and Waiting to Save for Retirement | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720114/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Scammers alleging to help you cancel your student debt are coming for you — whether you actually have student debt or not. To kick off this episode, Sean Pyles and Liz Weston walk you through how to outsmart these fraudsters. Then Sean and Liz are joined by their regular co-host, Sara Rathner, to talk about how you can save for retirement when your employer makes you wait to access its retirement plan.</description></item><item><title>When Your Bank Stiffs You, and Co-Signing Risks | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720115/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is your bank holding out on you? If you haven’t checked on your savings accounts lately, you should — or risk losing out on money you could be earning. In this episode, hosts Liz Weston and Sean Pyles talk about how Liz discovered her supposedly high-yield savings account was anything but. Then Sean is joined by personal finance Nerds Kim Palmer and Sara Rathner to discuss whether you should put your credit on the line to help a loved one by co-signing.</description></item><item><title>Financial Fears, and Do You Need Life Insurance? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720116/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fear can control your life — if you let it. And when it comes to financial fears, what haunts you can mean the difference between a life of prosperity and one of anxiety. To start off this episode, Sean Pyles and Liz Weston talk about their financial fears — and how you can overcome your own. Then they answer a listener’s money question about whether they should get life insurance, even if they don’t have children.</description></item><item><title>How the Nerds Do It: How a Student Loans Nerd Paid Off Her Debt | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720117/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Paying off student debt isn’t easy — even for a Nerd who writes about it. In this episode of our “How the Nerds Do It” series, student loans Nerd Anna Helhoski talks about how she paid off her debt, the challenges she faced along the way and how you can find the fastest and most affordable way to resolve your student loans. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Black Friday Is Canceled, and How to Get Holiday Travel Deals | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720118/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Black Friday isn’t the shopping extravaganza it once was. With rolling deals from major retailers, you might be able to get the best price for items on your list weeks — or months — before Nov. 25 rolls around. To kick off this episode, Sean Pyles and Anna Helhoski talk with personal finance Nerd Amanda Barroso about how to approach holiday shopping this year. Then Sean hosts a roundtable discussion with the Travel Nerds about how you can find the best prices when traveling over the holidays, including whether it’s better to drive or fly and how to combat credit card point inflation.</description></item><item><title>How the Nerds Do It: How a Mortgage Nerd Bought a House | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720119/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Buying a house takes grit, know-how — and, frankly, a good amount of cash. In this episode of our “How the Nerds Do It” series, mortgage Nerd Kate Wood talks about how she bought her first home, and why she almost fell for a house with a poisoned well. Kate also gives you her tips for buying a house, including the importance of finding a real estate agent whom you can trust.</description></item><item><title>Money News: How to Cancel Your Student Debt | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720120/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720120/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s finally here: The application to cancel up to $20,000 of your federal student loan debt is live. In this episode, Sean Pyles is joined by student debt and breaking news Nerd Anna Helhoski to walk through the debt cancellation application in real time. They also talk about scams and when you can expect your debt to be canceled. Call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Zelle Scams, and When to Sell Investments | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720121/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720121/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s Cybersecurity Awareness Month. Do you know where your passwords are? To start off this episode, Sean Pyles and Sara Rathner discuss the risks of peer-to-peer payment apps. Then they talk about the one thing you should do this month to protect yourself online. In this episode’s money question segment, Sean and Liz Weston answer a listener’s question about when to sell stock — and when buy-and-hold might be too much of a good thing.</description></item><item><title>How the Nerds Do It: How a Travel Nerd Books a Trip | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720122/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Points or cash. Bargain hunting or splurging. Deep research or impulse booking. A lot can go into booking the perfect vacation. In this episode of our “How the Nerds Do It” series, travel Nerd Sam Kemmis talks through how he books his vacations and how you can get into the points game yourself. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Money Hot Takes, and Too Many Credit Cards | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720123/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720123/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s time for some money hot takes. To start off this episode, Sean and Liz share their (maybe unpopular) opinions about personal finance topics. Sean goes off about why buy now, pay later loans aren’t all they’re cracked up to be. And Liz shares her thoughts on how the credit bureaus can fix the way they handle your data. Then they answer a listener’s money question about when you might have too many credit cards — and what to do about it if you do.</description></item><item><title>How the Nerds Do It: How an Investing Nerd Maxed Out Her Roth IRA | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720124/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Saving for retirement can be a challenge for anyone — even our Nerds. To kick off a new series called “How the Nerds Do It,” Sean talks with investing Nerd Alana Benson about how she maxed out her retirement account. Alana explains what finally made her able to invest and her unique strategy for funding her Roth IRA. She also gives tips to make the most of your retirement savings.</description></item><item><title>What the Fed News Means for You, and Choosing a New Bank | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720125/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720125/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Fed has been in the news a lot lately, raising interest rates and causing recession fears. But what, exactly, do the interest rate hikes mean for various parts of your finances, like your savings and credit cards? We give you the rundown to start off this episode. Then we answer a listener’s money question about how to choose a new bank — including how to find one that fits your family’s needs.</description></item><item><title>Beating Money Procrastination, and When to Unfreeze Credit | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720126/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sometimes checking things off your financial to-do list can be a real slog. If you find yourself procrastinating, know that you have plenty of company. To start off this episode, Sean and Liz talk about how to overcome money procrastination. Then they answer a few recent listener questions about student debt cancellation. And in this episode’s money question segment, they talk about when to unfreeze your credit. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Fall Money Tasks, and Saving Enough to Retire | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720127/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720127/</guid><description>Podcast Description As we head into fall, is your money where you want it to be? To start off this episode, Sean and Liz give you a few easy money tasks so you can end the year right. Then they answer a listener’s money question about how to save enough money to retire — including when to start spending what you’ve saved up. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Live From Las Vegas! | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720128/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720128/</guid><description>Podcast Description The smart way to lose your money gambling, whether now is a good time to invest and how to manage a big financial gift. In the first-ever live episode of the podcast — recorded at a NerdWallet conference in Las Vegas this summer — Sean and Sara cover these topics and more. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Student Debt Cancellation News, and Money 101 | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720129/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720129/</guid><description>Podcast Description The dust is settling after President Biden announced his student debt cancellation and repayment plan. But there are still a number of unknowns. This episode, Sean, Liz and Sara talk about the latest debt cancellation news, including new scams that are popping up. Then they answer a listener’s question about the best way to set up their finances for long-term success. At the end of the episode, they give their tips for the best investments you can make in yourself.</description></item><item><title>Protecting Your Privacy, and Front-Loading a 401(k) | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720130/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Maxing out a 401(k) is a great step toward saving for retirement, but have you ever thought about front-loading your plan? In this episode, hosts Sean Pyles and Liz Weston talk with investing Nerd Alana Benson about the pros, cons and potential pitfalls of front-loading your employer-sponsored retirement plan. Sean and Liz also talk about how to protect your privacy from companies that want to (literally) track your every move.</description></item><item><title>How to Manage Medical Debt with Emily Maloney | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720131/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Medical debt can be confusing and, for some, financially debilitating. In this episode of the Nerdy Book Club series, NerdWallet writer Kim Palmer talks with author Emily Maloney about her personal experience with the health care system — both as an ER worker and a patient. Maloney also sheds light on how quickly medical costs can spiral out of control. In her book of essays, “Cost of Living,” Emily Maloney shares how, after accumulating thousands of dollars of debt, she eventually gets free of it and suggests ways that those currently weighed down by medical debt can do the same.</description></item><item><title>Booking a Dream Disney Vacation for Cheap | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720132/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Disney theme parks are some of the most magical places on Earth. But vacation-wise, they can also be some of the most expensive. From tickets to lodging and food, you can easily spend thousands of dollars on a Disney trip. This episode, Sean and Liz talk with NerdWallet travel writer Sally French about how she booked her dream Disney vacation for cheap — and how you can, too. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Investing for Your Dream Life | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720133/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Building wealth over your life takes planning — and know-how. This episode, Sean and Liz talk with Angel Grace, a DIY YouTuber who wants to set her family up for success over the long term by investing and saving for her son’s college education. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.com. Like what you hear? Please leave us a review and tell a friend.</description></item><item><title>What the Heck Is Crypto, Anyway? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720134/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720134/</guid><description>Podcast Description You’ve heard of crypto, but do you really know what it is? Do you think you could explain it to a family member who is totally clueless about this newfangled digital money? In this episode, NerdWallet crypto writer Andy Rosen attempts to explain crypto to his aunt and uncle, including what drives its valuation, how the underlying technology works and what to consider before investing in any digital currency.</description></item><item><title>Answering Kids’ Money Questions: Where Does Money Come From? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720135/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kids aren’t known for having a lot of financial decisions to make, but that doesn’t mean they’re not curious about it. This episode we take on a couple of kids’ money questions that get at some of the more existential aspects of money. Namely, where does money come from, and where does it go? And when you have it, how much should you spend? To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Nerdy Business: Building a Brick-and-Mortar Business | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720136/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Opening a brick-and-mortar business isn’t for the faint of heart. This episode, Sean and small-business Nerd Rosalie Murphy interview Uyen Le. Le owns Beauty Bar, a full-service beauty salon with two locations in Colorado Springs. Le walks us through the ups and downs of securing financing to open her first location, getting a liquor license, hiring and growing her employees and weathering the COVID-19 pandemic. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Questioning the 50/30/20 Budget and Company Stock | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720137/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720137/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 50/30/20 budget is a simple way to organize your finances. But as rent prices soar and inflation impacts everything from gas to groceries, does this budget still make sense? To start this episode, Sean and Liz discuss the merits — and limits — of the 50/30/20 budget. Then they answer a few listeners’ questions about navigating company stock. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Nerdy Business: Building the Right Team | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720138/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720138/</guid><description>Podcast Description Starting a successful business means building the right team — and knowing when not to cut corners when hiring employees and partners. This episode, Sean and small-business Nerd Rosalie Murphy talk with Mariyah Saifuddin, co-owner of IT consulting firm Innovative Solution Partners. She shares what she’s learned over 20 years in business, from choosing the right vendors to continually diversifying your customer base. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Summer Travel Tips and Conflicting Financial Priorities | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720139/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Flight cancellations, rising gas prices and a surge of travelers — this year, summer travel might be more expensive (and headache-inducing). To start this episode, Sean and Liz share their tips for making the most of summer travel this year. Then they answer a listener’s question about how to balance conflicting financial priorities.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nerdy Business: Setting Your Business Up for Success | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720140/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Taking a side gig to a full-time job is a big — and daring — jump. This episode, Sean and small-business Nerd Rosalie Murphy kick off the new Nerdy Business series, where they interview business owners about how they got to where they are today and the lessons they have for other entrepreneurs. Sean and Rosalie talk with Theresa E. Gonzales, owner of 5-E Leadership and Marketing and host of the podcast “Latinas From the Block to the Boardroom.</description></item><item><title>Why Are Homes Pricey in the U.S. and Abroad? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720141/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720141/</guid><description>Podcast Description The home affordability crisis isn’t just an issue in the United States. This episode, Sean hosts a roundtable discussion with Nerds from Canada, the U.K. and the U.S. to explore what is driving up home prices in each country — and what consumers can do about it. Our countries might have more in common than you think. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Nerdy Deep Dive: Investing 101, Part 1 | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720142/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720142/</guid><description>Podcast Description You know you should start investing, but do you know the best way to get started? In the first episode of a three-part deep dive into investing, hosts Sean Pyles and Alana Benson explore how to get into the investing mindset, do a bit of myth-busting around investing and discuss how to actually get started. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Queer Money Talk | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720143/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720143/</guid><description>Podcast Description LGBTQ+ people face a number of unique personal finance challenges, including higher rates of poverty and a wage gap. As a wave of anti-LGBTQ+ legislation is enacted across the country, how can members of this community protect their money to strengthen their personal resilience? This episode Sean and Liz talk with David Auten and John Schneider, also known as the Debt Free Guys and hosts of the Queer Money Podcast, about how LGBTQ+ people can improve their personal finances while following their morals.</description></item><item><title>Small Business Inflation, and Sign-Up Bonuses | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720144/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720144/</guid><description>Podcast Description Inflation is hitting everyone’s budgets — including those of small-business owners. To kick off this episode, Sean and Liz talk about how inflation is impacting small businesses, and how you can still shop local as prices climb. Then they answer a listener’s question about the smart way to earn sign-up bonuses while protecting your credit score. Also, we’re running a short, two-question survey. Please share your feedback to help us improve the show for you.</description></item><item><title>Taking On the Racial Wealth Gap | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720145/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720145/</guid><description>Podcast Description The racial wealth gap was created and reinforced over centuries. Can it be solved in our lifetime? In this episode, Sean and Liz talk with journalist Kimberly Atkins Stohr about her series for The Emancipator about solving the racial wealth gap. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.com. Like what you hear? Please leave us a review and tell a friend.</description></item><item><title>What's Up With Eggs, and Home Improvement Projects | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720146/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eggs — why are they so expensive right now, and what can you do about it? To start this episode, Sean and Liz crack open the factors driving up egg prices at the moment. They also share their tips for making groceries more affordable at the moment, including whether you should start your own chicken coop. Then they talk about how to approach home improvement season in 2022. Materials and contractors can be expensive and hard to come by, so you might need to get creative to accomplish your goals.</description></item><item><title>Nerdy Deep Dive: How to Reduce Child Care Costs | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720147/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Child care can be a strain on many families’ budgets — but there are opportunities for you to minimize the cost. In Part 2 of this Nerdy deep dive, we talk with two of our own Nerds to highlight existing financial resources for parents at the federal and state level. We also discuss personal finance strategies that can help parents think long term, even if money is tight at the moment.</description></item><item><title>Recession Prep, and Lightning Round Money Questions | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720148/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720148/</guid><description>Podcast Description A recession is (maybe) imminent. To start off this episode, Sean and Liz talk about how to prepare for a recession, including how to think about investing. Then they answer a number of your questions in a lightning round. This time they talk about how to grow money, buying cars and travel credit cards. Also, we are running a short, two-question survey. Please share your feedback to help us improve the show for you.</description></item><item><title>Nerdy Deep Dive: Why is Child Care So Expensive? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720149/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Child care costs are pushing budgets to the brink. In the first episode of this two-part Nerdy deep dive, we go behind the scenes to untangle one of the largest budget items for many families. By listening to this series, parents and listeners of all stripes will become more aware of the system and know how to take advantage of supports that currently exist — while the fight for widespread policy changes continues.</description></item><item><title>Giving Family Money, and What's Happening with Inflation | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720150/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Your family or friend needs money in a pinch. Do you help them out, or tell them to look elsewhere for cash? To start this episode, Sean and Liz discuss different approaches to giving loved ones money. Then they talk about all things inflation — what’s driving it and when it might slow down — with Darian Woods from NPR’s podcast “The Indicator from Planet Money.” Also, we are running a short, two-question survey.</description></item><item><title>Get Creative About Money With Paco de Leon | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720151/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720151/</guid><description>Podcast Description If traditional money advice doesn’t work for you, then you might want to consider a more creative approach. In this episode, personal finance Nerd Kim Palmer talks with Paco de Leon, author of the new personal finance book, “Finance for the People.” She is also an illustrator, musician and founder of a financial education firm and bookkeeping agency. De Leon shares how to take a visual and creative approach to budgeting and making money decisions, including why — and how — to write a letter to your own debt.</description></item><item><title>Nerdy Travel Diaries: Use Points to Fly in Luxury | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720152/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720152/</guid><description>Podcast Description You can fly abroad in business class on points alone — if you know how to play the points game. To wrap up our Nerdy Travel Diaries series, Liz talks with travel Nerd Elina Geller about her strategy for booking international business class flights. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.com. Like what you hear? Please leave us a review and tell a friend.</description></item><item><title>Fruitful Yard Sale, and When Not to Refinance | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720153/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720153/</guid><description>Podcast Description Want to get rid of your junk and earn a buck? To start off this episode, Sean and Liz give you tips for a successful yard sale, including how to make your wares look more appealing to buyers and how to price items. Then they answer a listener’s money question about when it doesn&amp;rsquo;t make sense to refinance a mortgage. Send the Nerds your money questions by calling or texting the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373.</description></item><item><title>Nerdy Travel Diaries: Getaway to Costa Rica | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720154/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720154/</guid><description>Podcast Description After two years of sitting on credit card points and staying at home, you might be in a great position to book some luxurious international travel. In this episode of our Nerdy Travel Diaries series, Sean talks with NerdWallet travel editor Kevin Berry about his recent trip to an all-inclusive luxury resort in Costa Rica that he booked with points. They also discuss how you can use points to book your own international vacation.</description></item><item><title>New Student Debt, and a Couple's Money Baggage | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720155/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Student debt cancellation may be on the horizon. But a new generation of graduates is set to take on another load of burdensome debt. To start off this episode, Sean and Liz talk with NerdWallet data writer Liz Renter about her new report on the debt high school graduates may face — and how they can mitigate it. Then Sean and Liz answer a listener’s question about how to get past the money baggage in their relationship and manifest an exceptional financial future together.</description></item><item><title>Nerdy Travel Diaries: Scrimping and Splurging in Japan | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720156/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Traveling to Japan can be both expensive and intimidating — but it doesn’t have to be. In this episode of our Nerdy Travel Diaries series, NerdWallet travel writer Sam Kemmis shares how he crafted a vacation in Tokyo that included both luxury amenities and cost-saving travel hacks. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.com. Like what you hear?</description></item><item><title>Bitcoin 401(k)s and Choosing the Best Crypto | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720157/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720157/</guid><description>Podcast Description Crypto is coming to 401(k) accounts. Should you add it to your portfolio? And which crypto is the best to invest in right now? In this episode, Liz and Sara discuss how to think about investing in crypto, including how to understand which type will help you reach your financial goals. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Nerdy Travel Diaries: Weightlifting in New Mexico | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720158/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720158/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Travel Nerds know how to get the most from any trip — whether they’re staying in a luxury hotel on credit card points or finding the best airfare. To kick off this Nerdy Travel Diaries series, NerdWallet travel writer Sally French shares how she saved money on a trip to New Mexico for a weightlifting meet. One tip? Make sure you know where your credit card points have the most value.</description></item><item><title>Small Business Benefits, and Buying a Hybrid | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720159/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shopping at small businesses may offer more benefits than you know, including access to exclusive deals and insider information. To start this episode, Sean and Liz talk about the benefits of shopping at small businesses. Then they answer a listener’s money question about whether switching to a hybrid vehicle is a smart financial move right now. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Protecting Your Privacy, and Front-Loading a 401(k) | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720160/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720160/</guid><description>Podcast Description Maxing out a 401(k) is a great step toward saving for retirement, but have you ever thought about front-loading your plan? In this episode, hosts Sean Pyles and Liz Weston talk with investing Nerd Alana Benson about the pros, cons and potential pitfalls of front-loading your employer-sponsored retirement plan. Sean and Liz also talk about how to protect your privacy from companies that want to (literally) track your every move.</description></item><item><title>Student Debt Cancellation Debate, Part 2 | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720161/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720161/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is student loan cancellation the key to liberating those crushed under burdensome debt, or a potentially-ineffective political ploy? In this two-part Nerdy Deep Dive into student loans, Sean and student loans Nerd Anna Helhoski explore how taking on huge amounts of student debt has become the norm in America. They also discuss what’s shifting now in today’s student debt conversation. In Part 2, we speak with two experts — each falling on one side of the student debt cancellation debate.</description></item><item><title>Save Money at Weddings, and Vetting Mortgage Lenders | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720162/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720162/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wedding season is picking up steam. Are you — and your budget — ready? To kick off this episode, Sean and Liz talk about how you can save money attending weddings this year. Then Sean and Liz answer a listener’s question about the risks of going with the mortgage lender your real estate agent recommends. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Student Loans and the Cancellation Debate, Part 1 | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720163/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Student loans are a tool, as well as a dreaded financial reality, for most Americans who attend college. In this two-part Nerdy Deep Dive into student loans, Sean and student loans Nerd Anna Helhoski explore how taking on huge amounts of student debt has become the norm in America. They also discuss what’s shifting now in today’s student debt conversation. In Part 1, we trace the origins of student loan debt and how college got so expensive.</description></item><item><title>3 Money Tasks for Spring, and Alternative Debt Payoff Options | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720164/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720164/</guid><description>Podcast Description With spring in the air, money tasks might be the last thing on your mind. To kick off this episode, Sean and Liz talk about three easy tasks to knock out so you can have your money on track while you go enjoy the warmer weather. Then they answer a listener’s question about different ways to take care of their debt. Some routes can save you time and money — others can make a difficult situation worse.</description></item><item><title>Using Your Tax Refund, and Is Pet Insurance Worth the Cost? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720165/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720165/</guid><description>Podcast Description The windfall of a tax refund can be a boon to your savings, help fund a vacation — and more. To kick off this episode, Sean and Liz talk about different ways to use your tax refund and why you might have to wait awhile for yours. Then they answer a listener’s money question about whether pet insurance is worth the cost. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>The Fed Interest Rate Hike, and What’s a Credit Card Authorized User? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720166/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720166/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Federal Reserve is raising interest rates. To explore what it means for you, Sean kicks off this episode with a roundtable discussion about how the rate hike could affect mortgages, day-to-day finances and credit cards. Then Sean and Liz answer a listener’s question about how making family members (or friends, for that matter) authorized users on your credit cards can help them boost their credit. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Single-Income Couples, and When to Use Your HSA and FSA | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720167/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Going from a two-income household to a one-income household is not solely a financial challenge. But this change also creates opportunities to strengthen your relationship and set clear expectations. To start off this episode, Sean and Liz discuss how to manage finances in a one-income household. Then Sean and Liz answer a listener’s money question about using HSAs and FSAs. Both can cover health care expenses, but only one can be used as an investment vehicle.</description></item><item><title>How I Got Here: Tori Dunlap of Her First $100K | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720168/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720168/</guid><description>Podcast Description What does it take to save $100K by your mid-20s? Just ask Tori Dunlap, founder of the blog Her First $100K and the “Financial Feminist” podcast. In this episode, Sean interviews Tori about how she got to where she is today, the lessons she learned along the way and her advice for you to make the most of your finances. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Combating Inflation, and Saving for Retirement Amid Climate Change | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720169/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gas, groceries and just about everything else are getting more expensive. Sean and Liz share tips for protecting your purchasing power, including cutting expenses and using a savings account that earns interest at the rate of inflation. Then they answer a listener’s question about whether saving for retirement is worthwhile in the face of the climate crisis and other calamities. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Why to Sell Your House, and Managing Investment Fees | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720170/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Selling your house right now might sound like a great way to inject unnecessary stress into your life. But it could also be very lucrative, if you do it right. To start this episode, Sean and Liz talk about how and why you might want to sell your house. Then they answer a listener’s money question about how to manage fees on investment accounts. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>The Tax Episode | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720171/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720171/</guid><description>Podcast Description Taxes: You’ve got questions about ‘em, and we’ve got answers. On this episode, Sean and Liz answer a number of listener money questions about filing taxes this year, including how to navigate capital gains, when to hire a tax pro and knowing what you owe. Sean and Liz also discuss how to reduce your tax obligation through credits and deductions. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Lifestyle Creep, and Booking Cheap Travel | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720172/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lifestyle creep — where your growing expenses outpace salary increases — can deflate your budget and prevent you from building wealth. To start this episode, Nerds Sean Pyles and Sara Rathner talk about how to determine if you’re succumbing to lifestyle creep and how to be more intentional about your money, while still enjoying the finer things in life. Then Sean and Liz Weston answer a listener’s three-part question about whether to pay off student loans while they’re paused, what to do with their savings and how to find the best deals when booking travel.</description></item><item><title>Nerdy Book Club: Building Your Financial Smarts With Bola Sokunbi | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720173/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720173/</guid><description>Podcast Description Taking charge of your own financial education can help you get ahead and avoid classic money mistakes. In this episode, personal finance Nerd Kim Palmer talks with money author and educator Bola Sokunbi about her book, “Clever Girl Finance: Ditch Debt, Save Money and Build Real Wealth.” Sokunbi discusses how her mom taught her about money growing up, financial mistakes she made and learned from, and why she says it’s so important to have a side hustle.</description></item><item><title>Credit Union Perks, and Getting Into the Housing Market | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720174/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720174/</guid><description>Podcast Description Where you bank can have a big impact on your community. To start off this episode, Sean and Liz talk about the benefits of credit unions, including how they can offer lower rates on loans and higher rates on savings accounts — while keeping your money local. Then Sean and occasional co-host Sara Rathner answer a listener’s money question about how to get into the housing market. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Stock Market Shakiness, and Car Buying in 2022 | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720175/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720175/</guid><description>Podcast Description Has the recent stock market shakiness left you feeling jittery? To start off this episode, Sean and Liz talk about how you can manage your anxiety — and your portfolio — in moments of volatility. Turns out, sometimes doing nothing is the best thing you can do. Then they answer a listener’s money question about buying a car in 2022, including when the market might calm down a little.</description></item><item><title>No-Spend Month, and Making Money While Raising Kids | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720176/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720176/</guid><description>Podcast Description A no-spend month can help you reset your money habits and save cash. To start this episode, Sean and Liz kick off their no-spend month challenge and talk about how you can craft a plan that works for your lifestyle and budget. Then they answer a listener’s question about how to earn more money while raising kids. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Make a Plan to Achieve Your Dreams | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720177/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720177/</guid><description>Podcast Description Knowing what you want from your life and your money is one thing. Actually knowing how to make it happen is another. In this episode, Sean and Liz interview Andrew DaCosta, a pilot who has sky-high ambitions, but needs some help to get them off the ground. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.com. Enjoying the podcast? Please take a minute to rate and review.</description></item><item><title>COVID Tests, and Reversing a Credit Score Drop | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720178/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720178/</guid><description>Podcast Description Finding (and paying for) COVID tests is overly complicated. This episode, Sean and occasional co-host Sara Rathner start off by talking about how you can navigate getting COVID tests right now. They also talk about avoiding COVID testing scams. Then Sean and Sara answer a listener’s question about how to reverse a credit score drop. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Making Your Dream Life | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720179/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Living in a van, traveling the country and working wherever you want might sound like an odd dream, but that’s the life NerdWallet travel writer Sam Kemmis designed for himself. To continue our series about financial dreams, Sean and Liz talk with Sam about his experience and his tips for making your dream life. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>How Nerds Choose the Best, and Paying for College | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720180/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sifting through financial products can be a pain. That’s where NerdWallet comes in. Our Nerds just released the 2022 Best-Of Awards so you can find the best products for your money goals. To kick off this episode, Sean and Liz talk with the head of the NerdWallet Content team, Hanah Cho, about how you can make the most of the Best-Of Awards and how NerdWallet maintains editorial independence. Then they answer a listener’s question about how to pay for college.</description></item><item><title>Saving for Your Dream Retirement | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720181/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vacations across the world, spending quality time with your friends and family and — most importantly — not being obligated to work a 9-to-5 job: Your retirement is supposed to be about freedom. Getting to that point takes time, money and focus. To continue our series about financial dreams, Sean and Liz talk with personal finance YouTuber Marissa Lyda about how she plans to save in 2022 for her dream retirement.</description></item><item><title>New Money Resolutions, and Strategizing Debt Payoff | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720182/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720182/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s not too late to make your money resolutions for the new year. To kick off the episode, Sean and Liz discuss why you might want to take time to detail what you want out of your money in 2022. They also give tips to help you achieve your goals. Then Sean and Liz answer a listener’s question about how to balance paying off debt while achieving other financial goals like saving for a down payment on a house.</description></item><item><title>Buying Your Dream House | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720183/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720183/</guid><description>Podcast Description What would you do to buy your dream house? Move across the country? Maybe even purchase it sight unseen? That’s exactly what one Nerd did. To kick off our series about financial dreams, Sean and Liz talk with a Nerd who bought her dream house. They also discuss how you can buy your dream home, including preparing your finances and mindset for such a big purchase. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Saving at the Pump, and 401(k) Limits | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720184/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720184/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode, Sean and Liz share their tips for saving at the pump, including how the way you drive and when you get gas can make a difference. Then they answer a listener’s money question about saving for retirement if your access to a 401(k) or Roth IRA is limited. This is an episode from our archives. ﻿To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>What Our Listeners Accomplished This Year, Part 2 | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720185/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720185/</guid><description>Podcast Description As 2021 comes to a close, we are continuing our celebration of what our listeners accomplished with their money in 2021. Sean and Liz discuss mortgage refinancing, paying down credit card debt, the benefits of scheduling a day for money tasks and more. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What Our Listeners Accomplished This Year, Part 1 | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720186/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720186/</guid><description>Podcast Description Did you buy a house in 2021? Maybe you got a new job or finally hit a big savings goal. We encouraged our listeners to brag about what they did with their money this year — and so many answered the call that we made two episodes out of it. Sean and Liz also share what they accomplished in 2021. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Countering Uncertainty, and Building Wealth Early | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720187/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720187/</guid><description>Podcast Description The best time to start building wealth was yesterday. The second best time is today. This episode, Sean and Liz answer a listener’s question about how to start building wealth early. Before they get into that, Sean and Liz discuss how to counter today&amp;rsquo;s uncertainty. Focusing on the fundamentals and tapping your support system can help. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Why to Question Your Bills, and Making the Most of a Raise | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720188/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720188/</guid><description>Podcast Description Question your bills. Otherwise, you might be paying more than you need to for things like healthcare, car insurance and even bar tabs. To start off this episode, Liz and Sean talk about how to scrutinize your bills. Then they answer a listener’s money question about how to manage their finances after getting a big raise, including balancing saving for retirement and paying down debt — and how to avoid lifestyle creep.</description></item><item><title>Travel Tips, and Finding the Right Financial Advisors | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720189/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720189/</guid><description>Podcast Description Traveling during the holidays can be a drag, but it doesn’t have to be. To kick off this episode, Sean and Liz talk about recent trends in holiday travel. They also discuss how they are approaching holiday travel and how to get back in the swing if you’re a little rusty. Then they answer a listener’s money question about how to find the right financial advisors for their needs.</description></item><item><title>Big Purchases, and Overcoming Money Guilt | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720190/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720190/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode, Liz starts off by talking with credit card Nerd Sara Rathner about how to manage a big expense on a credit card — including how to earn the most points and avoid paying interest. Then Sean joins Liz to answer a listener’s question about overcoming money guilt. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Holiday Shopping Trends, and Self-Employed Retirement Options | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720191/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720191/</guid><description>Podcast Description What’s your plan for holiday shopping this year? To kick off this episode, Sean and Liz talk about NerdWallet’s latest holiday shopping report, which explores how shoppers are navigating — and paying for — this unusual holiday season. They also discuss how they’re approaching shopping this year. Then they answer a listener’s question about retirement account options for self-employed workers. While these workers have a number of options to explore, the choice that is best for them may depend on how many employees they have.</description></item><item><title>The Benefits of Being Boring with Your Money, and Why to Make a Will ASAP | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720192/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720192/</guid><description>Podcast Description Your money doesn’t have to be complicated or stressful. To start off this episode, Liz Weston and occasional co-host Sara Rathner discuss the benefits of being boring with your finances. Then, Liz and co-host Sean Pyles answer a listener’s question about whether to make a will, including why setting it up isn’t as complicated — or time consuming — as you might think. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>3 Crypto Questions, and Improving Credit to Buy a House | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720193/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720193/</guid><description>Podcast Description With crypto back in the news, you might be tempted to climb aboard the hype train. To start this episode, Liz and Sean talk through 3 questions you should ask yourself before jumping into the world of crypto. Then, Sean and Liz answer a listener’s question about how to improve their credit with the goal of buying a house, including whether a balance transfer credit card would help. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Holiday Shopping Scams, and Paying Off Law School Debt | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720194/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720194/</guid><description>Podcast Description Scammers are cooking up new ways to swindle your money from you. Two of their tactics this year? Social media ads and hyper-targeted emails. To start this episode, Sean and Liz talk about scams shoppers might encounter this holiday season and how to avoid them. Then they answer a listener’s question about how to pay off $200,000 in student loans. They also touch on the likelihood of student loan forgiveness and recent changes to the Public Service Loan Forgiveness program.</description></item><item><title>What People Get Wrong About Credit, and Self-Employed Budgeting | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720195/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720195/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you know the right way to manage your credit? To kick off this episode, Sean Pyles and Sara Rathner dig into a few common credit myths — and how people can confidently raise their credit. Then Sean and Sara answer a listener’s money question about how to get a grip on their budget with an irregular income. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Finding a New Job, and Rent vs Buy in a New City | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720196/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720196/</guid><description>Podcast Description More people are leaving their jobs, but it’s important to set yourself up for success when looking for your next gig. To start this episode, Sean and Liz discuss how to put yourself in the best position to land your next job. Then Sean and occasional co-host Sara Rathner answer a listener’s question about whether to rent or buy when moving to a new city. They also get into how to make friends in a new city.</description></item><item><title>Nerdy Deep Dives: Investing, Part 3 | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720197/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720197/</guid><description>Podcast Description What’s your risk tolerance? Investing always carries the risk of loss — but can also build your wealth. How you choose to invest may mean the difference between high-risk investments with low returns or lower-risk investments that have greater returns In the final episode of the three-part deep dive into investing, hosts Sean Pyles and Alana Benson talk about some different investing strategies and how they compare when it comes to risk and return.</description></item><item><title>Haggling Tips, and What's Driving Volatile Car Valuation | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720198/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720198/</guid><description>Podcast Description Negotiating can save you money and help you earn more over the course of your career. To start off this episode, Sean Pyles and Liz Weston give their favorite tips for haggling, whether you&amp;rsquo;re shopping for a mortgage, negotiating a salary or shopping online. Then Sean and occasional co-host Sara Rathner answer a listener&amp;rsquo;s question about why the value of their car keeps changing. They also discuss whether now is a good time to buy a car.</description></item><item><title>Nerdy Deep Dives: Investing, Part 2 | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720199/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720199/</guid><description>Podcast Description You’ve heard of stocks, bonds and mutual funds. But do you know how to use them to build wealth? In the second episode of our three-part deep dive into investing, hosts Sean Pyles and Alana Benson discuss each of these investment vehicles and help you understand their pros and cons. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.com.</description></item><item><title>5 Financial Tasks for Fall, and Kid Debit Cards | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720200/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720200/</guid><description>Podcast Description With fall officially here, how ready are you feeling for the final quarter of the year? Sean and Liz give you five financial tasks to take on this fall, including checking in on your money goals for the year and how to optimize your retirement savings. Then Sean is joined by occasional Smart Money co-host Sara Rathner to talk about kid debit cards — when they’re useful and whether there are any risks with these products.</description></item><item><title>Nerdy Deep Dives: Investing, Part 1 | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720201/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720201/</guid><description>Podcast Description You know you should start investing, but do you know the best way to get started? In the first episode of a three-part deep dive into investing, hosts Sean Pyles and Alana Benson explore how to get into the investing mindset, do a bit of myth-busting around investing and discuss how to actually get started. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>DIY Investing, and Lightning Round Money Questions, Part 2 | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720202/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720202/</guid><description>Podcast Description DIY investing has had a splashy year, but it might not be right for everyone. To start this episode, Sean Pyles and Liz Weston talk about DIY investing — what it is, how it works and potential risks. Then, you sent us your money questions, and we’re answering them — back to back to back. In this episode, Sean and Liz take on a number of your questions in another lightning round.</description></item><item><title>Lifestyle Creep, and Booking Cheap Travel | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720203/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720203/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lifestyle creep — where your growing expenses outpace salary increases — can deflate your budget and prevent you from building wealth. To start this episode, Nerds Sean Pyles and Sara Rathner talk about how to determine if you’re succumbing to lifestyle creep and how to be more intentional about your money while still enjoying the finer things in life. Then Sean and Liz Weston answer a listener’s three-part question about whether to pay off student loans while they’re paused, what to do with their savings and how to find the best deals when booking travel.</description></item><item><title>Redlining, and the Credit Impact of Paying Off a Car Loan | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720204/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720204/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode, Sean Pyles talks with mortgage writer Linda Bell about the legacy of redlining and the racial wealth gap. Then, Liz Weston and Sean answer a listener&amp;rsquo;s question about whether to pay off a car loan early — and the potential impact on their credit. To have the Nerds answer your money questions, email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.</description></item><item><title>Delta Spending Habits, and Marriage vs Mortgage | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720205/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720205/</guid><description>Podcast Description How has the delta variant of the coronavirus changed how you’re managing your money? To start this episode, Sean Pyles and Sara Rathner talk about how they’re adapting to the latest chapter of the pandemic and what you can do to increase your financial resiliency. Then they answer a listener&amp;rsquo;s question about how to manage competing financial priorities use their savings — whether they should put it toward a mortgage or a wedding.</description></item><item><title>School Supply Shopping Tips, and Breaking Bad Money Habits | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720206/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720206/</guid><description>Podcast Description With supply chain issues and uncertainty about whether classes will be in person, virtual or a hybrid, back-to-school shopping this year poses unique challenges. To start this episode, Sean Pyles and Sara Rathner give the Nerds’ favorite tips for how to save when buying school supplies. Then Sean and Sara answer a listener’s question about how to break bad money habits. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Home Affordability, and Unmarried Partners Buying a House | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720207/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720207/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you’re jumping into the housing market, know what you’re getting yourself into. This episode, Sean Pyles and Sara Rathner talk with NerdWallet data writer Liz Renter about her new home buying report, including how first-time home buyers should navigate the market. Then Sean and Liz Weston answer a listener’s question about how to buy a house with a partner when you’re not married. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwal</description></item><item><title>Job Scams, and Maxing Out Roth IRAs | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720208/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720208/</guid><description>Podcast Description More Americans are job hunting, but more are falling for job scams, too. Liz and Sean talk about how to spot and avoid scams in the job market right now. Then they answer a listener’s question about the best way to max out a Roth IRA. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Getting Ahead of Your Next Money Crisis with Michelle Singletary | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720209/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720209/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a matter of when — not if — you have a money crisis. No matter your financial circumstance, preparing for an emergency can help you make smart moves under pressure. This episode Liz and Sean talk with Washington Post personal finance columnist Michelle Singletary about how to manage a money crisis and how her experience as a Black woman informs her writing.
To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Health Insurance Deadline, and Getting the Best Car Insurance Rates | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720210/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720210/</guid><description>Podcast Description An important deadline looms for getting health insurance on the ACA exchanges. Liz and Sean discuss what you should know, even if you already have health insurance. Then they answer a listener’s question about how to find the best rates (and coverage) when shopping for car insurance. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rethinking Credit Reporting, and Lightning Round Money Questions | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720211/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720211/</guid><description>Podcast Description Credit reporting is flawed. Liz and Sean discuss what the issues are and how they can be fixed. Then they answer a number of listener questions back to back in a lightning round of money questions, including managing taxes while working remotely and how to find a high yield savings account. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Combating Inflation, and Risks of Small Mortgage Lenders | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720212/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720212/</guid><description>Podcast Description Inflation is on the rise, as your budget has surely noticed. This episode, Sean talks with investing Nerd Alana Benson about what’s happening and what it means for your finances. Then Sean and Liz answer a listener’s question about the potential risks of going with a smaller mortgage lender. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Saving at the Pump, and 401(k) Limits | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720213/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720213/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rising gas prices got you down? On this episode, Sean and Liz break down how you can save at the pump, including how to find the best prices and how to manage your fuel efficiency. Then they answer a listener&amp;rsquo;s question about 401(k) contribution limits. Visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Midyear Money Check-In, and Managing Finances Abroad | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720214/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720214/</guid><description>Podcast Description How are your 2021 money goals coming along? Now that we’re halfway through the year, Sean and Liz talk about how to do a check-in on what you want from your money this year. Then they answer a listener’s question about how to manage their finances abroad, including how to save money on conversion rates and using credit cards strategically. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>Savings Tips, and Updates to the Child Tax Credit | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720215/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720215/</guid><description>Podcast Description We all want to save more money, but actually doing it can be a challenge. This episode, Sean and Liz share their favorite tips to make saving easier, including how to save with purpose and how to trim expenses. Then they answer a listener’s question about changes to the Child Tax Credit, and whether that should influence FSA contributions. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>When Travel Insurance Is Worth It, and Buying an Electric Car | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720216/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720216/</guid><description>Podcast Description With more travelers taking to the sky, should they be booking travel insurance? Liz and Sean discuss. Then they answer a listener’s money question about how to buy an electric car, including how to negotiate with salespeople and how to take advantage of financial incentives for electric vehicles. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Crypto-Earning Credit Cards, and Short-Term Investing | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720217/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720217/</guid><description>Podcast Description Credit cards are hopping aboard the crypto hype train, with some offering rewards in cryptocurrency. Sean, Liz and Sara discuss what they are and their risks. Then Sean and Liz answer a listener’s question about how to approach short-term investing. Also, please take a few seconds to fill out our two-question survey: http://bit.ly/nerdwallet-podcast-survey To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>The Psychology of Debt, and When to Refinance | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720218/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720218/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode, Sean and Liz discuss the psychology of credit card debt — why some people see it as useful and others call it &amp;ldquo;evil.&amp;rdquo; Then they answer a listener&amp;rsquo;s question about whether now is a good time to refinance, even if they just got the mortgage last year. Send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info.</description></item><item><title>Buy Now, Pay Later Loans, and Getting Started Building Wealth | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720219/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720219/</guid><description>Podcast Description You’ve probably seen the offers when shopping online: Break up your purchase into smaller payments over a few weeks or months. But are buy now, pay later loans a good deal? Sean and Liz break it down. Then they answer a listener’s question about how to get started building wealth. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.com.</description></item><item><title>Big Purchases, and Overcoming Money Guilt | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720220/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720220/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode, Liz starts off by talking with credit card Nerd Sara Rathner about how to manage a big expense on a credit card — including how to earn the most points and avoid paying interest. Then Sean joins Liz to answer a listener’s question about overcoming money guilt. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Free Health Insurance, and Finding Scholarships | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720221/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720221/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sean and Liz break down how to find out if you’re eligible for free or lower-cost health insurance under the American Rescue Plan. Then they answer a listener’s question about how to find scholarships and make higher education more affordable. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Pet Scams, and Buying Different Home Types | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720222/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720222/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you’re in the market for a new pet, scammers may have you in their sights. Sean and Liz talk about avoiding common pet scams. Then they answer a couple of listener questions about buying different home types, including new homes, existing homes, condos and more. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Air Travel, and Collections Accounts on Credit Reports | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720223/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720223/</guid><description>Podcast Description More travelers are taking to the sky as vaccines roll out. Sean and Liz discuss how to find affordable flights as ticket prices climb. Then they answer a listener’s question about how long a collections account stays on your credit report — and how to mitigate any damage to your credit score. Want the Nerds to answer your money question? Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373.</description></item><item><title>Cannabis Investing, and Too Much Cash | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720224/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720224/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cannabis investing — specifically in ETFs — might seem like a savvy move to break into a budding industry. But there are unique risks to investing in cannabis. Sean and Liz discuss the pros and cons with investing Nerd Chris Davis. Then they answer a listener’s money question about whether you can have too much cash in your accounts. To contact the Nerds, email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373.</description></item><item><title>Retiring Early, and Finding Lost Money | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720225/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720225/</guid><description>Podcast Description More Americans are retiring early, but not all of them are doing it the right way. And you may have long-forgotten money waiting to be claimed — here&amp;rsquo;s how to find it. To have your money question answered on a future episode, email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Pandemic Savings Goals, and Taxes on Inheritance | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720226/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720226/</guid><description>Podcast Description Find yourself saving more cash during the pandemic? On this episode, Sean talks with banking Nerd Chanelle Bessette about what people are doing with their pandemic-driven savings. Then, Liz and Sean answer a listener’s question about when you owe taxes on an inheritance. To have the Nerds answer your money questions, email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.</description></item><item><title>Spring Cleaning, and COVID Taxes | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720227/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720227/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode, Sean and Liz talk about how they’re approaching spring cleaning their finances this year, including tidying up their digital lives. Then, they answer a listener’s question about how to manage filing taxes in the age of COVID — including whether you owe taxes on your stimulus. To have the Nerds answer your money questions, email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.</description></item><item><title>Redlining, and the Credit Impact of Paying Off a Car Loan | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720228/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720228/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode, Sean talks with mortgage writer Linda Bell about the legacy of redlining and the racial wealth gap. Then, Liz and Sean answer a listener&amp;rsquo;s question about whether to pay off a car loan early — and the potential impact on their credit. To have the Nerds answer your money questions, email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.</description></item><item><title>Procrastination, and Paying Student Loans vs. Investing | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720229/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720229/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fear of making mistakes can fuel procrastination, but that can be costly when you’re putting off important money tasks. One task that may be OK to delay, however, is paying off student loans. To send the Nerds your money questions, email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Pandemic Debt, and Moving Costs | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720230/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720230/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode, Sean and Liz discuss how to manage debt in our K-shaped economic recovery. Then they answer a listener&amp;rsquo;s question about how to manage expenses for a cross-country move. Want the Nerds to answer your money question? Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Saving at the Pump, and 401(k) Limits | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720231/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720231/</guid><description>Podcast Description You may have noticed that gas prices are on the rise. On this episode, Sean and Liz break down how you can save at the pump, including how to find the best prices and how to manage your fuel efficiency. Then they answer a listener&amp;rsquo;s question about 401(k) contribution limits. Visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why to File Your Taxes Early, and Tapping Your Home's Equity | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720232/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720232/</guid><description>Podcast Description Filing your taxes isn&amp;rsquo;t fun, we get it. On this episode, Sean and Liz give you three reasons why to file early (including how it can save you money). Then, they answer a listener&amp;rsquo;s question about when to tap your home&amp;rsquo;s equity. Want the Nerds to answer your money question? Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.</description></item><item><title>Money News You Missed, and the 50/30/20 Budget | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720233/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720233/</guid><description>Podcast Description A lot happened at the end of 2020. Sean and Liz discuss news you might have missed about important changes that could affect college financial aid and/or your employee benefits. Then they answer a listener&amp;rsquo;s question about how to use the 50/30/20 budget. Want the Nerds to answer your money question? Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.</description></item><item><title>Stock Market Shenanigans, and Talking About Money with Your Partner | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720234/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720234/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode, Sean talks with investing Nerd Chris Davis about whether the GameStop frenzy will affect your retirement account. Then Sean and Liz answer a listener&amp;rsquo;s question about how to start having money conversations with your partner. The secret? Talk openly, often and set shared goals. Visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jackpot Windfall, and Extra COVID Cash | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720235/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720235/</guid><description>Podcast Description Suddenly find yourself the winner of a billion dollars? Sean and Liz discuss how you should think about your winnings — and other windfalls, like tax refunds. Then they&amp;rsquo;re joined by personal finance Nerd Amrita Jayakumar to answer a listener&amp;rsquo;s money question about how to change your money habits and use cash saved up during the pandemic. Want the Nerds to answer your money question? Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text 901-730-6373.</description></item><item><title>How to Buy a House in 2021 | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720236/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720236/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wrapping up the #NewMoneyGoals series, Liz and Sean talk with home buying Nerd Holden Lewis about what would-be homebuyers need to know in 2021. Want the Nerds to answer your money question? Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Buying Crypto, and Dealing with Debt | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720237/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720237/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ever wanted to buy cryptocurrency? Well, on this episode you can live vicariously through Sean, who talks with Liz about his experience dabbling in Dogecoin. Then, they discuss our current debt crisis and how to manage debt in 2021. Visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>New COVID Scams, and Easy Money Moves | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720238/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720238/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here’s how to recognize COVID-related scams and what to do if you’ve given out information you should not have, plus, small changes in your money that can have an outsized impact. Want the Nerds to answer your money question? Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How You Can Achieve Money Goals in 2021 | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720239/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720239/</guid><description>Podcast Description What do you want to accomplish in 2021? This month, our #NewMoneyGoals bootcamp will set you up for success. To start, know how to craft — and actually achieve — your money goals. That means making them SMART. Sean and Liz talk with money Nerd Kim Palmer about how you can get what you want from your money in 2021. Turn to the Nerds for help with your money questions!</description></item><item><title>Spot fake reviews, and see if you're saving too much | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720240/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720240/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;re off for the holiday break, so here&amp;rsquo;s an episode from our archives.
Learn how to spot fake online reviews to save money. Speaking of saving, don&amp;rsquo;t avoid retirement accounts from a fear that you won’t be “liquid” enough. You typically can borrow or withdraw retirement funds in an emergency.
Send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.</description></item><item><title>What our listeners learned from the pandemic | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720241/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720241/</guid><description>Podcast Description 2020 was a year of challenges — and opportunities. In this episode, listeners share the money lessons they learned over the past year, including why savings is more important than ever and the benefits of debt payoff.
You know you have money questions — so send them to the Nerds! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.</description></item><item><title>Charitable giving, and using savings to pay student loans | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720242/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720242/</guid><description>Podcast Description Feeling charitable this holiday season? Use discretion as you choose where to give. Also, Sean and Liz answer a listener&amp;rsquo;s question about whether to use savings to pay off student loans.
You know you have money questions — so send them to the Nerds! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Pandemic money lessons, and balancing saving for a down payment vs retirement | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720243/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720243/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sean and Liz share what they learned about managing money during the pandemic. Then they answer a listener&amp;rsquo;s money question about how to save for retirement while saving for a down payment on a house. You know you have money questions — so send them to the Nerds! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What Biden may do for your finances and how to make money | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720244/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720244/</guid><description>Podcast Description Consumer protection will see a revival in 2021, but student loan forgiveness and pandemic relief are still question marks. Plus, what to do if you need to get your hands on some money (relatively) fast.
You know you have money questions — so send them to the Nerds! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The holiday shopping episode | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720245/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720245/</guid><description>Podcast Description How are you planning to shop this holiday season?
According to our shopping Nerds, we’ll shop differently, but we’ll still shop. Many stores will be closed on Thanksgiving, but the Black Friday deals have already begun. Here&amp;rsquo;s how to find the best deals. You know you have money questions — so send them to the Nerds! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.</description></item><item><title>Holiday travel and giving money advice to family | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720246/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720246/</guid><description>Podcast Description The two things we should rethink this holiday season are travel and offering financial advice to family members. Either should be done cautiously, if at all.
Want the Nerds to answer your money question? Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Open Enrollment and HSA vs. FSA | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720247/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720247/</guid><description>Podcast Description Picking health insurance is a pain, but the right choice can save you serious cash. Also, a health savings account can be a great option if you can handle a high deductible health insurance plan, but it’s not for everyone. A traditional plan with a flexible savings account could be a better fit.
Want the Nerds to answer your money question? Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373.</description></item><item><title>Finding financial stability and protecting yourself from ID theft | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720248/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720248/</guid><description>Podcast Description With the election, the pandemic and everything else that&amp;rsquo;s happened in 2020, finding stability can be a challenge. Sean and Liz discuss how to make your money a source of security right now. Then, they answer a listener&amp;rsquo;s money question about how to protect yourself from identity theft. Want the Nerds to answer your money question? Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.</description></item><item><title>Beating burnout and the best college savings plans | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720249/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720249/</guid><description>Podcast Description Feel like you working longer and more draining hours during the pandemic? You&amp;rsquo;re not alone. Liz and Sean share their tips to beat burnout.
Then they answer a listener&amp;rsquo;s question about how to choose the best college savings plan for their child with the help of Kim Palmer. Want the Nerds to answer your money question? Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.</description></item><item><title>Retiring early and finding lost money | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720250/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720250/</guid><description>Podcast Description More Americans are retiring early, but not all of them are doing it the right way. And you may have long-forgotten money waiting to be claimed — here&amp;rsquo;s how to find it. To have your money question answered on a future episode, email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cut your tax bill, and how to choose the best investment platform | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720251/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720251/</guid><description>Podcast Description Looking to cut your tax bill? You have a few go-to strategies, but only a few months left to reduce what you&amp;rsquo;ll owe next year. Also, the right investment platform depends on how you want to invest and how much help you need. Want your money question answered by our Nerds? Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.</description></item><item><title>Unequal unemployment recovery, and whether to buy a new or a used car | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720252/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720252/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sean and Liz dig into what unemployment trends mean for our economy. Then they answer a listener&amp;rsquo;s money question about whether it&amp;rsquo;s best to buy a new or a used car. Want your money question answered by our Nerds? Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode. If you’re looking for an app to track all your money in one place, then check out the free NerdWallet app: https://nerdwallet.</description></item><item><title>The psychology of debt and when to refinance | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720253/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720253/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode, Sean and Liz discuss the psychology of credit card debt — why some people see it as useful and others call it &amp;ldquo;evil.&amp;rdquo; Then they answer a listener&amp;rsquo;s question about whether now is a good time to refinance their home, even if they just got the mortgage last year.
Send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.</description></item><item><title>Used cars in short supply, and Shea Couleé talks money | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720254/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720254/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tight supplies and steady demand are driving up used car prices, but you can still save money. Speaking of saving money, the winner of RuPaul’s Drag Race All Stars is saving some of the $100,000 prize money to buy a house.
Send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Fake reviews and saving too much | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720255/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720255/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learning how to spot fake online reviews can save you money. Speaking of saving, you shouldn’t avoid retirement accounts from a fear that you won’t be “liquid” enough. You typically can borrow or withdraw retirement funds in an emergency. Saving a big chunk of your income while you’re young can give you a great start.
Send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373.</description></item><item><title>Investing while paying off student loans | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720256/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720256/</guid><description>Podcast Description Should you invest or pay off debt? This question can get especially tricky when you’re talking about investing in your company’s stock versus paying down your student loans. Sean and Liz help a listener who wants to know if she should exercise her stock options or focus on paying her $90,000 student loan debt.
As always, send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373.</description></item><item><title>Renters are struggling, and what to do with an old 401(k) | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720257/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720257/</guid><description>Podcast Description Renters are far more likely to be struggling in the pandemic than homeowners. Also, don’t put off a 401(k) rollover. If you want to move money out of an old employer’s plan, ask if your new employer will take it or consider rolling over to an IRA.
Send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.</description></item><item><title>Buying local and emergency loans | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720258/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720258/</guid><description>Podcast Description Buying local could help a favorite small business survive the pandemic. Meanwhile, people who don’t have savings may be tempted to take out emergency loans to cover unexpected expenses. But these small dollar loans can come with high interest rates and short repayment terms, leading to a debt trap.
Send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.</description></item><item><title>Pet costs and extreme couponing | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720259/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720259/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pets can cost a lot more than you think. Pet insurance can help, but it’s not for everyone. Likewise, extreme couponing can pay off for the most dedicated adherents, but there are easier ways to use coupons to save.
As always, send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to take advantage of lower rent and mortgage rates — and move safely | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720260/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720260/</guid><description>Podcast Description August is shaping up to be another record month on the mortgage front. Here’s what it means for you. And if you want to move apartments right now, look at your goals and know how to move safely.
As always, send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is it safe to travel right now, and how to handle a collections to improve credit | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720261/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720261/</guid><description>Podcast Description Air travel brings you in close contact with others, sometimes for hours. A road trip may be a better option. Also, handle old collection accounts with care. Paying an old debt typically doesn’t help your credit, and may lead to a lawsuit. As always, send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.</description></item><item><title>Losing your health insurance, and setting financial goals | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720262/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720262/</guid><description>Podcast Description Losing your health insurance can expose you to medical bills that could bankrupt you. Most people can get subsidized coverage through HealthCare.gov. Also, setting financial goals requires thinking about what’s most important to you and then making a plan.
As always, send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>COVID impulse spending, and building credit while paying debt | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720263/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720263/</guid><description>Podcast Description Spending more impulsively because of the pandemic? You’re not alone. Also, different debt payoff methods have their merits, but paying off small balances first can help your credit.
As always, send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tax returns are due, and how to get started creating wealth | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720264/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720264/</guid><description>Podcast Description The IRS has payment plans if you can’t pay what you owe on July 15. Also, the steps to building wealth are simple, even if they’re not easy: spend less than you earn and save or invest the difference.
As always, send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The wealth gap, and how to cope with variable rate student loans | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720265/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720265/</guid><description>Podcast Description Discrimination affected wealth creation and opportunity in the U.S., leading to vastly different median incomes, unemployment levels and homeownership rates. Also, people with variable-rate student loans can struggle to predict what their future payments will be, which can make budgeting difficult.
As always, send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Setting money goals at milestone birthdays, and scoring big bucks with bank bonuses | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720266/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720266/</guid><description>Podcast Description As you approach your 30s, 40s or beyond, let the milestone birthday be an excuse to set some new money goals. Also, some banks will pay you to open a new bank account, but you need to look beyond the bonus to see if you’ll pay more in fees or collect less interest.
As always, send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373.</description></item><item><title>What a recession economy means for you, and how to handle an inheritance | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720267/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720267/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Sean and Liz give tips for managing your finances in a recession. Then they answer a listener&amp;rsquo;s money question about how to handle an inheritance — and whether you owe any taxes on it.
As always, send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The pandemic is changing our financial lives, and what to know about refinancing now | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720268/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720268/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Sean and Liz discuss survey results that show how money habits are changing as a result of COVID-19. Then, they answer a listener&amp;rsquo;s money question about whether home improvement projects can help home refinancing odds — and if it’s still a good time to refinance.
As always, send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.</description></item><item><title>Make your donations go further; Plan for new baby expenses | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720269/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720269/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Sean and Liz start off by discussing how you can make your donations to social causes go further.
Then, they answer a listener&amp;rsquo;s money question about how to plan for expenses as a new parent. Kim Palmer, a Nerd with a lot of first-hand experience managing baby costs, joins the conversation. As always, send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373.</description></item><item><title>Is identity theft protection worth the cost? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720270/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720270/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can identity theft protection services really protect us from identity theft? No, but they can serve as an (expensive) early warning signal. Most people should first consider some free ways to reduce the chances of becoming a victim, such as credit freezes and monitoring a credit score.
As always, send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.</description></item><item><title>Is Bitcoin a safe investment? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720271/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720271/</guid><description>Podcast Description People who invest in bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies need to be ready for a wild ride. Values can soar and plunge, plus there’s no guarantee you’ll get your money back. Cryptocurrency is more of a gamble than an investment, and shouldn’t be more than a small portion of your overall portfolio.
As always, send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.</description></item><item><title>I Got Laid Off! What Should I Do with My Retirement Fund? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720272/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720272/</guid><description>Podcast Description Getting your retirement account squared away is just one of the many tasks facing the newly unemployed, but it’s an important one. Rolling the money into an IRA could be the best choice, particularly if your former employer isn’t allowing the new “coronavirus hardship withdrawals.” As always, send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.</description></item><item><title>Where have all the 0% offers gone? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720273/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720273/</guid><description>Podcast Description It used to be easy for people with good credit scores to get 0% balance transfer offers. As lenders pull back, those with credit card debt may need alternative plans to deal with their balances.
As always, send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How can I buy my first home in an expensive city? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720274/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720274/</guid><description>Podcast Description Being a first-time homeowner can be daunting, especially in a pricey market like Southern California. Chris Browning of the Popcorn Finance podcast has questions about what to expect, and he turns to the Nerds for some answers.
As always, send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373. And visit www.nerdwallet.com/podcast for more info on this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Where's my coronavirus relief check — and how should I use it? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720275/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720275/</guid><description>Podcast Description Most American adults are eligible for government relief checks of $1,200, but many are still waiting for their money — plus the usual advice about what to do with a windfall doesn’t apply in a crisis. Sean and Liz discuss how to find out where your payment is and put it to the best use.
As always, send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373.</description></item><item><title>How should I spring-clean my finances? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720276/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720276/</guid><description>Podcast Description Don’t stop with your closets. Spring cleaning your finances can be just as satisfying, not to mention more lucrative. Whip your budget into shape, check your credit and make sure your investments are on track.
As always, send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Help! I owe the IRS! | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720277/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720277/</guid><description>Podcast Description You were expecting a tax refund — but wound up owing money. Changing tax laws and the gig economy mean many taxpayers who traditionally got money back are now having to pay. Sean and Liz help a reader navigate paying a tax bill, as well as steps for avoiding a tax bill next year.
As always, send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373.</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus Special Edition, Part IV: The CARES Act and Your Student Loans | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720278/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720278/</guid><description>Podcast Description The economic stimulus package gave millions of student loan borrowers some important breaks, but people are confused about what they are and what they have to do. Sean and Liz get the scoop from student loan nerd Ryan Lane.
As always, send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus Special Edition, Part III: Coronavirus and Your Portfolio | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720279/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720279/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nauseating drops in the stock market can be hard to endure, but most of us should try to do just that &amp;ndash; and even invest more, if we can. If you need the money within five years or you’re losing sleep, though, you might need to get at least some of your portfolio to safer ground.
As always, send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373.</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus Special Edition, Part II: Saving, Budgeting and Travel | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720280/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720280/</guid><description>Podcast Description The coronavirus pandemic has scrambled people’s travel plans and their budgets. Here are the most important things to know now about emergency funds, spending plans and travel in the coming months.
As always, send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus Special Edition, Part I: Mortgages and the Market | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720281/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720281/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mortgage rates dropped and then soared, making life difficult for people who wanted to refinance and buy homes. Mortgage and real estate Nerd Holden Lewis explains why that happened and what the future may bring.
As always, send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How can I brace financially for coronavirus? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720282/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720282/</guid><description>Podcast Description The economic impact of the novel coronavirus and the COVD-19 disease it causes is likely to be profound. Sean and Liz discuss how to cope with the potential financial fallout.
As always, send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>My credit score randomly dropped — a lot. What happened? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720283/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720283/</guid><description>Podcast Description Unexpected credit scores drops are the worst &amp;ndash; especially when you’re trying to do everything right. Sean and Liz dig into the details of how credit scores work to help a reader whose scores dived seemingly without reason.
As always, send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What's the best way to save for a down payment on a house? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720284/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720284/</guid><description>Podcast Description Many first-time home buyers wonder how to save for a down payment and where to put the money while they’re saving. Sean and Liz talk to mortgage and real estate authority Holden Lewis about the options.
As always, send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How can I get into the travel credit card points game? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720285/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720285/</guid><description>Podcast Description Want to get the most points from your travel credit card, but don&amp;rsquo;t know where to start? We&amp;rsquo;ve got you covered. In this episode, Sean and Liz talk with travel Nerd Sara Rathner, who offers up her insider tips about how to get the most points from your travel. And if you want to become a savvy traveler but don&amp;rsquo;t care about travel credit cards, we&amp;rsquo;ve got tips for you, too.</description></item><item><title>Are Roth conversions a good idea? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720286/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720286/</guid><description>Podcast Description Roth conversions can give you a big tax advantage in retirement, but they&amp;rsquo;re not right for everyone. Sean and Liz talk with retirement Nerd Andrea Coombes to help you figure out if you could come out ahead with a Roth conversion.
As always, send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What's the best way to do a spending fast? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720287/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720287/</guid><description>Podcast Description A spending fast can help you save money — fast! The idea is to hit the pause button on non-essential spending for a set period, usually a month. Sean and Liz are veterans of spending fasts and have some tips for how they work, what to watch out for and staying motivated.
As always, send us your money questions!
As always, send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373.</description></item><item><title>Should I invest or pay off my student loans? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720288/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720288/</guid><description>Podcast Description Should you invest or pay off debt? This question can get especially tricky when you’re talking about investing in your company’s stock versus paying down your student loans. Sean and Liz help a listener who wants to know if she should exercise her stock options or focus on paying her $90,000 student loan debt.
As always, send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373.</description></item><item><title>How do we manage money as a couple? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720289/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720289/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yours? Mine? Ours? Managing your money as a couple can be stressful, and there’s no one right way to do it. Sean and Liz offer some strategies for figuring out what will work best for both of you.
As always, send us your money questions! Email podcast@nerdwallet.com or call or text the NerdHotline at 901-730-6373.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>From the archive: "What's the best way to rack up travel rewards quickly?" | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720290/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720290/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;ll be back in a couple weeks. In the meantime, here&amp;rsquo;s how you can use these winter months to rack up the credit card points to fund your summer travel. And be sure to send us your money questions! Call or text the Nerd Hotline at 901-730-6373, or email podcast@nerdwallet.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>From the archive: "How can I pay off my debt faster?" | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720291/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720291/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;ll be back in a few weeks, so here&amp;rsquo;s an episode from our archives that can help you tackle your holiday debt.
In the meantime, send us your money questions! Call or text the Nerd Hotline at 901-730-6373, or email podcast@nerdwallet.com. Talk to you soon!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Happy New Year from the SmartMoney team! | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720292/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720292/</guid><description>Podcast Description Thanks for a great 2019! We&amp;rsquo;re taking a little holiday break but will be back in 2020 with loads of new episodes for you.
In the meantime, send us your money questions! Text or call our Nerd Hotline at 901-730-6373, or email us at podcast@nerdwallet.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How can I (actually) keep my new year’s money resolution? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720293/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720293/</guid><description>Podcast Description New Year’s money resolutions are common, sure. But keeping them is a whole different story. In this episode, Sean talks with Nerd Kim Palmer about the best tips that can help you actually achieve your money goals in the new year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What are your best tips to save on family holiday travel? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720294/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720294/</guid><description>Podcast Description Holiday travel can be expensive — especially if you’re traveling with family. But you have options to make the cost more manageable. In this episode, Sean talks with travel Nerd Sara Rathner about how you can save on family holiday travel costs.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Does Black Friday live up to the hype? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720295/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720295/</guid><description>Podcast Description Black Friday might seem like the best time to get the biggest deals of the holiday shopping season. But is the shopping extravaganza all it’s made out to be? The answer: Sometimes. In this episode we give you the tips to get the best holiday shopping deals, including when and where to shop.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Which accounts can make me the most money? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720296/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720296/</guid><description>Podcast Description You can make money just by putting your cash into the right account. Which account to choose depends on a few factors, though. In this episode, Sean talks with investing Nerd Arielle O’Shea about the best ways to make money off of cash you have sitting in a bank account.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How much house can I afford? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720297/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720297/</guid><description>Podcast Description Think you’re finally ready to buy a home? Here’s how to know how much house you can afford with your budget, what you might need for a down payment, and how to think about the emotional aspect of homebuying.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How can I pay off my debt faster? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720298/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720298/</guid><description>Podcast Description Want to pay off your debt fast? You can, with a bit of know-how. In this episode, Sean Pyles and Liz Weston break down how you can find the payoff path that might work best for you and your debt.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How do I buy a used car? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720299/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720299/</guid><description>Podcast Description Buying a used car can be confusing. Should you shop around a used car lot, or are the online classified ads a better route? With the help of NerdWallet car-buying whiz Philip Reed, that’s the debate Dayana and Sean settle this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How can my credit score save me money? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720300/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720300/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sure, you got a high credit score — but how can you make the most of it? Sean and Dayana talk with NerdWallet all-star Liz Weston to see how you could use your high credit score to save thousands of dollars.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Should I refinance my student loans? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720301/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720301/</guid><description>Podcast Description Refinancing student loans might save you money — if you’re a good candidate. But that’s not the only way to help manage your student debt. In this episode Dayana and Sean get to the bottom of when student loan refinancing is a good idea, so you can see if it’s right for you.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>My prescription drug costs are wrecking my budget. What can I do? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720302/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720302/</guid><description>Podcast Description Having Type 1 diabetes can be expensive. Just ask Paloma Kemak, aka Glitter Glucose on Instagram, who pays over $1,000 a month for her insulin. Dayana and Sean talk with her about her experience living with diabetes and offer tips to help manage the costs.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What's the best way to rack up travel rewards quickly? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720303/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720303/</guid><description>Podcast Description You can rack up travel credit card points quickly — if you know the right tips. In this episode, Sean and Dayana give you the inside scoop so you can earn points and miles fast to fund a vacation on credit card rewards.
For more, visit: https://www.nerdwallet.com/podcast/
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Am I saving enough for retirement? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720304/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720304/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here’s how to know if you’re saving enough for retirement — and what to do if you’re behind, or haven&amp;rsquo;t even gotten started yet. Dayana and Sean explain easy steps to help you set aside a pot of gold to spend in your golden years.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Welcome to NerdWallet's Smart Money podcast! | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720305/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720305/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to NerdWallet&amp;rsquo;s Smart Money podcast, where we answer your money questions. Wondering how to start investing? Or which credit card is best for you? Maybe you just need some budget help. Whatever your question, turn to the Nerds. To send the Nerds your money questions, call or text the Nerd hotline at 901-730-6373 or email podcast@nerdwallet.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Travel-Hack the Holidays | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720306/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720306/</guid><description>Podcast Description Want to make holiday travel a little less hectic? Dayana and Sean get the scoop from NerdWallet’s travel-hacking expert, Joe Cortez, to give you the insider tips to do just that. Learn how to cut lines, make the most of your Priority Pass and more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Inside student loan scams | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720307/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720307/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are companies that offer to reduce or eliminate your debt legit? We hear Selina’s story about what happened with her $60,000 student debt and tell you how to get real help.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What's a side hustle and should I start one? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720308/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720308/</guid><description>Podcast Description There are a lot of side gigs out there. (Nerds took some for a test drive!) Here’s how to tell which ones are worth it and which are scams.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>I want to invest. How should I start? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720309/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720309/</guid><description>Podcast Description We dive into the basics — getting financially ready, finding a good first investment, how to wade in safely and get over the fear of losing money.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to get out of debt: Interview with The Debt Free Guys | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720310/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720310/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Debt Free Guys, John Schneider and David Auten, reveal how they paid off over $50,000 in credit card debt, and the need for personal finance education in the LGBTQ community.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is a travel credit card right for me? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720311/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720311/</guid><description>Podcast Description From application, to acceptance, to acquiring and using points, NerdWallet card sharks share tips on finding the right rewards program.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How do I prioritize my budget? | NerdWallet's Smart Money Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8820720312/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 21:20:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8820720312/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wants versus needs. Spending versus saving. You can have it all (even the fun stuff) by following a simple budget to direct your dollars wisely.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>