<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>All There Is with Anderson Cooper on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/all-there-is-with-anderson-cooper/</link><description>Recent content in All There Is with Anderson Cooper on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 09:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/all-there-is-with-anderson-cooper/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Greatest Loss | All There Is with Anderson Cooper</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1381050014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1381050014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Katie Talman, was grieving an unimaginable loss when she left a message for Anderson Cooper, one of more than a thousand voicemails he received from podcast listeners. Anderson called Katie back at her home in Texas and she agreed to share her story. When Katie was 23 weeks pregnant, her daughter Everly died. “Nothing could have prepared me to deliver a stillborn baby,” Katie says. The grief over her daughter’s death, the silence in the delivery room, the inability of some in her life to understand or even acknowledge the depth of her pain - Katie and Everly’s story is a moving testament to a family’s love and a mom’s courage in the face of the greatest loss.</description></item><item><title>A President’s Grief | All There Is with Anderson Cooper</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1381050001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1381050001/</guid><description>Podcast Description “You gotta come home, there&amp;rsquo;s been an accident.” It was 1972 when Joe Biden heard the news that changed his life forever: his wife Neilia and 13-month-old daughter Naomi were killed in a car crash. Decades later his beloved son Beau died of cancer. In this deeply personal interview President Biden reveals how he has found solace in his grief and learned to search for purpose beyond his pain.</description></item><item><title>Facing Our Grief | All There Is with Anderson Cooper</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1381050002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 09:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1381050002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Grief doesn’t just go away, no matter how hard we may want it to. So how can we live with it and learn from it? These are the questions Anderson Cooper struggles to answer after the first season of All There Is ends. Anderson spends months playing more than 1000 unheard voicemail messages about grief from podcast listeners, and once again finds himself in his basement surrounded by boxes, full of letters, photos and objects that belonged to his late father, mother, and brother.</description></item><item><title>Season 2: All There Is | All There Is with Anderson Cooper</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1381050003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 15:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1381050003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do we ever move on from grief, or do we just learn to live with it? In Season 2 of All There Is, Anderson Cooper continues his deeply personal journey to understand his own feelings of grief in all its complexities, and in moving and honest discussions, learn from others who’ve experienced life-altering losses. All There Is with Anderson Cooper is about the people we lose, the people left behind, and how we can live on – with loss and with love.</description></item><item><title>When Anderson Met Audie | All There Is with Anderson Cooper</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1381050004/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1381050004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anderson is pleased to present the first episode of Audie Cornish&amp;rsquo;s new podcast: The Assignment&amp;hellip; but first a conversation on the intimacy of podcasting with Audie and Anderson.
Fiery Twitter threads and endless news notifications never capture the full story. Each week on The Assignment, host Audie Cornish pulls listeners out of their digital echo chambers to hear from the people who live the headlines. From the sex work economy to the battle over what’s taught in classrooms, no topic is off the table.</description></item><item><title>You Are Not Alone | All There Is with Anderson Cooper</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1381050005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1381050005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anderson shares poignant and profound messages from listeners and reflects on the conversations he&amp;rsquo;s had during the first season of the podcast. To learn more about how CNN protects listener privacy, visit cnn.com/privacy Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Live Your Beautiful Life, Baby | All There Is with Anderson Cooper</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1381050006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1381050006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Writer and poet Elizabeth Alexander talks with Anderson about how she and her two children coped with the sudden death of her husband, Ficre, ten years ago, and the recent death of her father. To learn more about how CNN protects listener privacy, visit cnn.com/privacy Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Laurie Anderson: The Release Of Love | All There Is with Anderson Cooper</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1381050007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1381050007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Artist and composer Laurie Anderson reflects on the death of her husband, rock legend Lou Reed and also her beloved dog Lolabelle. She talks with Anderson about grief and the unexpected feelings she has experienced surrounding loss. To learn more about how CNN protects listener privacy, visit cnn.com/privacy Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Anticipatory Grief | All There Is with Anderson Cooper</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1381050008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1381050008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Filmmaker Kirsten Johnson lost her mother to Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s in 2007, now her father has dementia, and is disappearing before her eyes. As Kirsten struggles with grief over the inevitable loss of her father, she finds ways to celebrate his life and get closer to him. She tells Anderson it&amp;rsquo;s never too late to get to know someone you love more deeply even after they are gone. To learn more about how CNN protects listener privacy, visit cnn.</description></item><item><title>Molly Shannon’s Unspeakable Loss | All There Is with Anderson Cooper</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1381050009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1381050009/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Molly Shannon was four, her mother, baby sister and cousin were killed in a car crash. Her father was at the wheel. Growing up, few people ever spoke with her about her grief. She and Anderson explore how early loss shaped both their lives, and propelled them forward in unexpected ways. To learn more about how CNN protects listener privacy, visit cnn.com/privacy Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Sadness Isn’t An Enemy | All There Is with Anderson Cooper</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1381050010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1381050010/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this deeply personal episode, Anderson reflects on the suicide of his brother, Carter, and the impact that loss still has on his life today. Anderson is joined by Dr. BJ Miller, a hospice and palliative care physician whose sister, Lisa, died by suicide. BJ brings exceptional wisdom to a difficult conversation and suggests some surprising ways to think about sadness and grief. This episode contains discussions of suicide.</description></item><item><title>Stephen Colbert: Grateful for Grief | All There Is with Anderson Cooper</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1381050011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 08:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1381050011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can we learn to love the things we most wish had never happened? Can we really become grateful for grief? Heartbreak? The deaths of loved ones? Stephen Colbert believes we can, and sits down with Anderson to explain why and how. It is a deeply moving, thought-provoking, and at times funny conversation that Anderson says has had a major impact on his life. To learn more about how CNN protects listener privacy, visit cnn.</description></item><item><title>Facing What’s Left Behind | All There Is with Anderson Cooper</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1381050012/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 23:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1381050012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alone in his late mother, Gloria Vanderbilt’s apartment, Anderson begins recording his thoughts and memories as he packs up her things. He makes some unexpected discoveries while sorting through boxes of love letters, journals, and cherished keepsakes. Feeling isolated and alone in his grief, Anderson reaches out to a close friend of his mother, who joins him to share insights about her and suggestions about what to do with the things she left behind.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: All There Is with Anderson Cooper | All There Is with Anderson Cooper</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1381050013/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 15:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1381050013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anderson Cooper takes us on a deeply personal exploration of loss and grief. He starts recording while packing up the apartment of his late mother Gloria Vanderbilt. Going through her journals and keepsakes, as well as things left behind by his father and brother, Cooper begins a series of emotional and moving conversations about the people we lose, the things they leave behind, and how to live on - with loss, with laughter, and with love.</description></item></channel></rss>