<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/think-fast-talk-smart-communication-techniques/</link><description>Recent content in Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 15:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/think-fast-talk-smart-communication-techniques/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>119. Best Of: How to Embrace the Benefits of Stress | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030121/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030121/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Stress is natural,” says Alia Crum, an assistant professor of psychology at Stanford. “Stress is inevitable when you’re living a life that’s connected with things you care about. And learning how to embrace it, learning how to work with it is really what helps us thrive and grow and perform at our highest level.”
In this episode of&amp;nbsp;Think Fast, Talk Smart, lecturer and podcast host Matt Abrahams talks with&amp;nbsp;Crum about her work as the principal investigator at the&amp;nbsp;Stanford Mind &amp;amp; Body Lab, where she is studying how people can benefit from stress.</description></item><item><title>118. Maximizing your Personal Brand: Communicating Who You Are to Help Get What You Want | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030001/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030001/</guid><description>Podcast Description What comes to people’s minds when they think about you, and can you control it? Dorie Clark says you can — with the power of your personal brand.
According to Clark, “You have brand equity in your own life.” Your personal brand or reputation, she says, “makes things either easier or harder for you” as you pursue your personal and professional goals. The key question, she says, is “What kind of reputation have you built up?</description></item><item><title>117. Say It, See It: How to Connect Through Conversation | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Communication is about so much more than sharing words. As neuroscientist Shane O’Mara explains, communication is about sharing reality.
According to O’Mara, “A conversation is where we create a shared reality together.” As a professor of experimental brain research at Trinity College Dublin, his research has focused on how human brains sync up through communication. “The essence is that we are creating a shared reality where we come to share the same states of emotion, the same states of memory, and we come to think about the future together in a new way.</description></item><item><title>116. Quick Thinks: Don't Sweat the Small Talk | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Even if you don’t think you’re a natural, anyone can become proficient at the art of small talk by utilizing the right tactics and behaviors. In this collaboration with Harvard Business Review, strategic communications lecturer Matt Abrahams shares his tips and techniques for cocktail party chit chat, networking small talk, and holiday dinner-table conversation. Watch the full video on HBR's YouTube channel.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>115. Best of: How We Set and Achieve Goals | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why do we do what we do? What factors drive us? And how do things like competition with others help us achieve our goals?
These are the questions most interesting to&amp;nbsp;Szu-chi Huang, an associate professor of marketing with a specific interest in motivation. “Competition definitely increases motivation,” says Huang. “It makes attaining the goal more valuable.”
In this episode of&amp;nbsp;Think Fast, Talk Smart, Huang and host Matt Abrahams explore the intersection of human psychology, behavior, and goal attainment — and how communication connects them all.</description></item><item><title>114. Communication Means Paying Attention: The Four Pillars of Active Listening | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030005/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030005/</guid><description>Podcast Description We should all be audience-centric in communication. But, as Julian Treasure contests, we need to take it one step further.&amp;nbsp;What is the listening I am speaking into?, he says, is the question every speaker should ask themselves over and over.
"Every human being’s listening is unique ... we listen through a set of filters and those filters develop as we grow and mature in life and we have experiences.</description></item><item><title>113. Missing Something? How to Kick FOMO with Conscious Decision-Making | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030006/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030006/</guid><description>Podcast Description What if you had that job? What if you were with that person? What if there’s a better option out there? If you find yourself asking these questions, Patrick McGinnis invented the term for what you’re experiencing: FOMO.
First coined by McGinnis in a piece published by the Harvard Business School newspaper, FOMO (Fear of Missing Out) describes the anxiety we feel when thinking that other people are having more fun and living more fulfilling lives than we are.</description></item><item><title>112. From Mistakes to "Missed Takes" | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030007/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030007/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode we're sharing an excerpt from Matt Abrahams's audiobook, Think Faster, Talk Smarter.&amp;nbsp;Listen in as Matt explains how to think like a movie director, where a mistake isn't a grave error, but rather a "missed takes" and an opportunity to try again with a new approach.
*This audio excerpt is courtesy of Simon &amp;amp; Schuster Audio from THINK FASTER, TALK SMARTER by Matt Abrahams, read by the author.</description></item><item><title>111. Best Of: How to Spark Creativity in Your Communication | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030008/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Sparking communication starts with asking why or what or how.”
On this episode of&amp;nbsp;Think Fast, Talk Smart,&amp;nbsp;Tina Seelig, the Professor of the Practice at Stanford’s department of management science and engineering and the executive director of the&amp;nbsp;Knight-Hennessy Scholars program, chats with host and lecturer Matt Abrahams about the importance of asking questions about everything we do.
“Having a mindset of curiosity opens the door to great communication,” Seelig says.</description></item><item><title>110. Write It Well: How to Craft an Email to Capture Busy Readers | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Whatever you’re writing, Todd Rogers says most people are too busy to read it. That’s why, he says, “you want to make it as easy as possible for them."
Rogers is a professor of public policy at the Harvard Kennedy School of Government and the author of the book Writing for Busy Readers: Communicate More Effectively in the Real World. From text messages to fundraising letters to political speeches, Rogers says effective writing makes it “easy for busy readers to navigate what we send them, pull out the key information, and do what they are planning to do anyway, which is move on to the next thing.</description></item><item><title>109. Simplify! How to Communicate Complex Ideas Simply and Effectively | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030010/</guid><description>Podcast Description You said it. But did they hear it? For Frances Frei, communication is about saying things simply enough for an audience to truly understand.
As a professor of technology and operations management at Harvard Business School, Frei knows that shaping culture within organizations requires communicating in ways that influence how people think and act. The problem for many leaders, she says, is that when we “understand something deeply, we describe it in a complicated way.</description></item><item><title>108. All In: How Improv Helps You Show Up and Communicate Well | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030011/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030011/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you’re reading from your notes, you’re going to miss the magic of the moment. That’s why Adam Tobin, Dan Klein, and Patricia Ryan Madsen bring improv techniques to all their communication.
Communication experts in their respective fields of media, performance, and drama, Tobin, Klein, and Madsen all see the immense power of improv in helping us communicate more freely. As Tobin says, “You do the preparation so that you are expert in the material.</description></item><item><title>107. Think Faster, Talk Smarter: How to Speak Successfully When You're Put on the Spot | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030012/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030012/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, executive producer Jenny Luna interviews host and strategic communications lecturer Matt Abrahams about the tips and tools in his new book, Think Faster, Talk Smarter: How to Speak Successfully When You're Put on the Spot See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>106. Best Of: Using Skills From Improv to Master Your In-The-Moment Communication | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030013/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030013/</guid><description>Podcast Description In January of 2020 we launched Think&amp;nbsp;Fast Talk Smart with the goal of helping people improve their communication skills. Now, with more than 100 episodes and an engaged audience tuning in from more than 200 countries, we're proud to take you back to the very first episode, where the magic began.
As we've discussed multiple times on the show, most professional communication is spontaneous in nature. It’s providing feedback in the moment, answering questions, introducing people.</description></item><item><title>105. Radical Candor: The Communication Shift That Can Transform Your Career | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Moving forward in our careers often means giving and receiving feedback. But how candid can we be in communicating with others? For Kim Scott, anything less than radical just isn’t enough.
An executive, speaker, author, and executive coach,&amp;nbsp;Scott&amp;nbsp;is known for her concept of radical candor, which she defines as “caring personally and challenging directly at the same time." By mapping communication onto the axes of caring and challenging, she derives four quadrants of feedback behavior: radical candor, obnoxious aggression, manipulative insincerity, and ruinous empathy.</description></item><item><title>104. How to Change: Building Better Habits and Behaviors (And Getting Out of Your Own Way) | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030015/</guid><description>Podcast Description "We're wired to look for the path of least resistance and efficiency, and that's normally a good thing, but it can get in the way when we want to make a change," says Wharton professor&amp;nbsp;Katy Milkman.&amp;nbsp;Through her research on decision making and in her recent book&amp;nbsp;How to Change the Science of Getting From Where You Are to Where You Want To Be, Milkman examines the many barriers we create for ourselves when it comes to achieving goals.</description></item><item><title>103. Simple Is a Superpower: How to Communicate Any Idea to Any Audience | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030016/</guid><description>Podcast Description The best communicators express ideas simply. And to do that, says Carmine Gallo, “you have to connect with people in a language they understand.”
Gallo is an author, communication coach, and lecturer at the&amp;nbsp;Harvard Graduate School of Design. For him, the cornerstone of good communication is empathizing with an audience enough to truly speak their language. “Think about the audience first,” he says. “If you cannot speak the same language to different stakeholders and adapt the language for those different stakeholders, you’ll never get anything done.</description></item><item><title>102. Create a Presence: How to Communicate in a Way Others Can Feel | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030017/</guid><description>Podcast Description What does it take to have a presence that’s felt by those around us? According to Muriel Wilkins, the answer is simple: Be present.
“Having presence, at the root of it, [is] your ability to be present,” says Wilkins, a C-suite advisor, executive coach, and host of the HBR podcast, Coaching Real Leaders. Working with some of the business world’s top brass, Wilkins helps leaders discover how they can use presence to communicate more effectively, lead more authentically, and create more impact in their organizations.</description></item><item><title>101. We Belong Together: How Communication Fuels Connection and Community | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030018/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030018/</guid><description>Podcast Description When it comes to emotional and physical wellbeing, Psychology professor Geoffrey Cohen says there is one healthy behavior that outweighs the others: authentic connection. “It is really, really important,” he says.&amp;nbsp;
Deep connections with other people are foundational to a happy and healthy life. As Cohen explores in his new book, Belonging: The Science of Creating Connection and Bridging Divides, achieving a sense of belonging isn’t just a nice-to-have — it’s essential.</description></item><item><title>100. Shut Up! How to Communicate Better by Talking Less | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030019/</guid><description>Podcast Description What does it take to be a more effective communicator? According to Dan Lyons, it starts with knowing when to shut your mouth.
As a journalist, author, and screenwriter, Lyons knows a thing or two about wielding words. But as he reveals in his book, STFU: The Power of Keeping Your Mouth Shut in an Endlessly Noisy World, most of us talk too much and listen too little. “A great conversation is about listening.</description></item><item><title>99. Best of: How to Handle Challenging Conversations | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030020/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Being a better listener has a lot to do with silence, says Collins Dobbs, a lecturer in management at Stanford Graduate School of Business. “A lot of people are uncomfortable with the smallest modicum of silence, but learning often happens when we create distance for useful reflection.”
In this episode of&amp;nbsp;Think Fast, Talk Smart,&amp;nbsp;Dobbs&amp;nbsp;talks with host Matt Abrahams about the importance of “space, pace, and grace” when you’re receiving others’ feedback and handling the emotions that come out during tough discussions.</description></item><item><title>98. Give It to Me Straight: How to Give Honest, Constructive Feedback | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030021/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;nbsp;How do we deal with professional blind spots? According to&amp;nbsp;David Dodson,&amp;nbsp;MBA ’87, we need the panoramic perspective of those who work around us.
“360 reviews, done properly, are a massive competitive weapon,” says&amp;nbsp;Dodson, also a lecturer in management at Stanford GSB&amp;nbsp;and author of the new book, The Manager’s Handbook. Such comprehensive and constructive feedback, he says, can be transformational for employees and managers alike. “The first time I did a 360 review and got feedback was a massive turning point in my development as a manager,” he says.</description></item><item><title>97. No Rules, No Trust: How Accountability Shapes Communication | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Communication is like a game. For it to work, each person has to trust that their partner will play by the rules. As Professor Anat Admati says, the same is true for corporations and their stakeholders.
“To have good governance, you need trust and accountability,” says Admati, a professor of finance and economics and the director of the Corporations and Society Initiative. How does a society ensure that markets, businesses, and governments are all on the same page?</description></item><item><title>96. Rock and Role: How Assigning Gender to Inanimate Objects Influences Us | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why is a boat a “she?” Why give names like Alexa or Siri to inanimate pieces of software? According to assistant professor of organizational behavior&amp;nbsp;Ashley Martin, ascribing gender to everyday objects helps us to connect with them more deeply.
“Gender is this humanizing force that allows people to interact with non-human things as if they’re human,” says&amp;nbsp;Martin, whose research focuses on gender equality, gender inclusion, and gender’s role within team and organizational dynamics.</description></item><item><title>95. The Power of No: How Boundaries Help Us Live More Empowered Lives | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030024/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Saying no can seem risky. We worry about offending others, damaging relationships, or hurting our own reputation. But as Vanessa Patrick says, no is an empowering word that gives us greater agency in our lives.
Saying no “is not a rejection of the other person,” says Patrick, a professor of Marketing at the University of Houston. Instead, it allows you to set boundaries and “[give] voice to what you believe and what you care about.</description></item><item><title>94. LEADing ideas: Research-Backed Tips and Tools from Four Stanford Professors | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030025/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Breaking new ground, Think Fast, Talk Smart steps into the world of live events, bringing together an eager audience of LEAD students from Stanford University and a top-notch panel of former podcast guests: Jesper B. Sørensen, Sarah Soule, Jonathan Levav,and Szu-chi Huang. Topics include crafting strategy for successful leadership and tips on how to effectively lead a hybrid team.
This episode also features an interactive audience segment, where various participants of the Stanford LEAD program answer the three questions traditionally posed to guests.</description></item><item><title>93. All the Feels: The Personal and Professional Power of Emotional Awareness | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030026/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030026/</guid><description>Podcast Description How are you feeling right now? According to Celine Teoh, we all need to ask ourselves that question more often — and be more precise in how we answer it.
Teoh is a facilitator of the course Interpersonal Dynamics, or “Touchy Feely,” as it’s affectionately known on campus. In her work with students and as a CEO coach, she encourages people to get better acquainted with their feelings. “Feelings are data,” she says.</description></item><item><title>92. No Regrets: How to Take Risks in Your Communication, Relationships, and Career | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030027/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 18:27:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030027/</guid><description>Podcast Description “What people regret over time are things they didn't do. They didn't take that trip, they didn't ask that person out on a date. They didn't start that business,” says former political speech writer and best-selling author Dan Pink. “I think it's because we are slightly over-indexed on risk. We overstate the risk in many circumstances.”&amp;nbsp;
On this episode of Think Fast, Talk Smart, strategic communications lecturer Matt Abrahams sits down with Pink to hear how we should all take more risks and how leaders can inspire others by focusing on the why instead of the how.</description></item><item><title>91. Um, like, so: How Filler Words Can Create More Connected, Effective Communication | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030028/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030028/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re often advised not to use “um” or “uh”, or “so” and “you know” in our communication. But linguist Valerie Fridland might argue otherwise. “Language is about how we encode both the linguistic message and a social message,” she says. “Crutch&amp;nbsp;words … are really valuable and they have arisen to serve a need.”&amp;nbsp;
In this episode of&amp;nbsp;Think Fast, Talk Smart: the podcast,&amp;nbsp;Fridland sits down with host and strategic communications lecturer Matt Abrahams to discuss how and when we use "</description></item><item><title>90. Best of: Brains Love Stories – How Leveraging Neuroscience Can Capture People’s Emotions | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030029/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030029/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of&amp;nbsp;Think Fast, Talk Smart, lecturer and podcast host Matt Abrahams sits down with David Eagleman, a neuroscientist and the host of the PBS series The Brain, to discuss why our brains are wired for storytelling and how new senses might impact our connection and communication with others.
“I’ve always been really interested in this idea of how we can pass information to the brain via unusual channels,”&amp;nbsp;Eagleman says.</description></item><item><title>89. Listen, Listen, Listen: How to Build Deep Connections | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030030/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Whether you’re trying to build a romantic or professional connection, Rachel Greenwald’s advice is exactly the same. “Focus on how you make someone feel more than you focus on the words that you're saying,” she says. As a professional coach, Greenwald helps people develop better communication skills, from executives in the business world to singles in the dating world. Building deep connections may at times be challenging, but as Greenwald says, it’s ultimately not complicated.</description></item><item><title>88. Best of: Leading From Home – How to Create the Right Environment for Communication | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030031/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030031/</guid><description>Podcast Description *This episode of Think Fast, Talk Smart recently won "Best Business Podcast Episode" at the 2023 Webby Awards.* “You’re not going to hit the mark with everybody, but you still need to be mindful of everybody,” says Jonathan Levav, a professor of marketing at Stanford Graduate School of Business. “That’s critical to create an environment where communication is effective.”
In this podcast episode,&amp;nbsp;Levav&amp;nbsp;sits down with podcast host Matt Abrahams to talk about how to lead from home and how to foster an environment for creativity, innovation, and collaboration.</description></item><item><title>87. Know What You’re Saying: How Communicating Tests Our Understanding | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030032/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030032/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’ve all been there — we think we understand something, but when it comes time to explain it to someone else, we flounder.
According to Gregory LaBlanc, a lecturer in management at Stanford GSB, attempting to communicate concepts reveals whether or not we properly grasped them in the first place. “If you think you understand something but you're incapable of communicating it, it probably means that you don't really understand it,” he says.</description></item><item><title>86. Building Habits: The Key to Lasting Behavior Change | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030033/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Whether you want to read more books or exercise more regularly, BJ Fogg has good news. “Habits are easier to form than most people think,” he says, “If you do it in the right way.”
As the founder and director of Stanford's Behavior Design Lab, Fogg has devoted much of his career to researching human psychology, motivation, and behavior. According to him, habit formation isn’t a product of simply doing something over and over again.</description></item><item><title>85. Best of: Don't Get Lost in Translation | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030034/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Having to communicate in a language other than our native tongue can be quite a challenge, especially without a script or prepared speech.
In this "Best of" episode, we revisit Matt's conversation with Kenneth Romeo about specific tactics that non-native speakers can use to handle in-the-moment challenges. Romeo also discusses why letting go of perfection is a key step toward speaking with confidence. Romeo has served as the associate director of the&amp;nbsp;Stanford Language Center and a teacher of English to non-native speakers through Stanford Continuing Studies.</description></item><item><title>84. Quick Thinks: How Others Define Us | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030035/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030035/</guid><description>Podcast Description “The self is incompatible with freedom, the way most people understand it, because the self is a constraint,” says social psychologist and professor of organizational behavior&amp;nbsp;Brian Lowery. “The ‘you’ you’re talking about is actually the relationships you have, the social interactions you have and the cultural context you exist in."
In this Quick Thinks episode of&amp;nbsp;Think Fast, Talk Smart, Lowery sits down with podcast host and lecturer in strategic communications Matt Abrahams to talk about his new book,&amp;nbsp;Selfless: The Social Creation of You.</description></item><item><title>83. You Need a Manifesto: How to Communicate Your Convictions | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030036/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030036/</guid><description>Podcast Description “If you're not living life according to your own values, you're most likely living them according to someone else's,” says Charlotte Burgess-Auburn.
Burgess-Auburn&amp;nbsp;is a designer, artist, educator, and the Director of Community at the d.school. With her recently published guide,&amp;nbsp;You Need A Manifesto: How To Craft Your Convictions And Put Them To Work,&amp;nbsp;she aims to help people identify their core values and then codify them to chart a course of meaning and purpose.</description></item><item><title>82. It’s Not About You: Why Effective Communicators Put Others First | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030037/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030037/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s easy to feel like the star of the show when giving a presentation. But according to communication guru Nancy Duarte, you’re not the hero of this story.
For Duarte, founder and CEO of world-renowned communication consulting firm Duarte Inc, effective communication is built on the foundation of empathy, which means considering your audience first and foremost. “All the attention is on us. But in reality, the audience is the one,” she says.</description></item><item><title>81. Fact or Fiction? How to Communicate When We Hold Different Beliefs | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030038/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why does disagreement feel so personal? According to author, journalist, and physician Seema Yasmin, it’s because beliefs aren’t just about what we think, they’re about who we are.
“What [people] believe is entrenched in them, and it’s to do with their sense of belonging and their sense of identity,” says Yasmin. Whether we’re butting heads over something trivial like sports or something major like COVID-19 vaccines, Yasmin points out that the disagreement is just the surface — underneath are complex layers of geopolitics, history, language, dialect, culture, faith, family history, and power hierarchies.</description></item><item><title>80. Magic Words: Change What You Say to Inspire and Influence Others | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Words have impact. But when it comes to enchanting audiences and captivating with communication, Jonah Berger, PhD ’07, says some words are more potent than others.
Berger is a Wharton School professor and an internationally bestselling author. His most recent book, Magic Words: What to Say to Get Your Way, identifies language we can use to communicate more effectively in all sorts of personal and professional contexts. “Subtle shifts in language can have a huge impact on everything from convincing clients and holding attention to connecting with loved ones in our lives,” Berger says.</description></item><item><title>79. Equity by Design: How Diversity Ignites Creativity | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030040/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030040/</guid><description>Podcast Description If we want healthier companies, schools, and teams associate professor of organizational behavior Adina Sterling says investing in the health of marginalized groups “can have enormous spillover effects for everyone.”
Sterling is an organizational theorist and economic sociologist whose research explores how human relationships affect organizations and markets. As she says, “The outcomes that individuals, groups, and organizations experience have to do with the social networks that they have.</description></item><item><title>78. Three Guiding Principles for Successful Communication | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030041/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030041/</guid><description>Podcast Description To celebrate our 75th episode,&amp;nbsp;we hosted a live "Ask Me Anything" event with Matt. In this global gathering, listeners called in with questions ranging from making a first impression and giving negative feedback to presenting virtually and the&amp;nbsp;worst&amp;nbsp;communication advice Matt's ever received. In addition to audience questions,&amp;nbsp;Matt also shares a short lecture to outline his top three guiding principles when it comes to being a confidence speaker and leader.</description></item><item><title>77. Quick Thinks: AI Has Entered The Chat – A "Conversation" with ChatGPT | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030042/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030042/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this "Quick Thinks" episode, host Matt Abrahams interviews ChatGPT, an AI natural language processing chatbot, about its purpose, sources of information, ethical considerations, and the importance of human communication skills.
To produce this episode, Matt typed his questions to ask ChatGPT, then recorded them in the studio. Producers then used Descript Overdub to "read" ChatGPT's responses.
[Show Notes]
The purpose of ChatGPT is to provide informative and accurate responses to questions in natural language.</description></item><item><title>Think Fast, Talk Smart: The Podcast | Season 4 Trailer | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 23:18:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join Matt Abrahams, a lecturer of strategic communication at Stanford GSB, as he sits down with experts from across campus to discuss public speaking anxiety, speaking off the cuff, nailing a Q&amp;amp;A, and more.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>76. Change My Mind: Using “Pre-suasion” to Influence Others | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030044/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Want to change someone’s mind? First, explains Robert Cialdini, you have to change their framing.
For&amp;nbsp;Cialdini, the Regent's Professor Emeritus of Psychology and Marketing at Arizona State University, persuasion begins before we even deliver our pitch or presentation. Through what he calls “pre-suasion,” communicators can prime audiences to receive messages in a specific way, simply by drawing their attention in specific directions.&amp;nbsp;
“It involves focusing people on—putting them in mind of—those motivators before they encounter [them] in the communicator’s message,” Cialdini says, “bringing people’s focus of attention onto something that is nested in the message…before that message is delivered, so they have been readied for the concept.</description></item><item><title>75. Love &amp; Money: How to Talk About Big Decisions Together | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030045/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do love and money mix? Labor economist and Stanford Graduate School of Business professor emerita Myra Strober says absolutely.&amp;nbsp;
“Separating money and love is not a good idea. I have had 40 years to think about this, and, in my class at the GSB on work and family, each semester I realize how important it is to intertwine love and money."
In this podcast episode, Matt Abrahams sits down with Strober and social innovation leader Abby Davisson to discuss the thorny topics of work, money, career, and love.</description></item><item><title>74. Best Of: How Emotion Shapes Our Communication, Decisions, and Experiences | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030046/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030046/</guid><description>Podcast Description In one of our most popular episodes, professor of Marketing&amp;nbsp;Baba Shiv&amp;nbsp;shares his research on how emotions affect decision making. Knowing this, and applying techniques to help guide our audience through information and emotion, can help us make our messages stick. In this best-of episode we've included extra footage from Matt Abrahams's conversation with Shiv from November of 2020 that touches on how to best approach writing emails.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>73. Listen Up: Why It’s Better to Be Interested than Interesting | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030047/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030047/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a communication expert, Alison Wood Brooks spends a lot of time talking about talking. But, as she says, listening is just as important.
“My course is called TALK,” says Wood Brooks, who is the O'Brien Associate Professor of Business Administration and Hellman Faculty Fellow at Harvard Business School. “The great irony is that it should really be called LISTEN. It’s hard to be a good listener yet so very important.</description></item><item><title>72. Quick Thinks: Talk It Out – How to Successfully Negotiate and Resolve Conflict | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030048/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030048/</guid><description>Podcast Description When it comes to negotiating and managing conflict, Professor Michele Gelfand says it’s time to get creative.
Everybody has wants and needs. So what do we do when our priorities compete with those of other people? According to Gelfand, a professor of organizational behavior, negotiations and conflict management are exercises in creative problem-solving, ones where we look for ways to not only get what we want, but for those on the other side of the table to get what they want too.</description></item><item><title>71. Strategy Success: How to Communicate Your Gameplan | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030049/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030049/</guid><description>Podcast Description As Professor&amp;nbsp;Jesper Sørensen&amp;nbsp;sees it, a winning strategy is the result of conversations, not commands.
Sørensen says strategy can be directed from the C-suite, but it doesn’t have to be. “Lots of great strategies are discovered,” he says, “they're discovered because the leaders were able to listen to their frontline workers or their frontline managers.” A more iterative approach, says Sørensen, helps companies adapt their strategy to an ever-changing landscape.</description></item><item><title>70. Ideas Fuel Innovation: Why Your First Ideas Aren’t Always the Best | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030050/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030050/</guid><description>Podcast Description What’s the secret to coming up with good ideas? For Jeremy Utley, it’s about generating as many as possible.&amp;nbsp;
The director of executive education at the Stanford d.school, Utley says, “very few problems we face in business or in life have a single right answer.” All ideas — the good, the bad, and the ugly — are “a necessary input to an innovation process,” and an essential step in getting to solutions that will actually work.</description></item><item><title>69. Feeling Nervous? How Anxiety Can Fuel Better Communication | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030051/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stress, anxiety, nervousness — when these feelings inevitably arise, lecturer Kelly McGonigal says it’s not about making them go away, but using them to your advantage.
“What I have come to value about anxiety,” says McGonigal, “is it’s a sign that I care.” As she explains, feelings of stress alert us to things that matter to us and help us stay present in the moment — particularly useful, she says, when it comes to communication.</description></item><item><title>68. Directive vs. Dialogue: Communicating Better as a Leader | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030052/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030052/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the dean of Stanford Graduate School of Business, Dean Jon Levin knows the importance of crafting the right message and sharing it in the right way. But, as he says, one of the biggest challenges for any leader is to know what to communicate, and how.&amp;nbsp;
How do leaders strike the balance between being clear and directive, and as Levin says, “leaving space for people to form their own opinions, to discuss ideas, to debate”?</description></item><item><title>67. What Is Normal? How Culture Affects Communication Styles | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030053/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why do we drive on only one side of the road? Why don’t we sing in libraries? Why wear a swimsuit?
For Professor Michele Gelfand, it all comes down to culture. As a cross-cultural psychologist, Gelfand is fascinated by social environments and their effects on human behavior, particularly, how strictly people adhere to social norms.
In this episode of Think Fast, Talk Smart, Gelfand joins host and lecturer of strategic communications Matt Abrahams to explain why some cultures are “tight” and “have strict social norms,” while others are “loose,” with “more permissibility of behavior.</description></item><item><title>66. Best Of: Lessons from Neuroscientist Andrew Huberman to Help You Hack your Speaking Anxiety | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030054/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030054/</guid><description>Podcast Description “There’s no difference between the physiological response to something that you’re excited about and something that you’re nervous about or dreading,” says Andrew Huberman associate professor of neurobiology and ophthalmology at Stanford University.
In this “Best of” episode, we revisit one of our most popular interviews. In it, Huberman, from the wildly popular Huberman Lab Podcast, shares his research on the autonomic continuum, a spectrum between states of high alertness or fear all the way down to deep sleep, and shares how to use the system to your advantage.</description></item><item><title>65. Ties That Bind: Why Remote and Hybrid Teams Need the Right Connection | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030055/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030055/</guid><description>Podcast Description “We need to be much more adaptive in the way we think about hybrid work,” says Michael Arena. “Experiment, experiment, experiment.”
Innovation relies on teams connecting in very specific ways. But are those connections possible in a hybrid work reality? Glenn Carroll, a professor of management at Stanford GSB, and Michael Arena, a faculty member of Penn's Master's in Organizational Dynamics program, have been looking for the answer — studying how team interactions have changed since millions of workers went remote.</description></item><item><title>64. Best of: Techniques for Managing Your Reputation | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030056/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030056/</guid><description>Podcast Description How others perceive us in person and via social media can impact our careers and social standing. But we can build the reputation we want through conscious communication.
On this podcast episode, strategic communication lecturers Matt Abrahams and Allison Kluger share techniques on effectively improving and managing your reputation.
Listen for details on this episode’s “homework assignment” and share on LinkedIn.
Join the community &amp;amp; conversation by following the Think Fast, Talk Smart LinkedIn page.</description></item><item><title>63. Cheap Talk: What Economics Has to Say About Communication | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030057/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 18:18:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Your words — are they credible? Or are they what Paul Oyer calls “cheap talk?”
According to professor of economics Paul Oyer, how our words align with our actions isn’t just a matter of communication, but a matter of economics too. Economic concepts hold in all areas of life, which Oyer’s research has explored in everything from Uber driving to online dating.
“Economics is everywhere,” Oyer says. “It's an incredibly powerful lens to analyze almost anything in the real world.</description></item><item><title>62. Best Of: Summer Learning Series, How Humor Can Be a Secret Weapon in Communication | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030058/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030058/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the kickoff to our Summer Learning Series, we're revisiting one of our favorite episodes. This interview features Stanford GSB faculty members Jennifer Aaker and Naomi Bagdonas and gives specific insights into how humor can transform your communication at home and at work. At the time of this episode, their book Humor, Seriously was just set to launch.
Enjoy and see you on LinkedIn!
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>61. Courage, Ambiguity, Belonging and Data: How to Design Your Communication for Success | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030059/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030059/</guid><description>Podcast Description All communication comes from a place of creativity and creativity is rooted in design. In this episode of Think Fast, Talk Smart,&amp;nbsp;strategic communications lecturer and podcast host Matt Abrahams interviews four authors from the&amp;nbsp;Stanford d.school. Each conversation challenges convention in how we approach our communication, be it visual, body language, or speech.&amp;nbsp;
Listen to this episode to hear more from Ashish Goel, author of&amp;nbsp;Drawing on Courage;&amp;nbsp;Susie Wise, author of&amp;nbsp;Design for Belonging;&amp;nbsp;Carissa Carter, author of&amp;nbsp;The Secret Language of Maps; and&amp;nbsp;Andrea Small, co author of&amp;nbsp;Navigating Ambiguity.</description></item><item><title>60. Communicating Uncertainty: How to Connect With Your Audience, Even When The Answers Aren’t Clear | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030060/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030060/</guid><description>Podcast Description “It's not reassuring when we don't know the answers to critically important questions involved in health and wellbeing. But it's far more of a problem if we try to pretend we do.” In this episode of&amp;nbsp;Think Fast, Talk Smart,&amp;nbsp;Stanford Medical School dean&amp;nbsp;Lloyd Minor&amp;nbsp;sits down with podcast host Matt Abrahams to discuss transparency in leadership. “Rather than pushing ambiguity away, we should lean into it, and use it as a stimulus to guide our communication in more effective ways.</description></item><item><title>59. From Dreaming to Doing: How We Set and Achieve Goals | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030061/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why do we do what we do? What factors drive us? And how do things like competition with others help us achieve our goals?
These are the questions most interesting to&amp;nbsp;Szu-chi Huang, an associate professor of marketing with a specific interest in motivation. “Competition definitely increases motivation,” says Huang. “It makes attaining the goal more valuable.”
In this episode of&amp;nbsp;Think Fast, Talk Smart, Huang and host Matt Abrahams explore the intersection of human psychology, behavior, and goal attainment—and how communication connects them all.</description></item><item><title>58. Forgiveness: How the Right Communication Repairs Relationships | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030062/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030062/</guid><description>Podcast Description In relationships between imperfect people, mistakes are inevitable. And when we find ourselves with damaged connections, it’s a specific kind of communication that can help us make amends.
Fred Luskin is the Director of the&amp;nbsp;Stanford University Forgiveness Project, and has devoted much of his career to researching the way forgiveness affects our psychological, relational, and physical health.
“Apology is one of the few things that research shows actually facilitates forgiveness,” Luskin explains.</description></item><item><title>57. Are You Listening?: How to Stay Open and Curious to Other People’s Ideas | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030063/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030063/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Listening actively and deeply happens when I genuinely believe that the person who's speaking has intrinsic worth and brings a perspective that I lack and need.”
This episode of Think Fast, Talk Smart features Kristin Hansen, lecturer in management and executive director of Civic Health Project, a nonpartisan, nonprofit organization working to reduce extreme polarization and foster healthier civil discourse in U.S. citizenry, politics, and media.
Together with host Matt Abrahams, Hansen shares how from our workplaces to our personal lives, communication thrives when we cultivate open-mindedness, intellectual humility, and genuine curiosity.</description></item><item><title>56. Lean Messaging: How Simple Messages Really Stick | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030064/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030064/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Anyone can make a complicated thing sound complicated. It takes real skill to make it sound simple.”
This episode of&amp;nbsp;Think Fast, Talk Smart&amp;nbsp;features&amp;nbsp;Steve Blank, seasoned entrepreneur, marketer, and Stanford adjunct professor in the&amp;nbsp;Department of Management Science and Engineering.&amp;nbsp;
“Messages need to be memorable,” he tells podcast host and strategic communications lecturer Matt Abrahams. “The more memorable the message, the greater its ability to create change.”
Blank teaches courses on Lean Startups, innovation, and entrepreneurship, and throughout his 45 years of launching businesses and helping others do the same, he’s learned the importance of crafting the perfect message by keeping it simple.</description></item><item><title>55. Ideas &amp; Empathy: How to Design and Communicate with Others in Mind | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030065/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030065/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Very often, you are not designing for yourself. And you kind of have to get out of your own way to effectively design with others’ needs in mind.”
In this podcast episode, lecturer Matt Abrahams is joined by Sarah Stein Greenberg, Director of the Hasso Plattner Institute of Design, aka the Stanford d.school, and author of Creative Acts for Curious People: How to Think, Create, and Lead in Unconventional Ways.</description></item><item><title>54. Leadership and Ethics: How to Communicate Your Core Values | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030066/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030066/</guid><description>Podcast Description “A mistake that some leaders make is to assume that the people in your organization share your core values. Some of the time some of them do, but there's a bunch who don't, and those are the most difficult sorts of situations.”&amp;nbsp;
In this podcast episode, Political Science professors Neil Malhotra and Ken Shotts sit down with host and lecturer Matt Abrahams, to discuss how to lead others whose values may not align with your own.</description></item><item><title>53. Step Up and Stand Out: How to Create the Right Environment for Communication | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030067/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030067/</guid><description>Podcast Description “You’re not going to hit the mark with everybody, but you still need to be mindful of everybody,” says Jonathan Levav, the King Philanthropies Professor of Marketing. “That’s critical to create an environment where communication is effective.”
In this podcast episode, Levav sits down with podcast host Matt Abrahams to talk about the science behind decision fatigue, how to lead effectively while working from home, and how to create the right company culture both in the office and online.</description></item><item><title>52. Communicating Our Mistakes: How to Avoid Common Flaws and Make Better Decisions | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030068/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030068/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of&amp;nbsp;Think Fast, Talk Smart,&amp;nbsp;host Matt Abrahams sits down with&amp;nbsp;finance professors Jonathan Berk and Jules van Binsbergen to talk about their new podcast,&amp;nbsp;All Else Equal.
Think Fast, Talk Smart&amp;nbsp;is a podcast produced by Stanford Graduate School of Business. Each episode provides concrete, easy-to-implement tools and techniques to help you hone and enhance your communication skills.&amp;nbsp;
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.</description></item><item><title>51. We Asked, You Answered: Celebrating our 50th Episode with your Anxiety Management Plans | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030069/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030069/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this 50th episode of Think Fast, Talk Smart, host Matt Abrahams and executive producer Jenny Luna share the winners' plans from our Confident Communicator Challenge and offer new, research-backed techniques for managing nervousness both before and during your communication. Thank you to many, many listeners from all over the world who sent in their anxiety management plans. See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>50. Telling Good Stories: How to Use the Elements of Narrative to Keep Listeners Engaged | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030070/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030070/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Make them want to turn the page,” says Paula Moya, a professor at Stanford University and author of The Social Imperative: Race, Close Reading, and Contemporary Literary Criticism.&amp;nbsp;
In this episode of Think Fast, Talk Smart, Moya sits down with strategic communication lecturer Matt Abrahams to share how the elements of story can be used in other types of communication. Create compelling situations, full of sense and surprise, she says.</description></item><item><title>49. Make Numbers Count: How to Communicate Data Effectively | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030071/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030071/</guid><description>Podcast Description “We have to make data emotional because emotions are what drive us to act,” says&amp;nbsp;Chip Heath, a professor of organizational behavior and author of the new book,&amp;nbsp;Making Numbers Count: The Art of Science of Communicating Numbers. In this interview with podcast host Matt Abrahams, Heath talks about ways that data and statistics can be used to illuminate — or obscure — our message.&amp;nbsp;“A lot of people in the world don’t understand numbers like the numbers people,” he says.</description></item><item><title>48. Speaking Up Without Freaking Out: How to Tackle Communication Anxiety | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030072/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030072/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Eighty five percent of people report being nervous about speaking in public, and I believe the other 15% are lying,” says Matt Abrahams, lecturer in Strategic Communication and podcast host.&amp;nbsp;“What is it about speaking in front of others that makes most of us nervous? Well, those of us who study this ubiquitous fear believe it is part of our human condition.”&amp;nbsp;
In this special episode of&amp;nbsp;Think Fast, Talk Smart,&amp;nbsp;Matt Abrahams returns to one of the podcast's main goals: helping people become more confident communicators.</description></item><item><title>47. Quick Thinks: How to Use Storytelling to Be a Better Founder | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030073/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 01:24:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030073/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Great founders are great storytellers,” says Stanford Graduate School of Business professor Stephanos Zenios in this “Quick Thinks” episode. Zenios is the director of the Center for Entrepreneurial Studies and heads Startup Garage, a project-based course where teams design and test business concepts that address real-world problems. “Founders have to tell a story to their customer so that they can inspire them to test and use their new product.</description></item><item><title>46. Stay Creative: How to Keep Your Ideas Fresh and Practical | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030074/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030074/</guid><description>Podcast Description “To be creative, ideas must be both novel and useful. That’s the definition that we use in creativity research,” says Justin Berg, an assistant professor of organizational behavior at Stanford Graduate School of Business. But, he warns: “Novel ideas are often not very useful and useful ideas are often not very novel.”
In this episode of Think Fast, Talk Smart, Berg sits down with lecturer and podcast host Matt Abrahams to share lessons from his work on creativity, which has included conducting experiments with both movie directors and circus performers.</description></item><item><title>45. Recipes From the “Communication Kitchen”: How to Handle Three Common Challenges This Holiday Season | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030075/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030075/</guid><description>Podcast Description In each episode of Think Fast, Talk Smart, Stanford GSB lecturer and podcast host&amp;nbsp;Matt Abrahams&amp;nbsp;asks his guests the same question: “What are the first three ingredients in a successful communication recipe?” Answers have ranged from specific and poetic, to impactful and thought-provoking. In this episode, we bring you some favorite responses, as well as Matt’s tips for solving three common communication challenges that tend to arise during the holiday season.</description></item><item><title>44. Act Like a Leader: How Lessons From The Theater Can Help You Step into Power | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030076/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030076/</guid><description>Podcast Description "Leadership is a role that you play, like a part you play in other people’s lives. And [your] expression of that role is your responsibility as a leader,” says Stanford GSB lecturer Melissa Jones Briggs. Jones Briggs’ work combines techniques from the theater with social science research to teach lessons about power and communication. In this conversation with podcast host Matt Abrahams, she discusses how acting in a leadership position requires staying present and also knowing when to step back.</description></item><item><title>43. Get Psyched: How Time and Situations Shape Our Communication | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030077/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 16:06:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030077/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Social psychologists believe that if we want to understand our own behavior and the behavior of others, the first thing we have to ask or notice is, ‘What is the situation in which they are performing, in which they are behaving?’ And then we want to know as much about the situation as possible.”
In this episode of&amp;nbsp;Think Fast, Talk Smart, Stanford emeritus psychology professor&amp;nbsp;Phillip Zimbardo&amp;nbsp;sits down with host Matt Abrahams to discuss how time influences our perception and our positive or negative thought processes.</description></item><item><title>42. Space, Pace, and Grace: How to Handle Challenging Conversations | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030078/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Being a better listener has a lot to do with silence, says Collins Dobbs, a lecturer in management at Stanford Graduate School of Business. “A lot of people are uncomfortable with the smallest modicum of silence, but learning often happens when we create distance for useful reflection.”
In this episode of&amp;nbsp;Think Fast, Talk Smart,&amp;nbsp;Dobbs talks with host Matt Abrahams about the importance of “space, pace, and grace” when you’re receiving others’ feedback and handling the emotions that come out during tough discussions.</description></item><item><title>41. Speak like a Founder: How Successful Entrepreneurs Communicate to Their Teams | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030079/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030079/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Part of teamwork is dating,” says Stefanos Zenios, The Investment Group of Santa Barbara Professor of Entrepreneurship and Professor of Operations, Information &amp;amp; Technology. “Dating each other to see whether you can work well together. It’s about developing how you will speak with each other in the team, how you will manage difficult conversations, and how to be respectful, but also how to help each other grow.”&amp;nbsp;
In this episode of Think Fast, Talk Smart, host Matt Abrahams sits down with Professor Zenios to hear more about the methods shared in the Stanford GSB project-based course Startup Garage.</description></item><item><title>40. Mindset Matters: How to Embrace the Benefits of Stress | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030080/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030080/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Stress is natural, stress is inevitable when you're living a life that's connected with things you care about. And learning how to embrace it, learning how to work with it is really what helps us thrive and grow and perform at our highest level, according to psychologist and associate professor at Stanford, Alia Crum.&amp;nbsp;
In this podcast episode, Crum talks with host and lecturer Matt Abrahams about her research and findings as principal investigator of the Stanford Mind and Body Lab where she is focusing on reshaping our mindset to embrace stress.</description></item><item><title>39. Brains Love Stories: How Leveraging Neuroscience Can Capture People's Emotions | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030081/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030081/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of&amp;nbsp;Think Fast, Talk Smart, lecturer and podcast host Matt Abrahams sits down with&amp;nbsp;David Eagleman, a neuroscientist and the host of the PBS series&amp;nbsp;The Brain, to discuss why our brains are wired for storytelling and how new senses might impact our connection and communication with others.&amp;nbsp;“I’ve always been really interested in this idea of how we can pass information to the brain via unusual channels," Eagleman says.</description></item><item><title>38. The New Normal: How Hybrid Work Actually Works | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030082/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030082/</guid><description>Podcast Description “One of the things I think is really exciting about all this, and perhaps a little bit frightening, is nobody actually knows how to do it. It is not something that we’ve ever done before. And I’ve studied a lot of globally distributed work, and virtual teams, and so forth. But hybrid work is not that and it’s not telecommuting, which we know a bit about. But it’s something that is a mix of these multiple different modes of working,” says Pamela Hinds, Fortinet Founders Chair and professor of management science and engineering at Stanford University.</description></item><item><title>37. Be Better: How Communication Catalyzes Business Transformation | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030083/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030083/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Think Fast, Talk Smart, Stanford GSB Lecturer Robert Siegel&amp;nbsp;sits down with Matt Abrahams to discuss the role of communication in helping businesses to adapt and transform and his new book The Brains and Brawn Company: How Leading Organizations Blend the Best of Digital and Physical Specifically.&amp;nbsp;“You have to see how things are interacting with each other. You have to see how your organization is interacting both internally and externally.</description></item><item><title>36. Perfecting Teamwork: Building High-Performing Teams By Encouraging Learning | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030084/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030084/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Think Fast, Talk Smart, Sara Singer, a professor of organizational behavior (by courtesy) at Stanford Graduate School of Business and a professor of medicine at Stanford School of Medicine, sits down with lecturer Matt Abrahams to discuss the role of open communication in high-performing teams. “Learning requires leadership that reinforces learning, a supportive environment, including especially psychological safety, but also an appreciation for differences when you’re working with people of lots of different backgrounds, and openness to new ideas,” she says.</description></item><item><title>35. Leading From The Hot Seat: How To Communicate Under Pressure | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030085/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 01:53:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030085/</guid><description>Podcast Description “I say sometimes that leadership is a journey into yourself. It’s self-renewal, self-reflection,&amp;nbsp;self-confidence. It’s going to bed kind of scratching your head and saying, “Man, I’m not as&amp;nbsp;good,” and waking up the next morning and trying it again — and I think that’s what matters.”&amp;nbsp;In this episode of Think Fast, Talk Smart, former CEO of General Electric and Stanford Graduate School of Business lecturer&amp;nbsp;Jeff Immelt&amp;nbsp;sits down with lecturer Matt Abrahams to discuss communicating during times of challenge and pressure.</description></item><item><title>34. How We Gain — Or Give Away — Authority While Speaking | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030086/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030086/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Simple language, forceful language, vivid language, and keeping it simple and direct,” says Professor Jeffrey Pfeffer, are all tools to increase the strength of your communication. In this episode of&amp;nbsp;Think Fast, Talk Smart,&amp;nbsp;host and lecturer Matt Abrahams interviews Jeffrey Pfeffer, author of&amp;nbsp;Dying for a Paycheck,&amp;nbsp;about the verbal and nonverbal ways we can harness, or give away, our authority in communication.&amp;nbsp;
To hear more from Jeffrey, listen to Pfeffer on Power, a podcast about accelerating your career.</description></item><item><title>33. Hacking your Speaking Anxiety: How Lessons from Neuroscience Can Help You Communicate Confidently. | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030087/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030087/</guid><description>Podcast Description “There’s no difference between the physiological response to something that you’re excited about and something that you’re nervous about or dreading,” says Andrew Huberman, associate professor of neurobiology and ophthalmology at Stanford University. In this podcast episode, Huberman talks with host and lecturer Matt Abrahams about his research on the autonomic continuum,&amp;nbsp;a spectrum between states of very high alertness or fear, all the way down to deep sleep, and shares how to better-use the system to your advantage.</description></item><item><title>32. Speech That Empowers: How to Encourage Growth and Resilience in a Younger Audience | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030088/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 17:20:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030088/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Communication is such a delicate dance and kids need to emerge from childhood having practiced,” says Julie Lythcott-Haims, former associate vice provost of undergraduate education Stanford University.&amp;nbsp;
In this episode of Think Fast, Talk Smart, lecturer and podcast host Matt Abrahams sits down with Lythcott-Haims to discuss her new book, Your Turn: How to be an Adult, and ideas on how to communicate with young people so they feel empowered to take on the various (and often intimidating) duties of adulthood.</description></item><item><title>31. Quick Thinks: How to Shine Online and Excel at Virtual Communication | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030089/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030089/</guid><description>Podcast Description It has been over a year since millions of people have switched from office work to working from home. In this episode of Think Fast, Talk Smart, lecturer and host Matt Abrahams highlights guests’ top takeaways on how to best communicate, share information, and cultivate a professional presence though the screen.&amp;nbsp;
“I think we have to find ways to reduce cognitive overload,” says Professor and Senior Associate Dean Sarah Soule.</description></item><item><title>30. Dissolve Disagreements: How Communication Impacts Conflict | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030090/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030090/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Communication, conflict, and cooperation are intertwined in a multitude of ways,” says&amp;nbsp;Nir Halevy, associate professor of organizational behavior at Stanford Graduate School of Business. In this episode of Think Fast, Talk Smart, Halevy sits down with host and lecturer Matt Abrahams, to discuss how we can often solve conflicts and disagreements by employing the correct strategy in our communication.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
“How you articulate a particular grievance, your choice of words, the nonverbal aspects of your claim, such as the tone of your voice, can definitely influence reactions to your claim,” Halevy says.</description></item><item><title>29. Question Everything: Why Curiosity Is Communication’s Secret Weapon | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030091/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030091/</guid><description>Podcast Description The information you receive is only as strong as the questions you ask. In this episode of&amp;nbsp;Think Fast, Talk Smart, Stanford Graduate School of Business lecturers Matt Abrahams and Debra Schifrin discuss how to craft inquiries that can lead to better communication outcomes. Questions are also instrumental in building relationships, Schifrin points out.&amp;nbsp;“If you’re asking questions, you’re signaling to the other person that you value them. You’re taking time to listen to their answers.</description></item><item><title>28. Building Strong Relationships: How to Effectively Communicate in Your Professional and Personal Life | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030092/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 22:29:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Recognizing the importance of forging connections with others — and learning how to build those bonds in real time — is the focus of a course that’s been the most popular elective at Stanford GSB for decades: Interpersonal Dynamics. The iconic course has taught thousands of students and professionals what it means to have exceptional relationships and how to interact with others in a way that contributes to deeper, stronger connections.</description></item><item><title>27. Psychology Trumps Technology: How to Be a Better Communicator on Social Media | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030093/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 22:55:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030093/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Psychology trumps technology,” says Jeff Hancock, founding director of the Stanford Social Media Lab and professor in the Department of Communication at Stanford.
“If you want to understand what's going on in social media, the first place to start is with what's going on psychologically.”
On the latest episode of *Think Fast, Talk Smart,* lecturer and podcast host Matt Abrahams sits down with Professor Hancock, to talk about the communication tendencies, styles, and mistakes of social media users.</description></item><item><title>26. Writing to Win: How to Quickly Capture Readers and Keep Them Engaged | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030094/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030094/</guid><description>Podcast Description “The reader is impatient,” says Glenn Kramon, Stanford GSB lecturer in management and editor at the New York Times. “Start with the most important conclusion and then explain how you got there.”
On the latest episode of Think Fast, Talk Smart, lecturer and podcast host Matt Abrahams sits down with Glenn Kramon to talk about just how important our writing is — from a lengthy report to the opening line of an email.</description></item><item><title>25. Quick Thinks: All Effective Communication Must Start With This | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030095/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030095/</guid><description>Podcast Description As we look back on more than 20 interviews with&amp;nbsp;Think Fast, Talk Smart&amp;nbsp;guests, we’ve heard one piece of advice over and again: Know Your Audience. This wisdom echoes what research clearly shows: Content that is relevant and meaningful to an audience is more likely to be heard, retained and acted upon.&amp;nbsp;
The word communication comes from the Latin for to “make common,” yet many of us start our message from the wrong place.</description></item><item><title>24. Feelings First: How emotion shapes our communication, decisions, and experiences | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030096/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 20:32:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030096/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Something like 90 to 95% of our decisions and behaviors are constantly being shaped the non-consciously by emotional brain system.” In this episode of Think Fast, Talk Smart, Professor of Marketing Baba Shiv sits down with lecturer and host Matt Abrahams to share his research on how emotions affect our, and our audience’s, decision making.&amp;nbsp;
“You’ve got to pay careful attention to the audience that you’re talking to and allow the person to talk,” Shiv says.</description></item><item><title>23. Look Within: How to Lead with Self Awareness and Vulnerability | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030097/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 21:29:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030097/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Effective is being able to achieve your goals, which is important, but there are plenty of people who achieve their goals that most of us would find unworthy. So the question what does it take to be a good leader requires you to reflect on the values that you hold dear.”
In this episode of *Think Fast, Talk Smart*,&amp;nbsp;Senior Associate Dean and Professor of Organizational Behavior Brian Lowery sits down with lecturer and host Matt Abrahams to discuss the importance of self inquiry and an examination of one's own values in order to be effectively communicate and lead.</description></item><item><title>22. Under Pressure: How to Communicate Clearly and Timely During a Crisis | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030098/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 21:20:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030098/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Knowing your values gives you a beacon, or a lamppost, that can inform how you’re going to prioritize your actions.”&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
In this episode of Think Fast, Talk Smart, Stanford Graduate School of Business lecturer and Stanford University’s former Vice President of Public Affairs David Demarest speaks with host and lecturer Matt Abrahams on why knowing your values and the concerns of your stakeholders lays the foundation for any communication during a time of crisis.</description></item><item><title>21. Words Matter: How to Make Your Communication Inclusive | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030099/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2020 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030099/</guid><description>Podcast Description What way can the language we use reinforce existing stereotypes and biases? In this episode of Think Fast, Talk Smart, Sarah Soule, Senior Associate Dean and Professor of Organizational Behavior sits down with lecturer and host Matt Abrahams to discuss how even the details of our word choice can shape culture, for better or worse.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Think Fast, Talk Smart is a podcast produced by Stanford Graduate School of Business.</description></item><item><title>20. Question Your Questions: How to Spark Creativity in Your Communication | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030100/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030100/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Sparking communication starts with asking why or what or how.” On this episode of Think Fast, Talk Smart, Tina Seelig, the Professor of the Practice in Stanford’s department of Management Science and Engineering, sits down with podcast host and lecturer Matt Abrahams to talk about the structures of storytelling that will help become more creative communicators and the importance of asking questions about everything we do.&amp;nbsp;
“Having a mindset of curiosity opens the door to great communication,” Seelig says.</description></item><item><title>19. Showing Your Smile From Behind a Mask: How Culture and Emotion Impact Communication | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030101/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030101/</guid><description>Podcast Description “In companies, you’re interacting with other people who come from different cultural contexts, and in order to be effective, you have to understand how much of your own communication and other people’s communication is shaped by their cultural ideas and their cultural values.”&amp;nbsp;On this episode of Think Fast, Talk Smart, host Matt Abrahams sits down with Jeanne Tsai, an associate professor of Psychology at Stanford and director of the Culture and Emotion Lab.</description></item><item><title>18. Managing in the Moment: How to Get Comfortable with Being Uncomfortable | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030102/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030102/</guid><description>Podcast Description “The less time you can spend dwelling on your mistakes, the more mental energy you can devote to doing what you need to do in that moment.” On this episode of Think Fast, Talk Smart, Christian Wheeler, the StrataComm Professor of Management and Professor of Marketing at Stanford Graduate School Business, sits down with podcast host and lecturer Matt Abrahams to talk about embracing failure and managing your team in-the-moment.</description></item><item><title>17. Think Fast: You Asked, We Answered | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030103/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030103/</guid><description>Podcast Description We asked listeners to send in their communication conundrums and ended up with an inbox full of thoughtful, specific questions.&amp;nbsp;
In this episode of Think Fast, Talk Smart, host and Stanford GSB lecturer Matt Abrahams is joined by Shawon Jackon, MBA ’21, to share techniques on crafting written responses, dealing with constant interruptions, and confronting the power dynamics present in most communication. Shawon is the founder of Our Voices Matter, a public speaking program for high school students of color and a dual-degree student between Stanford GSB and Harvard Kennedy School.</description></item><item><title>16. Quick Think: How to Craft Your Body Language When Confronting Objections | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030104/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 17:18:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Knowing what to say to a skeptical audience is paramount, but how can your body language communicate empathy, openness, and power?&amp;nbsp;
In this “Quick Think” episode of Think Fast, Talk Smart, we revisit Matt Abrahams’s conversation with Stanford GSB lecturer Burt Alper about how to keep body language in mind when it comes to handling objections.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Think Fast, Talk Smart&amp;nbsp;is a podcast produced by Stanford Graduate School of Business and hosted by Matt Abrahams.</description></item><item><title>15. The Art of Negotiation: How to Get More of What You Want | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030105/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Whether we realize it or not, we negotiate everyday. But when we approach these situations as a win-or-lose battle, we’re already showing resistance, and setting ourselves up for difficulty.&amp;nbsp;But what if you reframed the whole idea, to think of a negotiation not as a fight, but as a problem-solving exercise involving emotions?
In this episode of Think Fast, Talk Smart Matt&amp;nbsp;Abrahams&amp;nbsp;speaks with Stanford GSB Professor emeritus Maggie Neale (and author of Getting More of What You Want: How the Secrets of Economics and Psychology Can Help You Negotiate Anything, in Business and in Life) about what she has learned in her decades of researching negotiation and the steps that lead to more collaborative problem solving.</description></item><item><title>14. Be Better At Work: How to Communicate Better With Coworkers and Employees | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030106/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Most of the work we do requires coordinating and collaborating with others. But how can we ensure the benefits of working with others, while avoiding conflict that’s inherent to communicating within groups?
In this podcast episode, Matt Abrahams speaks with Bob Sutton, Professor of Management Science and Engineering at Stanford School of Engineering and GSB Professor of Organizational Behavior (by courtesy) about maximizing productivity while minimizing what he calls “friction.</description></item><item><title>13. Make ’Em Laugh: How to Use Humor as a Secret Weapon in Your Communication | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030107/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Humor does more than just make people laugh. It allows you to connect with your audience, diffuse tension, elevate status, and compel others to your point of view. Humor can also help you and your message stand out, yet most of us hesitate to use humor, especially in our professional lives.
In this episode of Think Fast, Talk Smart, Matt Abrahams speaks with Stanford GSB Professor Jennifer Aaker and Lecturer Naomi Bagdonas about when and how humor operates in the work place.</description></item><item><title>12. It's Not What You Say, It’s How You Say It: How To Communicate Power | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030108/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Power exists in every relationship — whether we like that idea or not — and to be effective in any role, power needs to be understood.&amp;nbsp;
In this episode, Matt Abrahams sits down with Professor of Organizational Behavior Deborah Gruenfeld to discuss her new book, Acting with Power: Why We Are More Powerful Than We Believe. Deborah shares how body language can give us power, or take it from us, and advises how we can use power for good.</description></item><item><title>11. The Science of Influence: How to Persuade Others And Hold Their Attention | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030109/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030109/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re constantly bombarded with competing images, messaging, and bids for our attention. That's why as communicators, it’s increasingly important to know what engages people.
In this episode of Think Fast, Talk Smart, Matt Abrahams speaks with Stanford GSB Professor Zak Tormala about the subtle ways you can structure your speech to get people to pay attention. “It’s not really about tricking people into doing what you want,” Professor Tormala says.</description></item><item><title>10. High-Stakes Communication: How to Manage Anxiety When Speaking in Front of Others | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030110/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Most people feel nervous in situations such as speaking in front of a class, pitching a big idea, or giving a toast, yet research-backed techniques can help manage both the symptoms and sources of our speaking jitters.
Matt Abrahams sits in the interviewee chair for this episode and talks with the podcast's producer, Jenny Luna, to share his backstory with public speaking anxiety and how by recognizing the causes of our nervousness, and applying mitigating techniques, we can gain confidence in our communication.</description></item><item><title>9. Quick Think: How Being Present-Oriented Improves Communication | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030111/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Although it may feel counter intuitive, letting go of our prepared notes and focusing on the present can help us communicate more effectively.
In this "Quick Thinks" podcast episode, host Matt Abrahams speaks with Stanford University lecturers and improv theater experts Dan Klein and Adam Tobin on how staying in the moment allows communicators to connect with their audience.&amp;nbsp;
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>8. Don't Get Lost in Translation: How Non-Native Speakers Can Communicate With Confidence | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030112/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Having to communicate in a language other than our native tongue can be quite a challenge. In this podcast episode, host Matt Abrahams speaks with Ken Romeo, the Associate Director for the Stanford Language Center, on specific tactics and approaches non-native speakers can use to prepare for speeches or presentations. Ken also shares advice on how to handle in-the-moment challenges, improve fluency, and let go of the need for perfection.</description></item><item><title>7. Quick Think: Use This Framework to Speak up in Virtual Meetings | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030113/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030113/</guid><description>Podcast Description We've all been in the situation where you have something important to contribute to a meeting and you don't know how to insert your thoughts.&amp;nbsp;On this "Quick Thinks" episode of Think Fast, Talk Smart, podcast host Matt Abrahams offers the three ways to insert your ideas, either by paraphrasing, asking a question, or stating an emotion. He also outlines the "What, So What, Now What" framework and explains how to use this structure to communicate your ideas more effectively.</description></item><item><title>6. Quick Think: Communicating and Leading Virtually | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030114/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 20:57:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Leading successful meetings remotely and being a strong speaker on-screen require specific skills.&amp;nbsp;Communicating effectively&amp;nbsp;has to do with your presence, ability to leverage tools, and your audience engagement.&amp;nbsp;In this Quick Thinks episode, Stanford GSB Strategic Communications lecturer Matt Abrahams shares best practices for becoming a more effective and engaging online communicator. &amp;nbsp;
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>5. From Monologue to Dialogue: How to Handle a Skeptical Audience | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030115/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Preparing to speak in front of a skeptical audience is more than thinking about objections beforehand – there are specific techniques you can use to respond to these challenging situations without sounding defensive, evasive, or dismissive. Here, we offer a few key tips for how to handle skepticism with aplomb.
In this podcast, host Matt Abrahams and Stanford GSB lecturer Bert Alper share how to prepare for these challenges from your audience and discuss the importance of tactics like acknowledging audience input, reframing responses, and how to remain cool, collected, and credible.</description></item><item><title>4. The Journey to Mastery: How Self Reflection Can Improve Communication | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030116/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030116/</guid><description>Podcast Description What does it mean to truly master communication? How can we speak and write for the most impact? In this podcast episode of&amp;nbsp;Think Fast, Talk Smart,&amp;nbsp;Stanford Graduate School of Business lecturers JD Schramm and Matt Abrahams discuss how to use self reflection for self improvement. They also offer methods for preparing for a high stakes situation such as a pitch meeting or an everyday interaction like an email.&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>3. When Knowing Too Much Can Hurt Your Communication: How to Make Complex Ideas Accessible | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030117/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030117/</guid><description>Podcast Description As communicators, we often need to take complex information&amp;nbsp;(e.g., financial, technical, or scientific)&amp;nbsp;and make it more understandable for our audience – we’re experts and they likely aren’t. But having so much knowledge on the topics we discuss can often make the job more difficult: we dive in too quickly,&amp;nbsp;forget about our audience's needs,&amp;nbsp;or use jargon that goes over their heads.&amp;nbsp;
In this episode of&amp;nbsp;Think Fast, Talk Smart, strategic communications lecturers Matt Abrahams and Lauren Weinstein explore the “curse of knowledge” and offer specific techniques you can use to be more successful in getting your point across.</description></item><item><title>2. Communicating Our Multiple Selves: How to Effectively Manage Your Reputation | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030118/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030118/</guid><description>Podcast Description How others perceive us in person and via social media can impact our careers and social standing. But we can build the reputation we want through conscious communication. On this podcast episode, strategic communication lecturers Matt Abrahams and Allison Kluger share techniques on effectively improving and managing your reputation.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>1. Speaking Without a Net: How to Master Impromptu Communication | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030119/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Most professional communication is spontaneous in nature: it’s providing feedback in the moment, answering questions, introducing people. On this podcast episode, Strategic Communication lecturer Matt Abrahams speaks with Stanford lecturers Adam Tobin and Dan Klein on how to become more comfortable and confident in in-the-moment speaking situations. Think Fast, Talk Smart is produced by Stanford Graduate School of Business. See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Introducing Think Fast, Talk Smart: The Podcast | Think Fast, Talk Smart: Communication Techniques</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2434030120/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 17:55:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2434030120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join Matt Abrahams, lecturer in strategic communication at Stanford Graduate School of Business, as he sits down with experts from across campus to discuss public speaking anxiety, speaking off the cuff, nailing a Q&amp;amp;A, and more.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>