<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Kurzgesagt on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/tags/kurzgesagt/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Kurzgesagt on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 15:29:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/kurzgesagt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/el/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 15:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/el/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Βίντεο Αποσπάσματα ﻿Οἱ ἄνθρωποι ὑπάρχουν ἐδῶ καὶ ἐκατομμύρια ἔτη, ὡς μέρος τῆς φύσεως.
Ἀλλὰ μετά, κάτι ἄλλαξε. Καὶ σὲ ἕνα πολὺ μικρὸ χρονικὸ διάστημα,
γαιοποιήσαμε αὐτὸν τὸν πλανήτη καὶ τὸν σχεδιάσαμε σύμφωνα μὲ τὶς ἀνάγκες μὰς.
Ἀπὸ ὅσο γνωρίζουμε, εἴμαστε τὸ πρῶτο εἴδος ποὺ ἀφυπνίστηκε καὶ κατέλαβε ἐντελῶς ἕναν πλανήτη.
Ἡ μετάβαση ἀπὸ τὸ κυνῆγι καὶ τὴν συλλογὴ τροφῆς, στὴν γεωργία καὶ τὴν δόμηση, ἦταν τόσο τρομακτικὰ
γρήγορη, ὥστε ὁ τρόπος ποὺ σκεπτόμαστε γιὰ κάποια πράγματα δὲν εἶναι πλέον χρήσιμος.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/id/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 14:59:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/id/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripsi ﻿Manusia telah ada selama jutaan tahun, sebagai bagian dari alam.
Tapi kemudian, sesuatu berubah. Dan dalam jumlah yang sangat singkat,
&amp;hellip;kita mengubah planet ini dan dirancang agar sesuai dengan kebutuhan kita.
Sejauh yang kita tahu, kita adalah makhluk pertama untuk membangkitkan dan benar-benar mengambil alih planet.
Peralihan dari berburu dan mengumpulkan, menuju pertanian dan membangun, begitu cepat, sehingga banyak dari cara kita berpikir tentang dunia yang tidak lagi berguna.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/sr/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 13:37:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/sr/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Видео Транскрипт ﻿Људи постоје, као део природе, милионима година.
Али се онда нешто променило. И за невероватно кратко време
смо тераформитрали планету и дизајнирали је да одговара нашим потребама.
Колико знамо, ми смо прва бића која су пробудила и комплетно освојила планету.
Транзиција од лова и сакупљања до земљорадње и изградње је била толико брза,
да многи од наших погледа на свет више нам нису корисни
Једна од наших најзастарелијих идеја је та да, најчешће коришћени календар на планети</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/lt/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 12:59:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/lt/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripcija ﻿Žmonės, kaip gamtos dalis, egzistavo milijonus metų.
Bet tada kai kas pasikeitė. Ir per neįtikėtinai trumpą laiko tarpą.
Mes pakeitėme šią planetą ir pritaikėme ją savo reikmėms.
Kiek žinome, mes esame pirmosios būtybės įgavusios sąmonę ir visiškai perėmusios planetą į savo rankas.
Perėjimas nuo medžioklės ir maisto rinkimo iki ūkininkystės bei statybos buvo toks beprotiškai greitas, jog didelė dalis to, kaip mes suvokėme pasaulį, neteko prasmės.
Tai, jog dauguma plačiausiai naudojamų kalendorių teigia, jog mes gyvename 2016-taisiais metais, yra viena iš labiausiai atgyvenusių mūsų idėjų.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/hr/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 12:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/hr/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripcija ﻿Ljudi su postojali milijunima godina, kao dio prirode.
Ali onda, nešto se promijenilo. I u nevjerojatno kratkom vremenu
oblikovali smo ovaj planet i dizajnirali ga kako bi odgovarao našim potrebama.
Koliko nam je poznato, mi smo prva bića koja su se probudila i i potpuno preuzeli planet.
Prijelaz iz lova i sakupljanja, na uzgoj i građenje, bio je tako zapanjujuće brz da mnogi od naših načina razmišljanja o svijetu više nisu korisni.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ar/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 11:22:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ar/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>فيديو نص ﻿تواجد البشر كجزء من الطبيعة لملايين من السنين.
ولكن , حدث تغيير في وقت قصير بشكل مذهل.
لقد اخضعنا الكوكب وصممناه ليكون مناسبًا لاحتياجاتنا.
وبقدر ما نعرف , نحن اول كائنات تستعمر وتسود كوكبًا.
وكان الانتقال من الصيد والحصاد الى البناء والزراعه سريعًا جدًا مما جعل بعض افكارنا عن العالم لا قيمه لها.
واحدة من اكثر الافكار التى عفا عليها الزمن أن التقويم الاكثر استخدامًا يُصر أننا نعيش في العام 2016.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/de/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 11:07:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/de/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkript ﻿Menschen existieren jetzt seit Millionen von Jahren, als ein Teil der Natur, &amp;hellip;
&amp;hellip; doch dann hat sich etwas geändert &amp;hellip;
&amp;hellip; und in einer unglaublich kurzen Zeit haben wir diesen Planeten umgebaut, sodass er unseren Bedürfnissen entspricht.
Soweit wir wissen, sind wir die ersten Wesen, die einen Planeten komplett übernommen haben.
Der Übergang vom Jagen und Sammeln zur Landwirtschaft und Baukunst &amp;hellip;
&amp;hellip; war so unglaublich schnell, dass viele Wege über unsere Welt zu denken nicht länger von Nutzen sind.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/sk/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 10:18:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/sk/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Prepis ﻿Ľudia existujú už milióny rokov
ako súčasť prírody.
Ale potom sa niečo zmenilo
a v neuveriteľne krátkom čase
sme premenili túto planétu
a nadizajnovali ju aby odpovedala našim potrebám.
Zatiaľ podľa toho čo vieme sme prvé bytosti ktoré sa prebudili a úplne osídlili planétu
Zmena od lovu a zberu k farmárčeniu a stavaniu bola tak neuveriteľne rýchla, že
veľa našich myšlienok o svete sú už nepoužiteľné
Jedna z našich najzastaralejších myšlienok</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/et/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 10:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/et/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkriptsioon ﻿Inimesed on olnud looduse osa miljoneid aastaid.
Aga siis muutus midagi ja uskumatult lühikese ajaga
kujundasime selle planeedi ümber
ja kohandasime selle oma vajadustega.
Meile teadaolevalt oleme esimesed ärganud ja planeedi täielikult üle võtnud olendid.
Üleminek küttimiselt ja koriluselt põllundusele ja ehitamisele
oli nii hingematvalt kiire, et paljude meie arusaamadega maailma asjadest ei ole enam midagi peale hakata.
Üks meie kõige aegunumatest ideedest seisneb selles, et meie kõige enamkasutatavam kalender</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/fi/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 09:53:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/fi/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkriptio ﻿Ihmiset ovat olleet olemassa osana luontoa miljoonien vuosien ajan.
Mutta sitten jokin muuttui ja hämmästyttävän lyhyessä ajassa
me muokkasimme tämän planeetan
ja suunnittelimme sen vastamaan tarpeitamme.
Omien tietojemme mukaan olemme ensimmäisen laji koskaan, joka on kyennyt ottamaan koko planeetan haltuunsa.
Muutos metsästäjä-keräilijäkulttuurista maanviljelyyn ja rakentamiseen oli niin nopea, että monet ajattelutapamme maailmasta eivät ole enään käyttökelpoisia.
Yksi jälkeenjääneimmistä ideoistamme on se, että käytetyin kalenteri maailmassa väittää, että elämme vuotta 2016.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/fr/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 09:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/fr/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Vidéo Transcription ﻿Les humains ont existé dans la nature durant des millions d&amp;rsquo;années.
Mais ensuite, quelque chose a changé.
Et dans un laps de temps incroyablement court,
nous avons terraformé cette planète et l&amp;rsquo;avons modifiée pour répondre à nos besoins.
Pour autant que nous sachions, nous sommes les seuls êtres à nous réveiller et prendre le contrôle d&amp;rsquo;une planète entière.
La transition de chasse et cueillette à agriculture et construction fut si incroyablement rapide</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/es-es/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 07:58:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/es-es/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcripción ﻿Los humanos hemos existido en la naturaleza durante millones de años.
Pero un día algo cambió y en un periodo de tiempo increíblemente corto
terraformamos este planeta y lo diseñamos para adaptarlo a nuestras necesidades.
Que sepamos, somos la primera especie en despertar y controlar por completo un planeta.
Pasamos tan rápidamente de cazar y recolectar a sembrar y construir
que muchas de nuestras formas de ver el mundo ya no son útiles.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ms/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 07:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ms/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripsi ﻿Manusia telah wujud sejak berjuta-juta tahun, sebagai sebahagian daripada alam .
Kemudian, sesuatu berubah. Dalam masa yang amat singkat
kita mengubah planet ini dan merekanya untuk memenuhi keperluan kita.
Setakat yang kita tahu, kita makhluk pertama yang bangunkan dan mengambil alih sebuah planet.
Peralihan dari memburu dan mengumpul, ke pertanian dan bangunan, begitu cepat hingga kebanyakan cara kita berfikir tentang dunia tiada guna lagi.
Salah satu idea kita yang paling kolot ialah kalendar yang paling biasa digunakan di dunia menegaskan bahawa kita hidup pada tahun 2016.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/bg/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 07:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/bg/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Видео Транскрипция ﻿Хората са съществували милиони години като част от природата.
Но нещо се е променило. И за невероятно кратък период
сме изменили планетата, така че да подхожда на нуждите ни.
Доколкото знаем, сме първите същества, завладели напълно цяла планета.
Преминали сме от лов и събирачество към земеделие и строителство толкова бързо, че много от идеите ни за света вече не са полезни.
Една от най-остарелите ни идеи, е че най-широко разпространения календар в света гласи, че живеем в 2016-та година.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/tr/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 07:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/tr/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkript ﻿İnsanlar doğanın bir parçası olarak, milyonlarca yıldır var olmuştur.
Ama sonra bir şeyler değişti
ve inanılmaz derecede kısa bir sürede bu gezegeni şekillendirip ihtiyaçlarımıza uyacak şekilde tasarladık.
bildiğimiz kadarıyla gözü açılıp bir gezegeni fetheden ilk varlıklarız
avlanma ve toplamadan tarıma ve inşaya geçiş o kadar nefes kesici bir hızdaydı ki Dünya hakkında düşündüğümüz bir çok yol artık kullanılabilir değil
hükmü kalmamış fikirlerimizden biri çoğunlukla kullanılan takvim 2016&amp;rsquo;da yaşadığımıza ayak direr</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/ko/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 07:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/ko/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>비디오 대본 ﻿인류는 수 백만년 동안 자연의 일부로서 존재해 왔습니다. 하지만 그 이후, 무언가가 변했습니다. 믿기지 않을 만큼 짧은 시간동안 우리는 이 행성을 변화시</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/zh-hant/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 06:48:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/zh-hant/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>影片 文字稿 ﻿人類與大自然已經共處了數百萬年之久 但在極短的時間內，某些事發生了 人類改變了這顆星球，以符合我們的需求 就我們所知，人類是第一個覺醒</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/uk/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 06:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/uk/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Відео Транскрипція ﻿Мільйони років люди існували як частина природи.
Але потім щось змінилося. І за неймовірно короткий проміжок часу
Ми змінили лице цієї планети та пристосували її до наших потреб.
Наскільки нам відомо, ми є першими створіннями, які пробудилися та повністю заволоділи планетою.
Перехід від мисливства й збирання до землеробства та будівництва був настільки вражаюче швидким, що ми більше не можемо покладатись на наші уявлення про світ.
Одне з найбільш застарілих уявлень у тому, що за найрозповсюдженішим календарем світу ми нібито живемо у 2016 році.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/sv/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 05:37:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/sv/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkription ﻿Människor har funnits i miljontals år
som en del av naturen.
Men plötsligt ändrades något
och på väldigt kort tid terraformade vi planeten
och utformade den för att passa våra behov.
Så vitt vi vet är vi de första varelserna som totalt har tagit över en planet.
Övergången från jägare-samlare till jordbruk och byggande
var så otroligt snabb att många av våra tankesätt inte längre är användbara.
En av våra mest utdaterade idéer är att den mest använda kalendern idag insisterar att vi lever i år 2016.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/th/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 05:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/th/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>วิดีโอ สรุป ﻿มนุษย์มีชีวิตอยู่มานานนับล้านปี เป็นส่วนหนึ่งของธรรมชาติ
แต่แล้วเกิดการเปลี่ยนแปลง และในเวลาที่สั้นอย่างไม่น่าเชื่อ
เราปรับโลกใบนี้และออกแบบ เพื่อให้พอดีกับความต้องการของเรา
เท่าที่เรารู้ เรากำลังเป็นพวกแรกที่ตื่นรู้ และครองโลกอย่างสมบูรณ์
การเปลี่ยนแปลงจากการล่าสัตว์ และเกิดชุมชนเพื่อการเกษตรและสร้างบ้าน ก็เป็นไปอย่างรวดเร็ว
จนหลายอย่างที่เคยคิดเอาไว้เกี่ยวกับโลกนี้ ใช้ไม่ได้แล้ว
หนึ่งในความคิดที่ล้าสมัยที่สุดของเราคือ ปฏิทินที่ใช้มากที่สุดในโลกยืนยันว่าเรามีชีวิตอยู่ในปี 2016
มุมมองนี้บิดเบือนประวัติศาสตร์ของเราเอง และทำให้มันยากที่จะเข้าใจว่าเราเป็นใคร
และที่เรามาได้ไกลแค่ไหน ในเวลาที่สั้นอย่างไม่น่าเชื่อ
บางทีมันอาจจะถึงเวลาที่จะเลือกปีที่ 0 สำหรับมนุษยชาติ
ปี 0 ที่แท้จริงหมายถึงเราเป็นสายพันธุ์และรวมถึงทุกวัฒนธรรม
ปี 0 คือจุดที่เราเริ่มสร้างโลกใหม่ของเราทับโลกใบเก่า
12,000 ปีที่ผ่านมา มนุษย์หลายร้อยมารวมกัน อยู่ในภูเขาทางตอนใต้ของอนาโตเลีย
พวกเขาล่าสัตว์และเก็บของป่า ไม่มีความรู้ การเกษตรหรือการใช้โลหะ
ทั้งหมดที่พวกเขามีอยู่ คือ เครื่องมือที่ทำจากหินและไม้
แต่พวกเขาสร้างความเป็นมนุษย์อย่างแรก โครงการก่อสร้างขนาดใหญ่
7,000 ปีก่อนที่ปิรามิดที่ถูกสร้างขึ้นในอียิปต์
วงของเสาหินขนาดใหญ่ที่บรรพบุรุษของเราสร้างขึ้น กินเนื้อที่กว่า 300 เมตร
แต่ละอัน สูงถึง 6 เมตร และน้ำหนัก 40 ตัน
การตกแต่งด้วยศิลปะรูปสัญลักษณ์ และแกะสลักหินรูปสัตว์และสัตว์ในตำนาน
เราคิดไม่ออกว่า พวกเขาสามารถที่จะทำเช่นนี้
มันอาจจะเป็นโครงการขนาดใหญ่สำหรับยุคหิน ซึ่งต้องใช้ระดับงานแบบองค์กร เราไม่อาจรู้ได้
ว่ามนุษย์เริ่มแรกมีความสามารถนี้ จนเรามาพบสถานที่นี้
ดังนั้น ทำไมพวกเขาสร้างมัน?
ทฤษฎีที่นิยมมากที่สุด คือ นี้เป็นวัดแรกของมนุษยชาติที่อุทิศแด่พระเจ้าที่ถูกลืมมานาน</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/eo/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 05:20:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/eo/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transskribo ﻿Homo ekzistas dum milionoj da jaroj, kiel parto de naturo.
Sed tiam, io ŝanĝiĝis. Kaj dum ege mallonga kvanto de tempo,
ni teroformigis ĉi tiun planedon kaj desegnis ĝin por taŭgi niajn bezonojn.
Laŭ nia scio, ni estas la unuaj estaĵoj vekiĝi kaj tute transpreni planedon.
La transiĝo de ĉasado kaj kolektado, al farmado kaj konstruado, estis tiom senspirige rapida, ke multe da niaj manieroj de pensi pri la mondo ne plu estas utilaj.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/it/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 05:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/it/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Trascrizione ﻿L&amp;rsquo;uomo è esistito per milioni di anni, come parte della natura,
ma poi, qualcosa è cambiato
e in un tempo incredibilmente breve, abbiamo terraformato questo pianeta
e l&amp;rsquo;abbiamo progettato per soddisfare le nostre esigenze.
Per quanto ne sappiamo, siamo i primi esseri ad esserci risvegliati e ad aver preso il controllo completo di un pianeta.
Il passaggio da caccia e raccolta ad agricoltura e costruzioni, è stato così sorprendentemente veloce</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/nl/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 05:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/nl/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcriptie ﻿De mensheid bestaat al voor miljoenen jaren als een onderdeel van de natuur.
Maar toen veranderde iets. En in een heel erg korte tijd,
hebben we deze planeet geterraformeerd en ontworpen om onze benodigdheden te voldoen.
Voor hoever wij weten zijn wij het eerste ras die compleet zijn eigen planeet heeft overgenomen.
De verandering van jagen en bijeenkomen naar landbouw en bouwen, was zo adembenemend snel dat veel van onze manieren om over de wereld te denken niet langer van toepassing waren.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/pt-br/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 05:07:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/pt-br/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Vídeo Transcrição ﻿Os humanos existem há milhões de anos como parte da natureza,
mas então, algo mudou,
e em uma quantidade incrivelmente pequena de tempo nós terraformamos este planeta
e fizemos com que atendesse às nossas necessidades.
Até onde sabemos, somos os primeiros seres a acordar e tomar completamente um planeta.
A transição de caçar e coletar para plantar e construir foi tão impressionantemente rápida&amp;hellip;
&amp;hellip;que muitas de nossas maneiras de pensar no mundo não são mais úteis.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 04:19:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Humans have existed for millions of years, as part of nature.
But then, something changed. And in an incredibly short amount of time..
..We terraformed this planet and designed it to fit our needs.
As far as we know, we&amp;rsquo;re the first beings to awaken and completely take over a planet.
The transition from hunting and gathering to farming and building, was so breathtakingly fast,
that many of our ways of thinking about the world are no longer useful.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/he/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 04:17:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/he/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>וידאו טְק֡ס֙ט ﻿בני אדם היו קיימים במשך מיליוני שנים, כחלק מהטבע.
אבל אז, משהו השתנה, ובפרק זמן קצר ביותר
שינינו את העולם הזה והתאמנו אותו לצרכינו.
ככל שאנחנו יודעים, אנחנו היצורים הראשונים שקמו ולגמרי השתלטו על כוכב לכת.
המעבר מציד ואיסוף לחקלאות ובנייה, היה מהיר כל כך באופן עוצר נשימה שרוב הדרכים בהן חשבנו על העולם הן כבר לא מועילות.
אחד הרעיונות הכי מיושנים שלנו הוא שלוח השנה עם השימוש הכי נפוץ בעולם מתעקש שאנחנו חיים בשנת 2016.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/no/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 03:46:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/no/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripsjon ﻿Mennesket har eksistert i millioner av år som en del av naturen.
Men så skjedde det noe. I løpet av utrolig kort tid
terraformet vi planeten, og tilpasset den etter våte egne behov.
Så vidt vi vet, er vi den første arten som noen gang har fullstendig tatt over en planet.
Overgangen fra å være jegere og samlere, til å være bønder og byggmestere, skjedde så utrolig fort at mange av måtene vi fortsatt tenker på, ikke lenger er nyttige.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/tl/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 03:42:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/tl/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkripsyong ﻿Ang mga tao ay nagsimula noong milyong taong nagdaraan, bilang parte ng kapaligiran.
Pero noong panahon na iyon, may nag-iba. At sa isang sobrang madaling panahon&amp;hellip;
..binago natin ang mundong ito at dinisenyo ito upang magkasya ang aming mga pangangailangan.
Bilang malayo bilang alam namin, tayo ay ang unang nilalang na at ganap na kumuha ng higit sa isang planeta.
Ang paglipat mula sa pangangaso at pagtitipon sa pagsasaka at gusali, ay saksakan ng bilis,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/pl/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 03:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/pl/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transkrypcja ﻿Ludzie istnieli przez miliony lat jako część przyrody
lecz wtedy coś się zmieniło i w niezwykle krótkim okresie czasu
zmieniliśmy tę planetę i dostosowaliśmy ją do naszych potrzeb.
Z tego co nam wiadomo, jesteśmy jedynymi istotami, które &amp;ldquo;przebudziły się&amp;rdquo; i całkowicie zdominowały swoją planetę.
Przejście z łowiectwa i zbieractwa do rolnictwa i budownictwa nadeszło tak szybko,
że wiele sposobów myślenia o tym świecie okazuje się nieprzydatne
Jednym z naszych najmniej aktualnych pomysłów jest fakt, że według najczęściej używanego kalendarza żyjemy w roku 2016.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/es-419/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 02:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/es-419/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcripción ﻿Los humanos han existido por millones de años
como parte de la naturaleza
Pero luego algo cambió
Y en muy poco tiempo nosotros terraformamos este planeta
y lo diseñamos para satisfacer nuestras necesidades
hasta donde sabemos, somos los primeros seres en
despertarnos y tomar el control del planeta.
La transición de cazar y recolectar
a cultivar y construir, fue tan increíblemente rápida
que muchas de las maneras de pensar sobre el mundo ya no son útiles.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/pt-pt/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 02:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/pt-pt/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Vídeo Transcrição ﻿Os humanos existem por milhões de anos como parte da natureza,
mas então, algo mudou,
e em uma quantidade incrivelmente pequena de tempo nós terraformamos este planeta
e o desenhamos para que atendesse às nossas necessidades.
Até onde sabemos, somos os primeiros seres a acordar e tomar completamente um planeta.
A transição de caçar e coletar para plantar e construir foi tão impressionantemente rápida&amp;hellip;
&amp;hellip;que muitas de nossas maneiras de pensar no mundo não são mais úteis.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/bn/post/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 01:31:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/bn/post/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>ভিডিও ট্রান্সক্রিপ্ট ﻿মানুষ প্রকৃতির অংশ হিসাবে, কোটি কোটি বছর ধরে টিকে আছে.
কিন্তু তারপর, কিছু পরিবর্তন. এবং সময় একটি অবিশ্বাস্যভাবে স্বল্প পরিমাণ
আমরা এই গ্রহের terraformed এবং আমাদের চাহিদা মাপসই এটা পরিকল্পিত.
যতদুর আমরা জানি, আমরা প্রথম মানুষ জাগ্রত এবং সম্পূর্ণরূপে একটি গ্রহের উপর নিতে যাচ্ছেন
ট্রানজিশন শিকার ও জমায়েত থেকে, চাষাবাদ এবং ভবন, তাই breathtakingly দ্রুত যে বিশ্বের সম্পরকে আমাদের উপায়ে অনেক লোক আর দরকারী ছিল.
আমাদের সবচেয়ে সেকেলে ধারণা এক বিশ্বের মধ্যে সবচেয়ে বেশি ব্যবহৃত ক্যালেন্ডারের যে জোরাজুরি যে আমরা 2016 বছরের মধ্যে বাস</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
