<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Political Currency on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/political-currency/</link><description>Recent content in Political Currency on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 18:39:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/political-currency/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Keir Starmer’s popularity problem | Political Currency</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4523030001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 18:39:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4523030001/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s not just Rishi Sunak’s approval rating which has taken a battering. Keir Starmer has his own popularity problem. Why?
The so-called ‘five families’ of the Tory party threaten to “go to the mattresses” over the Rwanda bill, but end up bottling it. Is Mark Francois really the next Don Corleone?&amp;nbsp;
Ukraine’s President Zelensky has embarked on a world tour, pleading for more money for the Ukraine war. Is it time to rethink their strategy?</description></item><item><title>Tory shambles: Rwanda resignation and Boris at the Covid inquiry | Political Currency</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4523030002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 16:50:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4523030002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Another week… another meltdown for the Conservatives. Ed and George ask whether the Tory civil wars have been reignited by the rift over Rwanda and Robert Jenrick’s shock resignation. Is Sunak’s position weaker than ever?
Meanwhile former prime ministers haunt party leaders wherever they go. Boris Johnson is giving evidence at the Covid inquiry, painting a picture of chaos during his tenure. George shares his own theories about the dire state of Johnson’s personal finances.</description></item><item><title>Sunak's Greek Tragedy | Political Currency</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4523030003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 18:17:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4523030003/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Autumn Statement hasn’t delivered the stability and calm that Sunak and Hunt likely hoped for. A rift in the party over immigration, a chaotic Covid inquiry and to top it off, a diplomatic incident with the Greek PM over the Parthenon Sculptures. In a week where Sunak hoped his Global Investment Summit would grab the headlines, why are the Tories failing to land their message?
Meanwhile, it's reported Sunak rebuffed Cabinet Secretary Simon Case’s proposals to allow talks between the opposition and the Civil Service to begin.</description></item><item><title>Losing control of migration? | Political Currency</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4523030004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 17:22:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4523030004/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Autumn Statement continues to ripple through Westminster, and a new energy price cap puts the cost of living back into the spotlight. As the Chancellor continues his media rounds and Labour weighs in with their response, Ed and George share their experiences of the political traps set by big budget shakeups.&amp;nbsp;
Meanwhile, immigration is the big topic around the world today, as new migration figures are released in the UK, and elections are won in the Netherlands and Argentina over the issue.</description></item><item><title>HOT TAKE: The pre-election Autumn Statement? | Political Currency</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4523030005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 16:48:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4523030005/</guid><description>Podcast Description George and Ed react to Jeremy Hunt's Autumn Statement. Is he really the tax cutting Chancellor he's claiming to be, and are we on course for an early election? And we’ll be back again tomorrow with more detail on the Chancellor’s plans as the picture becomes clearer.
Email: questions@persephonica.com
Exec producer: Dino Sofos
Producer: Rachel Balmer
Production Manager: Flick Heath
Political Currency is a Persephonica Production and is part of the Acast Creator Network</description></item><item><title>Tories at war and a Labour rebellion | Political Currency</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4523030006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 18:53:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4523030006/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been a wild week in Westminster and it’s starting to look like the Tories are losing their grip. Ed and George chew over the Supreme Court’s judgment on Rwanda and what it means for Sunak. Could his new Foreign Secretary slam the brakes on some Tories’ hopes to leave the ECHR?
Meanwhile, Keir Starmer faced a huge rebellion of his MPs over the SNP’s ceasefire amendment. Ed explains why this isn’t as big a threat to the Labour leader as it first appears.</description></item><item><title>HOT TAKE: The Return of David Cameron | Political Currency</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4523030007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 15:34:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4523030007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rishi Sunak has finally sacked Suella Braverman, and the reshuffle has opened the door for the most unlikely return to politics: David Cameron.&amp;nbsp;
In our first HOT TAKE bonus episode, Ed Balls and George Osborne - his closest political friend - brings us the inside scoop on our new Foreign Secretary.
Email questions@politicalcurrency.co.uk
Follow us on social media: @polcurrency
Exec producers: Ellie Clifford and Dino Sofos
Producer: Rachel Balmer</description></item><item><title>How do you solve a problem like Suella? | Political Currency</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4523030008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 18:34:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4523030008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Suella Braverman has attacked the Met Police Chief’s decision to allow the pro-Palestine march this Saturday, putting Rishi Sunak in a tricky position. Ed asks George whether firing her is the only option.
Civil servants and ministers are currently scrambling around the Treasury to get everything ready for the upcoming Autumn Statement. All eyes will be on Jeremy Hunt: will he survive his big moment?
And Nadine Dorries’ book is out today, shedding light on the shadowy group she calls ‘the Movement’ operating at the heart of government.</description></item><item><title>The price of Johnson's toxic Downing Street culture | Political Currency</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4523030009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 20:32:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4523030009/</guid><description>Podcast Description It was Dominic Cummings' turn at the Covid inquiry this week and - as George predicted - we heard about the misogynistic language being used in Boris Johnson's Number 10. What does it reveal about the toxic culture operating in Westminster at that time? And why this isn't ancient history for the Tories.
Trouble is still brewing for Keir Starmer over his party's response to the Israel-Gaza conflict. Is his political authority in danger?</description></item><item><title>Disgusting Covid WhatsApps, Starmer’s Gaza dilemma and Sunak’s AI adviser | Political Currency</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4523030010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 19:19:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4523030010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Keir Starmer has shifted his position on Gaza. But he’s still not calling for a ceasefire. Has this incident been a wake up call for the Labour party? George Osborne reveals that we’ll be hearing about some “shocking and disgusting” messages sent by Boris Johnson and Dominic Cummings at the Covid inquiry next week. And we’re joined by Matt Clifford, Rishi Sunak’s representative for the AI Safety Summit. He’s warning of the need to avoid a “Three Mile Island” moment for AI.</description></item><item><title>Starmer’s Israel mis-step, by-elections and Covid angst | Political Currency</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4523030011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 18:25:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4523030011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Keir Starmer’s potentially got his party into hot water this week over his position on Israel’s right to defend herself - what should he do next? And what risk does it pose to Labour support in any upcoming elections?
Speaking of elections: As we await results of two by-elections, George and Ed give their predictions and share memories of outgoing Mid Bedfordshire MP Nadine Dorries.&amp;nbsp;
George has been giving evidence in the Covid-19 inquiry, which is back in session.</description></item><item><title>Israel-Gaza: What are Sunak and Starmer privately thinking? | Political Currency</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4523030012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 17:13:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4523030012/</guid><description>Podcast Description The violence between Israel and Gaza rages on. What are Rishi Sunak and Keir Starmer thinking behind the scenes in Westminster? And what does the conflict mean for the global economy?
Elsewhere, it was Labour’s turn to set our their stall at conference. Keir Starmer gave a glittering performance with housing at its core, and the ex-Bank Of England chief gave Rachel Reeves a glowing endorsement. But Ed and George both think there’s more to do to convince voters.</description></item><item><title>Is Sunak tearing the Tories apart? | Political Currency</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4523030013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 18:31:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4523030013/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's conference season and Ed and George aren't short of speeches to dissect. The Prime Minister has launched his new and improved radical Rishi persona this week - is it enough to save the Conservatives at the next election? And can it compete with the real talk of the conference - a certain Mr Farage spotted here there and everywhere?
Meanwhile, Labour are preparing to take to the stage for their own conference in Liverpool, with Rachel Reeves' hotly anticipated speech on Monday.</description></item><item><title>Suella, conference mayhem and a mystery turd... | Political Currency</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4523030014/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 17:51:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4523030014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Suella Braverman has caused a row this week after her controversial comments on Britain’s immigration policy. Ed and George argue over whether she took the right approach.&amp;nbsp;
The Conservative party prepares to head off to its conference. Why is this a critical moment for Prime Minister Rishi Sunak?
Is Manchester mayor Andy Burnham’s support for HS3 a gift to Sunak, and a disaster for HS2?
And why did George and David Cameron have to scoop a turd out of Rupert Murdoch’s pool?</description></item><item><title>Sunak cuts the ‘green crap’ | Political Currency</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4523030015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 18:47:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4523030015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is Boris Johnson the real target of Rishi Sunak’s rollback of green policies? George reveals there is a split in the Conservative party over rumours that the government will abandon its HS2 expansion. The Bank of England leaves interest rates unchanged - should we be surprised? And why we should be paying attention to the escalating row over the killing of a Sikh separatist on Canadian soil.
Email: questions@politicalcurrency.</description></item><item><title>HS2 in doubt, China spies and the triple lock | Political Currency</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4523030016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 18:22:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4523030016/</guid><description>Podcast Description As Jeremy Hunt scrambles for&amp;nbsp;pre-election tax cuts, the northern leg of HS2 is under threat and&amp;nbsp;pensioners are facing a smaller raise in&amp;nbsp;payments than they were expecting. Is the Chancellor making mistakes that will cost his&amp;nbsp;party an important support base? And pressure is mounting on Rishi Sunak over allegations of a Chinese spy in&amp;nbsp;parliament, but that's far from his only problem - with oil prices soaring, how can the Prime Minister make sure he keeps his inflation pledge?</description></item><item><title>Introducing... Political Currency | Political Currency</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4523030017/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 23:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4523030017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to Political Currency! Before we bring you our first episode this Thursday, 14th September, we thought we'd tell you what our podcast is all about.
Ed Balls and George Osborne will take you behind closed doors into the rooms where decisions are made. Having battled it out across the despatch box, the former Chancellor and shadow chancellor are now meeting in the studio to discuss the decisions that affect the nation’s pockets.</description></item></channel></rss>