<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The President's Daily Brief on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-presidents-daily-brief/</link><description>Recent content in The President's Daily Brief on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 20:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-presidents-daily-brief/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>PDB Afternoon Bulletin | December 18th, 2023: IDF’s Lethal Mistake &amp; Red Sea Task Force | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800338/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800338/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin: We delve into the heart-wrenching incident in northern Gaza, where a grave mistake by the IDF resulted in the death of three Israelis who were trying to surrender. This tragic event has placed the Netanyahu government under renewed scrutiny, prompting calls for the resumption of hostage negotiations. We explore the United States&amp;rsquo; forthcoming announcement of an international maritime task force. This initiative is designed to safeguard shipping vessels navigating the Red Sea, a critical commercial route under threat from Iranian-backed Houthi militants.</description></item><item><title>December 18th, 2023: Houthi Hostilities, Ballistic Brinkmanship, &amp; Antisemitic Attitudes | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800339/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800339/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: We discuss the intensification of hostilities in the Red Sea, with the U.S. and allies responding to drone attacks, signaling a potential shift toward a military response to the Houthi rebels. We cover North Korea&amp;rsquo;s latest provocation, as they test the waters with a new missile launch, escalating tensions in the region. We delve into Russia&amp;rsquo;s strategic moves, as they bolster their nuclear capabilities by deploying a new intercontinental ballistic missile with MIRV technology.</description></item><item><title>PDB Afternoon Bulletin | December 15th, 2023: EU Grants Ukraine Membership &amp; Venezuela Agrees To Keep The Peace | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800001/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800001/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin: European leaders managed to bypass Hungary and voted to open membership talks with Ukraine to join the European Union, despite failing to reach an agreement on additional financial and military aid.
Amid the ongoing territorial dispute in South America, the leaders of Venezuela and Guyana met at a neutral site on Thursday, signaling their intention to keep the tense situation peaceful.</description></item><item><title>December 15th, 2023: Hamas Plot Foiled, Ukraine Ultimatum, &amp; South Korea Scrambles | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800002/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800002/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: We start with the latest details on a major Hamas-linked terror attack foiled in Europe, showcasing the ongoing challenges in global security. A bold statement from Vladimir Putin: no peace in Ukraine until Russia&amp;rsquo;s objectives are achieved. Tension escalates as South Korea dispatches fighter jets in response to Russian and Chinese aircraft entering their air defense zone. In today’s Back of the Brief segment, we delve into the controversy surrounding Boston&amp;rsquo;s progressive Mayor, who faces criticism after her office issued a racially exclusive invitation for a holiday party.</description></item><item><title>PDB Afternoon Bulletin | December 14th, 2023: Hungary Holds EU Hostage &amp; Iran's Ominous Red Sea Warning | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 20:58:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800003/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin: A showdown is brewing in Brussels today between Hungary and their fellow European Union members, as tensions mount over whether to grant additional emergency aid to Ukraine and allow them to begin proceedings to join the EU.
Iran is threatening the U.S. over plans to establish an international maritime taskforce to protect shipping vessels in the Red Sea from Iranian-back Houthi militants, warning any efforts would face “extraordinary problems.</description></item><item><title>December 14th, 2023: Cash for Hamas, Gaza Tunnels Flooded, &amp; South Korea's Warning | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800004/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: A New York Times report unveils a decades-long strategy by the Israeli government, allegedly supporting Hamas in Gaza through substantial cash payments. Israel begins pumping seawater into the underground terror tunnels beneath Gaza. South Korea&amp;rsquo;s defense minister issues a dire warning to North Korea, following the abandonment of a pivotal 2018 military agreement, signaling potential severe repercussions. In our Back of the Brief segment, we delve into the latest development in the Hunter Biden controversy as the president’s son confronts Congressional inquiries with defiance.</description></item><item><title>PDB Afternoon Bulletin | December 13th, 2023: Russia's Decimated Military &amp; Biden Buckles On Border Policy | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 20:22:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800005/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin: A declassified U.S. intelligence report reveals that Russia has lost 87 percent of the ground troops that they began the war with, along with more than two-thirds of their armored tanks.
It appears President Joe Biden is willing to make major concessions on border policy to Republicans in Congress in an effort to convince lawmakers to pass an emergency aid package to Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>December 13th, 2023: Biden Blasts Bibi, Zelensky's Plea, &amp; Monarchy for Germany? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800006/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: We examine the emerging rift between the United States and Israel, with President Biden urging Israeli Prime Minister Netanyahu to reconsider his approach in Gaza amidst growing international concern. Ukrainian President Zelensky engages in a crucial plea for financial support from the U.S., signaling a pivotal moment for Ukraine. A new and deadly terror group emerges in Pakistan, claiming the lives of numerous police officers in a devastating attack.</description></item><item><title>PDB Afternoon Bulletin | December 12th, 2023: Biden Bypasses Deadlocked Congress &amp; Harvard's President Retains Power | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800007/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 20:13:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800007/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin: The Biden administration quietly bypassed a deadlocked Congress over the weekend to approve the sale of more than $100 million in tank ammunition to Israel for their war effort in Gaza.
Harvard has announced that they will not fire their current president despite mounting criticism over her widely condemned testimony last week on antisemitism.
Please remember to subscribe if you enjoyed this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin.</description></item><item><title>December 12th, 2023: Hamas Atrocities Exposed, Putin Critic Vanishes, &amp; South American Talks | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800008/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: A deep dive into the recent report by Israeli physicians documenting Hamas&amp;rsquo; sexual violence on October 7th, and the UN&amp;rsquo;s lackluster response. Just as Vladimir Putin announcement a fifth presidential term, we learn of the mysterious disappearance of his chief critic. A focus on the upcoming meeting between Guyana and Venezuela&amp;rsquo;s leaders, and the regional concerns over their ongoing territorial dispute.</description></item><item><title>PDB Afternoon Bulletin | December 11th, 2023: Zelensky's Final Plea &amp; Europe's Empty Arsenals | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800009/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 20:55:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800009/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin: Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky is traveling to Washington this week in an increasingly desperate bid to convince American leaders to extended emergency aid to his war-torn country.
There is growing alarm surrounding the diminished military stockpiles of our European allies, who have seen already sparse resources dry up in the face of Russia’s invasion of Ukraine.
Please remember to subscribe if you enjoyed this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin.</description></item><item><title>December 11th, 2023: Gaza Timeline, Putin For President, &amp; Tax Troubles For Hunter | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800010/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief:
We analyze Israel&amp;rsquo;s planned timeline for military operations in the Gaza Strip amidst rising tensions. Vladimir Putin positions himself for another presidential term, potentially extending his leadership in Russia until 2030. Hunter Biden is hit with new federal charges stemming from a Justice Department tax probe. And in our Back of the Brief segment, more fallout from the controversy surrounding university presidents&amp;rsquo; responses to antisemitism on campus.</description></item><item><title>PDB Afternoon Bulletin | December 8th, 2023: Iranian Proxies Hit US Embassy &amp; Backlash Mounts Against Ivy League Leaders | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800011/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 20:37:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800011/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin: Multiple mortars rained down on the U.S. embassy in Baghdad on Friday, in a sign that Iranian-backed militants are escalating their attacks on U.S. and coalition forces in the region.
MIT, Harvard and UPenn are facing national outrage after their presidents struggled to condemn widespread antisemitism on their campuses. As donors pull funds and calls for resignations mount, Congress is now launching an investigation into how these schools deal with the continued harassment of their Jewish communities.</description></item><item><title>December 8th, 2023: Article 99 Activated, Venezuela's Crackdown, &amp; Cyber-Security Breaches | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800012/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800012/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: UN Secretary-General Antonio Guterres invokes a rare power in the UN Charter in a strong move to push for a ceasefire in the Gaza conflict. As the situation in Venezuela escalates, we delve into the government&amp;rsquo;s latest actions against political dissidents and the rising border tensions with Guyana. The UK levels serious allegations against Russia&amp;rsquo;s Security Service, charging them with an extensive cyber-hacking campaign.</description></item><item><title>PDB Afternoon Bulletin | December 7th, 2023: Russian War Crimes &amp; Travel Ban On Israeli "Extremist Settlers" | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800013/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin: Prosecutors with the Justice Department charged four Russian troops with war crimes on Wednesday in a historic indictment aimed at holding the Putin regime accountable for the abduction and torture of an American citizen living in Ukraine.
The State Department has announced a travel ban on Israeli “extremist settlers” in the West Bank, who have been involved in deadly attacks on Palestinians in the region.</description></item><item><title>December 7th, 2023: Hamas Headhunt, Houthi Drone Dangers &amp; China's Cash Crunch | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800014/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800014/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief:
We analyze the latest military maneuvers in Gaza as the IDF intensifies efforts to capture two leading figures of Hamas.
The U.S. Navy intercepts yet a drone from Yemen aimed at an American warship as Saudi Arabia asks for restraint in dealing with Iran-Backed Houthi militants.
We’ll examine the latest signs that point to a looming financial crisis in China.</description></item><item><title>PDB Afternoon Bulletin | December 6th, 2023: Zelensky Ducks Congress &amp; Maduro Moves on Guyana | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800015/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin: Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky canceled a planned briefing with U.S. senators on Tuesday, where he was expected to make one last appeal for emergency military aid. We’ll discuss the ongoing fight in Congress over Ukraine funding, and Zelensky’s increasingly precarious position within his own borders.
In the wake of a referendum claiming much of Guyana as Venezuelan territory, President Nicolas Maduro has told the country’s state-owned companies to immediately start exploiting Guyana’s rich deposits of oil and minerals.</description></item><item><title>December 6th, 2023: Wray’s Warning, Hostage Horrors, &amp; Menendez’s Mystery | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800016/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: FBI Director Christopher Wray highlights an imminent terror threat to America, drawing parallels to the rise of ISIS. A deep dive into the plight of hostages under Hamas, and the terror unleashed in the October 7th massacre. Analyzing Russian President Vladimir Putin&amp;rsquo;s strategic Middle East visit amidst international tensions. In the Back of the Brief: Unraveling the connection between gold bars found in Senator Bob Menendez&amp;rsquo;s home and a 2013 armed robbery.</description></item><item><title>PDB Afternoon Bulletin | December 5th, 2023: US Strikes Back At Iranian Proxies &amp; Nuclear Hack Coverup Exposed | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800017/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin: The U.S. is once again responding to attacks by Iranian-backed militants in the Middle East, launching a deadly airstrike against a militia in Iraq on Sunday, and proposing an allied maritime task force to provide security for ships in the Red Sea.
A recent investigation has found that officials at the U.K.’s largest nuclear waste and decommissioning site have reportedly engaged in a years-long cover up of a hack by a foreign cyber group that may have compromised the sprawling facility’s systems.</description></item><item><title>December 5th, 2023: New Frontline in Gaza, COP28 Conflict, &amp; Ukraine’s Aid Crisis | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800018/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800018/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: We delve into the escalating conflict in the Middle East, examining the Israeli Defense Forces&amp;rsquo; expansion of their ground offensive into southern Gaza. A surprising twist emerges at the COP28 Climate Summit, as the conference president openly questions the science behind climate change, sparking a wave of controversy among attendees and observers. We explore the precarious economic situation in Ukraine, where financial instability looms large.</description></item><item><title>PDB Afternoon Bulletin | December 4th, 2023: Internal Divisions Grow in Ukraine &amp; Maduro Claims Guyana For Venezuela | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800019/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin: The mayor of Kyiv has lashed out at Ukraine President Volodymyr Zelensky’s leadership, warning the country is becoming increasingly autocratic under his tenure. It&amp;rsquo;s the latest sign of the growing discontent within the Ukrainian government as the war drags on.
A territorial dispute in South America is heating up after Venezuela approved a referendum on Sunday claiming sovereignty over a large swathe of their oil-rich neighbor Guyana.</description></item><item><title>December 4th, 2023: Ceasefire Crumbles, Maritime Mayhem, &amp; Venezuela's Annexation Ambitions | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800020/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: We delve into the recent flare-up of violence in Gaza, examining the factors that shattered a week-long ceasefire. We analyze the renewed aggression against US naval and commercial vessels in the Red Sea, and what it means for the already tense Houthi-controlled waters off Yemen. We discuss Venezuela&amp;rsquo;s controversial referendum on annexing a large portion of Guyana, and how this could send shockwaves through South American geopolitics.</description></item><item><title>PDB Afternoon Bulletin | December 1st, 2023: Israel's Shocking Intelligence Failure &amp; China's Influence Operations | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800021/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800021/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin: The New York Times has released a jarring report revealing that Israeli officials knew about Hamas’s intentions to orchestrate a massive attack inside Israel&amp;rsquo;s borders more than a year ago, but repeatedly dismissed the plans as something far outside Hamas’s capabilities.
Meta recently revealed they have broken up a number of Chinese influence operations targeting Americans on their social media sites, and warned that these campaigns are stepping up efforts to sow discord within the U.</description></item><item><title>December 1st, 2023: Ceasefire Crossroads, Troublesome Turkey, &amp; Pneumonia Panic | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 11:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800022/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: We examine the dilemma facing Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu as he navigates between the demands of the United States for a prolonged ceasefire and the threat of his own government&amp;rsquo;s collapse if the attack on Hamas is not resumed. A deep dive into the United States&amp;rsquo; diplomatic efforts to persuade Turkey to withdraw its support for Hamas, alongside an analysis of Russia&amp;rsquo;s position in the conflict.</description></item><item><title>PDB Afternoon Bulletin | November 30th, 2023: Russia's Weapons Trade With Iran &amp; India's Ties To An Attempted Assassination | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800023/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin: Leaders in Tehran and Moscow have finalized a deal on a weapons package that will see the Iranian regime get their hands on advanced aircraft in exchange for their continued military support of Putin’s war in Ukraine.
The attempted assassination of a Sikh separatist in New York appears to be linked to a larger network targeting the separatist group with ties to an official inside the Indian government.</description></item><item><title>November 30th, 2023: Hostage Horrors, Saudi-Iranian Olive Branch, &amp; Russia vs. Mother Nature | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800024/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800024/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: We delve into the harrowing experiences of hostages recently freed from 50 days of captivity, revealing the harsh conditions and brutal treatment they endured. Saudi Arabia extends a diplomatic gesture to Iran, proposing a deal to curb Tehran&amp;rsquo;s role in the ongoing Israel-Hamas conflict. A closer examination of the situation at America&amp;rsquo;s borders, as surprise inspections unveil severe overcrowding and extended detentions at CBP facilities.</description></item><item><title>PDB Afternoon Bulletin | November 29th, 2023: Mystery Pneumonia Surge &amp; The Finland-Russia Border Crisis | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800025/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin: Cases of pneumonia are spiking among children in parts of Europe for unknown reasons, sparking concerns in light of the mystery respiratory illness that is currently running rampant in China.
Finland will shutter their last remaining border crossing with Russia amid the intensifying migrant crisis and rising tensions with the Putin regime. Please remember to subscribe if you enjoyed this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin.</description></item><item><title>November 29th, 2023: Hostage Handovers, Musk the Mensch, &amp; Kochs Back Nikki | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800026/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: As additional hostages are released in Gaza a major question arises: why are so few American hostages returning home? Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s surprise visit to Israel makes waves as he meets Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu and endorses the campaign against Hamas. A deep dive into the Capitol&amp;rsquo;s ongoing debate over financial aid to Ukraine. In the Back of the Brief: The Republican presidential primary is upended by an unexpected endorsement for Nikki Haley from prominent figures.</description></item><item><title>PDB Afternoon Bulletin | November 28th, 2023: Iran-Backed Hackers Hit US &amp; Biden Warns Israel Over Destruction In Gaza | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800027/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800027/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin: Iranian-backed hackers infiltrated a local U.S. water system over the weekend in a shocking display of the reach of Iran’s many proxy groups.
The Biden administration has warned Israel to restrict their upcoming military campaign in southern Gaza, requesting the IDF create “areas of deconfliction” to avoid the destruction seen during their initial response in the north. Please remember to subscribe if you enjoyed this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin.</description></item><item><title>November 28th, 2023: Houthi Missile Menace, North Korean Military Moves, &amp; Polish Border Blockades | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800028/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800028/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: A harrowing encounter in the Gulf of Aden: Iranian-backed Houthi insurgents launch missiles at a US Destroyer amidst a maritime hijacking crisis. Tensions escalate on the Korean peninsula as North Korea embarks on a military escalation following its recent spy-satellite deployment. Commercial chaos ensues as Polish truckers commence continuous blockades at crucial Ukrainian border crossings. In the Back of the Brief: The Dublin riots take a new turn with Conor McGregor under investigation for provocative comments.</description></item><item><title>PDB Afternoon Bulletin | November 27th, 2023: Israel Extends Hamas Truce &amp; Tensions Flare In The South China Sea | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800029/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800029/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin: Israel and Hamas have agreed to extend their fragile truce for another two days. We discuss what this means for the hostages in Gaza and the broader implications for the Israel-Palestine conflict.
Tensions flared this weekend in the South China Sea after China drove an American warship from the disputed waters and accused the U.S. of jeopardizing stability in the region.</description></item><item><title>November 27th, 2023: China’s Mystery Illness, Hostages Head Home, &amp; Dublin Disorder | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800030/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800030/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: A mysterious new respiratory illness is sweeping parts of China, local healthcare facilities are inundated, and the international community is on alert. The fragile ceasefire persists in Israel as Hamas releases dozens of hostages in exchange for Palestinian prisoners. Ukraine launches a significant drone offensive targeting Moscow in response to a similar Russian attack. Civil unrest in Dublin: Anti-immigrant sentiments boil over into riots following a knife attack that injured five, including three children.</description></item><item><title>PDB Afternoon Bulletin | November 24th, 2023: Israel's Laser Defenses &amp; The Migrant Crisis On Finland's Border | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800031/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Description:
In this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin: Israel is making rapid progress in the development of their next generation “directed energy” weapon dubbed the “Iron Beam,” which they recently used to shoot down an enemy rocket fired by Hamas.
Finland is shuttering all but one of their border crossings with Russia this week in response to the Putin regime flooding their country with displaced migrants. We look at the unfolding crisis along the border.</description></item><item><title>November 24th, 2023: Killer Robots, Indian Assassins, &amp; Wuhan Warnings | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800032/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800032/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief:
We dive into the global controversy surrounding the deployment of AI-controlled drones and the mounting pressure for international regulation. A covert assassination initiative out of India is unearthed as an attempt on the life of a Sikh separatist in the U.S. is thwarted. Documents surface, indicating that U.S. scientists expressed alarm over the safety protocols at the Wuhan virology lab well before the pandemic was on anyone&amp;rsquo;s radar.</description></item><item><title>November 23rd, 2023: PDB Thanksgiving Edition | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800033/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Host Mike Baker delivers a Thanksgiving message as we kick off the holiday season. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>PDB Afternoon Bulletin | November 22nd, 2023: Iranian Missiles for Moscow, &amp; Hostage Deal Details | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800034/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800034/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin: The White House has warned that Iran is preparing to send advanced short-range ballistic missiles to Russia for use in Ukraine, in a sign the already cozy relationship between the two regimes is drawing even closer.
Israel has approved an agreement with Hamas to pause fighting for four days and trade Palestinian prisoners for 50 hostages taken during the 7 October attacks.</description></item><item><title>November 22nd, 2023: Hostage Breakthrough, NYC On Notice, &amp; North Korea's Space Quest | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800035/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800035/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief:
A groundbreaking development as Israel and Hamas agree to a hostage exchange deal, freeing dozens of Israeli hostages. Concerning intelligence report that suggests an uptick in the likelihood of a terror attack in New York City. A significant advancement in North Korea&amp;rsquo;s military capabilities, with the launch of a new rocket made possible by Russian assistance, aimed at deploying their first military reconnaissance satellite.</description></item><item><title>PDB Afternoon Bulletin | November 21st, 2023: Iran's Hypersonic Missile &amp; Discontent at Biden's Defense Department | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800036/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800036/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin: Iran unveiled a new version of their alleged hypersonic missile at a weapons display on Sunday. We discuss the regional implications and whether or not the new missile technology is actually functional.
As Iran’s belligerence continues in the wake of the 7 October attacks, a new report details the growing rift within the Biden administration over how to deter the growing threat.</description></item><item><title>November 21st, 2023: Another Hospital Siege, Adams Investigated, &amp; Biden Dodges a Bullet | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800037/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800037/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: The IDF initiate a siege on yet another medical facility in Gaza, sparking heated debate among Democrats about stipulations on aid to Israel. We delve into the uproar following the arrest of an NBC journalist by Israel on charges of inciting terrorism. We also examine New York City Mayor Eric Adams&amp;rsquo; ties with Turkey and the implications for his administration. In the Back of the Brief, we analyze how President Joe Biden seems to have narrowly avoided repercussions in the controversy over his handling of classified documents.</description></item><item><title>PDB Afternoon Bulletin | November 20th, 2023: High Sea Houthi Hijacking &amp; Outsider Upset in Argentina | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800038/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800038/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin: Iranian-backed Houthi militants in Yemen hijacked an Israeli-linked cargo ship Sunday in the Red Sea, stoking fears that the Israel-Palestine conflict is at risk of bubbling over into a larger regional war.
Libertarian Javier Milei, a self described “Anarcho-Capitalist,&amp;quot; won an upset victory in Argentina’s presidential run-off election Sunday, marking a seismic shift in its political scene. Please remember to subscribe if you enjoyed this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin.</description></item><item><title>November 20th, 2023: Biden's Gaza Proposal, Hostage Hopes, &amp; Hamas’ Hospital | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800039/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800039/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: President Biden shares his perspective on the future of Gaza amid the ongoing conflict, as detailed in his recent op-ed for the Washington Post, and we explore its impact on his approval ratings. A potential breakthrough in the Israel-Hamas conflict: the sides seem close to agreeing on a deal to exchange hostages for a temporary cease-fire. The Israeli Defense Forces reveal evidence of Hamas activities within the al-Shifa hospital.</description></item><item><title>November 17th, 2023: Atomic Ambitions, Menacing Missiles, &amp; Domestic Discord | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800041/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800041/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: Alarming findings from UN nuclear watchdogs about Iran’s burgeoning nuclear capabilities and the implications for global security. Tension escalates in the Red Sea as a US warship responds to a drone attack from Yemen. A new development from Russia as it advances its arsenal with a hypersonic missile, setting a formidable challenge for US defense. In our Back of the Brief segment, the spotlight turns to domestic unrest, with an account of pro-Palestinian protesters targeting the DNC headquarters in a surge of violence.</description></item><item><title>PDB Afternoon Bulletin | November 17th, 2023: CCP Biolabs in America &amp; TikTok Love for Bin Laden | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800040/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800040/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin: A Congressional report has found that the owner of an illegally run biolab discovered in California has strong ties to China&amp;rsquo;s CCP, and that an investigation of the facility was hamstrung by CDC officials. Disturbing videos went viral this week on the social media app TikTok that centered around praise for an antisemitic letter written by Osama Bin Laden in the wake of the September 11 terrorist attacks.</description></item><item><title>PDB Afternoon Bulletin | November 16th, 2023: Al-Shifa Hospital Captured &amp; The Xi-Biden Summit | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800042/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800042/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin: An update on the situation at Al-Shifa hospital in Gaza City, which was captured by Israeli troops in an operation Wednesday morning. We’ll discuss what the IDF found inside and the international response to these developments. A look at yesterday&amp;rsquo;s meeting between CCP leader Xi Jinping and President Joe Biden at the APEC summit in San Francisco. Please remember to subscribe if you enjoyed this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin.</description></item><item><title>November 16th, 2023: Fossil Fuel Fraud, Erdogan’s Anger, &amp; Assad’s Arrest Warrant | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800043/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800043/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: A new climate pledge emerges from a meeting between President Biden and Chinese President Xi Jinping, but we dig into why China&amp;rsquo;s promises on fossil fuels may not hold up.
New details emerge about Iran’s involvement in the October 7th attacks as the Biden administration renews a sanctions waiver, granting Iran access to significant financial resources.
The tension between Turkey and Israel escalates as President Erdogan intensifies his rhetoric.</description></item><item><title>PDB Afternoon Bulletin | November 15th, 2023: China's Disinformation Campaign &amp; Russia's Staggering Military Losses | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800044/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin: A new report investigates a vast CCP backed disinformation network operating for years within the U.S. A UK intelligence report details the staggering losses Putin’s military has suffered in Ukraine. Please remember to subscribe if you enjoyed this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin. Email: PDB@TheFirstTV.com. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>November 15th, 2023: Xi-Biden Summit, Hospital Standoff, &amp; Iceland On Edge | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800045/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800045/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief:
President Biden prepares for a significant meeting with Chinese President Xi Jinping in San Francisco.
We delve into the a Gaza hospital and the truth behind Hamas’ “de-facto headquarters.”
More internal dissent within the Biden administration over the White House’s strategy and decisions regarding the ongoing war.
In the Back of the Brief, we focus on a small town in Iceland as it braces for the potential impact of a volcanic eruption.</description></item><item><title>PDB Afternoon Bulletin | November 14th, 2023: Iranian Espionage &amp; Ukraine's Winter Strategy | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800046/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800046/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin: A new report, delivered to President Biden and members of Congress, details Iran’s high-level influence and espionage operation within the U.S. government and the effect it&amp;rsquo;s had on policies and public narratives concerning the regime. With winter fast approaching on the eastern front, we’ll take a look at both the challenges and opportunities it presents for Ukraine, and how their leadership plans to leverage the season to gain an upper hand on Russia in the war.</description></item><item><title>November 14th, 2023: Biden Backlash, Austin's Alert, &amp; Disappearing Embassies | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800047/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800047/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief:
Tensions are rising within the White House, President Biden receives flak from his own administration over statements made concerning alleged war crimes in Gaza. US Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin expresses concerns to Israel regarding its recent actions against Hezbollah and the rising tensions with Lebanon. The latest developments in the investigation into the sabotage of the Nord Stream pipeline — a story that&amp;rsquo;s taken an unexpected turn.</description></item><item><title>PDB Afternoon Bulletin | November 13th, 2023: Hospital Siege &amp; Syrian Strikes | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800048/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800048/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The PDB Afternoon Bulletin: Israel closes in on Al-Shifa Hospital, the largest medical facility in Gaza City, as intense fighting rages in the surrounding area. The hospital is believed to house large facilities and tunnel networks underneath that serve as an unofficial headquarters for Hamas leadership. U.S. escalates response to attacks on American troops in Iraq and Syria, striking two facilities in eastern Syria, likely killing or injuring several militants.</description></item><item><title>November 13th, 2023: Hamas's Hostages, Netanyahu's Red Line, and San Francisco's Sweep | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800049/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800049/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: Major news regarding hundreds of hostages being held by Hamas and Israeli Prime Minister Netanyahu&amp;rsquo;s firm stance: no leadership role for the Palestinian Authority in Gaza post-conflict. China capitalizes on the Gaza war to advance its geopolitical ambitions. San Francisco&amp;rsquo;s race against time for a citywide cleanup before Chinese President Xi Jinping&amp;rsquo;s high-profile visit. In the Back of the Brief, the scandal enveloping New York City&amp;rsquo;s Mayor as the FBI investigates whether his campaign accepted illegal foreign donations from Turkish entities.</description></item><item><title>Special Weekend Edition: What Are Sleeper Cells? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800050/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800050/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this Special Weekend Edition of the PDB, Mike Baker Speaks to First TV host Mike Slater about how our Intelligence Agencies Protect U.S. From Terror Threats. Plus, what exactly are sleeper cells? This interview was part of The First TV Special - America On Alert: Imminent Threat Watch the full special here &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; https://www.thefirsttv.com/america-on-alert-imminent-threat/ Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>November 10th, 2023: Media and Militants, America Strikes Back, &amp; Sex and Power in DC | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800051/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800051/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief:
Startling questions surrounding journalists from Reuters, The Associated Press, and CNN, and whether they had prior knowledge of the Hamas attacks in southern Israel on October 7th.
American forces launch a second round of airstrikes against Iran-backed militias in retaliation to continued hostilities.
Unpacking intelligence reports on Russia’s Wagner Group, and its potential plans to enhance Hezbollah’s capabilities with advanced air defense systems.</description></item><item><title>November 9th, 2023: Hamas Confessions, Blinken's Warning, &amp; Diplomatic Crossroad | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800052/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800052/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: IDF&amp;rsquo;s significant advance into Gaza City and the startling admissions from Hamas leaders regarding their motivations behind the October 7th attacks. U.S. Secretary of State Antony Blinken&amp;rsquo;s warnings to Israel about reoccupying Gaza, advocating for Palestinian Authority governance post-conflict. Positive shifts in U.S.-China relations ahead of a critical summit, with both nations indicating a readiness to ease tensions. Bipartisan action in Congress as a member faces censure over controversial remarks concerning Israel.</description></item><item><title>November 8th, 2023: Gaza Security Reversal, DPRK-Russian Axis, &amp; Treaty Turmoil | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800053/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800053/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President’s Daily Brief:
We unpack Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu&amp;rsquo;s recent announcement that Israel may take a more assertive stance on Gaza’s security, signaling a potential shift away from long-standing policies.
Dive into the dynamics between Russia and North Korea as South Korean intelligence sheds light on a lethal collaboration that could have global ramifications.
Western powers and Russia step away from a key treaty meant to limit military deployments in Eastern Europe.</description></item><item><title>November 7th, 2023: Israel Anniversary, Militia Threats, &amp; TikTok Propaganda | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800054/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800054/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief:
We’ll reflect on the one-month anniversary of the Hamas-initiated conflict in the Middle East and the current state of affairs.
Analysis of the increased hostility from Iranian-backed militias toward U.S. forces, and the implications for broader regional stability.
Investigative insights into the alleged funding of activism with Hamas connections by liberal financial networks.
Concerns about China’s potential influence on the American perspective of the Israel-Palestine conflict through TikTok&amp;rsquo;s algorithms.</description></item><item><title>November 6th, 2023: Democrats Divided, Hezbollah's Caution, &amp; Ukraine's Quiet Talks | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800055/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800055/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief:
A stark rift forms in the Democratic party over the Gaza conflict, with accusations of genocide creating political shockwaves.
Hezbollah&amp;rsquo;s leader Hassan Nasrallah makes a statement on the Israel-Hamas conflict, eschewing calls for escalation to the relief of some and the dismay of others.
With the possibility of Hamas&amp;rsquo;s destruction in Gaza, we examine the prospects of the Palestinian Authority filling the power vacuum post-conflict.</description></item><item><title>November 3rd, 2023: Refugee Outcry, Biden's Motives, and Ukraine's Frozen Conflict | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800056/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800056/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief:
We explore the recent strikes on a Gaza refugee camp and the resulting international outcry. Just who are Palestinian refugees?
There’s a noticeable shift in the White House&amp;rsquo;s policy on the IDF offensive in Gaza. What could possibly be the political motivations behind President Biden&amp;rsquo;s stance?
European border and immigration policies come under scrutiny as a series of tragic incidents brings them to the forefront of international debates.</description></item><item><title>November 2nd, 2023: Life After Hamas, Debunking Yemen Reports, &amp; America's New Arrivals | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800057/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800057/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: As the situation escalates between the IDF and Hamas, we explore the potential aftermath of the conflict and discuss possible scenarios for the region after Hamas. Yemeni rebels acknowledge attacks on Israel, but has Yemen really ‘declared war’ on the Jewish state? We provide an update on the hundreds of American and other foreign nationals who are currently stranded in Gaza.</description></item><item><title>November 1st, 2023: FBI Warnings, Russia's Israel Backstab, &amp; UN Uselessness | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800058/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800058/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: Israeli forces press on with their deep incursion into Gaza, while America&amp;rsquo;s FBI director raises alarms about escalating threats to the U.S.
Vladimir Putin and Russia seem to be changing their stance. We dive into why they&amp;rsquo;re now vocal critics of Israel, in contrast to their historical ties.
The United Nations makes another controversial decision. Find out why their recent move highlights their perceived ineffectiveness.</description></item><item><title>October 31st, 2023: Bibi’s Blame Game, Hamas's Silent Crisis, &amp; Russia's Disturbing Mob Scene | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800059/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800059/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief:
Israeli forces make a major move on Gaza&amp;rsquo;s northern city, and Prime Minister Netanyahu&amp;rsquo;s controversial comments lead to heightened tensions.
A silent crisis unfolds in Gaza: foreign nationals, held as hostages by Hamas, prevented from leaving despite exit offers from neighboring nations.
Turning our gaze to Russia, we unpack the harrowing incident at an airport where an anti-Semitic mob targeted passengers from an incoming Tel Aviv flight.</description></item><item><title>October 30th, 2023: Ground Offensive, Strikes in Syria, &amp; Brooklyn Protests | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800060/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800060/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief:
The second phase of Israel&amp;rsquo;s war in Gaza continues to unfold. Israeli forces have expanded their operations, resulting in reported casualties on both sides, including injuries to an Israeli officer and soldier in northern Gaza.
Tensions are escalating following a drone attack in western Iraq by Iranian proxies in retaliation against U.S. airstrikes in Syria.
President Erdogan&amp;rsquo;s stern warning to Israel is also discussed, highlighting his support for Hamas and implications of potential military intervention.</description></item><item><title>October 27th, 2023: Ground Zero Gaza, Hamas Hostage Horrors, &amp; Ukraine's Dwindling Support | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800061/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800061/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief:
Israel&amp;rsquo;s ground forces make their first major push into Gaza, targeting Hamas sites.
We break down a concerning statement from Hamas regarding the Israeli hostages&amp;rsquo; situation, with the group claiming that nearly 50 of the over 200 Israeli hostages have died in Gaza bombings.
Turning our focus to Eastern Europe, we discuss how Ukraine is grappling with a significant blow after a key ally decides to withdraw its military backing.</description></item><item><title>October 26th, 2023: Gaza Invasion Postponed, Iran’s Fingerprints, Newsom's Beijing Surprise | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800062/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800062/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief:
We discuss Israel&amp;rsquo;s decision to postpone its anticipated Gaza invasion at the U.S.&amp;rsquo;s request, and the measures the U.S. is taking to bolster its regional air defenses.
We reveal the Pentagon&amp;rsquo;s disclosure on the injuries sustained from the recent drone strikes targeting U.S. bases in Iraq and Syria.
Fresh intelligence points to Hamas fighters receiving training in Iran ahead of their October attack on Israel.</description></item><item><title>October 25th, 2023: Homeland Warnings, Hostage Horrors, &amp; CIA Shadows in Ukraine | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800063/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800063/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief:
Federal officials raise concerns about potential attempts by terrorists from Hamas, Hezbollah, and Palestinian Islamic Jihad to penetrate the southern U.S. border.
An exclusive insight into the life of a Hamas hostage: Israelis abducted on October 7th narrate their harrowing experiences inside the intricate tunnels beneath Gaza.
U.S. intelligence reports highlight Iranian-backed militias&amp;rsquo; strategies to increase attacks on American forces in response to the U.</description></item><item><title>October 24th, 2023: Hamas' Chemical Threat, Hospital Blast Revisited, &amp; Domestic Standoffs | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800064/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800064/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief:
The IDF intensifies its bombing campaign with over 320 military targets hit in Gaza within a day and the elimination of high-ranking Hamas officials. Plus, Israeli forces confirm a USB drive found on a Hamas member, carrying instructions to manufacture chemical weapons.
A closer look at the Gaza hospital blast: The New York Times&amp;rsquo; admission of their mistake in their preliminary reporting, and global intelligence agencies backing Israel&amp;rsquo;s analysis that a stray Hamas rocket was the cause.</description></item><item><title>October 23rd, 2023: Hostage Release, China's Warships, and Russia's Battlefield Setbacks | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800065/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800065/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief:
We delve into the latest developments in the Israel-Hamas conflict, shedding light on the recent release of two American hostages and Israel&amp;rsquo;s airstrikes on two airports in Syria.
The tension in the Middle East escalates as China sends six warships to the region amidst the ongoing Israel-Hamas strife.
The security threats to U.S. forces in the Middle East continue to evolve with a new rocket attack on an Iraqi base housing American troops.</description></item><item><title>October 20th, 2023: West Bank Unrest, U.S. Base Attacks, &amp; China's Nuclear Surge | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800066/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800066/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief:
We begin with an analysis of a recent joint operation by the Israeli military and the Shin Bet security agency, where over 80 suspected Hamas operatives were apprehended in the West Bank. As the global alert from the State Department rings across continents, we dissect the advisory urging all Americans abroad to heighten their vigilance. Shifting to Syria and Iraq, we delve into recent drone strikes targeting US bases.</description></item><item><title>October 19th, 2023: Fact-Checking the Gaza Hospital Bombing &amp; Iran's Ominous Warningv | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800067/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800067/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: We start by examining the contentious Gaza hospital bombing allegations. Although initial narratives blamed Israel for the massive loss of Palestinian lives, emerging details question this account. Iran sending a stark message to Israel in the aftermath of the Gaza hospital incident, ominously stating, &amp;ldquo;Time is Up.&amp;rdquo; Shifting our gaze to Brussels, we uncover the horrific attack claimed by the Islamic State, which resulted in the tragic loss of two Swedish soccer enthusiasts.</description></item><item><title>October 18th, 2023: Refugees Rejected, Biden's Israel Adventure, &amp; Russia's Nuclear Shift | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800068/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800068/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: We kick off with a crucial update on the ongoing crisis in Israel, focusing on Jordan&amp;rsquo;s King Abdullah and his firm stance on accepting Palestinian refugees. So, why are Jordan, Egypt, and other neighboring nations shutting their borders to countless Palestinians? President Joe Biden makes a wartime visit to Israel, showcasing support while also pushing for humanitarian assistance in the Gaza Strip.</description></item><item><title>October 17th, 2023: Awaiting Israel's Move, Hamas's Hostages, &amp; Gaza's Subterranean Secrets | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800069/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800069/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief:
As Tel Aviv grapples with intense rocket attacks, we delve into the reasons behind the IDF&amp;rsquo;s hesitation, shedding light on multiple facets from concerns over Hezbollah&amp;rsquo;s movements in the north to the daunting labyrinth beneath Gaza.
We then shift our focus to the escalating hostage crisis. The heart-wrenching reality for nearly 200 families: notifications of their kin, now in the clutches of Hamas.</description></item><item><title>October 16th, 2023: Israel’s Gaza Challenge, China Chimes In, &amp; Refugee Controversies | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800070/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800070/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: We dive deep into the current situation in southern Israel as the IDF gears up for its offensive into the Gaza Strip. With the Hamas terrorists&amp;rsquo; rampage going on for more than a week, the challenges of evacuating civilians from an imminent war zone come into focus. China&amp;rsquo;s stance on Israel comes under the spotlight. They&amp;rsquo;ve been vocal about their concerns, specifically targeting Israel&amp;rsquo;s response to Hamas, questioning if it&amp;rsquo;s just self-defense.</description></item><item><title>October 13th, 2023: Palestine for Dummies, America’s Aid to Israel, &amp; Frozen Iranian Assets | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800071/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800071/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: We kick off with the latest updates on the Hamas terrorists&amp;rsquo; attacks on southern Israel, giving you the most recent developments. Dive deep into a historical overview of the Israel-Palestine conflict. We aim to dispel widespread misconceptions about this age-old dispute in our segment, &amp;lsquo;Palestine for Dummies.&amp;rsquo; As Israel prepares for a ground invasion into Gaza, and we discuss the U.</description></item><item><title>October 12th, 2023: Missed Warnings, Hezbollah's New Front, &amp; US Border Alarm | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800072/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800072/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief:
We delve into the updates of the sixth day since Hamas&amp;rsquo; terrorist activities in southern Israel and fresh insights indicate Israel might have disregarded vital alerts preceding the attack. We delve into the second front of this conflict: Israel&amp;rsquo;s confrontation with the Iran-backed terrorist group, Hezbollah, on its northern boundary. Shifting our attention to the U.S., we shed light on some unsettling reactions from American political figures.</description></item><item><title>October 11th, 2023: Gaza Ground Offensive, US's Hostage Challenge, &amp; EU's Aid Dilemma | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800073/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800073/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief:
We delve into day five of the conflict between Israel and Hamas, exploring the unfolding developments on the ground. What will a ground offensive deep into Gaza look like? We take a closer look at the next potential chapter of this ongoing saga.
The episode keeps you updated on the alarming hostage crisis. As the situation escalates, the US contemplates a bold move: a possible commando rescue mission for the detained Americans in Gaza.</description></item><item><title>October 10th, 2023: Israel Retaliates, Music Festival Massacre, and Missing Victims | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800074/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800074/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: On the fourth day of Israel&amp;rsquo;s war against Hamas, we’ll highlight the responses from both the Israeli government and the Israeli Defense Forces. We shine a spotlight on the tragic massacre at the Supernova music festival, a pivotal moment that many believe defines the conflict. Dozens of people are unaccounted for, believed to have been kidnapped by Hamas militants. We’ll look at the strategy behind the kidnapping of civilians and the growing hostage situation.</description></item><item><title>October 9th, 2023: Israel At War: The Hamas Offensive, Israel's Tragic Oversight, and Iran's Support | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800075/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800075/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief:
Israel is at war. We’ll spotlight how the terror group Hamas masterminded its actions on Israel’s southern frontier. A question of intelligence: How could Israel overlook the warning signs of this major assault? We then pivot to Iran, highlighting its position as one of the few countries openly supporting these aggressive attacks on Israel. Finally, we bring it back home, dissecting the U.</description></item><item><title>October 6th, 2023: Biden's Border Flip, Artillery Aid to Russia, and NATO's Aerial Drama | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800076/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800076/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief:
A major policy reversal by the Biden administration suggests a deeper crisis on the border. With the waiving of 26 federal laws in South Texas, border wall construction reminiscent of the Trump era is set to resume in Starr County, a focal point for illegal entry.
As North Korea deepens its ties with Russia, it taps into its Cold War-era arsenal, sending artillery to back Putin&amp;rsquo;s offensive in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>October 5th, 2023: McCarthy's Successor, NATO's Ammo Alarm, and America's Healthcare Unrest | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800077/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800077/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief:
A major upset in Congress as eight Republicans, led by Congressman Matt Gaetz, collaborate with Democrats to remove Rep. Kevin McCarthy from the Speaker of the House position. As the GOP looks for a new leader, we dive deep into the political turbulence hitting Capitol Hill.
As the Ukraine conflict intensifies, western militaries are sounding the alarm over a severe ammunition shortage.</description></item><item><title>October 4th, 2023: Canada’s Diplomatic Drama, Michigan's Billion-Dollar Dilemma, and Frontline Pawns | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800078/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800078/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: Canada and India&amp;rsquo;s diplomatic clash escalates. India reacts fiercely, demanding the removal of several Canadian diplomats after allegations of their involvement in the assassination of a Sikh separatist leader in Vancouver. Green Charter Township, Michigan stands at the epicenter of the U.S.-China dispute. A Chinese company, Gotion, proposes a $2.4 billion EV battery factory, sparking an economic and political debate. The project, though transformative, raises concerns over the influence of the Chinese Communist Party and mirrors U.</description></item><item><title>October 3rd, 2023: Iranian Influence, Ukraine's Corruption, and the Wagner Group's Next Era | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800079/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800079/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: First up, we uncover an explosive story from Washington. A high-level Iranian influence ring has been exposed, and shockingly, now-suspended Iran envoy Robert Malley is implicated. The objective? To influence U.S. policy toward Iran. We&amp;rsquo;ll trace this network from Tehran all the way to the corridors of power in Washington DC. Later, we analyze a confidential U.S. strategy document, obtained by POLITICO.</description></item><item><title>October 2nd, 2023: Averted Shutdown, Slovakia’s Shift, and Turkey’s Turmoil | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800080/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800080/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief:
Congress manages to prevent a government shutdown by passing a stopgap bill, but not without controversy. The bill&amp;rsquo;s lack of vital funding leads to bipartisan disagreements, and some Republicans contemplate a shift in leadership. Former Prime Minister Robert Fico of Slovakia leads his leftist party to an unexpected victory with a pro-Russian and anti-American agenda, creating possible ripples for the European Union and NATO.</description></item><item><title>September 29th, 2023: Menendez's FBI Probe, Pentagon's Arms Dilemma, and Auto Industry Showdown | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800081/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800081/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief:
Senator Bob Menendez faces indictment and calls to resign as he&amp;rsquo;s accused of leveraging his Senate Foreign Relations Committee role for personal gain. Learn about an intriguing FBI counterintelligence probe into Menendez and his wife.
Dive into a financial shortfall crisis at the Pentagon, where they&amp;rsquo;re struggling to replace $5 billion worth of arms sent to Ukraine. With only $1.6 billion left for new contracts, the looming threat of a government shutdown adds complexity to the situation.</description></item><item><title>September 28th, 2023: Biden's Troubles, Fauci's CIA Mission, and Nazi Ovation Fallout | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800082/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800082/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief:
Day 1 of Impeachment Inquiry of President Joe Biden takes an unexpected turn. As the controversy surrounding his son, Hunter Biden&amp;rsquo;s business dealings deepens, Republicans on the House Oversight Committee shed light on hefty funds received by Hunter from Chinese business partners. And the surprise? The beneficiary address on these transactions is Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s Delaware home.
We delve into shocking allegations that Dr.</description></item><item><title>September 27th, 2023: Shocking Ovations, A Commander's Resurrection, and The EU’s Warning to Musk | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800083/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800083/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: We delve into the shocking incident from Canada where Prime Minister Justin Trudeau is ensnared in controversy after a Nazi SS veteran received a standing ovation in Parliament. As Trudeau issues an apology, the clamor for accountability and resignations grows nationwide. We follow up on the surprising revelation that Russia’s Black Sea Fleet Commander Viktor Sokolov may be alive, contradicting Ukraine’s claims of his death in a missile strike.</description></item><item><title>September 26th, 2023. Deportation Pledge, Black Sea Strike, and the President’s Picket Line. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800084/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800084/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief with Mike Baker: A record-breaking surge of migrants cross into the U.S. prompting a new agreement between Mexico and the United States. Mexico commits to deporting migrants from border cities in a bid to deter further migration. From the frontlines of the conflict, Ukraine claims a major victory against Russia by targeting and eliminating the commander of Russia&amp;rsquo;s Black Sea Fleet in Crimea.</description></item><item><title>September 25th, 2023: Senate Scandals, Long Range Missiles, and D.C. Deadlines | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800085/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 10:44:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800085/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of &amp;ldquo;The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief&amp;rdquo;: New Jersey Senator Robert Menendez, chairman of the Senate Foreign Relations Committee, faces serious charges including bribery, fraud, and extortion. Amidst the ongoing Russia-Ukraine conflict, President Joe Biden promises new missiles to Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s President Volodymyr Zelenskyy, a move that could pivot the dynamics on the ground. The clock is ticking in Washington D.C. as lawmakers hurry to avert a government shutdown.</description></item><item><title>September 22nd, 2023: Arms Race Alert, Diplomatic Duels, and Workers on the Warpath | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800086/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800086/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of &amp;ldquo;The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief&amp;rdquo; with Mike Baker:
We begin by unpacking Saudi Arabian Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman&amp;rsquo;s resolute declaration: Should Iran pursue nuclear ambitions, Saudi Arabia will not be left behind. This remark, voiced in a recent Fox News interview, ignites growing apprehensions of a looming Mideast arms contest.
We then revisit our lead story from Thursday. As Ukrainian President Vladimir Zelensky seeks support from US lawmakers, Poland makes an unexpected decision, halting weapon provisions to Ukraine due to deepening grain import disputes.</description></item><item><title>September 21st, 2023: Fractured Alliances, Climate Calls, and Pennsylvania's Voting Gamble | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800087/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800087/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: We spotlight a potentially fracturing alliance between Ukraine and Poland as they navigate a tricky grain crisis. With a key ally looking shaky, what lies ahead for Ukraine? Amid the diplomatic maneuvers at the UN General Assembly, UN Chief Guterres issues a dire warning. The Biden Administration introduces its ambitious American Climate Corps program. Is this America&amp;rsquo;s answer to climate concerns, or is it just creating an army of paid progressive activists?</description></item><item><title>September 20th, 2023: Murder Mysteries, Military Moves, and Senate Makeovers | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800088/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800088/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief:
A chilling murder mystery is unfolding in Canada. Was India complicit in the assassination of a Sikh activist? With ties to a controversial movement on Canadian soil, the incident could have widespread international consequences.
With more than 150 Chinese warplanes hovering near Taiwan within a week, tensions are escalating between Taiwan and China.
At the UN General Assembly, Ukrainian President Zelensky and U.</description></item><item><title>September 19th, 2023. Prisoner Exchanges, Political Gatherings, and Mystery in the Skies | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800089/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800089/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: Five Americans make their way home after a significant prisoner exchange in Iran — but there&amp;rsquo;s a catch, as the nation pushes back against nuclear oversight.
The political arena heats up in New York City with the United Nations General Assembly, and we&amp;rsquo;ll break down what&amp;rsquo;s on the agenda.
Over in Ukraine, it&amp;rsquo;s out with the old as President Zelensky makes sweeping changes in the defense ministry.</description></item><item><title>September 18th, 2023: Auto Strikes, Far East Mysteries, and Border Breakthroughs | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800090/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800090/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief: • The unprecedented strike by the United Auto Workers against America&amp;rsquo;s top three automakers. Discover why this standoff is more than just an industry dispute. • Journey with Mike to the Far East, where mysteries surround China&amp;rsquo;s defense minister and alarms sound over Kim Jong Un&amp;rsquo;s Russian rendezvous. • The Department of Homeland Security announces a record-breaking intervention, stopping 160 individuals on the terror watchlist from illegally entering the US.</description></item><item><title>September 15th, 2023: Indictments, AI Oversight, and China's Naval Surge | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800091/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800091/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of &amp;ldquo;The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief&amp;rdquo;:
We start in Delaware, where Hunter Biden faces unprecedented charges, marking the first time a sitting president&amp;rsquo;s child has been indicted by the Justice Department. This explosive development comes after a collapsed plea deal and could severely impact President Biden&amp;rsquo;s 2024 reelection campaign.
We take you inside the closed doors of the U.S. Senate, where top tech execs rally behind government regulations on Artificial Intelligence.</description></item><item><title>September 14th, 2023: Cold War Echoes: Putin’s Meeting with Kim &amp; Nature’s Fury in North Africa | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800092/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800092/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of &amp;ldquo;The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief&amp;rdquo;:
A new alliance stirs as Kim Jong Un and Vladimir Putin meet in Russia, hinting at an ammunition deal that might boost Moscow&amp;rsquo;s efforts in Ukraine.
Nature’s fury tests Libya and Morocco.
An update on Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s contentious decision in occupied Crimea as a key Democratic lawmaker is demanding an investigation.
Please remember to subscribe if you enjoyed this episode of the President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief.</description></item><item><title>September 13th, 2023: House Speaker Kevin McCarthy Pushes for President Joe Biden's Impeachment | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800093/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800093/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of &amp;ldquo;The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief&amp;rdquo;: The Biden administration&amp;rsquo;s decision to release $6 billion in frozen Iranian funds and its implications for detained Americans in Iran. What will Iran do with this significant windfall? Whistleblower testimony reveals the CIA&amp;rsquo;s alleged attempts to influence the narrative on COVID-19&amp;rsquo;s origins in a Wuhan lab. Plus, as House Speaker Kevin McCarthy pushes for President Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s impeachment, delve into allegations concerning the Biden family&amp;rsquo;s international business ties.</description></item><item><title>September 12th, 2023: UK Police Arrest Alleged Chinese Spies | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800094/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800094/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of &amp;ldquo;The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief&amp;rdquo;: Elon Musk turns down Kyiv&amp;rsquo;s urgent plea for Starlink access in Crimea, igniting a widespread debate on the ethical responsibilities of private corporations in global conflicts. Should business leaders be neutral arbiters or active participants in international disputes? Kim Jong Un leaves Pyongyang aboard his armored train for a crucial meeting with Russian President Vladimir Putin. What geopolitical ramifications could this high-stakes discussion have?</description></item><item><title>September 11th, 2023. 22 Years Later... | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800095/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800095/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of &amp;ldquo;The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief&amp;rdquo;: We start off in New Delhi, India, where the G20&amp;rsquo;s closing declaration has exposed increasing fractures between global superpowers. What does this widening chasm mean for future collaborations and world diplomacy? From there, we shift our focus to Afghanistan. As the drug market flourishes, the Taliban&amp;rsquo;s promise of curbing illicit trade faces scrutiny. Can they be trusted to control this shadow economy?</description></item><item><title>September 8th, 2023: Tensions Rise as Moscow's Concerns Grow | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800096/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800096/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of &amp;ldquo;The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief&amp;rdquo;: We kick off in New Delhi, India (or should we say, Bharat?), setting the stage for the G20 summit and discussing its key highlights and potential implications.
The labor front heats up with the top dog of the United Auto Workers taking aim at management…and the president.
As tensions rise, we examine Russia&amp;rsquo;s concerns about the U.S.&amp;rsquo;s latest armament commitment to Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>September 7th, 2023: An Alarming Incident on the Romanian-Ukraine Border | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800097/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 10:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800097/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of &amp;ldquo;The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief&amp;rdquo;: We begin in Washington DC, exploring voters&amp;rsquo; growing concerns about the age of our elected officials and a critical debate on age and fitness to serve. Then, we journey to China, unveiling the mysteries from a clandestine meeting of the communist party elders and what it reveals about the nation&amp;rsquo;s internal dynamics. As tensions escalate, we analyze an alarming incident on the Romanian-Ukraine border.</description></item><item><title>September 6th, 2023: Is North Korea's Kim Jong Un Heading to Russia? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800098/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of &amp;ldquo;The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief,&amp;rdquo; Mike Baker looks at critical developments both at home and abroad: Tensions are escalating within the United Auto Workers, one of America&amp;rsquo;s most significant labor unions, as they stand on the brink of a major strike. We delve into the implications this could have on the domestic economy and the auto industry. We revisit the international stage with an update on North Korea’s Supreme Leader Kim Jong Un, who is reportedly gearing up for a trip to Russia.</description></item><item><title>September 5th, 2023: New Details on America’s Withdrawal from Afghanistan | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800099/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800099/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of &amp;ldquo;The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief,&amp;rdquo; host Mike Baker brings you crucial updates on pivotal global issues unfolding right now including: The ASEAN summit in Jakarta, where Southeast Asian leaders convene to address escalating violence and regional tensions. Are we on the brink of diplomatic breakthroughs, or should we brace for further strife? The ouster of Ukraine’s Defense Minister. What does this change in leadership signify for a nation embroiled in conflict and battling corruption at its highest echelons?</description></item><item><title>PDB is Back! Meet your new host, Mike Baker | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800100/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Meet Mike Baker, former CIA Operations Officer and the new host of the President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief. New episodes begin September 5th. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>'The President's Daily Brief ' Trailer | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800101/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 20:27:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each morning, the President of the United States receives a highly classified briefing on the most important issues facing the country &amp;ndash; The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief. Now you can hear your very own PDB, in the form of a podcast hosted by former CIA Operations Officer Mike Baker. Each morning at 6am Eastern, he&amp;rsquo;ll bring you 20 minutes of the most important topics of the day and why you should care, arming you with what you need to know to help solve America&amp;rsquo;s most pressing challenges.</description></item><item><title>February 23rd, 2023. Who and What is the Wagner Group and What is Their Role in Moscow? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800102/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800102/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s February 23rd. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got three briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, we’ve got a couple updates on Mexico and immigration this morning, including a new rule from the Biden Administration about asylum seekers. But here’s the kicker: it’s actually an old policy promoted by Donald Trump.</description></item><item><title>February 22nd, 2023. Biden Admin Attempts to Enact a Trump-Era Immigration Policy | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800103/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800103/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s February 22nd. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got three briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, we’ve got a couple updates on Mexico and immigration this morning, including a new rule from the Biden Administration about asylum seekers. But here’s the kicker: it’s actually an old policy promoted by Donald Trump.</description></item><item><title>February 21st, 2023. Exploring Russia's Allies to Determine Moscow's Ability to Survive the War of Attrition | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800104/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800104/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s February 21st. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got three briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, get those passports ready because we are going around the globe this morning, all because of the War of Attrition in Europe. We’re stopping first in Asia, then Middle East, plus an update in the Mediterranean Sea.</description></item><item><title>Presidents Day 2023 | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800105/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800105/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s February 20th. You are listening to the President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief. I&amp;rsquo;m your host and former CIA officer Brian Dean Wright. Your morning Intel starts now. It is President&amp;rsquo;s Day and I sure hope you all get to enjoy a day off. Rest up or do something fun in celebration of the holiday. I&amp;rsquo;m actually gonna take part of the day off, but mostly I&amp;rsquo;ll be reading and preparing for the rest of the week.</description></item><item><title>February 17th, 2023. Biden Claims That We Are "In Contest" with China, Not Conflict. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800106/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800106/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s February 17th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got three briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, Joe Biden delivered an update on the Chinese balloon saga yesterday. But he said one thing about managing conflict with Beijing / that we really need to talk about.</description></item><item><title>February 16th, 2023. The Skies Over the U.S. Are Filled with... Mexican Cartel Drones? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800107/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800107/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s February 16th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got five briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, there’s been a lot of talk about balloons lately but we should really talk about drones. Specifically the ones being flown over America by Mexican cartels. That’s coming up.</description></item><item><title>February 15th, 2023. Can Your Electric Vehicle Be Hacked, Crashed, and Held for Ransom? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800108/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800108/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s February 15th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got four briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, Ford Motor Company has halted production of their electric pickup truck because of a battery issue. We’ll talk about that, plus how Ford has a new source of cobalt for those batteries when they work.</description></item><item><title>February 14th, 2023. Cold War 2: Diplomacy Battles for the Pacific | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800109/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800109/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s February 14th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got four briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, get ready for lots of talk about inflation today. The latest numbers are set for release about whether inflation is going up or down in America. I’ll explain what to expect — and what it means.</description></item><item><title>February 13th, 2023. Is Biden a Compromised President? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800110/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800110/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s February 13th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got four briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, we’ve got more flying objects being shot down. Two more, in fact, over the weekend. We’ll discuss that, and why Joe Biden says Chinese spy balloons crossing America are not a major breach of US security.</description></item><item><title>February 10th, 2023. Biden Blames His Staff For The Classified Documents Found in His Homes | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800111/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800111/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s February 10th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got four briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, Joe Biden says it’s not his fault that he had classified material at his home and office. No no. I’ll tell you though who is.
Second, an update to the China Balloon Saga this morning, with an assessment by a Democrat Senator from Montana that is spot on.</description></item><item><title>February 9th, 2023. Inflation Continues to Impact Your Pocket Book | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800112/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800112/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s February 9th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got a special State of the Union brief for you this morning that helps explain America — and the world.
Last night, Joe Biden delivered the annual State of the Union address in Washington DC. As expected, he touted his accomplishments on a range of issues, domestically and abroad.</description></item><item><title>February 8th, 2023. The State of the Union... According to Joe Biden. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800113/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800113/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s February 8th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got a special State of the Union brief for you this morning that helps explain America — and the world.
Last night, Joe Biden delivered the annual State of the Union address in Washington DC. As expected, he touted his accomplishments on a range of issues, domestically and abroad.</description></item><item><title>February 7th, 2023. Why the US Allowed the Chinese Spy Balloon to Cross the US. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800114/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800114/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s February 7th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got four briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, an update on the Chinese Spy Balloon saga. It turns out my counsel to you all yesterday was spot on regarding one thing in particular. We’ll discuss it.</description></item><item><title>February 6th, 2023. The Balloon. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800115/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800115/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s February 6th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got a Special Brief for you this morning.
We are going to discuss the Chinese spy balloon saga that has unfolded over the past 10 days or so. And to be clear, it’s not just one balloon over the United States. We have reports this morning out of the South American country of Colombia that they too had one of these Chinese spy balloons pass over the top of their nation.</description></item><item><title>February 3rd, 2023. Breaking: Chinese Spy Balloon Traveling Across America | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800116/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800116/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s February 3rd. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got four briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, we’re hearing reports of a new shipment of weapons to Ukraine. I’ll tell you why it’s important, and why an increasing number of Americans don’t support it.
Second, a critical deadline arrives on Sunday.</description></item><item><title>February 2nd, 2023. FBI Raids Another Joe Biden Property. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800117/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800117/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s February 2nd. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got three big briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, Joe Biden’s beach house was searched yesterday by the FBI. But there’s another place they should be taking a look at. I’ll tell you all about it.</description></item><item><title>February 1st, 2023. Grand Forks, North Dakota Decides to Cancel Fufeng Mill... | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800118/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800118/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s February 1st. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got four briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, the city of Grand Forks, North Dakota has decided to cancel that Chinese mill that was going to be built in their city, just 16 miles from a key air force base.</description></item><item><title>January 31st, 2023. The Cold War Returns? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800119/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800119/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s January 31st. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got two big briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, there is a fight tomorrow at the White House, with Republicans squaring off against Joe Biden over the debt ceiling. I’ll give you a brief to help you sort through the arguments you’re going to hear — and decide who’s right.</description></item><item><title>January 30th, 2023. Biden Intel Scandal Continues to Unfold. Updates on Our Involvement in Ukraine and The Impact on A Potential War on China. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800120/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800120/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s January 30th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got five briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, an update on the Joe Biden Intel Scandal. We’ve now got notebooks of classified material to talk about. Not just a few pages.
Second, the recent rains in California came down a little too hard, leaving farmers in a tough spot.</description></item><item><title>January 27th, 2023. Bryan Is Wrong, Part 1. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800121/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800121/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s January 27th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Today is our Special Brief about how Bryan is Wrong. It was an opportunity for you all to write in, tell me about how I was wrong about something, and offer up your view of what’s right.
The first three topics this morning are on domestic affairs. First, we talk immigration — a fellow named Rowdy from Texas says I shouldn’t say the word migrant when discussing this issue and instead say immigrant.</description></item><item><title>January 26th, 2023. Good News From Europe! Also, JFK's Assassination. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800122/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800122/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s January 26th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got four briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, we’ve got some US economic data coming out today. I’ll explain what it is, and how it’s connected to our second brief on…
Europe. They’ve also got some economic news, good news, that you should know about.</description></item><item><title>January 25th, 2023. Another Intel Scandal... And Why These Classified Documents Matter. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800123/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800123/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s January 25th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got four briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, we’ve got an update on America’s intel scandal. This time it’s not Joe Biden. A new politician says that he too had classified material at his home. Second, we’ve got an update on Ukraine, with how global powers are doubling down on their investments in the war — with your money.</description></item><item><title>January 24th, 2023. Protests Continue in South America. What Impact Will This Have on You? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800124/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800124/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s January 24th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got four briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, we start in Peru with the latest on growing protests there and how they’re impacting copper prices — and the global economy.
Second, we head over to Brazil where the country’s president there is cracking down on protestors — and blaming Donald Trump for inspiring them.</description></item><item><title>January 23rd, 2023. The FBI Searched President Biden's Home and Found Even More Classified Documents | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800125/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800125/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s January 23rd. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got three big briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, the FBI searched Joe Biden’s home in Delaware late last week and they found more classified material. Meanwhile, Mr. Biden says he has no regrets about how he’s handled the growing scandal.</description></item><item><title>January 20th, 2023. Russia Claims to Have Arrested an American Spy. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800126/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800126/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s January 20th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got four briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, we’ve got some spies to talk about. One that was in Ukraine, and another just arrested in Russia. I’ve got details on both.
Second, we’re off to Africa this morning to Timbuktu.</description></item><item><title>January 19th, 2023. PM of Iraq Requests that American Troops Stay in the Country for Many Years to Come. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800127/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800127/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s January 19th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got six briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, a former Mexican government official is facing charges today, all because he helped the cartels to flood our border with drugs.
Second, the Prime Minister of Iraq says he’d like for American troops to remain in his country for years to come.</description></item><item><title>January 18th, 2023. The Joe Biden Classified Intel Scandal Continues... | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800128/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800128/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s January 18th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got four briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, the Prime Minister of the Netherlands was in Washington DC yesterday, talking about a very small product with global implications. I’ll share those details.
Second, there are lots of headlines out this morning about China, from their economy to falling population numbers.</description></item><item><title>January 17th, 2023. Surprise, Surprise? Returning to the Wheat Wars, Ukraine’s Wheat Didn’t Get to the Nations It Was Supposed To | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800129/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800129/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s January 17th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got five briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
Today we’re going to focus our foreign briefs mostly on Europe. First, we’ve got an update on the Wheat Wars. Turns out that Ukraine’s wheat did not end up with poor nations as planned.</description></item><item><title>January 16th, 2023. MLK Day. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800130/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Folks, today is Martin Luther King Day, a national holiday, of course. And rather than do a show today, I’m going to enjoy a little bit of time off. But mostly, I’m going to be answering your emails and prepping for the rest of the week.
Good day. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>January 13th, 2023. Japan Growing Concerned with Chinese Military Activity | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800131/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800131/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s January 13th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got six briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world. First up, Japan’s Prime Minister is in Washington DC today, with a big focus on China. Second, the CIA Director made a surprise visit to Libya this week. Third, protests continue to escalate in the country of Peru, with copper mines now being targeted.</description></item><item><title>January 12th, 2023. More Classified Documents Found in Biden Offices? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800132/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800132/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s January 12th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got three briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world. First, Joe Biden has promised that $7B in new aid to Central America / will stop or slow illegal immigration. We’ll talk about whether or not that is likely true.</description></item><item><title>January 11th, 2023. The Taliban Signs a $500M Deal for Afghanistan's Oil and Gas. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800133/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800133/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s January 11th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got three briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world. First, leaders from the US, Canada, and Mexico are celebrating trade between their nations this morning. All connected to a free trade agreement called USMCA. But China has found a sneaky way to get in the middle of it — and take advantage.</description></item><item><title>January 10th, 2023. Classified Files Found in Joe Biden's Possession from His Days as VP. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800134/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800134/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s January 10th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got three briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, some breaking news out of Washington DC. The White House confirming this morning that Joe Biden mishandled classified information — and may have put the country at risk. I’ll share the latest.</description></item><item><title>January 9th, 2023. Biden, Trudeau, and AMLO Meet to Discuss Drugs, Trade, and Immigration. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800135/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800135/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s January 9th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. I’ve got four briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world. First, a big brief on North America this morning, where we start in Washington DC, then Denver, El Paso, and two stops south of the border. That’s where the leaders of Canada, the US, and Mexico are gathered this morning talking drugs, immigration, and trade.</description></item><item><title>January 6th, 2023. President Biden Announces New Immigration Policies, and They Look A Lot Like Trumps. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800136/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800136/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s January 6th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got four briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, an update on the Drone Wars in Ukraine. Turns out that American-made electronics are helping those Russian drones attack Ukrainian targets.
Second, China has created mosquitos that inject vaccines into unsuspecting patients.</description></item><item><title>January 5th, 2023. China is Engineering Vaccine Injecting... Mosquitos | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800137/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800137/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s January 5th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got four briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, an update on the Drone Wars in Ukraine. Turns out that American-made electronics are helping those Russian drones attack Ukrainian targets.
Second, China has created mosquitos that inject vaccines into unsuspecting patients.</description></item><item><title>January 4th, 2023. European Journalism Committee Warns of Ukraine's Trend Towards Dictatorship | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800138/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800138/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s January 4th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got five briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, allegations this morning by European journalists that Ukraine is slipping into a dictatorship. Second, the country of Norway just reached a milestone on electric vehicle sales. Some are saying America should do the same.</description></item><item><title>January 3rd, 2023. Natural Gas Prices Plummet in Europe, Thanks to You | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800139/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800139/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s January 3rd. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got five briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, an update on the Natural Gas Wars in Europe. Plus a reminder of why it’s so important to all of us.
Second, America’s not the only country facing an immigration crisis this morning.</description></item><item><title>January 2nd, 2023. New Info on the German Intelligence Officer Spying for Russia | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800140/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800140/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s January 2nd. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day and a Happy New Year, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got four briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, we start in Germany where I’ve got an update on that German intelligence officer who was secretly working for the Russians. It’s more bad news for our War in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>December 30th, 2022. Dirty Green Energy: Electric Vehicles | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800141/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800141/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s December 30th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Today is the final episode of our five part series this week on the Dirty Green Revolution. Over the past week, we’ve talked about solar panels, wind turbines, and the batteries that store and distribute their energy. But, as the facts make clear, none of that stuff is clean, green, or renewable at all, despite what proponents might say.</description></item><item><title>December 29th, 2022. Dirty Green Energy: Renewable Energy Batteries, Part 2. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800142/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800142/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s December 29th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Today is Part IV of our Series on Dirty Green Energy — Or as some might say, “renewable energy” or “clean energy.” But always we here at the PDB are asking, “How clean or green is this stuff - really?”
Well, so far we’ve discovered that solar panels are not clean or green. They use Chinese slave labor and lots of coal energy to create polysilicon.</description></item><item><title>December 28th, 2022. Dirty Green Energy: Renewable Energy Batteries, Part 1 | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800143/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800143/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s December 28th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Welcome back to Part III of this week’s updated and refreshed series on Dirty Green Energy. Others might call it Renewable Energy, or Clean Energy. But not us, not here. That’s because we’re setting aside the spin and agendas, and instead we’re sticking to the facts. And it turns out, the facts and data say there’s nothing clean or green about the two issues we’ve already covered: solar and wind energy.</description></item><item><title>December 27th, 2022. Dirty Green Energy: Wind Farms | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800144/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800144/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s December 27th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. It’s day two of Dirty Green Energy — that’s this week’s updated and refreshed five part series looking at what many folks might otherwise know as Renewable Energy. And we’re focused on this issue for one simple reason: Whether you like it or not, America is radically changing. We are being forced to drop oil, gas, and coal for things like solar, wind, and batteries to store their power.</description></item><item><title>December 26th, 2022. Dirty Green Energy: Solar Panels | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800145/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800145/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s December 26th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. I’ve got an update, my friends. A Dirty Green Update.
For folks new to the podcast, you might not know what that is. But I bet you’ve heard about Green Energy, or Renewable Energy.
Yes, we’re talking about solar panels and wind turbines. Plus the batteries that store and distribute all of that energy.</description></item><item><title>December 23rd, 2022. A Russian Spy Inside Germany's Government. What Critical Information Did He Send to the Kremlin Before His Arrest? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800146/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800146/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s December 23rd. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got four briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, Germany’s got a spy problem. We’ll talk about how that could impact us here in America. Second, an update on those explosions of Russia’s natural gas pipelines. Investigators are starting to rule out suspects.</description></item><item><title>December 22nd, 2022. Mr. Zelensky Goes to Washington, Will The War Ever End? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800147/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800147/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s December 22nd. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got four briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, we’ve got updates on the War in Ukraine which will leave us asking, when will this war ever end? I’ve got some answers. Second, we head to Ireland where that country’s government has confirmed that some of their cows must die to stop climate change.</description></item><item><title>December 21st, 2022. Ukraine's Zelensky Is on His Way to Washington D.C. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800148/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800148/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s December 21st. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got four briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, Ukraine’s President is making a surprise stop in America today, meeting with Joe Biden and speaking with Congress later tonight. I’ve got that update, plus why some of the weapons we’ve sent to Ukraine aren’t working anymore.</description></item><item><title>December 20th, 2022. Trump Immigration Plan “Title 42” Is on Its Last Leg, Some Democrats Are Fighting to Keep It | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800149/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800149/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s December 20th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got four briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First off, we start today on America’s southern border, with a story about a migrant that reminds us of the real challenge to stopping illegal migration.
Next, we travel to Vietnam, with that country replacing the United Kingdom on a very special list.</description></item><item><title>December 19th, 2022. People Who Got the COVID-19 Vaccine are Three Times More Likely to Get COVID-19 | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800150/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800150/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s December 19th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got four briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First up, we travel to Germany where I’ve got three puzzle pieces of intel about energy and we’re going to see if there’s a big picture trend in those puzzle pieces that you would brief to the president.</description></item><item><title>December 16th, 2022. China Has Moved Into Afghanistan, Islamic Fighters Now Targeting Chinese Businessmen | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800151/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800151/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s December 16th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got four briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First up, we start in Afghanistan where Islamic fighters are targeting Chinese businessmen. I’ll explain why.
Second, we travel to Vietnam, where American weapons manufactures are looking to sell that country military gear.</description></item><item><title>December 15th, 2022. A Surprising Demographic Has Been Training Chinese Fighter Pilots | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800152/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800152/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s December 15th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got five briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world. And for today’s podcast, grab those maps because we’re circling the globe.
First, we start in Africa, or at least with the 50+ African leaders gathered at the White House.</description></item><item><title>December 14th, 2022. UK Prime Minister Rishi Sunak says "No More Illegal Immigrants" | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800153/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800153/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s December 14th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got five briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world. And for today’s podcast, grab those maps because we’re circling the globe.
First, we start in Africa, or at least with the 50+ African leaders gathered at the White House.</description></item><item><title>December 13th, 2022. Another Day, Another 15,000 Illegal Migrants Across the Southern Border | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800154/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800154/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s December 13th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got five briefs for you this morning — mostly on energy today — that are shaping America — and the world.
First, over 15,000 illegal migrants came across America’s southern border in the past 48 hours. I’ll explain who they are. Second, the Biden Administration said yesterday that it’s using taxpayer dollars to help open new mining operations to support Dirty Green Energy.</description></item><item><title>December 12th, 2022. Libyan Terrorist Accused of 1988 Lockerbie Airplane Bombing is in US Custody | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800155/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800155/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s December 12th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got five briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, a Libyan terrorist has been captured. I’ll explain what it means and why Europe’s demand for oil and gas might have played a role in it.
Second, the Biden Administration slapped sanctions last week on Central American leaders for corruption.</description></item><item><title>December 9th, 2022. Energy Crisis Across Multiple Continents. Is Dirty Green Energy to Blame? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800156/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800156/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s December 9th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got five briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, the United Kingdom is discovering that sometimes the wind doesn’t blow, and that means their wind turbines won’t be creating electricity this weekend.
Second, another electricity crisis to tell you about, this one in the southern African countries of Zambia and Zimbabwe.</description></item><item><title>December 8th, 2022. Dr. Fauci Admits that He Lied to the American Public About the Lab Leak Theory to Protect China | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800157/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800157/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s December 8th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got five briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world. First, some high drama in the South American country of Peru to tell you about, plus why it matters.
Second, the Russian economy is chugging along, with buyers still lining up for Russian oil, coal, and wheat.</description></item><item><title>December 7th, 2022. Breaking: US to Rescind COVID Vaccine Mandate for Military Personnel | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800158/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800158/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s December 7th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got four briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, secret material leaked yesterday about the Mexican Military, with important implications for America’s security.
Second, the company Chevron is taking control of an oil production facility in Venezuela this morning.</description></item><item><title>December 6th, 2022. The Massive Gang Problems in Central America | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800159/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800159/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s December 6th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got two big briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, Joe Biden announced yesterday his plans to meet with the leaders of Canada and Mexico next month. On the agenda should probably be what’s happening in Central America this morning.</description></item><item><title>December 5th, 2022. NATO's New War Against Russia. Ad Free PDB is Live! | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800160/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800160/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s December 5th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got three briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, the United States and Europe just launched a new war against Russia — an economic war. And it may have a huge impact on your pocketbook.
Second, China is starting to back off its ZERO COVID policies.</description></item><item><title>December 2nd, 2022. The Railroad Strikes Have Been Thwarted... Probably. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800161/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800161/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s December 2nd. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got five briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, America’s rail-road strike has been thwarted. Probably. I’ll explain.
Second, an update on our southern border and migrants from Mexico. Two new records to tell you about. I’ll let you decide if either are good.</description></item><item><title>December 1st, 2022. Gas Prices and Rent are Down Across America. How Much Should We Be Celebrating This News? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800162/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800162/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s December 1st. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got three briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, America’s immigration policies might come down to one word being debated at the Supreme Court.
Second, some folks are talking about good news regarding gas prices and rent in America.</description></item><item><title>November 30th, 2022. China is Tripling Their Total of Nuclear Warheads | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800163/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800163/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s November 30th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got four briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, some sobering news out of China. They’re on target to triple the number of nuclear warheads in their arsenal. Second, the Netherlands is going to buy or seize upwards of 3,000 farms, all in the name of fighting climate change.</description></item><item><title>November 29th, 2022. Apple Threatens to Remove Elon Musk's Twitter from the App Store | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800164/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800164/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s November 29th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got one special brief for you this morning that is shaping America — and the world.
There’s a growing fight between two tech giants this morning — Twitter and Apple. And it’s largely focused on free speech. Although the White House weighed yesterday, and what they said suggests that this might actually just be about politics.</description></item><item><title>November 28th, 2022. China in Revolt. How Serious Will These Demonstrations Become? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800165/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800165/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s November 28th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got five briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, some incredible images coming out of China. Protests all around that communist country, and all because of a fire. I’ll explain.
Second, Dr. Tony Fauci and the Biden Administration have some COVID advice for China.</description></item><item><title>November 25th, 2022. Railroad Strike is Imminent, Will the Biden Admin Step In? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800166/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800166/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s November 25th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got four briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world. First, some good news and bad news out of Ukraine. And the good news will be welcomed by farmers and ranchers around the world.
Second, the Biden Administration just approved of a major expansion of an oil project in Texas.</description></item><item><title>November 24th, 2022. Thanksgiving Day Special: Jimmy Spessard, CIA Hero. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800167/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800167/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s November 24th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Thanksgiving of 1989. There was a home in Hagerstown, Maryland that was full of a lot of joy. Probably a lot like your home today. The Spessard family was celebrating Thanksgiving, with a dad named Jimmy, his young wife Debra, and their two small sons, Jared and Jason.
The next day Jimmy would be leaving town for a while.</description></item><item><title>November 23rd, 2022. Tony Fauci to Retire, Leaves Behind More COVID-19 Vaccine Misinformation on His Way Out | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800168/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800168/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s November 23rd. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got five briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, Dr. Tony Fauci delivered his final remarks at the White House before retirement, talking about COVID-19 booster shots. I’ll share what he said, to include some misinformation about COVID vaccines.</description></item><item><title>November 22nd, 2022. Special Brief: The Subtle War Over Renewable Energy | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800169/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800169/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s November 22nd. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got a Special Brief for you this morning that is shaping America — and the world.
Joe Biden and Kamala Harris have been traveling in Southeast Asia over the past week. Ms. Harris is in the Philippines this morning, while Mr. Biden was in Indonesia last week.</description></item><item><title>November 21st, 2022. American Banks are Still Operating in Russia, by Order of... The US Government? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800170/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800170/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s November 21st. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got five briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, an update on the War in Ukraine. Russia has two friends helping it out this morning. The first is the country of Iran – no surprise there. The second is the United States.</description></item><item><title>November 18th, 2022. The Biden Family Foreign Business Dealings. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800171/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800171/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s November 18th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got a few briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, Republicans have officially captured the House of Representatives. They’re promising to investigate Joe Biden and his family because of their foreign business deals. But is that fair? We’re going to look at the issue imagining that we’re investigators at the CIA.</description></item><item><title>November 17th, 2022. World War Three isn't Happening... At Least Not Yet. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800172/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800172/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s November 17th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got five briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, an update out of Ukraine. Looks like we dodged WWIII – for now. I’ll explain.
Second, we’ve got some crime numbers out this morning, with one company saying it’s bad and getting worse.</description></item><item><title>November 16th, 2022. A Missile Strikes a Town in Poland. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800173/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800173/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s November 16th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got four briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, an alarming development from the War in Ukraine – there was an explosion in the neighboring country of Poland. And they are blaming it on Russia. I’ll explain what’s going on, and why we’ve got to be very careful with what we’ll likely hear over the coming days.</description></item><item><title>November 15th, 2022. Sources Within US Government Continue to Raise Alarm Bells About China. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800174/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800174/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s November 15th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A good day to you, ladies and gentlemen. I’ve got three briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world. First, Joe Biden met with China’s president yesterday, promising to reduce tensions and work towards peace. But odds are, we’re headed towards conflict. I’ll explain why. Second, a warning from the National Fire Protection Association about a consumer product.</description></item><item><title>November 14th, 2022. Biden Meets with China's Xi and Travels to Egypt to Talk Climate Change. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800175/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800175/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s November 14th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Good Day, America. I’ve got five briefs for you this morning that are shaping America — and the world.
First, Joe Biden is traveling the globe. He stopped last Friday in Egypt talking climate change. But there wasn’t much more than talk to those meetings. I’ll discuss that. Second, Mr. Biden’s next stop is in Indonesia, meeting with China’s president today amongst others.</description></item><item><title>November 11th, 2022. Veteran's Day Special: Hugh Francis Redmond | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800176/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800176/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s November 11th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Seventy Seven years ago this month, there was a veteran in Yonkers, New York who was sitting at home after being discharged from the military, having been wounded in World War II. His name was Hugh Redmond.
Today we’re going to re-tell the story of Hugh Redmond his incredible life, his service as an intelligence officer, and his eventual death.</description></item><item><title>November 10th, 2022. Special Brief: Exploring the International Impact of Our Midterm Elections | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800177/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800177/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s November 10th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. We are two days out from America’s midterm elections. The Republicans have probably won the House of Representatives; confirmation likely sometime today. The Senate, however, is still up for grabs. I’ll leave it to others to get into the nitty gritty of all that, but here’s the bottom line: assuming Republicans take control of the House, things are likely going to be different in Washington DC.</description></item><item><title>November 9th, 2022. Pentagon Confirms, American Boots on the Ground in Ukraine | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800178/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800178/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s November 9th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Well, the results are trickling in for America’s midterm elections. And we’ll talk more about those tomorrow and next week. But there’s still a lot of other stuff happening out there. So let’s do a Big Five Update.
Five critical updates on stories we’ve covered previously that are shaping America — and the world.</description></item><item><title>November 8th, 2022. Election Day! Will the Losers of the Midterms Call Foul? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800179/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800179/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s November 8th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. It’s election day and polls show that Republicans are likely to win the US House and Senate. And that means we’re likely to hear some pretty outrageous claims from the politicians who lose. So we’re going to cover those claims and let you decide whether The End is Near, as some are saying, or rather that America is alive and pretty darn well.</description></item><item><title>November 7th, 2022. North Korea Launches ICBM as South Korea and the US Engage in War Exercises Nearby | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800180/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800180/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s November 7th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Welcome to a Big Five Update this morning. Five critical updates on stories we’ve covered previously that are shaping America — and the world.
First, North Korea is launching missiles and, apparently, sending weaponry to Moscow. Second, an update on the War in Ukraine. You might be hearing more talk of peace, but don’t believe it.</description></item><item><title>November 4th, 2022. Fentanyl Continues to Kill Americans 18-45. Who You Vote For Could Help Solve This Ongoing Tragedy | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800181/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800181/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s November 4th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. The CDC announced a few months back that, if you are an American between the ages of 18 and 45, there’s one thing that’s killing your generation more than any other: drug overdoses, especially by fentanyl. We’re going to do a deep dive into how this drug starts in China, transits into Mexico, and ends up in your hometown.</description></item><item><title>November 3rd, 2022. A Few Things to Remember Going Into Election Season | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800182/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800182/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s November 3rd. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. It’s election time, but not just here in America. There’s one country in Europe where voters just put back into power a prime minister who slaughtered 15 million animals over COVID fears. We’re going to talk about the lessons that leaves for voters here in America.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>November 2nd, 2022. How Clean Are The Solar Panels Leading the "Green Revolution"? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800183/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800183/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s November 2nd. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. For years we’ve heard about dirty oil, dirty coal, and dirty natural gas. All dirty because of their environmental record, plus their tie to foreign dictators. Well today begins a five part series on Dirty Green.
We’ll explore the debate of whether renewable energy is really the picture of purity that we are so often told or whether there are dirty secrets to the environment and connections to dictators abroad.</description></item><item><title>November 1st, 2022. U.S. Trained Afghan Special Forces Join the Fight in Ukraine... Fighting for the Russians | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800184/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800184/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s November 1st. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A lot of information coming out of Ukraine this morning. We’ve got a new suspect in the sabotage of those natural gas pipelines. Also, some bad news on the Wheat Wars. And most importantly — an alarming connection to our war in Afghanistan, with some the Special Forces that we trained there now showing up in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>October 31st, 2022. Elon Musk Officially Buys Twitter Promising to Create a "Beacon of Free Speech" | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800185/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800185/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s October 31st. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Businessman Elon Musk took over Twitter on Friday, promising to make the social media company a beacon for free speech. Well now he’s got his first test: rumors about something that happened at the home of Democrat House Speaker Nancy Pelosi. We’ll talk about why these developments are such big deal — even if you don’t use Twitter.</description></item><item><title>October 28th, 2022. Liberal “Sanctuary Cities” Continue to Be Overrun by Illegal Immigrants | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800186/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800186/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s October 28th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. FIRST UP, The Midterm Elections are approaching and the issue of immigration is driving part of the conversation of who to vote for. We’re going to talk about the costs of that illegal migration — based on a shocking $1B claim from New York City’s Mayor.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>October 27th, 2022. As Gas and Diesel Prices Continue to Rise, US Oil Companies are Exporting to Other Countries at Record Rates | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800187/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800187/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s October 27th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Welcome to a Big Five Update this morning. Five critical updates on stories we’ve covered previously that are shaping America — and the world.
First, if you’re thinking of buying an electric pickup truck, I’ve got some numbers you’ll want to hear about. All connected to a very big price tag. Second, another group of rail road workers has rejected a labor-deal that was negotiated by the Biden Administration.</description></item><item><title>October 26th, 2022. The White House Puts Out Even More COVID-19 Misinformation. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800188/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800188/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s October 26th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. We’ve got a Special Edition of the PDB this morning.
And it’s special because we’re going to talk about something nobody is talking about: Last month the US Government acknowledged that the batteries powering the Renewable Energy Revolution in this country — the electric vehicles, the solar and wind farms, all of it — those batteries are produced by child miners in the Congo.</description></item><item><title>October 25th, 2022. the US Government Reports That the Batteries Powering the Dirty Green Energy “Revolution” Come From Child Miners | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800189/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800189/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s October 25th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. We’ve got a Special Edition of the PDB this morning.
And it’s special because we’re going to talk about something nobody is talking about: Last month the US Government acknowledged that the batteries powering the Renewable Energy Revolution in this country — the electric vehicles, the solar and wind farms, all of it — those batteries are produced by child miners in the Congo.</description></item><item><title>October 24th, 2022. Russia &amp; Ukraine Conflict Continues to Escalate to Potentially Very Dangerous Levels | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800190/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800190/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s October 24th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. We’re going to do things a little differently this morning. I’ve got three full briefs on three important topics that need your attention.
First, we’ve got an alarming set of phone calls coming out of Russia, with their military warning nations around the world that we might see uncontrolled escalation in Ukraine. Second, Beijing wrapped up its big gathering over the weekend with three big messages for the world.</description></item><item><title>October 21st, 2022. Iranian Boots Are Allegedly on the Ground in Ukraine. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800191/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800191/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s October 21st. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. The Military of Iran has boots on the ground in Ukraine this morning. That is the allegation being made by governments in the US and Europe. We’ll discuss what Iran is allegedly doing, plus whether it’s an alarming development or something we would expect to see in war.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>October 20th, 2022. Listener Questions: War with China? Why Don't We Just Assassinate Putin? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800192/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800192/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s October 20th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Today we are going to do something special. It’s a podcast of only your questions. And we’re covering events from around the world. First, Wayne from Eureka, Missouri asks - What’s the timeline for a war with China? Because I have a son, and he could be drafted.
Second, Nick from Georgia asks - Why can’t we just kill Vladimir Putin and be done with this war in Ukraine?</description></item><item><title>October 19th, 2022. Biden is Still Searching for A Gas Price Scapegoat | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800193/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800193/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s October 19th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Joe Biden is taking aim at the oil and gas industry today because the price of gas and diesel are going up. But is he right to blame them? We’ll discuss that, plus whether there are any good solutions towards lowering those gas prices.
And folks, that will be our sole focus for today’s podcast.</description></item><item><title>October 18th, 2022. The Drone Wars Are Raging in the East as Russia Buys From Iran. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800194/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800194/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s October 18th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. The Drone Wars are back. We first talked about Ukraine’s use of drones back in April. Well this morning they’re being used again, but this time by the Russians. I’ll explain the latest, plus why you should care.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar.</description></item><item><title>October 17th, 2022. Will Xi Jinping Rule Over China for a Third Time? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800195/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800195/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s October 17th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. It’s a big week for China-related news. The Communists are gathering for the first time in five years to pick a new president and chart a path forward for the regime. We’ll talk about three key takeaways from that gathering and why you should care.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>October 14th, 2022. The Biden Admin Asks Saudi Arabia to Postpone Oil Cuts Until After U.S. Elections. Saudi Arabia Responds... Publicly. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800196/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800196/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s October 14th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. You might have heard the big news that the Biden Administration is in a big fight with Saudi Arabia. But what you might not have heard is how important this fight could become as the CIA now says the probability of a nuclear war in Ukraine has gone up from 1% to 25%. We’ll discuss the latest.</description></item><item><title>October 13th, 2022. Russia Makes Arrests for Bridge Bombing. Will Elon Musk be Arrested for Violating the Logan Act? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800197/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800197/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s October 13th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Welcome to a Big Five Update this Thursday morning. Five critical updates on stories we’ve covered previously that are shaping America — and the world.
First, Russia arrested nine people for bombing that very important bridge in Crimea. We’ll discuss details, Plus, bad news for Ukrainians trying to stay warm this winter. Second, energy prices here in America are going back up.</description></item><item><title>October 12th, 2022. Media Matters' Owner Creates 51 New Fake News Sites to Entice You to Vote Local | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800198/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800198/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s October 12th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Fake News. You’ve been told for years that it’s a problem, a crisis really, with misinformation and disinformation being spread by the Russians or Chinese. Well, turns out that these foreign powers have a new competitor — 51 fake news sites telling you to vote for Democrats. I’ll explain that story.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>October 11th, 2022. More Escalation Between Russia/Ukraine as Another Russian Symbol is Attacked. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800199/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800199/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s October 11th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. A very important update out of Ukraine, with an escalation of strikes on civilian targets over the past few days by both the Russians and Ukrainians. Plus, we’re seeing acts sabotage and cyber attacks in Europe and the United States. Coming up I’ll explain the latest, along with my assessment of why this war is likely to get much worse very soon.</description></item><item><title>October 10th, 2022. Columbus Day Brief. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800200/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800200/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today is Columbus Day. I sure hope you’re spending it in celebration, maybe some rest too. Regardless, today we are going to remind ourselves of the incredible story of Douglas Seymour MacKiernan. It’s part of the series I like to do on holidays, to highlight my brothers and sisters at the CIA who have died in line of duty — I want to share their lives and their sacrifice.</description></item><item><title>October 7th, 2022. Electric Vehicles are Catching Fire in Florida, and it's Bad. Fentanyl is the Number One Cause of Death for Americans Aged 18-45 | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800201/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800201/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s October 7th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First, Electric Vehicles are on fire in Florida this morning. And I mean literally on fire. We’ll talk about why. Second, some tough news out of Congress on the cost we are all paying for the fentanyl crisis.
Third, what do illegal migrants think about being bussed to sanctuary cities? I’ve got their fascinating answers.</description></item><item><title>October 6th, 2022. Russia Continues to Lose Bodies and Battles. Will This Force a Nuclear Escalation? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800202/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800202/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s October 6th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. I’ve got a big update on our War of Attrition — the Battle between Russia, Ukraine, and the West — most especially the United States. We’ve had a full week of developments, and I’m going to cover them — plus, what it all means.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>October 5th, 2022. The Dirty Green Revolution. Today, the Problems with Electric Vehicles. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800203/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800203/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s October 5th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. We’ve got a Special Edition of the PDB this morning. It’s a totally new episode on the Dirty Green Revolution. And today it’s all about Electric Vehicles.
For those unaware, we had a four part series, starting on September 12th, that look into solar, wind, batteries, and the mining of materials to make those batteries.</description></item><item><title>October 4th, 2022. How Cartel Members are Reaching Our Children for Illegal Acts. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800204/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800204/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s October 4th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. America’s kids are being offered cash from Mexican cartels to transport illegal migrants, both across the border AND once they get inside the country. We’re going to talk about how much the cartels are paying our kids and how they’re being recruited from across America. As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>October 3rd, 2022. Russia Tensions Continue to Rise as Sanctions Continue to Be Circumvented | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800205/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800205/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s October 3rd. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. The Russians are evading more sanctions this morning, and this time, it’s for timber. Odds are you’re actually buying some of it, and it’s helping to finance the war in Ukraine. I’ve got those the details coming up.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar.</description></item><item><title>September 30th, 2022. Putin to Claim His Currently Occupied Territory in Ukraine as a Permanent Part of Russia. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800206/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800206/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s September 30th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. It’s Friday and we’ve got a Big Five Update. Five critical updates on stories we’ve covered previously that are shaping America — and the world.
First, some big developments in our War of Attrition. Vladimir Putin is annexing land in Ukraine, and that means hopes for peace are growing very dim. Second, prescription drug makers in Europe are warning that they will likely end production because of electricity prices.</description></item><item><title>September 29th, 2022. The Underground Battle for the Pacific Islands. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800207/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800207/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s September 29th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. We’ve got a Special Edition of the PDB today. Some important news in the Battle for the Pacific — which is our long-running series on whether China or the United States will win the battle for influence amongst the many island nations of the North and South Pacific.
I’m doing this Special because the leaders of 14 of those island nations are in DC this morning, wrapping up a two day summit with Joe Biden and other Administration officials.</description></item><item><title>September 28th, 2022. Explosions Destroy Major Natural Gas Pipelines from Russia to Europe. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800208/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800208/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s September 28th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. We have a case of international mystery and intrigue this morning. Somebody blew up two pipelines / in the Baltic Sea, and it may be connected the War in Ukraine. I’ve got a full readout coming up.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar. First, Europe is placing a big order for solar panels.</description></item><item><title>September 27th, 2022. China Keeps Buying American Land Near Military Bases, Joe Biden's Team Doesn't Mind. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800209/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800209/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s September 27th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. The White House said something remarkable last week about China buying farm-ground near sensitive military bases. Joe Biden’s spokesman dismissed the concern, calling it a “home ownership” issue unworthy of his time. So we’ll discuss that statement, explore the facts, and let you decide.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>September 26th, 2022. New Nationwide Polls on Republican Efforts to Send Illegals to Sanctuary Cities. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800210/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800210/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s September 26th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. We’ve got a lot of news to cover this Monday morning, so I’m bringing you a Big Five Update. Five critical updates on stories we’ve covered previously that are shaping America — and the world.
First, we’ve got a bunch of new polls out on whether Americans support Republican efforts to send illegals to sanctuary cities.</description></item><item><title>September 23rd, 2022. Our Kids are Back in School, How Are They Doing? Europe Prepares for a Cold, Dark Winter. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800211/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800211/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s September 23rd. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. The nation’s kids are back in school It’s the first time for many since the COVID pandemic. So how are the kids doing, academically and socially? Well, as it turns out, not good. We’ll discuss that, plus what you and I can do to help. As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>September 22nd, 2022. Russia Escalates War, Calls for More Troops. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800212/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800212/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s September 22nd. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Russia has announced a major escalation in its War in Ukraine, with hundreds of thousands of new troops mobilized. I’ve got those details — plus three things that you should be watching for.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar. First, some bad news for Dirty Green Energy.</description></item><item><title>September 21st, 2022. China Continues to Aid in Russia's War of Attrition. NYC to House Immigrants on Cruise Ships? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800213/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800213/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s September 21st. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Welcome to a Big Five Update this morning. Five critical updates on stories we’ve covered previously that are shaping America — and the world.
First, China is helping Russia in their War of Attrition by making some big purchases of Russian energy. I’ve got the latest.
Second, an update on Dirty Green energy. A record price for Lithium means bad news for batteries.</description></item><item><title>September 20th, 2022. The US Border Continues to Leak as Over 2 Million Have Illegally Crossed Border in the Last Year. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800214/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800214/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s September 20th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Illegal migration numbers are out for August and we have set a record. Over 2M illegals have crossed into America in the past 11 months. We’ll dive into what that means and what we might do about it.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar.</description></item><item><title>September 19th, 2022. China Operating in Mexico to Avoid Tariffs. Is Ukraine Getting Too Much Help? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800215/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800215/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s September 19th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. China is using an industrial park in Mexico to cheat their way into the American marketplace. And probably to set up a den of spies. I’ll explain what we know.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar. First, a Wheat War update. We’ve got some cranky farmers in Europe, claiming Ukraine’s wheat and corn are flooding their market — not poor countries abroad.</description></item><item><title>September 16th, 2022. Railroad Strike Avoided, For Now. Biden to Give $3.5b Back to Afghanistan. A Medication for Autism? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800216/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800216/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s September 16th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Welcome to a Big Five Update this morning. Five critical updates on stories we’ve covered previously that are shaping America — and the world.
First, we’ve got an update on the potential rail-road strike some good news but not as much as some politicians might have you believe. Second, Joe Biden has decided that Afghanistan is going to get the $3.</description></item><item><title>September 15th, 2022. Dirty Green Energy: Part 4 of an Exploration Into the Corrupt and Dishonest Nature of Green Energy. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800217/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800217/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s September 15th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. We’ve got the final brief today on Dirty Green — that’s this week’s series on whether renewable energy is as green as proponents say or, instead, if it’s full of dirty secrets. Today we’re talking batteries. And I mean everything from the refiners, the manufacturers, and what happens when these specialized batteries stop working.</description></item><item><title>September 14th, 2022. Dirty Green Energy: Part 3 of an Exploration Into the Corrupt and Dishonest Nature of Green Energy. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800218/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800218/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s September 14th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Joe Biden is slated to be in Michigan today, celebrating electric vehicles and green energy. But what he probably won’t be celebrating are all the Dirty Green secrets buried inside those cars, secrets that the PDB is sharing all this week.
Today we’re talking about perhaps the dirtiest secret of all: mining for the minerals that go into the batteries that fuel the dirty green revolution.</description></item><item><title>September 13th, 2022. Dirty Green Energy: Part 2 of an Exploration Into the Corrupt and Dishonest Nature of Green Energy. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800219/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800219/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s September 13th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. It’s day two of this week’s series called Dirty Green — we’re asking whether renewable energy is really green or instead there are environmental and national security costs that people would rather we not discuss.
Yesterday we talked about Dirty Solar. And my goodness it is dirty. Today we’re talking wind energy. And we have got some dirt to discuss.</description></item><item><title>September 12th, 2022. Dirty Green Energy: Part 1 of an Exploration Into the Corrupt and Dishonest Nature of Green Energy. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800220/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800220/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s September 12th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. For years we’ve heard about dirty oil, dirty coal, and dirty natural gas. All dirty because of their environmental record, plus their tie to foreign dictators. Well today begins a five part series on Dirty Green.
We’ll explore the debate of whether renewable energy is really the picture of purity that we are so often told or whether there are dirty secrets to the environment and connections to dictators abroad.</description></item><item><title>September 9th, 2022. A Major US Railroad Strike is Near. US and Europe Buying Russian Aluminum. Putin Might Walk Away From Wheat Deal. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800221/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800221/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s September 9th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Today we are going to do a third Big Five Update this week. And I think you’re about to see why.
First, America has seven days to avert a major economic crisis, with railroad workers set to strike if a deal doesn’t come through. Second, some illegal goods are getting into America from China.</description></item><item><title>September 8th, 2022. Us Border Wars Continue to Intensify. A Future War with China? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800222/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800222/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s September 8th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Folks, we’ve got so much great news this morning that we are doing another Big Five Update. Five critical updates on stories we’ve covered previously that are shaping America — and the world.
First, a Border War update. New York City is running out of hotel rooms to house illegal migrants. They’re looking at summer camps instead.</description></item><item><title>September 7th, 2022. American Economy Heading in the Right Direction. Former CIA Director Says Republicans Are More Dangerous Than al-Qa’ida. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800223/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800223/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s September 7th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Welcome to a Big Five Update this morning. Five critical updates on stories we’ve covered previously that are shaping America — and the world.
First, some good economic news on jobs and housing. Second, some even better news for America’s ranchers.
Third, a new California law means consumers will pay more for their burger and fries.</description></item><item><title>September 6th, 2022. The Attrition War in Ukraine's Impact on Europe. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800224/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800224/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s September 6th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Today is a Special Edition of the PDB. All because of a protest in Europe.
Last Saturday, about 70,000 people in the Czech Republic gathered to protest the war in Ukraine and their outrage at higher electricity prices stemming from the war. It is the first time we’ve seen something of this magnitude over the War of Attrition — which of course is the battle between Russia, Ukraine, and the West.</description></item><item><title>September 5th, 2022. China Continues its Slave Labor Practices. Joe Biden Asks for More Money From Ukraine. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800225/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800225/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s September 5th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. It’s Labor Day — lots of us are relaxing and celebrating. But not one group of workers they’re 6,000 miles away in China, toiling in fields and factories by force. We’ll discuss what we know, how it got this bad, and what we might do to help.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>September 2nd, 2022. Updates on Our Economy; Some Good, Some Bad. Joe Biden is a National Security Nightmare. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800226/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800226/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s September 2nd. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Welcome to a special edition of the PDB this morning: We’re back to a Big Five Update. Five critical updates on stories we’ve covered previously that are shaping America — and the world.
First, some good economic news: America’s Manufacturers are holding steady in the face of a recession. Second, some bad economic news: America’s farmers are getting hit with record-setting expenses.</description></item><item><title>September 1st, 2022. A Young Male in Bend Oregon Opens Fire in a Store. Why? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800227/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800227/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s September 1st. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. It’s a Special PDB this morning. The Main Brief today and all week is chosen by you — things we’ve discussed before but updated with new information, new data, and fresh analysis. First, there was a random shooting in Bend, Oregon on Monday — the attacker killed two people before killing himself. And his story is like so many before — a young man falling into violence.</description></item><item><title>August 31st, 2022. Were Sanctions Against Russia Effective? North Korea's Leader Contracts COVID. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800228/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800228/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s August 31st. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. It’s a Special PDB this morning. The Main Brief today and all week is chosen by you — things we’ve discussed before but updated with new information, new data, and fresh analysis.
First, we are back at the ringside fight between Russia and Ukraine. Last week we used a boxing analogy to try to understand the punches being thrown, with one by America and Europe aimed at Russia’s economy.</description></item><item><title>August 30th, 2022. Climate Activists Want You to Stop Eating Meat, Will They Get Legal Backing? Two Updates from Ukraine. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800229/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800229/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s August 30th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. It’s a Special PDB this morning. The Main Brief today and all week is chosen by you — things we’ve discussed before but updated with new information, new data, and fresh analysis.
SO, FIRST UP THIS MORNING, Governments around the world want to stop climate change by slaughtering cows or taxing them out of existence.</description></item><item><title>August 29th, 2022. Vaccine Mandates: COVID vs. Flu? Cuba is Seeking Aid from the U.S. China Continues it's Attacks on a Texas Mining Company | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800230/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800230/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s August 29th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. It’s a Special PDB this morning. The Main Brief today and all week is chosen by you — things we’ve discussed before but updated with new information, new data, and fresh analysis.
First, vaccine mandates. Kids are going back to school and need certain shots. Including COVID jabs in some places. But should they?</description></item><item><title>August 26th, 2022. Big Five Update: China Gets a Heatwave During a Drought. Good News in the Wheat Wars. 150 Cops Arrested as Cartel Members in Mexico. California Bans Sales of Gas Cars. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800231/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800231/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s August 26th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Welcome to a special edition of the PDB this morning: a Big Five Update for you. Five critical updates on stories we’ve covered previously that are shaping America — and the world.
First, there’s a very bad drought and heat wave in China it’s getting worse. Odds are you will feel the effects here in America too.</description></item><item><title>August 25th, 2022. Special Brief: The Fight in Ukraine. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800232/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800232/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s August 25th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Welcome to this Special Edition of the PDB.
This week marks the six month anniversary of war in Ukraine. We have seen so many twists and turns, so many developments, that it’s been overwhelming at times. And maybe that’s why polls show Americans are kind of losing interest. A mid-July Fox News poll showed 69% of us were concerned about Russia’s invasion, but that’s down from 82% in March.</description></item><item><title>August 24th, 2022. Biden to Announce Student Debt Relief. CDC Admitted They Failed Us During COVID Response, We Have the Data to Back Up Their Guilt. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800233/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800233/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s August 24th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First, Joe Biden will likely announce today that he is canceling some of America’s student loan debt. But should he? And do people really need that debt relief? We’ll talk numbers, and why there might be a better way to help struggling students.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar.</description></item><item><title>August 23rd, 2022. How Green is Green Energy? The Chinese Government is Coming After our Cows | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800234/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800234/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s August 23rd. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First, Joe Biden is launching a national tour this week to promote his renewable energy revolution, to include electric vehicles. But here’s a question: when people plug those cars in, how green is their electric fuel? That’s an important part of this debate, and that is coming up shortly.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>August 22nd, 2022. The Hard Truth About Ukraine's Main Nuclear Plant. Chinese Coal Usage Continues to Rise. Coffee Crops are Plummeting. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800235/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800235/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s August 22nd. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First, there are lots of stories and rumors about Ukraine’s main nuclear power plant this morning. It’s not Chernobyl but a placed called Zaporizhzhia. I’m going to explain exactly what’s going on, the threats, and whether or not you should be worried.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar.</description></item><item><title>August 19th, 2022. Big Five Update: Military Equipment Left in Afghanistan. China Strengthens Ties in the South Pacific. European Energy Crisis. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800236/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800236/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s August 19th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Welcome to a special edition of the PDB this morning: another Big Five Update this week. Five critical updates on stories we’ve covered previously that are shaping America — and the world.
First, the US Department of Defense left behind a lot of military equipment in Afghanistan. How much? I’ve got new numbers.</description></item><item><title>August 18th, 2022. The CDC Admits They Handled COVID Poorly, Yet Monkeypox Response Has Seen No Improvement. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800237/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800237/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s August 18th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First, The CDC is admitting this morning that it failed during the COVID pandemic, its Director is promising to prevent such from ever happening again. But critics argue it’s too late, they’re already failing on the issue of Monkeypox. I’ll explain their argument.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar.</description></item><item><title>August 17th, 2022. Big Five Update: Biden Signs the "Climate" Bill. Electricity Prices Soar in Europe. US is Set to Increase Aid to Ukraine. Tariffs on Chinese Products. Lebanon Bank Robbery Rings Alarm Bells. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800238/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800238/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s August 17th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Welcome to a special edition of the PDB this morning: a Big Five Update. Five critical updates on stories we’ve covered previously that are shaping America — and the world.
First, Joe Biden signed the climate change bill yesterday, but there’s a problem already with solar panels and slave labor. We’ll discuss.
Second, electricity prices hit a record high in Europe yesterday, and some businesses there are starting to shut down.</description></item><item><title>August 16th, 2022. Tensions Continue to Rise Over Taiwan. Election Chaos in Kenya. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800239/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800239/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s August 16th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First, Important developments out of Taiwan this morning, with a new surprise delegation of American politicians showing up. As you’d expect, Beijing is not happy. So this morning we’re going to talk about what happens if this brewing conflict turns to war. How would a war over Taiwan affect you? That’s coming up.</description></item><item><title>August 15th, 2022. Update: Was it Legal for the FBI to Raid President Trump? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800240/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800240/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s August 15th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First, The FBI raid of the home of former President Donald Trump last week has been all over the news. But missing in the coverage is a very important Supreme Court case that suggests there is something very rotten about this raid, even unconstitutional. That’s coming up.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>August 12th, 2022. CDC Removes COVID Restrictions. Ukraine Government Orders Citizens to Purchase More Weapons. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800241/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800241/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s August 12th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First, the Center for Disease Control announced new COVID recommendations yesterday, rolling back lots of restrictions. You may have seen that story but what you probably didn’t see is that half of America plans to ignore that advice; they refuse to move on. We’re going to discuss who those people are, and why their refusal matters.</description></item><item><title>August 11th, 2022. Special Brief: Hawaii, a Case Study of Our Upcoming Energy Crisis. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800242/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800242/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s August 11th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Welcome to this Special Edition of the President’s Daily Brief. And it’s very special indeed, because America is about to undergo an energy revolution.
There is a $380B climate change bill that is set to pass the House of Representatives tomorrow following its previous passage in the Senate. After tomorrow’s vote, it heads to the desk of Joe Biden who will sign it.</description></item><item><title>August 10th, 2022. Big Five Update: Inflation. Boots on the Ground in Ukraine. Wheat Wars. Fentanyl from China. COVID Vaccines in Children. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800243/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800243/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s August 10th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. We’ve got a Big Five Update this morning. Five critical updates on five stories that are shaping America — and the world. First up, the federal government is out with inflation numbers this morning. I’ve got an update on where the all-important natural gas prices fit in that picture. Second, the Canadian and US Governments don’t want you to hear about something in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>August 9th, 2022. Breaking: Former President Donald Trump is Raided by the FBI. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800244/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800244/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s August 9th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Today is a Special Edition of the PDB. And that’s because of what happened yesterday in Florida.
The home of former president Donald Trump was raided by the FBI. So today we’re going to talk about that — what we know, what we don’t — but most especially I’m going to discuss the central question that you, me and other Americans are now going to have to wrestle with.</description></item><item><title>August 8th, 2022. Democrat Mayors Finally Start Addressing Illegal Immigration. Pelosi Visits Taiwan, China Responds. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800245/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800245/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s August 8th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First, Democrat Mayors are blasting Republican Governors in Texas and Arizona this morning for bussing illegal migrants into their towns. We’re going to look at the numbers and you can decide whether or not their outrage is warranted.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar.</description></item><item><title>August 5th, 2022. Do You Know How Many Terrorists Are in the United States? The FBI Says It Doesn’t Know Either... | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800246/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800246/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s August 5th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First, there are Afghan terrorists in America but the FBI has lost track of them. That’s the alarming admission made yesterday by the FBI Director. We’ll discuss the latest.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar. First up, the Chinese Government and its partners have bought over 200,000 acres of American land — including 300 acres near a key Air Force Base.</description></item><item><title>August 4th, 2022. Big Five Update: Wheat Wars. Ukraine/Russia. Biden and Xi. Bug-Fed Cows? Gas Prices. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800247/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800247/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s August 4th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. It’s the Big Five Update this morning on the PDB. Five briefs on five topics that I’ve discussed with you before with some important updates.
First, the Wheat Wars. On Monday the first ship out of Ukraine set sail for the Middle East. But how far did it get? I’ve got that for you.</description></item><item><title>August 3rd, 2022. ...And Then They Came for Your Food. Tensions Escalate Between US and Russia, and China and Taiwan. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800248/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800248/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s August 3rd. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First, Washington DC is targeting the nation’s cattle this morning, all because of climate change. But this is really about so much more. I’ll discuss what that is and what you can do about it.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar. First, public confirmation this morning that American intelligence is directing missile attacks against the Russians in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>August 2nd, 2022. Drone Strikes in Afghanistan Kill Al-Qa’ida Leader. Is America Headed for Civil War? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800249/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800249/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s August 2nd. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First, Al-Qa’ida’s leader Ayman al-Zawahri is dead. I’ll give you the latest on this very good news, to include what this death means in our War on Terror.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar. First, you may have seen the headlines about the horrible fires in Europe over the past couple weeks.</description></item><item><title>August 1st, 2022. The Inflation Reduction Act Will Actually Increase Inflation. Ukrainian Wheat Might Hit Finally Foreign Shores Again. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800250/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800250/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s August 1st. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First, Joe Biden’s $370B climate bill just got a thumbs down from fact checkers, saying his numbers don’t add up. I’ll share those findings, plus why this is a very bad sign for governing our country.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar. First, today is a big day for the Wheat Wars.</description></item><item><title>July 29th, 2022. The Senate Introduces Another Bill Aimed at Addressing Climate Change. Biden Tells Pelosi Not To Visit Taiwan... | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800251/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800251/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s July 29th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First up, The US Senate announced a big bill yesterday to address climate change. One of the reasons to pass it, supporters are saying, is that it gives America the moral authority to demand other nations to follow our lead. We’ll discuss whether that is convincing. As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>July 28th, 2022. Big Five Update: Biden and Xi. The Definition of Recession. Trouble for American Ranchers. Border Patrol Reports Illegal Crossings. COVID and the Common Cold. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800252/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800252/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s July 28th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. We’ve got a Big Five Update this morning, five issues that we have covered in previous podcasts, but with some important updates. First, we’ll be talking about Joe Biden’s phone call today with China.
Also today, numbers and a debate over whether we have entered a recession.
Third, America’s ranchers are getting hit hard.</description></item><item><title>July 27th, 2022. Biden Administration Attempts to Combat Corruption in Central America. Also, A Warning to Prepare for Your Next Electricity Bill. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800253/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800253/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s July 27th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First up, The State Department is on the attack against corruption in Central America this morning, all because Joe Biden and Kamala Harris think that will stop illegals from coming across our southern border. But will this war on corruption work? I’ve got the answer, coming up.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>July 26th, 2022. Biden to Speak with Xi Jinping. Monkeypox is Back in the News. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800254/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800254/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s July 26th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First, Joe Biden confirmed yesterday that he’s going to talk to China’s leadership this week, chatting about Taiwan, the economy and the climate. So this morning we’re going to dive into their climate conversation — and that China’s actually building more coal plants because they don’t have faith in renewables. We’ll discuss. As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>July 25th, 2022. CIA Director Burns Lied to Us About Afghanistan. Wheat Wars Negotiations Are Blown Up... Literally. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800255/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800255/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s July 25th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First, The CIA Director saying this morning that he is proud of the work the intelligence analysts did in Afghanistan. Which is odd, because they got it wrong. So what’s going on, and why does it matter? That’s coming up.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar.</description></item><item><title>July 22nd, 2022. Special Brief: Audience Questions | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800256/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800256/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s July 22nd. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now.
On Monday of this week, I issued you all a challenge:
Write to me with your questions about any topic, any place in the world. And even questions about me. I wanted to give you a chance to peak behind the podcast and learn more about how I bring you the PDB each day at 6am.</description></item><item><title>July 21st, 2022. Special Brief: Mexican President AMLO Laughs at Biden and Trudeau. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800257/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800257/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s July 21st. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Today is a Special Brief about a growing threat just under the radar, and just under our Southern Border.
Not the cartels this time. Not even drugs or gang violence. This morning we’re going to talk about Mexican President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador. His nickname is AMLO for short. Yesterday he said something remarkable when he was asked about a trade dispute that filed by Joe Biden and Justin Trudeau, who’s the Prime Minister of Canada.</description></item><item><title>July 20th, 2022. Joe Biden Makes Another Push Towards Green Energy, but Are the Solutions Viable? Congress Votes on the Respect for Marriage Act | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800258/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800258/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s July 20th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Email: PDB@TheFirstTV.com
First up, Joe Biden is in Massachusetts this morning, talking up green energy, and most especially off-shore wind projects. Odds are, though, he’s not going to tell America the full story about wind energy, and that it’s not that green. We’ve got a deep dive on the facts, coming up.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>July 19th, 2022. Ukraine Admits That Its Government Is Filled With Russian Spies. China Continues to Escalate Against U.S. Ships in South China Sea. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800259/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800259/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s July 19th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First up, The White House is confirming this morning that it will continue to share intelligence with Ukraine just one day after Pres. Zelynskyy admitted his government is full of Russian spies. That has major implications for our intel networks — and our $50B in aid. That’s up first.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>July 18th, 2022. Governor Abbott's "Operation Lone Star" is Lowering Illegal Immigration Rates. US Intel Warns Against Using Chinese Drones? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800260/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800260/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s July 18th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First up, some good news on America’s southern border. Fewer illegal migrants tried to cross into the country last month. And the reason? A Texas politician is playing hardball with the Mexican Government and their businesses. I’ll explain.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar.</description></item><item><title>July 15th, 2022. Just How Environmentally Friendly Is Solar Energy? France in War-Time Effort to Combat Energy Needs. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800261/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800261/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s July 15th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First up, Joe Biden is in Saudi Arabia, asking the Royal Family to please produce more oil, amongst other things. Biden’s supporters are saying this only underlines how important it is for us to go green, especially solar. But how green is solar energy? I’ve got the dirty answer to that question up next.</description></item><item><title>July 14th, 2022. Big Five Update: Wheat Wars, Inflation, Russia, COVID and Obesity, and Tony Fauci | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800262/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800262/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s July 14th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. This morning we’ve got a Big Five Update. Five Briefs on Five topics that I’ve shared with you before. So let’s get ready to go around the world.
First, some important news on the Wheat Wars. We could have a deal between Ukraine and Russia. I’ve got the very hopeful details coming up.</description></item><item><title>July 13th, 2022. Chinese COVID Policies Create Opportunity for American Manufacturing. The (Subtle) Battle for the South Pacific. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800263/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800263/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s July 13th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First up, A major steel hub in China has gone into lockdown this morning over one case of COVID. We’re going to discuss the implications of that Zero COVID policy in China and how, if our leaders handle it right, we could use it to launch a new era of American manufacturing. As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>July 12th, 2022. Joe Biden Sells US Emergency Oil Reserve to Chinese Company Affiliated with Hunter Biden. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800264/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800264/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s July 12th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First up, Joe Biden sold America’s oil to the Chinese. You probably heard about that story over the past week. But we’re going to dive deeper, because the whole story is actually even more outrageous than you’ve heard. That’s coming up.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar.</description></item><item><title>July 11th, 2022. Factories are Shutting Down as Gas Prices Continue to Rise. Mexico's President Urges Americans Not to Vote Republican. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800265/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800265/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s July 11th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First up, an aluminum mill in Kentucky is shutting down all because of the Natural Gas Wars in Europe. I’ll explain what’s going on, and why it could get worse.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar. First, Mexico’s president is on his way to Washington DC this morning.</description></item><item><title>July 8th, 2022; Special Brief: FBI Director Warns of Chinese Cyber Attacks. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800266/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800266/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s July 8th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. The FBI Director stepped up his assault on China this week, with special anger directed at Beijing’s cyber attacks. He said that those cyber crimes are a bigger threat than every other major country — combined. But as righteous as those words are, they’re not the first time that we’ve heard them.
During this morning’s special PDB, we’re going to quickly cover decades worth Washington DC’s attempts to deal with China — either by negotiations or strongly worded speeches.</description></item><item><title>July 7th, 2022. 5 Major Updates on the President's Daily Brief. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800267/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800267/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s July 7th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. Today is all about updates. Five Big Updates on five big briefs that I’ve shared with you previously from around the world. First up, the Drone Wars. Ukraine used them to great effect in the early stages of their war against Russia. But now? Not so much. I’ll explain why.
Second, COVID in China.</description></item><item><title>July 6th, 2022. Pentagon Admits That Weapons Sent to Ukraine are Difficult to Track. Gas Prices are Down Over the Last 21 Days? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800268/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800268/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s July 6th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First up, the Pentagon admitting that it has very little control over where weapons go once they reach Ukraine. We’re going to discuss the risk of that startling admission, and what you can do to fix it.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar. First, gas prices are down over the past 21 days.</description></item><item><title>July 5th, 2022. Biden Blames Gas Stations for High Prices, Is There Any Truth Behind His Statements? Zuckerberg Warns of Mass Lay Offs | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800269/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800269/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s July 5th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First up, Joe Biden attacked gas stations over the holiday weekend, adding to his list of reasons for why you are paying more at the pump. But is he right? And if not, why he’s doing it? We’ll discuss the facts.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar.</description></item><item><title>July 4th, 2022. Special Brief: Hugh Francis Redmond | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800270/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800270/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s July 4th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. On July 4th, 1967, a man named Hugh Redmond sat in a Chinese prison. His captors had allowed him to write his family on rare occasion. And on that particular day he penned what would be his final letter. He wrote, “It just dawned on me that today is the Fourth of July. Did you have a big celebration with fireworks and all?</description></item><item><title>July 1st, 2022. SCOTUS Issues Major Ruling Over Climate Change Regulations. China Tries to Stop US From Sourcing Rare Earth Metals. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800271/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800271/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s July 1st. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First, the Supreme Court ruled yesterday that environmental regulators are not allowed to issue sweeping regulations due to climate change. Only Congress, they said, has that authority. We’re going to talk about that case, and why it’s really about who controls our lives.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar.</description></item><item><title>June 30th, 2022. Illegal Migrant Tragedy in Texas. Climate Change Policies at the Gas Pump. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800272/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800272/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s June 30th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First up, you’ve seen the headlines about the terrible incident in Texas where 53 illegal migrants were killed in the back of a tractor trailer. But there is so much more to this story, and I’ve got details that you need to hear.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar.</description></item><item><title>June 29th, 2022. A Major Leak from the Biden Administration; Ukraine Can Not Win Without Our Support. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800273/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800273/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s June 29th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First up, an astonishing leak out of the Biden Administration yesterday, saying that Ukraine is not going to win without us and they’re going to have to give up some territory to the Russians. We’ll discuss.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar. First, if you tried to buy a home lately but you got outbid, it might have been because your competition were professional flippers.</description></item><item><title>June 28th, 2022. The FDA Approves COVID-19 Vaccines in Children Over 6 Months Old. China Commits to COVID Zero for 5 More Years | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800274/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800274/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s June 28th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First up, there’s a major new study out of Israel this morning on kids and COVID. Specifically whether kids get natural immunity once they’ve been infected, and how that stacks up to the vaccines. I’ve got the answers, coming up.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar.</description></item><item><title>June 27th, 2022. Roe v. Wade Overturned. The Cost of Electric Vehicles Continues to Increase. Social Unrest Returning to France? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800275/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800275/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s June 27th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First up, You’ve seen the headlines, the Supreme Court has overturned Roe vs. Wade. We’re going to talk about how we might handle what comes next — using an old experiment out of Colorado and a very personal story of mine as inspiration. As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar.</description></item><item><title>June 24th, 2022. Amidst Record High Gas Prices, the President of the Nation With the Highest Gas/Oil Exports Wants to Double Down on Renewable Energy | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800276/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800276/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s June 24th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First up, A new argument yesterday from Joe Biden that renewable energy is really about national security. But will solar and wind energy really keep us safer from foreign influence? I have the answer, coming up.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar. Word out of Mexico this morning that the Biden Administration has offered up 300,000 new visas to hopeful migrants, many of whom are waiting on the border.</description></item><item><title>June 23rd, 2022. India Is Purchasing a Massive Amount of Russian Oil, and Trying to Hide It. Russia Is Targeting the US in Cyber Attacks. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800277/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800277/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s June 23rd. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First up, the War of Attrition between Russia and Ukraine got a big jolt this week from an unlikely place: India. We’re going to talk about what Government in New Delhi is doing that will prop up Moscow and why that makes Ukraine more financially dependent on you.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>June 22nd, 2022. Did Russia Just Attack America? The FBI is Investigating | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800278/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800278/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s June 22nd. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First up, the Russians may have attacked America. There was a possible cyber attack a couple weeks ago in Texas that could be connected to the natural gas wars that I briefed you on yesterday. It’s a big story, and it’s coming up.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar.</description></item><item><title>June 21st, 2022. Putin Reduces Supply of Gas to Europe Causing an Energy Crisis and a Return to Coal. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800279/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800279/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s June 21st. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First up, Europe is in a major crisis running out of natural gas this morning to power the continent. And they’re scrambling to replace it with coal. We’re going to talk about what’s going on and why it matters to people here in America.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>June 20th, 2022. The War in Ukraine Could Go On for Years. A Left-Wing Terrorist Wins Power in Colombia. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800280/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800280/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s June 20th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First up, the War in the Ukraine could go on for years. That is the latest assessment from NATO leadership. I’ll explain why that means a very big bill for American taxpayers.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar. First, a former left-wing terrorist just won the presidency in Colombia.</description></item><item><title>June 17th, 2022. Our Southern Border Continues to Worsen. A Link Between Childhood Obesity and Dementia? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800281/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800281/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s June 17th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First up, America broke a record last month; it’s the number of arrests of illegal migrants. We’re going to talk about who these folks are, and what message this sends to our enemies around the world.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar. First, we’ve got some weird weather going on, and it’s all because of La Niña.</description></item><item><title>June 16th, 2022. Joe Biden Lies About the Causes of High Gas Prices. China Uses Smartphones to Punish Protestors. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800282/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800282/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s June 16th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. First up, Joe Biden said yesterday that oil and gas prices are up because oil companies aren’t doing their part, they’re not being patriotic. Which is pretty bold for him to say. We’re going to talk about why he said it, and whether he’s right.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>June 15th, 2022. An Update on Wheat Wars, Mining, and COVID Statistics, | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800283/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800283/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s June 15th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. I’ve got some big updates, my friends. Three Big Stories, Three Big Updates. So get out those maps — in your minds or on your computer screens — because we are going around the world this morning.
First Up: Wheat Wars. Some good news, some bad news, and some news that’s… well, could be good but let’s see what happens news.</description></item><item><title>June 14th, 2022. Special Brief: The History of Fake News. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800284/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800284/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s June 14th. You’re listening to a special edition of the President’s Daily Brief. If you have listened to the PDB since the beginning, you will likely remember this edition of the PDB. Unfortunately, Bryan has fallen ill and so we have returned to one of our favorite briefs that a large portion of our audience still has not yet heard. &amp;ldquo;Fake news&amp;rdquo; isn&amp;rsquo;t new. We have had biased, leaning, and flat-out misleading news for a very long time.</description></item><item><title>June 13th, 2022. Why Inflation Continues to Rise Even Higher. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800285/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800285/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s June 13th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now.
First up, Record inflation reported late last week, worst in 40 years. I’m going to explain how DC politics around natural gas and diesel are driving a big part of it.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar.</description></item><item><title>June 10th, 2022. American Leadership is Failing in South America. China Initiates Another Lockdown. Direct Connection Between Lockdowns and Dementia. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800286/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800286/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s June 10th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now.
First, Joe Biden is hosting leaders from North and South America this week. Well actually, not all of them. And that’s a problem. I’m going to explain why their absence was a dangerous failure of American leadership.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>June 9th, 2022. New Zealand is Proposing a Gas (and Burp) Tax. Should America Legalize Drugs? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800287/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800287/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s June 9th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now.
First, New Zealand is planning to tax cows based on how much they burp and — ahem — pass gas. It’s all part of a plan to stop climate change — and you might help pay for it. We’ll discuss.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>June 8th, 2022. Special Brief: Biden Lifts Tariffs Against China Helping Them Continue to Steal Our Economy | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800288/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800288/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s June 8th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now.
On Monday, Joe Biden waived tariffs on foreign solar panels. Now that didn’t get a lot of press probably because, well, it’s about solar panels. Not exactly the stuff of great consequence. But actually it is. It’s a really big deal. And I’m going to explain why.</description></item><item><title>June 7th, 2022. Afghanistan is an Al-Qaeda Safe Haven. Wheat Wars Continue. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800289/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800289/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s June 7th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now.
First up, Afghanistan has once again become a safe haven for al-Qa’ida. We’re going to talk about the latest from Kabul, including when you should expect that al-Qa’ida will be able to hit the American homeland once again.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>June 6th, 2022. Biden Sends Weapons Directly to Neo-Nazi Battalion. North Korea Launches More Missiles. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800290/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800290/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s June 6th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now.
First up, confirmation that the Joe Biden Administration has sent weapons to the Azov Battalion, which is a group of neo-Nazis fighting in Ukraine. That startling news broke over the weekend. We’ll discuss it.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>June 3rd, 2022. America’s Economic Dependence on Globalism Is About to Cause a Major Problem. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800291/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800291/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s June 3rd. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now.
First up, the economic war between Russia and the West took another bad turn yesterday. It has to do with neon gas, of all things. We’re going to discuss the potential major impact it could have on your family and this country.
As always, I’m watching a few other stories this morning, all updates from past briefs.</description></item><item><title>June 2nd, 2022. What Do We Do About School Shootings? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800292/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800292/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s June 2nd. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now.
First up, How can we prevent school shootings? There’s a new study out this morning that offers a possible solution, and it’s one that we can all take part in. I’ll discuss the latest.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>June 1st, 2022. Lockdowns Destroyed Our Immune Systems. Coffee Drinkers Rejoice, You Live Longer Than Non-coffee Drinkers. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800293/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800293/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s June 1st. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now.
First up, There’s a virus down in Australia that’s doing stuff that it’s not supposed to. And all because of COVID lockdowns. We’re going to talk about how it could affect you — and America. As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>May 31st, 2022. China Moves Closer to Hawaii. Update on Wheat Shortage. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800294/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800294/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s May 31st. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now.
First up, China is very busy in the South Pacific today, turning another island nation effectively into one of its bases. And that means the Communists are one step closer to Hawaii. I’ll update you on the latest.
As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>May 30th, 2022. The Memorial Day Brief. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800295/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800295/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s May 30th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now.
Friends, it’s a very busy time these days — for news, for all of our hectic lives — but for a moment we pause for Memorial Day to commemorate those who died in military service for the United States.
As we honor those men and women, I’d like to tell you a story about a man who wore the uniform — for the US Army — and then later served as a CIA Officer.</description></item><item><title>May 27th, 2022. The Escalation in the Ukraine, a Special Brief. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800296/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800296/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s May 27th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now.
This morning we’re going to talk about escalation and the odds of World War III, sparked by Russia’s invasion of Ukraine. Because whether you realize or not, we are at the closest point we’ve been to a global war than at any other time recent history.</description></item><item><title>May 26th, 2022. Cuba’s Sugar Crops Suffer, How Does This Impact the US? Putin Acts to Secure Russian Support | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800297/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800297/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s May 26th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now.
First up, There’s a new immigration crisis to report. Not from Mexico though, but Cuba. We’ll talk about what’s happening.
Your second brief, If you didn’t get sick during the COVID crisis — and I mean sick from any virus or bacteria — then that might be a very bad thing.</description></item><item><title>May 25th, 2022. North Korea Sends Missiles Towards Tokyo. COVID Variants Are Getting Weaker, Confirmed. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800298/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800298/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s May 25th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now.
First up, Joe Biden is back in DC after his big trip to Asia. North Korea gave him a parting gift as he left: three missiles. I’ll explain.
Your second brief, Ukraine’s President is saying that the only way its war with Russia ends is through diplomacy, not the battlefield.</description></item><item><title>May 24th, 2022: Russia Selling Stolen Wheat. Why Kabul Fell in Weeks. Biden Announced That We Will Aid Taiwan If Invaded By China. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800299/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800299/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s May 24th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now.
First up: There’s Ukrainian wheat getting out of the Black Sea this morning, but the ships aren’t being sailed by Ukrainian captains. They’re Russian. We have satellite imagery that we need to discuss.
Second: The Intel Community failed to predict what would happen in Afghanistan.</description></item><item><title>May 23rd, 2022. US/Mexico Relations Continue to Decline. Russia Denies Her Role in Wheat Shortage. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800300/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800300/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s May 23rd. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now. First up, Mexico is clamping down, but not on the bad guys. Mexico’s president is instead targeting America and a 30 year old program to stop the cartels. I’ll explain what’s happening. And as always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar.</description></item><item><title>May 20th, 2022. US And NATO Sending New Missiles to Ukraine. Monkeypox Outbreak? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800301/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800301/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s May 20th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now. First up, there’s a big development in Ukraine this morning. And it has to do with new missiles that can sink Russian ships. We’re going to discuss this weaponry and how it could lead to a major escalation. And as always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>May 19th, 2022. Special Brief: The Emerging Food Crisis. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800302/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800302/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s May 19th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now. This morning is a special brief, an update on the warnings we all heard back in March that the world was facing a food crisis because of the war in Ukraine. I’m sorry to report that the crisis has in fact begun most especially in regards to wheat.</description></item><item><title>May 18th, 2022. North Korean Super Hackers. US Intel Community Failures in Ukraine. Student Loan Forgiveness? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800303/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800303/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s May 18th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now. First up, North Korea is sending out the troops this morning. But not the ones you’d expect. We’re talking cyber warriors. We’ll discuss the latest and why you should care. Your second brief, The US intelligence community is admitting that it botched key predictions in both Ukraine and Afghanistan over the past year.</description></item><item><title>May 17th, 2022. Biden Threatens Americans By Removing Chinese Tariffs. Mexican Cartel Targeting American Children. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800304/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800304/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s May 17th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now. First up, Joe Biden is thinking about dropping tariffs against China. But there’s a spy in prison this morning that helps us understand why he shouldn’t. I’ll explain. Your second brief, If you’re looking for a good paying job, you might consider being a CEO for health insurance company.</description></item><item><title>May 16th, 2022. Sweden and Finland Look to Join NATO. Venezuela Asks for Support as Socialism Fails Again. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800305/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800305/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s May 16th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now. First up, Finland and Sweden are joining NATO. Well, maybe. We’re going to talk about what’s happening and how it could impact America. Your second brief, Graduation season is here, but not for some Air Force Academy cadets. And it has to do with the COVID vaccine.</description></item><item><title>May 13th, 2022: Mexican President's Cartel Policy: Hugs, Not Bullets? COVID and your Cash. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800306/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800306/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s May 13th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now. First up, Mexico’s president said yesterday that we should treat Cartel members kindly because they’re people, just like you and I. We’re going to talk about why he said that, and what it means for America. And as always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>May 12th, 2022. The Worst Drug in the West... | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800307/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800307/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s May 12th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now. Today is a special brief, and that&amp;rsquo;s because the CDC just announced that the number one cause of death for Americans between the ages of 18-45, is drug overdose, All up next on the President’s Daily Brief. Please remember to subscribe if you enjoyed this episode of the President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief.</description></item><item><title>May 11th, 2022. Illegal Protests Outside Supreme Court Judges' Homes. The US Commits $40 Billion to Ukraine. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800308/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800308/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s May 11th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now. First up, Protests continue at the homes of multiple Supreme Court justices. The White House says that’s a good thing. We’re going to talk about what that means for the country. Your second brief, The US House passed a bill last night giving Ukraine nearly $40B, with one Republican Senator saying the money is going to the most important issue facing the country.</description></item><item><title>May 10th, 2022. White House Claims 100m COVID Cases Incoming... | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800309/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800309/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s May 10th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now. First up, The Biden Administration is forecasting 100M new COVID cases this winter. And that could mean very bad news for America’s kids. We’re going to talk about why. Your second brief, The Governor of Texas says that his state shouldn’t have to pay for the schooling of children here illegally.</description></item><item><title>May 9th, 2022. American Generals Keep Pushing US Closer to War with Russia. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800310/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800310/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s May 9th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now. First up, America’s spies and Generals are pushing us closer to war with Russia. I’m going to explain how, and why they might be doing it. Your second brief, Democrats have a big protest planned today at the home a Supreme Court Justice, all because of the Roe v Wade debate.</description></item><item><title>May 6th, 2022: Who Is Entering The U.S. Illegally? China Has Learned Important Lessons From Russia's Invasion of Ukraine. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800311/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800311/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s May 6th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now. First up, Illegal immigration. There have been at least one million illegal immigrants crossing our southern border since Joe Biden came into office. We’re going to talk about who exactly they are. Your second brief, China is learning some big lessons from Russia’s poor performance in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>May 5th, 2022. The CDC Has Been Tracking Your Location. China is Moving in the Pacific. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800312/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800312/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s May 5th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now. First up, the CDC was tracking you during the pandemic. Your second brief, China is making a serious move in the Pacific, establishing a military relationship with the Solomon Islands. And as always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put these two on your radar.</description></item><item><title>May 4th, 2022. Roe v. Wade Leak Is Real, What Is the Reason It Was Leaked? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800313/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800313/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s May 4th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now. First up, There’s heated debate over the leaked Supreme Court ruling, specifically who leaked it? I’m going to explain who I think it is, and why you should care. Your second brief, Mexican Cartels, they’re poaching endangered animals and then trading them for drugs with their Chinese partners.</description></item><item><title>May 3rd, 2022. Proposed Authorization for a Strike Against Moscow. Supreme Court Overturning Roe v. Wade? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800314/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800314/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s May 3rd. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now. First, a new proposition that gives President Biden the authority to launch a direct strike against Moscow. Second, Biden is considering student loan relief of $10,000, that isn&amp;rsquo;t enough for AOC. As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put this one on your radar.</description></item><item><title>May 2nd, 2022. Your Grocery Bill Will Keep Inflating. Russian Spy... Dolphins? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800315/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800315/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s May 2nd. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now. First up, Oil Wars. The kind you put in your mouth — specifically, sunflower and palm oil. Prices are going up for both, and so too is your grocery bill. Your second brief, Swimming lessons in Nicaragua - illegals to learn how to better cross the Rio Grande River and into the United States.</description></item><item><title>April 30th, 2022. Special Brief: The History of Fake News. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800316/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800316/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s April 30th. You’re listening to a special edition of the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. &amp;ldquo;Fake news&amp;rdquo; isn&amp;rsquo;t new. We have had biased, leaning, and flat-out misleading news for a very long time. From William Randolph Heart and Joseph Pulitzer to the 2016 Presidential Election, this special brief takes a look at the history of fake news. Also, a suggestion on how to combat the urge to stop reading after the headline, Please remember to subscribe if you enjoyed this episode of the President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief.</description></item><item><title>April 29th, 2022. Yet Another Escalation in Ukraine. U.S. Government is Asking Doctors About Their Race. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800317/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800317/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s April 29th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now. First, another escalation in Ukraine, financially and otherwise. Your second brief, Doctors in Colorado are being asked to disclose their race and sexual orientation to the state. As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put this one on your radar. Workers in Mexico are asking for a raise, from $3/hour to $6/hour, I&amp;rsquo;ll tell you why this might matter to you,.</description></item><item><title>April 28th, 2022. China is Stealing Intellectual Property Again. Fauci Says COVID is Over! | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800318/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800318/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s April 28th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now. First, Tony Fauci just announced that the COVID pandemic is over in America. So what comes next? Your second brief, China is stealing our Intellectual Property again. As always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories. Put this one on your radar. The Biden Administration announced a new Disinformation Governance Board to protect you from Fake News.</description></item><item><title>April 27th, 2022. U.S. Escalates Intentions in Ukraine. Chinese Border Patrol... Geese? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800319/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800319/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s April 27th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now. First up, Ukraine. Some big news out of our nation’s capital about the escalating war effort. Your second brief, do you remember when we talked about an outbreak of hepatitis in kids? There is a possible COVID connection. And, as always, I’m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>April 26th, 2022. Drone Wars in Ukraine. An Incoming Subpoena for Twitter Executives? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800320/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800320/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s April 26th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now. First, the Supreme Court is hearing a case today that might determine border security for a generation. I have an update on Mexican lawmakers who are angry at Joe Biden. Your second brief, Drone Wars. We’re pumping Ukraine full of drones. The Russians and Chinese are too.</description></item><item><title>April 25th, 2022. New Data on COVID in Children. New Solutions to U.S. Inflation. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800321/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800321/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s April 25th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now. Your first brief this morning, COVID and kids. A new headline says you should be worried about children getting sick with the virus. But a closer look at the data tells a different story. Your second brief, Inflation. It’s hurting all us terribly. But if you’re looking for good news on this front — and maybe a new job — you’ll want to listen to this brief.</description></item><item><title>April 23rd, 2022. Special Brief: A Disinformation Campaign? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800322/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800322/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s April 23rd. You’re listening to a special edition of the President’s Daily Brief. Your morning intel starts now. With Barack Obama and Hilary Clinton pronouncing a war on disinformation; are they truly looking to protect democracy? Please remember to subscribe if you enjoyed this episode of the President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>April 22nd, 2022. Philadelphia Reverses Mask Mandate. Border Patrol Morale at All-Time Low. | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800323/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800323/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s April 22nd. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now. First up, Philadelphia reinstated its mask mandate, but last night, they dropped it. Second, the US Border Patrol is suffering from low morale. But it’s not just US agents; it’s also something that’s crippling Mexican Patrol Officers. I’ll explain why that’s important. Lastly, the War in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>President's Daily Brief - April 21st, 2022 | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800324/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800324/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s April 21st. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now. First up, the Biden administration is appealing their loss of the mask mandate, but they&amp;rsquo;re admitting this warning that the appeal isn&amp;rsquo;t based on public health, it&amp;rsquo;s about power. Second, the secret service has said that it has no records about who visits the president when he goes to his homes in Delaware.</description></item><item><title>President's Daily Brief - April 20th, 2022 | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800325/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800325/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s April 19th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now. First up, Joe Biden is having a hard time tracking where all those weapons are going once they get to Ukraine. Second, it appears that the Biden administration is on the March to forgive student loans. And as always, I&amp;rsquo;m keeping an eye out for developing stories.</description></item><item><title>President's Daily Brief - April 19th, 2022 | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800326/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800326/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s April 19th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now. First up, mask mandates it judges ruled them unlawful on public transport, but there&amp;rsquo;s a scandal buried in this decision. Second, terror at the border, amongst the record number of illegal crossers, likely terrorists. Finally, a Democrat Senator says us troops may be needed in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>President's Daily Brief - April 18th, 2022 | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800327/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800327/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s April 18th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now. First up, there are Chinese companies shutting down because of a COVID outbreak that will affect our economy and your wallet. Second, President Zelensky wants an additional $50 billion from the United States for aid. Finally, we&amp;rsquo;re going to talk about sacrifice. Joe Biden has asked you and your family for it.</description></item><item><title>President's Daily Brief - April 15th, 2022 | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800328/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800328/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s April 15th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now. First up, a Twitter takeover. The world’s richest man wants to buy the social media platform. Second, the CIA Director held his first public speech yesterday. I’m going to tell you three things that you need to know, and why some of it was flat wrong.</description></item><item><title>President's Daily Brief - April 14th, 2022 | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800329/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800329/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s April 14th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now. First up, we have credible reports that the Biden Administration is dramatically expanding the tactical and operational intelligence that it gives Kiev. Second, lots of updates on the border. The Governor of Texas is following up on his promises to ensure we have a southern border.</description></item><item><title>President's Daily Brief - April 13th, 2022 | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800330/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800330/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s April 13th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now. First up, inflation, and what a number I have for you; it&amp;rsquo;s a 40 year record. We&amp;rsquo;re going to talk about that and how you can make it through these very tough times. Second, everybody knows that communist China is bad. Well, except for Hunter Biden and &amp;ldquo;the Big Guy.</description></item><item><title>President's Daily Brief - April 12th, 2022 | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800331/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800331/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s April 12th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now. First up, new COVID mask rules in Philadelphia. But that runs contrary to what even Tony Fauci has said. We’ll talk about that. Second up, ghost guns. Joe Biden released a new federal rule that regulates these weapons. Is that a good development or bad?</description></item><item><title>President's Daily Brief - April 11th, 2022 | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800332/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800332/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s April 11th. You’re listening to the President’s Daily Brief. I’m your host and former CIA Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Your morning intel starts now. First, A jury found late last week that the nation’s top law enforcement officials had entrapped your fellow Americans and encouraged them to commit terrorism. Second, the latest on the war in Ukraine. Ukrainians are showing up on the southern border of the United States.</description></item><item><title>What is the Presidential Daily Brief? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800334/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800334/</guid><description>Podcast Description The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief (PDB) is a top-secret document produced and given each morning to the president of the United States, and is also distributed to a small number of top-level US officials who are approved by the president, and includes highly classified intelligence analysis, information about covert operations of the US Central Intelligence Agency. Now, you can have your own PDB, in the form of this podcast - hosted by Bryan Dean Wright.</description></item><item><title>Who is Bryan Dean Wright? | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800333/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800333/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bryan Dean Wright, Host of the Presidential Daily Brief podcast, grew up in Oregon, served in the CIA abroad for more than a decade. Originally a Democrat, Bryan watched with alarm as his lifelong party increasingly embraced bigotry, violence, and un-American attacks against his fellow citizens. He’s now focused on combating those destructive forces, giving life to the America First movement within the Republican Party. He has written about this political journey for multiple press outlets — from Fox News.</description></item><item><title>President's Daily Brief - April 8th, 2022 | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800335/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800335/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today&amp;rsquo;s PDB - a stunning report out of the intelligence community. They&amp;rsquo;re releasing unvetted, unreliable intelligence to the press regarding the war on Ukraine. Next, the FBI has apparently hacked into American companies over the past several weeks, all to patch, holes and computer networks that could have been otherwise exploited by Russian cyber attackers. An alarming update on who America is funding in Ukraine. Including information about the infamous Azov Battalion.</description></item><item><title>President's Daily Brief - April 6th, 2022 | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800336/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800336/</guid><description>Podcast Description This morning&amp;rsquo;s brief, we&amp;rsquo;re covering the following first, the ongoing saga of Hunter Biden. You&amp;rsquo;re paying for his protection on the beaches of Malibu, in case you didn&amp;rsquo;t know, you won&amp;rsquo;t believe how much that costs. Next, more bad news on inflation. I&amp;rsquo;m sorry to say, you&amp;rsquo;re going to pay more for wheat oil and gas. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain why and what you can do to soften the blow. Third, we have the results of a focus group of Democrat voters, and they are not happy; especially about crime rates.</description></item><item><title>'The President's Daily Brief ' Trailer | The President's Daily Brief</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8944800337/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8944800337/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each morning, the President of the United States receives a highly classified briefing on the most important issues facing the country &amp;ndash; The President&amp;rsquo;s Daily Brief. Now you can hear your very own PDB, in the form of a podcast hosted by former CIA Operations Officer Bryan Dean Wright. Each morning at 6am Eastern, he&amp;rsquo;ll bring you 20 minutes of the most important topics of the day and why you should care, arming you with what you need to know to help solve America&amp;rsquo;s most pressing challenges.</description></item></channel></rss>