<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TED Talks Daily on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/ted-talks-daily/</link><description>Recent content in TED Talks Daily on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 07:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/ted-talks-daily/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why AI will spark exponential economic growth | Cathie Wood | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690169/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Investor Cathie Wood explores this unique moment in technology, which she sees as being marked by the simultaneous evolution of five pivotal innovation platforms — a scenario unparalleled in history. Exploring the role of AI in reshaping economic paradigms, she predicts a surge in global GDP growth and productivity, underscoring the need for businesses and investors to adapt in order to keep up.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What happens as we die? | Kathryn Mannix | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690168/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have we lost the practical wisdom of what happens as people die? With lessons from a career witnessing thousands of people&amp;rsquo;s final breaths, palliative care expert Kathryn Mannix urges us to demystify the experience of death, sharing how a better understanding of what actually happens can reduce fear in the final days, for you and your loved ones.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to build a global pro-democracy movement | Yordanos Eyoel | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690167/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 15:35:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690167/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;Democracy is the most compelling vision we have for self-governance,&amp;rdquo; says freedom advocate Yordanos Eyoel. Taking a stand against predatory and opportunist authoritarian forces, she shares how to reimagine, accelerate and protect the pro-democracy movement — to build societies that are both functional and inclusive.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why helping people makes you happy | Asha Curran | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690166/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 15:56:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690166/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;We underestimate the power of our own generous actions,&amp;rdquo; says Asha Curran, CEO of the global generosity movement GivingTuesday. Sharing stories of people making a difference through simple acts of kindness, she shows how generosity, even in its simplest forms, can be a transformative force — and explains why we all benefit from a world grounded in giving.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Time is running out on climate change. The metaverse could help | Cedrik Neike | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690165/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 15:57:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690165/</guid><description>Podcast Description The metaverse could be our key to making real progress in the fight against climate change, says engineer Cedrik Neike. Examining how AI-powered modeling eliminates the trial and error of wasteful industries, he explores how this emerging technology is already improving everything from the gigafactories that churn out electric car batteries to the fuel efficiency of your home. Learn more about how these &amp;ldquo;digital twins&amp;rdquo; are transforming the world — and not a moment too soon.</description></item><item><title>The transformative potential of AGI — and when it might arrive | Shane Legg and Chris Anderson | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690163/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690163/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the cofounder of Google DeepMind, Shane Legg is driving one of the greatest transformations in history: the development of artificial general intelligence (AGI). He envisions a system with human-like intelligence that would be exponentially smarter than today&amp;rsquo;s AI, with limitless possibilities and applications. In conversation with head of TED Chris Anderson, Legg explores the evolution of AGI, what the world might look like when it arrives — and how to ensure it&amp;rsquo;s built safely and ethically.</description></item><item><title>Life lessons from Beethoven's Symphony No. 9 | Benjamin Zander | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 15:45:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Legendary conductor Benjamin Zander explains his view on the difference between &amp;ldquo;positive thinking&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;possibility&amp;rdquo; (one&amp;rsquo;s a fraud; the other&amp;rsquo;s the real thing, he says) and intersperses delightful stories from a lifetime in music with a sing-along to Beethoven&amp;rsquo;s Symphony No. 9.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How stress drains your brain — and what to do about it | Nicole Byers | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690002/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you ever feel extra forgetful? Stress could be the culprit. In a fascinating talk about how your memory works, neuropsychologist Nicole Byers shares the science behind how stress drains your brain&amp;rsquo;s resources, making it harder to remember things and easier to make mistakes. But fear not: she also shares a simple solution to recharge your brain and get your memory back on track.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The dark side of competition in AI | Liv Boeree | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690003/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Competition is a core part of human nature, and it can drive us to extraordinary feats. But when it goes wrong, the results can be devastating. Poker champion and science communicator Liv Boeree introduces us to &amp;ldquo;Moloch&amp;rsquo;s trap&amp;rdquo; — the dark force of game theory driving many of humanity&amp;rsquo;s biggest social problems, which is now threatening to derail the AI industry.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What will happen to marketing in the age of AI? | Jessica Apotheker | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 15:57:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Generative AI is poised to transform the workplace, but we still need human brains for new ideas, says marketing expert Jessica Apotheker. She explores how marketers can find their niche in the world of AI based on their preference for data or creativity, offering a pragmatic and hopeful look at the future of business.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to find humor in life's absurdity | Maira Kalman | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 15:55:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690005/</guid><description>Podcast Description With levity and profound insight, artist Maira Kalman reflects on life, death, dinner parties, not knowing the right answers, the joys of eating a hot dog from a street vendor and more. This talk, interwoven with her delightful paintings, is itself an artwork that seems to hold the entirety of life in all its absurd glory.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to stop the next pandemic? Stop deforestation | Neil Vora | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690006/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 15:58:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Clearing tropical forests isn&amp;rsquo;t just dangerous to the natural world — it&amp;rsquo;s also a threat to human health and wellbeing, says physician Neil Vora. Tracing how environmental devastation led to deadly epidemics like Ebola, he presents three ways deforestation unleashes disease and calls on each of us to help preserve the delicate ecological balance we depend upon.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Democracy works — we just need better leaders | Lindiwe Mazibuko | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 16:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690007/</guid><description>Podcast Description South Africa transitioned to democracy in the 1990s with a visionary constitution, but the promises of that constitution are largely unfulfilled to this day. Public leader Lindiwe Mazibuko explores how poor leadership failed to deliver a better life for the country&amp;rsquo;s citizens — and shares her mission to cultivate a new generation of ethical leaders who can revitalize democracy in South Africa and beyond.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A playbook for financing climate solutions | Nili Gilbert and David Blood | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690008/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tackling climate change costs a lot of money — and the financial sector is key to getting that money flowing. In a wide-ranging conversation, sustainable investment leaders Nili Gilbert and David Blood discuss where progress is being made on climate solutions, where capital still needs to move faster and why this is an unprecedented opportunity for sustainable growth.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The science behind how sickness shapes your mood | Keely Muscatell | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690009/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Your immune system is more socially aware than you think, says social neuroscientist and psychology professor Keely Muscatell. Investigating the interconnectedness of your mood and your inflammatory system, she offers an evolutionary reason as to why being sick may make you feel depressed — and vice versa.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to harness abundant, clean energy for 10 billion people | Julio Friedmann | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 15:57:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690010/</guid><description>Podcast Description We can produce abundant, sustainable and cheap energy — for everyone, says physicist Julio Friedmann. He explores the infrastructure, innovation and investment needed to supply energy to 10 billion people, offering case studies from Chile&amp;rsquo;s refurbished supply chain, built in partnership with Japan, to Namibia&amp;rsquo;s budding clean hydrogen production, inviting us to envision a greener, more equitably powered world.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Can we hack photosynthesis to feed the world? | Steve Long | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 15:50:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Photosynthesis is one of the most important processes on the planet, helping produce the food we eat and the air we breathe. Crop scientist Steve Long thinks it could be more efficient — and he&amp;rsquo;s intent on giving it a boost. He shows how hacking photosynthesis could help feed the world all while reducing climate change.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Life on the frontlines of war reporting | Jane Ferguson | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690012/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 15:45:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Covering global war stories can be hard and thankless — but it&amp;rsquo;s critical work if the rest of us are to understand what&amp;rsquo;s really going on in the world. For nearly two decades, journalist Jane Ferguson has reported on hostilities across Africa and the Middle East, and she&amp;rsquo;s witnessed firsthand the changing face of her profession. Via stories of her own experiences at the heart of complex conflicts, she shares fascinating details of how she and other female colleagues have changed the way that news is captured, shared — and understood.</description></item><item><title>The case for a new Great Migration in the US | Charles M. Blow | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 15:51:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Social progress in the United States often seems to take two steps forward and one step back, with hard-fought civil rights wins countered by a seemingly inevitable backlash. In this spirited talk, writer Charles M. Blow makes the case that history, inverted, suggests a potential path forward. It&amp;rsquo;s an unapologetically provocative proposal that Blow thinks just might spark a real shift toward equality in the US.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How gratitude rewires your brain | Christina Costa | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690014/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690014/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a psychologist who studies well-being ends up with a brain tumor, what happens when she puts her own research into practice? Christina Costa goes beyond the &amp;ldquo;fight&amp;rdquo; narrative of cancer &amp;ndash; or any formidable personal journey &amp;ndash; to highlight the brain benefits of an empowering alternative to fostering resilience in the face of unexpected challenges: gratitude.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Are you really as good at something as you think? | Robin Kramer | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690015/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Does confidence equal competence? Not quite. In a talk that will make you better aware of yourself, experimental psychologist Robin Kramer delves into the Dunning-Kruger effect — which argues that those who are least capable often overestimate their skills the most — and explores just how good you are at judging your own abilities.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why you shouldn't trust boredom | Kevin H. Gary | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you actually bored, or is something else going on? Educator Kevin H. Gary shares three practical takeaways to deal with the doldrums, so you can take control of your attention, figure out which feelings to trust and name the real problem.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The exciting, perilous journey toward AGI | Ilya Sutskever | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Just weeks before the management shakeup at OpenAI rocked Silicon Valley and made international news, the company&amp;rsquo;s cofounder and chief scientist Ilya Sutskever explored the transformative potential of artificial general intelligence (AGI), highlighting how it could surpass human intelligence and profoundly transform every aspect of life. Hear his take on the promises and perils of AGI — and his optimistic case for how unprecedented collaboration will ensure its safe and beneficial development.</description></item><item><title>When Biden met Xi (and what's going on with the US and China) | Ian Bremmer | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690018/</guid><description>Podcast Description US President Joe Biden and President of the People&amp;rsquo;s Republic of China Xi Jinping recently met in San Francisco. It was the first time Xi had visited the US in six years — and the first time the two leaders had met in person in a year. Geopolitical expert Ian Bremmer explains the implications of the meeting, sharing context and insight on areas where the pair agree — and flagging key areas where tensions might yet arise.</description></item><item><title>A crash course in making political change | Katie Fahey | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 16:05:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690019/</guid><description>Podcast Description You don&amp;rsquo;t need political power to make real change, says activist Katie Fahey. She tells the story of how she led a successful movement in Michigan to end gerrymandering — the practice of drawing district lines to favor one political party — and how it all started with a simple social media post.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Meet methane, the invisible climate villain | Marcelo Mena | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 15:54:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690020/</guid><description>Podcast Description A landfill on fire doesn&amp;rsquo;t only emit a horrid stench — it has devastating consequences for the environment, too. The culprit is methane, an often underestimated greenhouse gas produced in large part by food systems, organic waste and yes, cow burps. Biochemical engineer Marcelo Mena explains the source of this sneaky pollutant, why its emissions need to be cut in half by 2050 — and what you can do to help.</description></item><item><title>How to think computationally about AI, the universe and everything | Stephen Wolfram | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690021/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Drawing on his decades-long mission to formulate the world in computational terms, Stephen Wolfram delivers a profound vision of computation and its role in the future of AI. Amid a debut of mesmerizing visuals depicting the underlying structure of the universe, he provides a sweeping survey of his life&amp;rsquo;s work, offering a new perspective on the applications — and consequences — of AI powered by computational language.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The secret perks of driving electric | Cynthia Williams | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 15:59:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Electric vehicles need to be more than just eco-friendly — they have to be more chic, convenient and affordable than their gas-powered alternatives, says sustainability leader Cynthia Williams. She explores what it&amp;rsquo;ll take for an electric revolution to succeed in the US, calling on corporations, policy leaders, investors and more to collaborate in unprecedented ways.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A case for color blindness | Coleman Hughes | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Racial inequality provokes passionate opinions and varied ideas of how to build a fair, equitable society. One topic that&amp;rsquo;s been contentiously debated for generations is color blindness: the concept that we should look beyond race when thinking about equity. In this talk, writer and podcast host Coleman Hughes makes a case in favor of the idea, sharing why he thinks the key to reducing inequality and easing racial tensions is replacing race-based policies with class-based ones.</description></item><item><title>The real gold of our economy is in our hands | Salvatore Cali | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 15:58:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690024/</guid><description>Podcast Description The vast majority of our time at work is spent trudging through redundant and outdated workflows, says operations visionary Salvatore Cali. Laying out the most common time-wasting pitfalls, he urges policy leaders and businesses to reevaluate what they ask of both employees and consumers. &amp;ldquo;By rethinking the true purpose of each task, you will discover what is waste and what is the real gold of your company: the creation of value,&amp;rdquo; says Cali.</description></item><item><title>Why you should ditch deadly fossil-fuel appliances | Donnel Baird | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690025/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 15:51:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690025/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the US, people spend the overwhelming majority of their time inside buildings that burn fossil fuels, which are bad for both the environment and human health. (Think: breathing in air pollution from gas stoves, furnaces and water heaters.) If we&amp;rsquo;re going to fix this problem, we need to retrofit millions of buildings with all-electric equipment, says energy upgrader Donnel Baird. Hear about his ambitious plan to rip the fossil fuel infrastructure out of aging buildings and upgrade it with smarter, cleaner, healthier technology.</description></item><item><title>An economy powered by sun and wind — it's almost here | Kala Constantino | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690026/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690026/</guid><description>Podcast Description With some of the highest energy bills in Southeast Asia and extreme weather to match, the Philippines experiences the climate crisis &amp;ndash; and climate activism &amp;ndash; as a part of daily life. Clean energy advocate Kala Constantino highlights how people across the country are coming together to transform policies, power and the economy as the island nation maps out its green revolution.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The unexpected way spirituality connects to climate change | Gopal D. Patel | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690027/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 15:53:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Environmental activist Gopal D. Patel thinks the climate movement could learn a lot from one of the longest-standing social initiatives in human history: religion. Exploring three areas where frameworks from faith traditions could benefit the climate movement, Patel offers a playbook for discovering your big idea to build momentum towards powerful social change.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>It's time to rethink the role of First Lady | Irina Karamanos Adrian | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690028/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 15:56:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Irina Karamanos Adrian didn&amp;rsquo;t plan on becoming Chile&amp;rsquo;s First Lady — but she set out to transform the role all the same. She shares how she&amp;rsquo;s fighting gender stereotypes and protecting democracy by shifting political power back to where it belongs: to people who were actually elected.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Artificial skin? We made it — here's why | Anna Maria Coclite | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690029/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Material scientist Anna Maria Coclite unveils &amp;ldquo;smart skin&amp;rdquo; — artificial skin technology that responds to touch, temperature and humidity like your very own. (It&amp;rsquo;s actually even more sensitive than human skin!) From helping burn victims to paving the way to smarter, safer humanoid robots, Coclite highlights the broad-ranging potential of this innovation.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Photographing nature beyond the limits of human perception | Doris Mitsch | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690030/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 16:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Artist Doris Mitsch invites us to revel in the wonders of nature through her dazzling photography: stacked images of starlings in flight, hawks surfing thermal updrafts, bats echolocating through the night sky and more. Revealing the hidden trails created by creatures in flight, her work offers unique insight into the intelligence behind nature&amp;rsquo;s invisible rhythms.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is technology our savior — or our slayer? | Ruha Benjamin | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690031/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 16:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690031/</guid><description>Podcast Description When it comes to technology, we&amp;rsquo;re often presented with two contrasting visions of the future: one where technology fulfills all our desires, and another where it leads to chaos and conflict. Sociologist Ruha Benjamin is here with a more radical vision of the future — one where humanity isn&amp;rsquo;t saved or slayed by technology, but rather uses it to uplift ordinary people and make things like health care and housing for all a reality.</description></item><item><title>Regeneration can restore a broken world | Paul Hawken | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690032/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 14:45:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690032/</guid><description>Podcast Description A frog and a mockingbird changed Paul Hawken&amp;rsquo;s life, kindling a devotion to protect and restore nature. Now, as one of the world&amp;rsquo;s preeminent environmentalists, he advocates for regeneration — a calling and action plan for the world to come together to end the climate crisis in one generation and put life at the center of every decision we make.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The powerful possibilities of recycling the world's batteries | Emma Nehrenheim | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690033/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 14:54:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690033/</guid><description>Podcast Description The world has plenty of clean energy. The problem is storing that energy and getting it where we need it, when we need it, says battery recycling pioneer Emma Nehrenheim. While batteries are fundamental to powering a sustainable future, their production is surprisingly harsh on the environment. She lays out the science behind a breakthrough in recycling a battery&amp;rsquo;s core elements, offering a manufacturing solution that could vastly reduce the industry&amp;rsquo;s environmental impact and demand for new materials from mining.</description></item><item><title>The power of unconventional thinking | David McWilliams | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690034/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 14:58:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690034/</guid><description>Podcast Description From World War I to the 2008 economic collapse and beyond, history shows that economists don&amp;rsquo;t always see the future as clearly as they think they do, says economist David McWilliams. Using the words of W.B. Yeats, McWilliams makes the case for embracing unconventional thinkers – poets, artists and musicians – and offers a creative path towards a world filled with less confirmation bias and more understanding.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>AI is dangerous, but not for the reasons you think | Sasha Luccioni | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690035/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:46:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690035/</guid><description>Podcast Description AI won&amp;rsquo;t kill us all — but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t make it trustworthy. Instead of getting distracted by future existential risks, AI ethics researcher Sasha Luccioni thinks we need to focus on the technology&amp;rsquo;s current negative impacts, like emitting carbon, infringing copyrights and spreading biased information. She offers practical solutions to regulate our AI-filled future — so it&amp;rsquo;s inclusive and transparent.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How comedy helps us deal with hard truths | Roy Wood Jr. | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690036/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690036/</guid><description>Podcast Description There&amp;rsquo;s a saying that comedy is tragedy plus time. Perhaps that&amp;rsquo;s why some of our biggest problems feel easiest to manage with a dose of humor. Comedian, journalist and actor Roy Wood Jr. has spent his career finding the silly in the serious and using this tactic to influence real change. Listen in to learn how you can tap into the powers of humor in your own life. (This conversation, hosted by comedian Chris Duffy, was part of an exclusive TED Membership event.</description></item><item><title>My quest to end the horror of gun violence in the US | Lucy McBath | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690037/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690037/</guid><description>Podcast Description US Congresswoman Lucy McBath has made it her mission to seek bipartisan solutions for gun safety, leading the way in sponsoring so-called &amp;ldquo;red flag&amp;rdquo; laws that prevent gun violence and mass shootings. In a searing and timely talk, she shares the personal story that led her to this work — and a message for why comprehensive, common-sense gun legislation in the US is more urgent than ever.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A simple way to inspire your team | David Burkus | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690038/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Using paychecks, perks and carefully worded mission statements plastered on posters, companies are on a never-ending quest to find what drives morale at work. An underappreciated solution lies in the answer to one simple question, says management researcher David Burkus. With notable examples backed by decades of success, he presents a clear path to inspiring your team — and finding your purpose at work.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to make learning as addictive as social media | Luis von Ahn | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690039/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690039/</guid><description>Podcast Description When technologist Luis von Ahn was building the popular language-learning platform Duolingo, he faced a big problem: Could an app designed to teach you something ever compete with addictive platforms like Instagram and TikTok? He explains how Duolingo harnesses the psychological techniques of social media and mobile games to get you excited to learn — all while spreading access to education across the world.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to stop finding your self-worth through your job | How to Be a Better Human | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690040/</guid><description>Podcast Description For some of us it&amp;rsquo;s easy to lose ourselves in our work. But a lack of boundaries between your personal and work life is something mental wellness educator Gloria Chan Packer would warn you about twice. In conversation with host Chris Duffy, she speaks about the perils of gaining your sense of self-worth from your job, discusses her experience with burnout and stress and shares empowering insights on how to shift your perspective to create — and maintain — a healthy distance.</description></item><item><title>A cleaner world could start in a rice field | Jim Whitaker and Jessica Whitaker Allen | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690041/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 14:53:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rice is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest food source — and it&amp;rsquo;s also a massive emitter of methane gas, a key contributor to climate change. Fifth-generation rice farmer Jim Whitaker and his daughter, farmer and conservationist Jessica Whitaker Allen, are working to slash rice&amp;rsquo;s environmental impacts with innovative, sustainable farming practices. They share how they&amp;rsquo;re keeping their family farm in Arkansas profitable while also spreading green farming practices to their neighbors — and, eventually, the rest of the world.</description></item><item><title>The ordinary people doing extraordinary things in Ukraine | Oleksandra Matviichuk | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690042/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 14:58:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690042/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do we defend people&amp;rsquo;s freedom and dignity against authoritarianism, when the &amp;ldquo;law of war&amp;rdquo; doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to apply anymore? In the face of the Russian occupation of Ukraine, human rights lawyer and Nobel laureate Oleksandra Matviichuk considers this question every day. Exposing the failures of the international system of peace and security, she highlights the capabilities of ordinary people during extraordinary times — and urges us all to take an active position in the struggle for freedom.</description></item><item><title>The joy of learning random things on Wikipedia | Annie Rauwerda | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690043/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Writer Annie Rauwerda makes a habit of getting lost among the seemingly endless digital archives of Wikipedia, discovering fake towns, promiscuous tortoises, 19th-century fangirls and so much more. An avid editor of the crowd-sourced platform, she speaks to the joys of exploring niche and humorous subjects, accidentally learning just for fun — and broadening your horizons along the way.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Let's reframe cancel culture | Sarah Jones | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690044/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 14:47:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cancel culture launched a reckoning that was long overdue — but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean it&amp;rsquo;s getting everything right. Filmmaker and actor Sarah Jones slips in and out of various characters as she shares her personal experience with cancel culture and suggests a better way to hold others — and ourselves — to account.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to self-promote without shame | Fixable | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690045/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690045/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a standup comedian and the host of the TED podcast How to Be a Better Human, Chris Duffy knows how to be engaging in front of a microphone. However, he feels awkward about posting on social media &amp;ndash; yet also worries that not posting is costing him opportunities and a bigger audience. It&amp;rsquo;s a problem that hosts Anne Morriss and Frances Frei have faced, too. Together, they talk about the art and mindset of self-promotion and the ways you can rethink your online presence so it feels more aligned with what you stand for.</description></item><item><title>Unions for climate action! | Payton M. Wilkins | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690046/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 14:55:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690046/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the long term, shutting down a coal mine means cleaner air and a healthier environment — but in the short term, it can devastate a community or family that relied on the mine&amp;rsquo;s paychecks to make ends meet. Environmental justice advocate Payton M. Wilkins thinks we can protect both workers and the planet with an age-old solution: unions. He digs into the economic fallout of ditching fossil fuels and shows why unions are well-positioned to push the transition to clean energy and green jobs.</description></item><item><title>What does "wealth" mean to you? | Aisha Nyandoro | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690047/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 14:58:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690047/</guid><description>Podcast Description For people living in poverty, a guaranteed income can mean finally having the space to dream of a comfortable life. Sharing the stories of single moms who participated in a first-of-its-kind program that offered them $1,000 per month with no strings attached, poverty disrupter Aisha Nyandoro calls for us to redefine what it means to be wealthy — putting aside lavish vacations and fancy cars in favor of paid bills and a well-fed family — and to listen when people tell us what they need most.</description></item><item><title>The tech we need to fight workplace ageism | Piyachart Phiromswad | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690048/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690048/</guid><description>Podcast Description From exoskeletons and robotic arms to the mass adoption of remote work, economist Piyachart Phiromswad explores what seniors need to overcome the physical, mental and societal barriers to employment, a necessary shift in our rapidly aging world. Learn more about how these tools could empower elderly workers and better the world — for everyone.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lessons from my father, Alexey Navalny | Dasha Navalnaya | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690049/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 14:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dasha Navalnaya is the daughter of Alexey Navalny, the politician and leader of the Russian opposition to Vladimir Putin. Sharing the story of her father&amp;rsquo;s poisoning, persecution and current imprisonment, she details what it was like growing up under the watchful eye of government surveillance as her father led a decade-long investigation into the corruption of Putin&amp;rsquo;s regime — and shows why paying attention to what happens in Russia matters to everyone, everywhere.</description></item><item><title>We actually have a shot at stopping the climate crisis | Asmeret Asefaw Berhe | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690050/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 14:57:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690050/</guid><description>Podcast Description How is the US going to reach net zero by 2050? That&amp;rsquo;s the question Asmeret Asefaw Berhe, director of the Office of Science for the US Department of Energy, is urgently trying to answer. She shares the thinking behind what her team is calling &amp;ldquo;Energy Earthshots&amp;rdquo; — projects designed to accelerate innovation in the fight against climate change, from nature-based solutions in the soil to the creation of brand-new technologies — and calls for innovative, equitable policies backed by science.</description></item><item><title>Why meetings suck and how to fix them | WorkLife with Adam Grant | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690051/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Meetings often drain our joy and sap our focus-–and meeting overload kills productivity. So why do we have so many of them– and is a better world possible? Adam investigates the science of improving meetings and explores how workplaces are fighting meeting bloat. Available transcripts for WorkLife can be found at go.ted.com/WLtranscripts
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Israel-Hamas war — and what it means for the world | Ian Bremmer | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690052/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 17:10:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690052/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Hamas attacks on Israel in October 2023 stunned the world. In this timely conversation, political scientist Ian Bremmer explains the historical context of the conflict, how Israel might respond and what it means for Jews, Palestinians and the world at large. Listen in for analysis of the unprecedented events, how the US may factor into the global response and how to find reliable information amid the breathless media coverage and the fog of war.</description></item><item><title>3 practices for wisdom and wholeness | Krista Tippett | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690053/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 14:54:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690053/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do we stand before the pain and promise of the world and keep hope and courage alive? Journalist and podcast host Krista Tippett has spent a career interviewing some of the world&amp;rsquo;s wisest people in search of answers to that question. Listen along as she offers three practices to help you make sense of what it means to be human right now — and how to live in a way that helps remake the world for the better.</description></item><item><title>Work has changed. Why haven't resumes? | Nicos Marcou | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690054/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 14:51:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Resumes are a mainstay of the job application process — despite little evidence that they actually help job-seekers or employers get what they want. So why are we still so preoccupied with them? HR leader Nicos Marcou dives into the absurdity of these one-page documents (or can they be two pages?) and offers an update on how companies should think about hiring qualified candidates.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How business can drive solutions to social problems | Carlos Rodríguez-Pastor | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690055/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Driven by the belief that businesses can — and should — invest in the communities around them, Intercorp founder and philanthropist Carlos Rodríguez-Pastor has built schools, pharmacies and a literal bridge to better serve Peru&amp;rsquo;s growing middle class. In conversation with TED business curator Corey Hajim, he explores the immense possibility behind private-public partnerships — and his conviction that any individual can step up to create change.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to fix fashion and protect the planet | Amy Powney | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690056/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 14:50:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690056/</guid><description>Podcast Description From the field to your closet, your clothes go on a long journey before they enter your life. Designer Amy Powney explores the fashion industry&amp;rsquo;s brutal impact on the environment and human health, modeling what ethical, planet-friendly clothing can look like — and inviting us all to think beyond the label.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Encyclopedia of Invisibility — a home for lost stories | Tavares Strachan | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690057/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conceptual artist Tavares Strachan creates the kinds of projects that make you stop in your tracks, like a 4.5-ton block of Arctic ice he brought back to his birthplace in the Bahamas or a gold, Egyptian-inspired sculpture he launched into orbit around the Earth. Now he presents his latest creation, the Encyclopedia of Invisibility: a 3,000-page tome filled with more than 17,000 entries on people, places and events often left out of the history books — and encourages us all to unearth hidden stories before they disappear to the passage of time.</description></item><item><title>You don't actually know what your future self wants | TED Business | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690058/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690058/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;You are constantly becoming a new person,&amp;rdquo; says journalist Shankar Vendantam. In a talk full of beautiful storytelling, he explains the profound impact of something he calls the &amp;ldquo;illusion of continuity&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; the belief that our future selves will share the same views, perspectives and hopes as our current selves &amp;ndash; and shows how we can more proactively craft the people we are to become. Before and after the talk, TED Business host Modupe Akinola shares a clear-eyed and empowering perspective on your future self&amp;rsquo;s feelings.</description></item><item><title>10 lessons I learned from being a nerd | Jordan Dinwiddie | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690059/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 14:59:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you super devoted to a sports team, superhero or perhaps &amp;ldquo;Star Wars&amp;rdquo;? You&amp;rsquo;re part of a fandom, just like storyteller Jordan Dinwiddie. She shares 10 lessons she&amp;rsquo;s learned nerding out on all kinds of things and unpacks the joy, creativity and community that comes from being a fan. (Note: This talk contains graphic language.)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The truth about human population decline | Jennifer D. Sciubba | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690060/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 15:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690060/</guid><description>Podcast Description With birth rates falling, the worldwide human population is getting older and smaller. According to traditional thinking, this spells a future of labor shortages, bankrupt social security systems and overall economic collapse. Before you panic about the end of life as we know it, political demographer Jennifer D. Sciubba has a thoughtful playbook for managing the new normal – including ideas on the future of work and migration – and a reminder that a resilient future relies on present-day action.</description></item><item><title>This country runs on 98 percent renewable electricity | Ramón Méndez Galain | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690061/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 14:51:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fifteen years ago, Uruguay was experiencing an energy crisis brought on by its reliance on fossil fuels; today, the nation produces 98 percent of its electricity from renewable sources (and even exports extra energy to neighboring countries). How did they turn things around so quickly? Uruguay&amp;rsquo;s former secretary of energy, Ramón Méndez Galain, explains how they pulled off this unprecedented shift &amp;ndash; and shares how any other country can do the same.</description></item><item><title>The world's rarest diseases — and how they impact everyone | Anna Greka | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690062/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 14:44:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Physician-scientist Anna Greka investigates the world&amp;rsquo;s rarest genetic diseases, decoding the secrets of our cells through &amp;ldquo;molecular detective work.&amp;rdquo; She explains how her team is using new, advanced technology to solve decades-old medical mysteries — and shows how this work could help develop precision treatments for millions of people across the globe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why I gave my teenage daughter a vibrator | Robin Buckley | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690063/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 14:56:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690063/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;Why does a vibrator make us uncomfortable, but Viagra does not?&amp;rdquo; asks cognitive-behavioral coach Robin Buckley. Sharing her own personal story of empowering her teenage daughter to explore the power of pleasure, Buckley encourages parents to talk to their teens about healthy sexual development &amp;ndash; and shares why the awkward conversations are worth it.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CRISPR's next advance is bigger than you think | Jennifer Doudna | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690064/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 14:50:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690064/</guid><description>Podcast Description You&amp;rsquo;ve probably heard of CRISPR, the revolutionary technology that allows us to edit the DNA in living organisms. Biochemist and 2023 Audacious Project grantee Jennifer Doudna earned the Nobel Prize for her groundbreaking work in this field &amp;ndash; and now she&amp;rsquo;s here to tell us about its next world-changing advancement. She explains how her team at the Innovative Genomics Institute is pioneering a brand new field of science &amp;ndash; precision microbiome editing &amp;ndash; that uses CRISPR in an effort to solve seemingly insurmountable problems like asthma, Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s and climate change.</description></item><item><title>How I found myself — by impersonating other people | Melissa Villaseñor | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690065/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 15:01:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ever think you&amp;rsquo;d hear Sandra Bullock, Britney Spears and Dolly Parton in one TED Talk? Here they are, courtesy of &amp;ldquo;Saturday Night Live&amp;rdquo; star Melissa Villaseñor. She shares the life lessons of a comedian &amp;ndash; complete with celebrity impressions &amp;ndash; and reminds us to embrace all of our voices, even if they&amp;rsquo;re a little silly.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Are we the last generation — or the first sustainable one? | Hannah Ritchie | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690066/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 14:54:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690066/</guid><description>Podcast Description The word &amp;ldquo;sustainability&amp;rdquo; gets thrown around a lot these days. But what does it actually mean for humanity to be sustainable? Environmental data scientist Hannah Ritchie digs into the numbers behind human progress across centuries, unpacking why the conventional understanding of sustainability is misleading and showing how we can be the first generation of humans to actually achieve it.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The simple solution to fast fashion | Josephine Philips | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690067/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 14:56:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Your favorite pair of jeans &amp;ndash; the ones you refuse to throw out &amp;ndash; are actually a part of a global climate solution, says fashion entrepreneur Josephine Philips. When you value your existing clothes instead of chasing the latest trends, you help reduce waste and protect our planet for generations to come. Learn more about the impacts of what you wear &amp;ndash; and the incredible power of repairing your clothes.</description></item><item><title>Can AI help solve the climate crisis? | Sims Witherspoon | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690068/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 14:53:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690068/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;AI can be a transformational tool in our fight against climate change,&amp;rdquo; says Sims Witherspoon, a leader at the AI research lab Google DeepMind. Using wind power as her case study, she explains how powerful neural networks can help us better predict Earth&amp;rsquo;s changing ecosystems and accelerate the breakthrough science needed to create a carbon-free energy supply.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to supercharge renewables and energize the world | Rebecca Collyer | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690069/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 14:57:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690069/</guid><description>Podcast Description The power sector generates the electricity that sustains modern life &amp;ndash; but it&amp;rsquo;s also the number one contributor to climate change. We need a swift and equitable shift to renewable energy, says 2023 Audacious Project grantee and ReNew2030 executive director Rebecca Collyer. In conversation with TED&amp;rsquo;s David Biello, she introduces a new coalition of governments, businesses and communities that aims to drastically scale wind and solar capacity in the 30 highest-emitting countries.</description></item><item><title>Can the US and China take on climate change together? | Changhua Wu | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690070/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Climate change doesn&amp;rsquo;t care about ideological divides, says policy analyst and China expert Changhua Wu. Here&amp;rsquo;s what she says the US can learn from the progress China has made on the clean energy revolution &amp;ndash; and why collaboration instead of competition is the key to avoiding climate catastrophe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>An extreme weather report from America's weatherman | Al Roker | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690071/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 11:26:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690071/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s not just you: the weather is getting worse. And if there&amp;rsquo;s one person who would know, it&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;America&amp;rsquo;s weatherman,&amp;rdquo; Al Roker, who&amp;rsquo;s spent decades reporting live from some of the worst storms and natural disasters in history. He explains how we can each take action to address climate change and work towards a more sustainable, hopeful future for generations to come.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to solve the world's biggest problems | Natalie Cargill | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690072/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 14:45:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sometimes the world&amp;rsquo;s biggest issues can seem so intractable that meaningful change feels impossible. But what if the answer has been right in front of us all along? What if the answer is actually throwing money at the problems? In this thought-provoking talk, philanthropic advisor Natalie Cargill shares what might happen if we came together to spend 3.5 trillion dollars on fixing the world. And, yes, she also has a plan for where to get the money from.</description></item><item><title>The single most important parenting strategy | Becky Kennedy | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690073/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 11:46:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Everyone loses their temper from time to time — but the stakes are dizzyingly high when the focus of your fury is your own child. Clinical psychologist and renowned parenting whisperer Becky Kennedy is here to help. Not only does she have practical advice to help parents manage the guilt and shame of their not-so-great moments but she also models the types of conversations you can have to be a better parent.</description></item><item><title>Birds aren't real? How a conspiracy takes flight | Peter McIndoe | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690074/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 15:03:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Peter McIndoe isn&amp;rsquo;t a fan of birds. In fact, he has a theory about them that might shock you. Listen along to this eye-opening talk as it takes a turn and makes a larger point about conspiracies, truth and belonging in divisive times.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Does more freedom at work mean more fulfillment? | Sarah Aviram | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690075/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 14:43:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690075/</guid><description>Podcast Description The flexibility to work from anywhere won&amp;rsquo;t necessarily make you love your job, says HR leader Sarah Aviram. Sharing practical wisdom from research conducted while working remotely in 12 different countries, she reveals the real challenges that hybrid work policies can&amp;rsquo;t fix &amp;ndash; and shows how to truly thrive at your job no matter where you get it done.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Our creative relationship with AI is just beginning | K Allado-McDowell | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690076/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 15:08:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690076/</guid><description>Podcast Description K Allado-McDowell has co-written three books with AI, so they speak from experience when they say that nurturing a creative relationship with these systems can open minds and make new worlds possible. Before giving the stage over to a performance of &amp;ldquo;Song of the Ambassadors&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; their otherworldly opera, also co-created with AI &amp;ndash; Allado-McDowell presents three principles for a future where machines preserve and even enhance what it means to be human.</description></item><item><title>How to take the BS out of business speak | Bob Wiltfong | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690077/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 14:50:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690077/</guid><description>Podcast Description At its worst, &amp;ldquo;business speak&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; or the particular language we use at work &amp;ndash; can be jargony, confusing and even exclusionary. But it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be, says journalist and comedian Bob Wiltfong. Showcasing a smattering of corporate acronyms and phrases that don&amp;rsquo;t make much sense without context (think: &amp;ldquo;OKRs&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;when pigs fly&amp;rdquo;), he gives three tips on how to cut the BS out of business speak so we can all better understand each other at work.</description></item><item><title>Why you should stop setting goals (yes, really) | Emmanuel Acho | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690078/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 14:58:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690078/</guid><description>Podcast Description In athletics, in business, in life, everyone sets goals. But that&amp;rsquo;s not the way to excel, according to former NFL player Emmanuel Acho, now an author and TV sports analyst. Here&amp;rsquo;s what he says to do instead.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to hack your brain when you're in pain | Amy Baxter | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690079/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 14:50:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have we misunderstood pain? Researcher and physician Amy Baxter unravels the symphony of connections that send pain from your body to your brain, explaining practical neuroscience hacks to quickly block those signals. Her groundbreaking research offers alternatives for immediate pain relief &amp;ndash; without the need for addictive opioids. (Followed by a Q&amp;amp;A with TED current affairs curator Whitney Pennington Rodgers)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How labor unions create worker power | How to Be a Better Human | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690080/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690080/</guid><description>Podcast Description We don&amp;rsquo;t know about you, but we are fans of weekends. And social security. And health insurance. And the end of child labor! And all of these workplace protections exist because of the advocacy of labor unions. In this episode, political scientist Margaret Levi shares the long history of organizing labor and explains how unions create equality and protect worker rights. She also discusses her optimism about today&amp;rsquo;s young workforce and why she believes that an equitable future requires a revival of the labor movement.</description></item><item><title>How "digital twins" could help us predict the future | Karen Willcox | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690081/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 14:59:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690081/</guid><description>Podcast Description From health-tracking wearables to smartphones and beyond, data collection and computer modeling have become a ubiquitous part of everyday life. Advancements in these areas have given birth to &amp;ldquo;digital twins,&amp;rdquo; or virtual models that evolve alongside real-world data. Aerospace engineer Karen Willcox explores the incredible possibilities these systems offer across engineering, climate studies and medicine, sharing how they could lead to personalized medicine, better decision-making and more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The AI-powered tools supercharging your imagination | Bilawal Sidhu | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690082/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 14:57:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690082/</guid><description>Podcast Description How is AI changing the nature of human imagination and creativity? Through a mind-bending tour of new techniques he&amp;rsquo;s been tinkering with, creative technologist Bilawal Sidhu shows how anyone can use AI-powered tools &amp;ndash; like 3D scans that let you redesign the physical world in real time &amp;ndash; to expand the possibilities of artistic expression, often within just minutes.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why rivals are working together to transform shipping | Bo Cerup-Simonsen | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690083/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 14:45:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690083/</guid><description>Podcast Description What would it take to make global supply chains cleaner and greener? Bo Cerup-Simonsen &amp;ndash; who&amp;rsquo;s helping decarbonize the maritime industry as CEO of the Mærsk Mc-Kinney Møller Center for Zero Carbon Shipping &amp;ndash; discusses why tenacious collaboration is key to orchestrating systemic change. In conversation with TED&amp;rsquo;s Lindsay Levin, he shares important lessons on collective problem-solving and decision-making that could benefit any industry making a green transition.</description></item><item><title>The first-ever cargo ship powered by green fuel | Morten Bo Christiansen | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690084/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 14:42:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690084/</guid><description>Podcast Description The shipping industry is vital to the global economy, but it&amp;rsquo;s also a huge contributor to the climate crisis. Morten Bo Christiansen, a leader of the energy transition for the global shipping company A.P. Moller – Maersk, talks to TED&amp;rsquo;s Lindsay Levin about the launch of the first-ever cargo ship powered by green methanol, the industry&amp;rsquo;s urgent need to shift away from fossil fuels &amp;ndash; and what it could all mean for people&amp;rsquo;s pockets.</description></item><item><title>The dream of digital ownership, powered by the metaverse | Yat Siu | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690085/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 15:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Technologist Yat Siu believes the &amp;ldquo;open metaverse&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; a decentralized version of the internet also known as web3 &amp;ndash; is laying the foundation for a freer, fairer, more prosperous society. In a future-focused talk, he explores the transformative possibilities of web3, from enabling digital ownership and the creator economy to providing a much-needed update to capitalism.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The "adjacent possible" — and how it explains human innovation | Stuart Kauffman | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690086/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 15:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690086/</guid><description>Podcast Description From the astonishing evolutionary advances of the Cambrian explosion to our present-day computing revolution, the trend of dramatic growth after periods of stability can be explained through the theory of the &amp;ldquo;adjacent possible,&amp;rdquo; says theoretical biologist Stuart Kauffman. Tracing the arc of human history through the tools and technologies we&amp;rsquo;ve invented, he explains the impact human ingenuity has had on the planet &amp;ndash; and calls for a shift towards more protection for all life on Earth.</description></item><item><title>How AI art could enhance humanity's collective memory | Refik Anadol | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690087/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 14:58:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690087/</guid><description>Podcast Description With data as his paintbrush, media artist Refik Anadol trains AI algorithms to visualize the disappearing wonders of nature. He gives a beautiful tour of his recent work &amp;ndash; imagery of artificial coral reefs, flowers, rainforests &amp;ndash; and ponders: Can we use AI to preserve our memories of the fading natural world?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What's it like to be a giant sequoia tree? | Ersin Han Ersin | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690088/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 14:57:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Artist Ersin Han Ersin invites us to step inside a giant sequoia tree, peering through the bark into the tapestry of life within. Discover how his multisensory installations explore the concept of &amp;ldquo;umwelt,&amp;rdquo; or the unique sensory experience of different organisms, and reveal the deep interconnectedness of humanity with the natural world.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The molecular love story that could help power the world | Olivia Breese | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690089/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 14:57:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690089/</guid><description>Podcast Description The key to revolutionizing the world&amp;rsquo;s energy landscape may lie in an unlikely love story, says energy innovator Olivia Breese. She details the fateful marriage of a green electron and a water molecule &amp;ndash; a powerful source of carbon-free, sustainable energy &amp;ndash; and calls for universal investment in this potentially transformative resource. &amp;ldquo;A world which runs entirely on green energy, it&amp;rsquo;s not a luxury. It&amp;rsquo;s a necessity,&amp;rdquo; she says.</description></item><item><title>How to meet your child's difficult behavior with compassion | Yvonne Newbold | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690090/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 14:38:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yvonne Newbold&amp;rsquo;s son, Toby, is one of the millions of young people living with a disability. Parenting Toby has offered her some lessons on how to help children move from anxiety-led behavior towards happier times. Drawing on her personal experience, she outlines some of the most effective and actionable of these strategies &amp;ndash; starting with a dash of curiosity, kindness and creative thinking.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A 3-part plan to take on extreme heat waves | Eleni Myrivili | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690091/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690091/</guid><description>Podcast Description The deadliest severe weather phenomenon is something you might not realize: extreme heat. Eleni Myrivili, chief heat officer of the city of Athens, Greece, explains that extreme heat and heat waves are often overlooked because they&amp;rsquo;re not as dramatic as flooding or hurricanes – and breaks down three approaches to keep cities cool in a time of rapid global temperature rise. &amp;ldquo;Cranking up the air conditioner is just not going to cut it,&amp;rdquo; she says.</description></item><item><title>The climate crisis is expensive — here's who should pay for it | Avinash Persaud | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690092/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 14:47:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690092/</guid><description>Podcast Description The developing world is most affected by climate change but has contributed the least to the problem. Meanwhile, rich countries historically exacerbated the environmental crisis and grew wealthy as a result &amp;ndash; but aren&amp;rsquo;t helping developing countries build climate resilience, which is now more crucial than ever to slowing climate change everywhere. Economist Avinash Persaud has an ambitious proposal to reimagine that dynamic: the Bridgetown Initiative, a groundbreaking vision of how rich countries can catalyze climate mitigation, contribute to loss and damages and help build a sustainable future for all.</description></item><item><title>A flavorful field guide to foraging | Alexis Nikole Nelson | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690093/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Whether it&amp;rsquo;s dandelions blooming in your backyard or purslane sprouting from the sidewalk, vegan forager Alexis Nikole Nelson is on a mission to show how freely growing flora could make its way to your plate. With contagious enthusiasm and a live cooking demo, she explains the benefits of expanding your palate to include &amp;ldquo;wild&amp;rdquo; foods that are delicious, nutritious and planet-friendly &amp;ndash; and gives three tips for helping others go from skeptical to confident in their own food adventures.</description></item><item><title>A mysterious design that appears across millennia | Terry Moore | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690094/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 14:49:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690094/</guid><description>Podcast Description What can we make of a design that shows up over and over in disparate cultures throughout history? Theorist Terry Moore explores &amp;ldquo;Penrose tiling&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; two shapes that fit together in infinite combinations without ever repeating &amp;ndash; and ponders what it might mean.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is the US headed towards another civil war? | Barbara F. Walter | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690095/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 14:53:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Based on her work for a CIA task force aimed at predicting civil wars, political scientist Barbara F. Walter examines the rise in extremism and threats to democracies around the globe &amp;ndash; and paints an unsettling picture of the increasing likelihood of a second civil war in the United States.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to discover your authentic self -- at any age | Bevy Smith | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690096/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690096/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a talk packed with wry wisdom, pop culture queen Bevy Smith shares hard-earned lessons about authenticity, confidence, mature success and why, if you put in the work, &amp;ldquo;life gets greater later.&amp;rdquo;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The case for a 4-day work week | Juliet Schor | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690097/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690097/</guid><description>Podcast Description The traditional approach to work needs a redesign, says economist Juliet Schor. She&amp;rsquo;s leading four-day work week trials in countries like the US and Ireland, and the results so far have been overwhelmingly positive: from increased employer and customer satisfaction to revenue growth and lower turnover. Making the case for a four-day, 32-hour work week (with five days of pay), Schor explains how this model for the future of work could address major challenges like burnout and the climate crisis &amp;ndash; and shares how companies and governments could work together to make it a reality.</description></item><item><title>How targeted ads might just save your life | Sandersan Onie | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 15:19:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Could the tech industry&amp;rsquo;s complex algorithms support people during their darkest times, rather than just deliver targeted ads? Drawing from his own experience with depression, global mental health researcher Sandersan Onie shows how internet search behaviors can provide valuable insights into suicide risk and potentially help save lives by reaching people in a deeply personal way, at a crucial moment.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>In the age of AI art, what can originality look like? | Eileen Isagon Skyers | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690099/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 14:52:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690099/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happens when human and machine creativity meet? From an AI model trained on classic works to generate a seemingly infinite stream of portraits to a neural network that envisions otherworldly life-forms in impossible detail, media art curator Eileen Isagon Skyers showcases mind-bending art that embraces our increasingly technological future, showing how AI can stretch the scope of human imagination and help create worlds we could never design alone.</description></item><item><title>What the fossil fuel industry doesn't want you to know | Al Gore | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690100/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 14:59:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690100/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a blistering talk, Nobel Laureate Al Gore looks at the two main obstacles to climate solutions and gives his view of how we might actually solve the environmental crisis in time. You won&amp;rsquo;t want to miss his searing indictment of fossil fuel companies for walking back their climate commitments &amp;ndash; and his call for a global rethink of the roles of polluting industries in politics and finance.</description></item><item><title>The magic of a creative career | Michael Sheen | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690101/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 15:05:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690101/</guid><description>Podcast Description The city of Port Talbot in South Wales is known for a few things: a steel mill, a proudly working class population and a passionate commitment to the arts that produced Hollywood superstars Richard Burton and Anthony Hopkins. In this sweet, personal talk, actor Michael Sheen shares how he was also able to take advantage of all the city had to offer, why he&amp;rsquo;s worried that a change in approach to arts education means that kids now don&amp;rsquo;t get the same kind of chances &amp;ndash; and the steps he&amp;rsquo;s taking to ensure that creative up-and-comers get the support and access they deserve.</description></item><item><title>Climate action is on the cusp of exponential growth | Simon Stiell | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690102/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 14:47:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Climate action is speeding up &amp;ndash; and we each have the power to push that transformation forward. As the head of the UNFCCC, the UN&amp;rsquo;s entity supporting the global response to climate change, Simon Stiell points to clear social and technological signals that show we&amp;rsquo;re at the tipping points of a green revolution &amp;ndash; and invites us all to apply our unique skills to defending the planet against the catastrophic impacts of the climate crisis.</description></item><item><title>Why I built my own time machine | Lucas Rizzotto | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690103/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 14:50:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Experiential artist Lucas Rizzotto was going through a tough breakup, so he did what anyone would do: he built a personal time machine. In a playful talk, he shares how his free-ranging experimentation led to various delightful, unexpected innovations that are changing how people think about the relationship between technology and art. &amp;ldquo;Technology gives us the tools, but art shows us the way,&amp;rdquo; he says.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The power of an image — and the mind behind it | Misan Harriman | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690104/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 14:59:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690104/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a neurodivergent child going to school far from home, Misan Harriman found solace in the internet &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;an endless library of the extraordinary,&amp;rdquo; as he calls it. In this powerful talk, he shares his journey as a self-taught photographer of extraordinary range, from covering the greatest civil rights movements of our lifetimes to becoming the first Black man to shoot a cover for British Vogue. A reminder that each one of us can find our own ways to create a better world for all.</description></item><item><title>The beauty of building with mud and trash | Vinu Daniel | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690105/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 14:53:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690105/</guid><description>Podcast Description What if we could use waste to create resilient and sustainable buildings? Bringing out the beauty of the dirt beneath our feet, climate-responsive architect Vinu Daniel shares how he and his team are giving local and discarded materials (think: mud, plastic and used tires) a second life by using them to create dreamlike homes, schools and other public spaces.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Blindness isn't a tragic binary — it's a rich spectrum | Andrew Leland | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690106/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 14:46:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690106/</guid><description>Podcast Description When does vision loss become blindness? Writer, audio producer and editor Andrew Leland explains how his gradual loss of vision revealed a paradoxical truth about blindness &amp;ndash; and shows why it might have implications for how all of us see the world.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Can global food companies make the shift to regenerative agriculture? | Steve Presley | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690107/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 14:47:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sharing the inside scoop on how the world&amp;rsquo;s largest food company aims to reach net zero by 2050, Nestlé North America CEO Steve Presley joins TED&amp;rsquo;s Lindsay Levin to discuss the progress they&amp;rsquo;ve made so far and where they&amp;rsquo;re investing for sustainability. A big focus will be regenerative agriculture &amp;ndash; producing food in a way that helps the planet instead of harming it &amp;ndash; by working with farmers and other partners across the entire food production process.</description></item><item><title>How to make sure materials get reused — again and again | Garry Cooper | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690108/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 14:21:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690108/</guid><description>Podcast Description What if we could harness the power and value of all that we discard? Circular economy builder Garry Cooper presents a compelling vision for transforming cities into sustainable, circular economies, citing real-world examples of how repurposing materials from buildings to office furniture can significantly reduce greenhouse gas emissions, create jobs and foster economic growth. A hopeful reminder of the profound impact individual actions can have on our shared future.</description></item><item><title>Why change is so scary — and how to unlock its potential | Maya Shankar | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690109/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 14:44:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Unexpected change like an accident, an illness or a relationship that suddenly ends is inevitable &amp;ndash; and disorienting. With a heartfelt and optimistic take on life&amp;rsquo;s curveballs, cognitive scientist Maya Shankar shares how these challenging moments can inspire transformation, offering three questions to ask when facing uncertainty, so you can let go of rigidity and embrace change.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 1: The Internet's First Main Character? | The Redemption of Jar Jar Binks | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690110/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690110/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s 1999, and sixteen years after its original release, a new Star Wars is finally coming. Fans have been camping out in front of theaters across the country just to be the first to see it. The beloved intergalactic saga is set to debut a slew of brand new characters, one of whom is a revolutionary CGI creation named Jar Jar Binks. Whispers begin to spread about big changes coming to the galaxy far, far away – and not everyone&amp;rsquo;s happy about it.</description></item><item><title>The tree-growing movement restoring Africa's vital landscapes | Wanjira Mathai | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690111/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 14:47:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690111/</guid><description>Podcast Description 2023 Audacious Project grantee Wanjira Mathai is at the forefront of re-greening the planet. Through the forest restoration initiative Restore Local, she&amp;rsquo;s working to help both Africa&amp;rsquo;s people and its landscapes flourish. Learn more about how her team invests in local restoration projects across the continent &amp;ndash; including a tree-growing movement that aims to revitalize 100 million hectares of African land by 2030. (This ambitious idea is a part of the Audacious Project, TED&amp;rsquo;s initiative to inspire and fund global change.</description></item><item><title>How to be a leader for climate justice | David Lammy and Justin J. Pearson | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690112/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 14:48:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Climate justice is taking center stage &amp;ndash; geopolitically, socially and morally. In a contagiously courageous conversation, Member of Parliament in the UK David Lammy and Tennessee state representative Justin J. Pearson discuss how brave leadership can shepherd global movements and uplift historically marginalized communities in the face of humanity&amp;rsquo;s greatest challenge: climate change. &amp;ldquo;We must have outrage, but we must have optimism as well,&amp;rdquo; says Lammy.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The growing megafire crisis — and how to contain it | George T. Whitesides | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690113/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 14:59:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Megafires, or fires that burn more than 100,000 acres, are becoming more frequent worldwide, wreaking havoc on landscapes and communities &amp;ndash; and fire experts say the problem is only going to get worse. George T. Whitesides is focused on fighting these devastating natural disasters through innovative technologies and intentional changes to how we build communities. He presents three emerging solutions to this blazing dilemma, calling for us to redefine our relationship with fire in order to build a more resilient and sustainable future.</description></item><item><title>Is remote work better than being in the office? It's complicated | Mark Mortensen | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690114/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 14:44:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Opinions about remote work are plentiful and conflicting &amp;ndash; but what does the research say? Organizational design expert Mark Mortensen identifies the challenges of navigating the hybrid work debate and shares three conversation topics every workplace should explore as people change the way they show up on the job.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Could an orca give a TED Talk? | Karen Bakker | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690115/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 14:51:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690115/</guid><description>Podcast Description What if we could hear nature&amp;rsquo;s ultrasonic communication &amp;ndash; and talk back? From a bat&amp;rsquo;s shrill speech to a peacock&amp;rsquo;s infrasound mating call, conservation technology researcher Karen Bakker takes us through a sound bath of animal noises that are far outside humanity&amp;rsquo;s range of hearing, demonstrating how artificial intelligence has translated the incredible complexity of nature&amp;rsquo;s soundtrack. She asks us to consider the moral weight of such transformative technology and explores the futuristic opportunities presented for conservation, interspecies communication and more.</description></item><item><title>Why are we making pizza boxes out of endangered trees? | Nicole Rycroft | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690116/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 14:59:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690116/</guid><description>Podcast Description If we&amp;rsquo;re going to solve the climate crisis, we need to talk about supply chains, says biodiversity champion and 2023 Audacious Project grantee Nicole Rycroft. Her organization, Canopy, partners with key industry leaders to overhaul their base materials in favor of more sustainable alternatives. Learn more about how they&amp;rsquo;re shifting production of everything from T-shirts to the Harry Potter book series out of the world&amp;rsquo;s ancient and endangered forests &amp;ndash; and how solutions for every sector are closer than we think.</description></item><item><title>Detroit's climate crisis — and how to build a resilient future everywhere | Anika Goss | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690117/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 14:50:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690117/</guid><description>Podcast Description How can cities become resilient to the shocks of climate change? As a leading force behind Detroit&amp;rsquo;s ongoing revitalization, Anika Goss spends a lot of time thinking about this question. Connecting the city&amp;rsquo;s industrial past to its sustainable future, she explores the link between climate vulnerability and economic inequity, offering a vision for responding to both challenges at once.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The renewable energy revolution happening in Ukraine | Maxim Timchenko | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690118/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 15:21:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690118/</guid><description>Podcast Description What&amp;rsquo;s it like keeping the lights on during war? Ukrainian energy executive Maxim Timchenko shares how his company has diversified Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s power structures to survive Russian attacks, highlighting the resilience of renewable energy. Hear more about Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s present-day challenges, how it&amp;rsquo;s become a testing ground in the global fight against climate change and the transformative path towards sustainable energy independence.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Will superintelligent AI end the world? | Eliezer Yudkowsky | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690119/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 14:40:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Decision theorist Eliezer Yudkowsky has a simple message: superintelligent AI could probably kill us all. So the question becomes: Is it possible to build powerful artificial minds that are obedient, even benevolent? In a fiery talk, Yudkowsky explores why we need to act immediately to ensure smarter-than-human AI systems don&amp;rsquo;t lead to our extinction.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>War, AI and the new global arms race | Alexandr Wang | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690120/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 14:56:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lethal drones with facial recognition, armed robots, autonomous fighter jets: we&amp;rsquo;re at the dawn of a new age of AI-powered warfare, says technologist Alexandr Wang. He explores why data will be the secret weapon in this uncharted landscape and emphasizes the need to consider national security when developing new tech &amp;ndash; or potentially face all-out AI warfare.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>School is just the start. Here's how to help girls succeed for life | Angeline Murimirwa | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690121/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 14:51:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Education activist and 2023 Audacious Project grantee Angeline Murimirwa knows the power of educating girls, especially in places where they may not have easy access to schooling. But she says that&amp;rsquo;s not enough. In an inspiring talk, she clarifies why a support network around girls &amp;ndash; from the moment they enter the classroom to years after they graduate &amp;ndash; makes a radical difference for their lives in school and beyond.</description></item><item><title>Why thinking about death helps you live a better life | Alua Arthur | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690122/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 14:49:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690122/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a death doula, or someone who supports dying people and their loved ones, Alua Arthur spends a lot of time thinking about the end of life. In a profound talk that examines our brief, perfectly human time on this planet, she asks us to look at our lives through the lens of our deaths in seeking to answer the question: &amp;ldquo;What must I do to be at peace with myself so that I may live presently and die gracefully?</description></item><item><title>How life on Earth adapts to you and me | Shane Campbell-Staton | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690123/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 14:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690123/</guid><description>Podcast Description We tend to think of evolution as a slow, gradual process playing out over millions of years. But evolutionary biologist Shane Campbell-Staton says nature is now changing at breakneck speed to keep up with the world humanity has built. From tuskless elephants who escape poachers to wolves living in the radioactive Chernobyl Exclusion Zone, Campbell-Staton unpacks how life is rapidly adapting in surprising ways &amp;ndash; and asks us to rethink how we can protect the planet&amp;rsquo;s biodiversity.</description></item><item><title>How to embrace – and challenge – the idea of "beauty" (w/ Elise Hu) | How to Be a Better Human | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690124/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Humans have always been captivated by beauty, and for almost as long, we&amp;rsquo;ve been marketed products and new technologies to help us achieve certain beauty standards. Elise Hu is a journalist and the author of &amp;ldquo;Flawless: Lessons in looks and culture from the K-beauty industry.&amp;rdquo; In this episode, she shares the fascinating insights she&amp;rsquo;s learned from years of studying the $10 billion K-beauty industry and the cutting-edge skincare, niche makeup products, and technology that promise to optimize our appearance.</description></item><item><title>How your company can gain a global talent advantage | Johann Daniel Harnoss | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690125/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 15:00:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690125/</guid><description>Podcast Description If a diverse workforce makes a better company, why don&amp;rsquo;t more businesses hire internationally? Innovation and migration strategist Johann Daniel Harnoss details the advantage of global talent and how to best build the systems and culture to welcome immigrants to your staff.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to unleash your inner maximalist through costume | Machine Dazzle | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690126/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 14:51:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tapping into the transformational power of costume, concept artist Machine Dazzle takes us on a maximalist journey through art, history and fashion. From a jaw-droppingly intricate &amp;rsquo;60s bouffant ensemble to a 24-hour show of extravagant outfits, Dazzle shares pieces that channel unrealized dreams, urging us all to fully embrace the beautiful complexity of being ourselves.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A liberating vision of identity that transcends labels | Jioji Ravulo | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690127/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 14:59:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690127/</guid><description>Podcast Description How can we move past society&amp;rsquo;s inclination to box people in with binary thinking and labels? Social work professor Jioji Ravulo believes we need to embrace multiplicity, exploring how Indigenous perspectives can help create more welcoming, collective communities for everyone.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to fund real change in your community | Rebecca Darwent | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690128/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 14:47:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is there a way to give back that benefits everyone? Citing the success of collective giving practices from around the world, philanthropic advisor Rebecca Darwent asks donors to let communities lead decision-making, ushering in a new era of philanthropy that&amp;rsquo;s rooted in interconnected humanity.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A powerful new neurotech tool for augmenting your mind | Conor Russomanno | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690129/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 14:56:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690129/</guid><description>Podcast Description In an astonishing talk and tech demo, neurotechnologist Conor Russomanno shares his work building brain-computer interfaces that could enable us to control the external world with our minds. He discusses the quickly advancing possibilities of this field &amp;ndash; including the promise of a &amp;ldquo;closed-loop system&amp;rdquo; that could both record and stimulate brain activity &amp;ndash; and invites neurohacker Christian Bayerlein onto the TED stage to fly a mind-controlled drone by using a biosensing headset.</description></item><item><title>A modern argument for the rights of animals | Peter Singer | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690130/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 14:59:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why do we prioritize human rights over those of other species? Philosopher Peter Singer dives into what he calls &amp;ldquo;speciesism,&amp;rdquo; the root of the widely ignored mistreatment of animals around the world, from factory farms to product-testing facilities. He makes the case for ending the commercial exploitation of animals for food and invites everyone to reexamine the environmental and moral weight of the status quo. This conversation, hosted by head of TED Chris Anderson, was part of an exclusive TED Membership event.</description></item><item><title>Kung Fu, Star Trek and the many paths to spirituality | Rainn Wilson | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690131/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you feel overwhelmed by the complex issues facing our world, not to mention your own personal problems? Spirituality is the key to staying grounded and hopeful &amp;ndash; even for skeptics, says actor and author Rainn Wilson. He explains why it&amp;rsquo;s time for all of us to experience a spiritual shake-up and outlines two paths to tap into your innate wisdom, kindness and strength. The work begins within yourself.</description></item><item><title>Why Iranians are cutting their hair for "Woman, Life, Freedom" | Sahar Zand | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690132/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 14:39:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Filmmaker Sahar Zand vividly explores the ongoing struggle women face at the hands of Iranian morality police &amp;ndash; like living as second-class citizens with no right to travel, divorce or wear their hair uncovered &amp;ndash; and points to new hope as protests against this unfair treatment continue across the country and around the world. She urges us all to stand in solidarity with the fight for &amp;ldquo;Woman, Life, Freedom&amp;rdquo; and shows why hope is so dangerous to authoritarian regimes.</description></item><item><title>Why are we so bad at reporting good news? | Angus Hervey | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690133/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 14:58:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why is good news so rare? In a special broadcast from the TED stage, journalist Angus Hervey sheds light on some of the incredible progress humanity has made across environmental protection, public health and more in the last year, making the case that if we want to change the story of humanity this century, we have to start changing the stories we tell ourselves. &amp;ldquo;When we only tell the stories of doom, we fail to see the stories of possibility,&amp;rdquo; says Hervey.</description></item><item><title>A 3-step guide to believing in yourself | Sheryl Lee Ralph | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690134/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 14:54:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sheryl Lee Ralph is a force, delivering iconic performances both on stage and screen. But she didn&amp;rsquo;t always know if she&amp;rsquo;d make it big. In a lively talk sparkling with actionable advice, she shares how her struggles taught her what it takes to believe in herself &amp;ndash; and how we can all find the self-confidence to keep moving forward.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to solve the education crisis for boys and men | Richard Reeves | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690135/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 14:47:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690135/</guid><description>Podcast Description While studying inequality and social mobility, Richard Reeves made a surprising discovery: in some countries, like the US and UK, boys are drastically lagging behind girls across many academic measures. He explains why these struggles in school are indicative of the larger crises facing boys and men &amp;ndash; and outlines how society could thoughtfully tackle these challenges to work towards a more inclusive, equitable future. (Followed by a Q&amp;amp;A with head of TED Chris Anderson)</description></item><item><title>What is Juneteenth, and why is it important? | Karlos Hill and Soraya Field Fiorio | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690136/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690136/</guid><description>Podcast Description At the end of the Civil War, though slavery was technically illegal in all states, it still persisted in the last bastions of the Confederacy. This was the case when Union General Gordon Granger marched his troops into Galveston, Texas on June 19th and announced that all enslaved people there were officially free. Karlos K. Hill and Soraya Field Fiorio dig into the history of Juneteenth. [Directed by Rémi Cans, Atypicalist, narrated by Christina Greer, music by Jarrett Farkas].</description></item><item><title>No. You cannot touch my hair! | Mena Fombo | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690137/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 14:42:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Uninvited hair touching, an issue that primarily affects Black women and girls, is an invasion of personal space. To raise awareness of &amp;ldquo;hair attacks,&amp;rdquo; activist Mena Fombo started the &amp;ldquo;No, You Cannot Touch My Hair&amp;rdquo; campaign, showing how unwanted hair touching is an issue that has been and still is rooted in racism. She shares three steps to end this invasive behavior and move toward a world that respects everyone&amp;rsquo;s bodily autonomy.</description></item><item><title>How to weave a cultural legacy through storytelling | Cohen Bradley | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690138/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 14:49:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690138/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;I think of legacy as the weaving together of our stories passed on as a whole,&amp;rdquo; says Haida storyteller Cohen Bradley. Highlighting the significance of potlatch ceremonies (or gift-giving feasts) and other Indigenous traditions of the Haida Nation, Bradley shares why we all should prioritize our collective legacies &amp;ndash; and how they live on through the stories we tell.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The next global superpower isn't who you think | Ian Bremmer | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690139/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 14:57:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who runs the world? Political scientist Ian Bremmer argues it&amp;rsquo;s not as simple as it used to be. With some eye-opening questions about the nature of leadership, he asks us to consider the impact of the evolving global order and our choices as participants in the future of democracy.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"STILL C U" / "Figures" | Jessie Reyez | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690140/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 15:09:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690140/</guid><description>Podcast Description In between two songs that showcase her raw vocal powers, singer-songwriter Jessie Reyez delivers an inspiring talk about how she&amp;rsquo;s turned losses into wins &amp;ndash; and reminds us we&amp;rsquo;re all capable of magic. (This talk contains mature language.)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why is it so hard to get effective birth control in the US? | Mark Edwards | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690141/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 14:53:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nearly half of all pregnancies in the United States are unplanned, the result of millions of people being unable to get the birth control method that works best for them. Reproductive health advocate and 2023 Audacious Project grantee Mark Edwards discusses Upstream USA&amp;rsquo;s nationwide effort to expand access to high-quality contraceptive care by integrating it into primary health-care settings &amp;ndash; a crucial shift towards increasing equal health opportunities and empowering people to decide when and if they want to start families.</description></item><item><title>The natural building blocks of sustainable architecture | Michael Green | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690142/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 14:55:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690142/</guid><description>Podcast Description If we&amp;rsquo;re going to solve the climate crisis, we need to talk about construction. The four main building materials that humans currently use &amp;ndash; concrete, steel, masonry and wood &amp;ndash; have a heavy environmental impact, but what if we had a fifth option? Architect Michael Green proposes an entirely new, natural medium inspired by the structure of trees and plants. Learn more about the carbon-sequestering solution to our construction conundrum that&amp;rsquo;s laying the groundwork for a truly sustainable future.</description></item><item><title>The outlaws of the ocean — and how we're reeling them in | Tony Long | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690143/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 14:49:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pirate fishing, oil spills and other undetected crimes are destroying ocean ecosystems &amp;ndash; but we can&amp;rsquo;t stop what we can&amp;rsquo;t see. Harnessing the power of satellite data and AI to catch maritime offenders in the act, ocean conservation expert and 2023 Audacious Project grantee Tony Long introduces the first-ever live map of all industrial human activity at sea. He shares how his team at Global Fishing Watch is making it freely available to the world so conservationists, researchers and the public can help protect precious aquatic habitats.</description></item><item><title>Nature, art and magical blocks of flying concrete | Lonneke Gordijn | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690144/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 14:55:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690144/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our bodies instinctually respond to the movements and rhythms of nature, like the uplifting feeling you get when walking in a forest. Can art evoke the same emotions? Experiential artist Lonneke Gordijn takes us through her studio&amp;rsquo;s stunning, nature-inspired work &amp;ndash; flowering lights, murmurating drones &amp;ndash; and reveals a mysterious piece hiding in the shadows of the TED Theater that just might change your relationship with concrete.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How wireless energy from space could power everything | Ali Hajimiri | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690145/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 14:51:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Modern life runs on wireless technology. What if the energy powering our devices could also be transmitted without wires? Electrical engineer Ali Hajimiri explains the principles behind wireless energy transfer and shares his far-out vision for launching flexible solar panels into space in order to collect sunlight, convert it to electrical power and then beam it down to Earth. Learn how this technology could power everything &amp;ndash; and light up our world from space.</description></item><item><title>Can we recreate the voice of a 3,000-year-old mummy? | David M. Howard | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690146/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 14:51:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Drawing on his work reconstructing the vocal tract of an ancient Egyptian priest, speech scientist David M. Howard shares three evolutionary wonders of human speech &amp;ndash; and the importance of nurturing your own voice in an increasingly noisy world.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to design a school for the future | Punya Mishra | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690147/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 14:58:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690147/</guid><description>Podcast Description In all the conversations about improving education for children, the voices of students, teachers and community members are often left out. Educational designer Punya Mishra offers a method to shift that paradigm, taking us through new thinking on the root of success (and failure) at school &amp;ndash; and how a totally new, different kind of educational system could better meet students&amp;rsquo; needs.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The poetry of everyday language | Julián Delgado Lopera | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690148/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 15:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690148/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a captivating, poetic ode to the beauty and strength of mixed languages, writer Julián Delgado Lopera paints a picture of immigrant and queer communities united not by their refinement of language but by the creative inventions that spring from their mouths. They invite everyone to reconsider what &amp;ldquo;proper&amp;rdquo; English sounds like – and imagine a blended future where those on the margins are able to speak freely.</description></item><item><title>5 steps to fix any problem at work | Anne Morriss | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690149/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 14:53:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690149/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a practical, playful talk, leadership visionary Anne Morriss reinvents the playbook for how to lead through change &amp;ndash; with a radical, one-week plan to build trust and fix problems by following a step per day.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Your right to mental privacy in the age of brain-sensing tech | Nita Farahany | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690150/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 14:51:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Neurotechnology, or devices that let you track your own brain activity, could help you deeply understand your health. But without privacy protections, your innermost thoughts, emotions and desires could be at risk of exploitation, says neurotech and AI ethicist Nita Farahany. She details some of the field&amp;rsquo;s promising potential uses &amp;ndash; like tracking and treating diseases from depression to epilepsy &amp;ndash; and shares concerns about who collects our brain data and how they plan to use it, ultimately calling for the legal recognition of &amp;ldquo;cognitive liberty&amp;rdquo; as we connect our brains and minds to technology.</description></item><item><title>Could we treat Alzheimer's with light and sound? | Li-Huei Tsai | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690151/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690151/</guid><description>Podcast Description What if we could use brain waves to treat Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s? Professor and neuroscientist Li-Huei Tsai details a promising new approach to artificially stimulate gamma brain waves using light and sound therapy, to increase connectivity and synchrony and delay the onset of this deadly disease. This non-invasive therapy has already been shown to work in mice &amp;ndash; now it&amp;rsquo;s on to human clinical trials, with the potential to usher in a brighter future for everyone.</description></item><item><title>The dinosaur detectives of real-life Jurassic parks | Martin Lockley | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690152/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 14:55:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dinosaur tracks can teach us more about the day-to-day behavior of creatures like T. rex or the Stegosaurus than their skeletons ever could, says paleontologist Martin Lockley. From a &amp;ldquo;dinosaur&amp;rsquo;s lover&amp;rsquo;s lane&amp;rdquo; in Colorado to the rocky shores of South Korea, Lockley explores what we can learn from the traces of some of the most impressive creatures ever to walk the Earth.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Are life-saving medicines hiding in the world's coldest places? | Normand Voyer | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690153/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 14:51:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690153/</guid><description>Podcast Description Could the next wonder drug be somewhere in Canada&amp;rsquo;s snowy north? Take a trip to this beautiful, frigid landscape as chemist Normand Voyer explores the mysterious molecular treasures found in plants thriving in the cold. These scarcely investigated organisms could hold immense medical promise, he says – so long as we work quickly enough to discover them.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A foster care system where every child has a loving home | Sixto Cancel | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690154/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 14:58:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690154/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the US, youth in foster care are nearly twice as likely as war veterans to suffer from PTSD. Placed in foster care at just 11 months old, 2023 Audacious Project grantee Sixto Cancel experienced the faults of the system firsthand. Now, he&amp;rsquo;s the founder of Think of Us, an organization working to reform child welfare by centering kinship care, or placing a child with an extended family member or a familiar adult.</description></item><item><title>Is someone you love suffering in silence? Here's what to do | Gus Worland | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690155/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 14:45:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lots of people talk about the need to be physically fit, but mentally fit? Not as much. In a powerful talk, mental health advocate Gus Worland shares how an experience of deep grief from his own life sparked his mission to advocate for suicide prevention &amp;ndash; and shows why &amp;ldquo;looking after your own village&amp;rdquo; can be as simple as sending a text message, right now, to the person you cannot imagine living without.</description></item><item><title>The timeless, ancient language of art | Wangechi Mutu | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690156/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 15:33:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Using found materials and mesmerizing structures that unearth deep-rooted emotions, Wangechi Mutu&amp;rsquo;s visual creations celebrate our collective history and explore how art communicates into the future. From ancient rock carvings in the Sahel to her own chimeric abstractions, she shares her journey of self-discovery and reminds us all that we already speak the most ancient language of all.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The incredible creativity of deepfakes — and the worrying future of AI | Tom Graham | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690157/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 14:49:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690157/</guid><description>Podcast Description AI-generated media that looks and sounds exactly like the real world will soon permeate our lives. How should we prepare for it? AI developer Tom Graham discusses the extraordinary power of this rapidly advancing technology, demoing cutting-edge examples &amp;ndash; including real-time face swaps and voice cloning &amp;ndash; live from the TED stage. In conversation with head of TED Chris Anderson, Graham digs into the creative potential of this hyperreal content (often referred to as &amp;ldquo;deepfakes&amp;rdquo;) as well as its risk for exploitation and the new legal rights we&amp;rsquo;ll need in order to maintain control over our photorealistic AI avatars.</description></item><item><title>What makes a "good college" — and why it matters | Cecilia M. Orphan | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690158/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 14:59:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690158/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why are &amp;ldquo;good colleges&amp;rdquo; often the ones that accept the fewest students? Exposing the harmful consequences of society&amp;rsquo;s obsession with highly rejective (and expensive) universities, educator Cecilia M. Orphan asks us to rethink what makes institutions &amp;ldquo;prestigious&amp;rdquo; and consider directing funds and attention to where they&amp;rsquo;re needed most: regional public universities that serve all students. A call for schools to be judged by the opportunities they create &amp;ndash; not the ones they stifle.</description></item><item><title>Lessons from losing my mind | Andy Dunn | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690159/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 14:57:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Neurodiversity and innovation often go hand in hand, but does that mean visionary entrepreneurs get a free pass to say and do anything they want? Bonobos founder and mental health advocate Andy Dunn shares his experience navigating bipolar I in the midst of running a successful startup, offering lessons learned on his journey to wellness and steps to create a future where everyone is able to &amp;ldquo;dream crazy dreams&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; while being held accountable.</description></item><item><title>3 ways your money can fight climate change | Veronica Chau | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690160/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 14:52:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690160/</guid><description>Podcast Description What if we could solve the climate and housing crises at the same time? Financial institutions have pledged trillions to transform the economy and accelerate climate action &amp;ndash; but right now, that money is not flowing at the speed it needs to, says sustainable investing expert Veronica Chau. Illuminating the links between climate change and affordable housing, she suggests a playbook of moves to start mobilizing big money and transform climate financing challenges into opportunities.</description></item><item><title>What the world can learn from China's innovation playbook | Keyu Jin | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690161/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 14:52:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690161/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the last few decades, China has gone from technological scarcity to abundance. What sparked this shift? Economist Keyu Jin explores how China has fostered a model of innovation unlike any other and shows why understanding its competitive, collaborative approach could benefit the world &amp;ndash; and perhaps demystify some contradictions.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The urgent risks of runaway AI — and what to do about them | Gary Marcus | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690162/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 14:59:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690162/</guid><description>Podcast Description Will truth and reason survive the evolution of artificial intelligence? AI researcher Gary Marcus says no, not if untrustworthy technology continues to be integrated into our lives at such dangerously high speeds. He advocates for an urgent reevaluation of whether we&amp;rsquo;re building reliable systems (or misinformation machines), explores the failures of today&amp;rsquo;s AI and calls for a global, nonprofit organization to regulate the tech for the sake of democracy and our collective future.</description></item><item><title>Does working hard really make you a good person? | Azim Shariff | TED Talks Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2460690164/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 14:58:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2460690164/</guid><description>Podcast Description Around the world, people who work hard are often seen as morally good &amp;ndash; even if they produce little to no results. Social psychologist Azim Shariff analyzes the roots of this belief and suggests a shift towards a more meaningful way to think about effort, rather than admiring work for work&amp;rsquo;s sake.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>