<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Michelle Obama: The Light Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/michelle-obama-the-light-podcast/</link><description>Recent content in Michelle Obama: The Light Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 07:01:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/michelle-obama-the-light-podcast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introducing "Your Mama's Kitchen" | Michelle Obama: The Light Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7170430001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 07:01:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7170430001/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Tell me about your mama’s kitchen.” That’s the simple request which begins each episode of this new Higher Ground and Audible Original podcast from acclaimed journalist Michele Norris.&amp;nbsp;
On the very first episode of Your Mama’s Kitchen, Former First Lady Michelle Obama talks with Michele about her beginnings growing up in a working-class family on the South Side of Chicago and the delicious red rice her mother made that reminds her of home.</description></item><item><title>“Our Hair is a Portal into our Souls” with Tracee Ellis Ross | Michelle Obama: The Light Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7170430002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 07:01:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7170430002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michelle and Tracee Ellis Ross discuss their personal style, the power of self-expression, and finding self-worth outside of romantic relationships. (Plus: Sit-downs with Michelle’s personal stylists!)
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Barack Is My Home" with Oprah Winfrey | Michelle Obama: The Light Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7170430003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 12:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7170430003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michelle and Oprah talk about Michelle’s 50th birthday party on Oprah’s estate, how they foster relationships that last, and why—even after everything that has happened in our country—Michelle still believes in “going high." Find the episode transcript here: audible.com/tlp/episode8
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"The Friendship Bubble" with Elizabeth Alexander | Michelle Obama: The Light Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7170430004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 12:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7170430004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Legendary poet and teacher Elizabeth Alexander sits down with Michelle to discuss their 30 years of friendship, how they struggled as young mothers, and crucial support their friend group has given to them at the low points in their lives. Elizabeth also draws the curtain back on what really happens when you go on a retreat to Camp David with the First Lady. Find the episode transcript here: audible.</description></item><item><title>“Excellence Is My Practice” with Gayle King | Michelle Obama: The Light Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7170430005/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7170430005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Parenting is the focus of this conversation: Gayle opens up about how she approached raising her “favorite daughter” and “favorite son”, and Michelle discusses her fight to keep her daughters normal in the White House. (Spoiler: Driving lessons and dating are pretty tricky.) She also shares stories about watching the girls now that they’re launched and living together.
Find the episode transcript here: audible.com/tlp/episode6 Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>"The Power Of Small" with David Letterman | Michelle Obama: The Light Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7170430006/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 12:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7170430006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Legendary talk show host and comedian David Letterman talks to Michelle about anxiety—vulnerability, his struggles with taking criticism, and their mutual experiences in the public eye. They also swap knitting tips and Michelle shares the tools that she leans on to quiet her mind. Find the episode transcript here: audible.com/tlp/episode5
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Decoding Fear" with Ellen DeGeneres | Michelle Obama: The Light Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7170430007/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 12:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7170430007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ellen DeGeneres and Michelle discuss the role fear plays in their lives—why it’s important, the people who would weaponize it, and ways to turn the things that terrify you into rocket fuel. Michelle also tells the story of being forced to decide whether her husband would run for president and the time that inviting a Star Wars character to the White House ended up scarring one of her daughters.</description></item><item><title>“Telling Myself That I Was Enough” with Conan O’Brien | Michelle Obama: The Light Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7170430008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 12:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7170430008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan sits down with Michelle to talk about growing up feeling different and swap hard won lessons about relationships and marriage. Plus: Michelle tells stories of her White House travels, including an unexpected invitation from the Queen that ended in a solid gold room. Find the episode transcript here: audible.com/tlp/episode3
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>“We All Have A Light” with Tyler Perry | Michelle Obama: The Light Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7170430009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 12:00:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7170430009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tyler Perry and Michelle discuss their different—but extremely powerful—childhood memories, the drive to succeed as working class Black folks and the difficulty of raising kids in the spotlight. Bonus special guest Madea pops in with a few things to say about “going high”! Find the episode transcript here: audible.com/tlp/episode2
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>“Kids Just Want Our Gladness” with Hoda Kotb | Michelle Obama: The Light Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7170430010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 12:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7170430010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hoda and Michelle go deep on the importance of shining our light for others, especially children. They also talk about how they’ve navigated the most daunting challenges in their lives—from Michelle’s time as the first Black First Lady or Hoda’s decision to adopt kids late in life.
Find the episode transcript here: audible.com/tlp/episode1
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Introducing “The Sum of Us” | Michelle Obama: The Light Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7170430011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7170430011/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a new series from Higher Ground, author Heather McGhee embarks on a road trip across Covid-era America, unearthing stories of American hope and solidarity in a time of great division and peril for our democracy. In the first episode of the podcast, we’ll meet Heather and learn more about her journey—from rural Maine to the coast of California— as she meets extraordinary Americans who are crossing demographic, cultural and political lines to shape their communities for the better.</description></item><item><title>Introducing "Renegades: Born in the USA" | Michelle Obama: The Light Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7170430012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7170430012/</guid><description>Podcast Description So much has happened since the debut of The Michelle Obama Podcast—including President Barack Obama, launching a podcast of his own. Renegades: Born in the USA is a series of conversations between the former Commander in Chief and Bruce Springsteen about their lives, their favorite music, and their enduring love of America, despite all its challenges and contradictions. This episode—about fatherhood—is Mrs. Obama’s favorite. But they’re all terrific. Head to the Renegades: Born in the USA feed here to listen to all eight now.</description></item><item><title>Family Ties: On Raising Kids with Craig &amp; Marian Robinson | Michelle Obama: The Light Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7170430013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7170430013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michelle’s mom and brother join to talk all things parenting—from bringing babies home to dropping them off at college. Find the episode transcript here: https://spoti.fi/TMOP_transcripts Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Across Generations: Michelle Obama and Her Mentees | Michelle Obama: The Light Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7170430014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 07:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7170430014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Part two of our discussion about mentorship features Michelle in conversation with her younger team members, in which they explore the ups and downs of professional life and what it’s like to be a black woman right now. Find the episode transcript here: https://spoti.fi/TMOP_transcripts Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Working Women: Valerie Jarrett and the Importance of Mentorship | Michelle Obama: The Light Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7170430015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7170430015/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part one of her discussion about mentorship, Michelle reminisces with her friend and former boss Valerie Jarrett about personal growth in the workplace. Find the episode transcript here: https://spoti.fi/TMOP_transcripts Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>They Do: Talking Marriage with Conan O’Brien | Michelle Obama: The Light Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7170430016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 07:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7170430016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan O’Brien video chats with Michelle to discuss the challenges and joys of marriage. Find the episode transcript here: http://spoti.fi/TMOP_transcripts
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Gift of Girlfriends with Denielle, Sharon, and Kelly | Michelle Obama: The Light Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7170430017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 07:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7170430017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michelle Obama sits down with three of her dearest friends—Denielle Pemberton-Heard, Dr. Sharon Malone, and Kelly Dibble—to talk about women’s friendship and navigating the White House years. Find the episode transcript here: http://spoti.fi/TMOP_transcripts Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Growing Up Robinson with Craig and Michelle | Michelle Obama: The Light Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7170430018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 07:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7170430018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michelle chats with her beloved older brother about their childhood and growing up together on the South Side of Chicago. Find the episode transcript here: http://spoti.fi/TMOP_transcripts Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What Your Mother Never Told You About Health with Dr. Sharon Malone | Michelle Obama: The Light Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7170430019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 07:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7170430019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michelle talks with her friend, Dr. Sharon Malone, an OB-GYN, about women’s health, menopause, and aging. Find the episode transcript here: http://spoti.fi/TMOP_transcripts Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Protests and the Pandemic with Michele Norris | Michelle Obama: The Light Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7170430020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7170430020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Award-winning journalist Michele Norris joins Michelle to discuss how we can gain new understandings of ourselves during an international pandemic and national reckoning with race. Find the episode transcript here: http://spoti.fi/TMOP_transcripts Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>President Barack Obama | Michelle Obama: The Light Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7170430021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7170430021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michelle talks with her husband about the current moment and our responsibilities to our communities, our country, and each other. Find the episode transcript here: http://spoti.fi/TMOP_transcripts Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>