<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Culips Everyday English Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/culips-everyday-english-podcast/</link><description>Recent content in Culips Everyday English Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 19:03:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/culips-everyday-english-podcast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bonus episode #081 – Gabby Girl | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040203/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 19:03:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040203/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus episode #081 - Gabby Girl
Episode description
In this episode, Andrew tells a story about receiving a sudden and mysterious DM on Instagram, which led to him and his wife agreeing to watch a dog named Gabby for five days. Listen in to hear all the details while improving your English fluency in a fun and effective way!
Study with the interactive transcript: click here
Become a Culips member: click here</description></item><item><title>Real Talk #61 – Asking for a recommendation letter | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040202/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 21:12:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040202/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever had to ask for a recommendation letter? In this episode, Andrew and Kassy teach you many useful expressions that are helpful not only in that situation but also in many other everyday scenarios. This episode is designed to improve your vocabulary and boost your confidence in English. You don’t want to miss it!
Fun facts
Did you know that recommendation letters have been around for a long time?</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode #080 – Christmas market chaos | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040201/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 19:21:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040201/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus episode #080 - Christmas market chaos
Episode description
Join Andrew as he talks about unseasonably warm weather, the challenge of running down stairs, overheating, a chaotic Christmas market, Glühwein, and a winning hockey team! Improve your English fluency with these entertaining stories.
Study with the interactive transcript: click here
Become a Culips member: click here
Join the Culips Discord server: click here
Bonus 31 - A sweet mystery: click here</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #312 – Gaslighting | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 03:03:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever heard the term “gaslighting”? The verb “to gaslight” has become a very popular word over the past several years. Gaslighting is a manipulation tactic where someone makes another person doubt their own experiences and memories. In this episode, Andrew and Anna have a thought-provoking discussion about this concept. They introduce the definition of the term, its history, and their personal thoughts and experiences with gaslighting in their own lives.</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode #079 – Life is weird | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040002/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 17:55:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus episode #079 - Life is weird
Episode description
In this bonus episode, Andrew tells two stories about coincidences. He talks about buying a Nintendo, meeting one of his favorite podcast hosts, cold winds, closed stores, Hongdae cults, and meeting a Culips listener. Listen for fun and surprising tales!
Study with the interactive transcript: click here
Become a Culips member: click here
Join the Culips Discord server: click here</description></item><item><title>Fluency Files #67: Mood boosters | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040003/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 04:25:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;re sharing a special episode from our Fluency Files series, which is usually for Culips members only. In this one, Andrew talks about the 5 ways he boosts his mood to feel better when he’s tired or stressed.
Culips members get a study guide for this episode which includes an interactive transcript, vocabulary glossary, detailed vocabulary explanations with example sentences, listening comprehension questions, and prompts for speaking and writing practice.</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode #078 – Home alone | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040004/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 21:04:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus episode #078 - Home alone
Episode description
In this bonus episode, Andrew shares his experience of spending a week alone at home while his wife was away in Japan. He also discusses their reunion and the amazing gifts she brought back for him. Tune in to hear all the details!
Study with the interactive transcript: click here
Become a Culips member: click here
Join the Culips Discord server: click here</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #185 – Nintendo power | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040005/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 05:42:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040005/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this fun episode, Kassy and Andrew share their love of video games with each other. They mostly talk about games from the Nintendo franchise, which is famous for characters like Mario and Pikachu. Kassy chats about the cooperative game she has been playing with her husband on her Nintendo Switch recently and Andrew mentions his desire to buy a Switch himself. If you have nostalgia for classic Nintendo games, then this is the episode for you!</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode #077 – The spontaneous chef | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 06:54:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus episode #077 - The spontaneous chef
Episode description
In this episode, Andrew shares a story about finding the perfect sofa for his living room. He talks about the challenges of finding
In this bonus episode, join Andrew as he tells a story about an unplanned cooking adventure. Listen as he talks about deciding to make homemade pizza, sharing his experiences from selecting ingredients to the final delicious outcome.</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #311 – The Taylor Swift effect | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040007/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 03:25:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040007/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Andrew and Anna explore the &amp;lsquo;Taylor Swift effect,&amp;rsquo; which refers to Taylor Swift’s influence on her fans and society in general. They discuss the impact of her work, her personality, and the factors contributing to her remarkable success. If you’re a Taylor Swift fan or simply want to learn more about her, give this episode a listen!
Fun facts
Did you know that you can now study Taylor Swift at universities?</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode #076 – Daisy’s big day | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040008/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 19:13:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus episode #076 - Daisy’s big day
Episode description
In this episode, Andrew shares his experience of attending a unique wedding at a beer brewery. Tune in for a fun story that will help boost your English fluency.
Study with the interactive transcript: click here
Become a Culips member: click here
Join the Culips Discord server: click here
Check out Armchair Expert: click here
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #184 – Andrew and Kassy catch up (again) | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040009/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 07:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040009/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a couple of weeks apart, hosts Andrew and Kassy reunite in this episode to catch up! They talk about Kassy&amp;rsquo;s recent trip to South Korea and a health issue that Andrew has been facing. They also share their love for Korean food and discuss the dishes they crave the most when they’re out of the country.
Fun facts
Mudeungsan is a beautiful mountain located in a national park.</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode #075 – A sofa story | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040010/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 19:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus episode #075 - A sofa story
Episode description
In this episode, Andrew shares a story about finding the perfect sofa for his living room. He talks about the challenges of finding the right size, fabric, and color. Listen to hear all about the ups and downs of his sofa saga and improve your English fluency along the way.
Study with the interactive transcript: click here
Become a Culips member: click here</description></item><item><title>Real Talk #60 – How to ask for a recommendation at a bookstore | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040011/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 20:50:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you a bookworm? Do you enjoy reading books? In this episode, Andrew and Kassy discuss how to ask for a book recommendation at a library or a bookstore. They teach you many useful expressions that you can use in this situation and in various other everyday conversations. Make sure to listen to this lesson to improve your vocabulary and boost your speaking confidence!
Fun facts Did you know that silent reading, which is a common thing today, wasn’t always normal in the history of reading?</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode #074 – Memories of a marathon | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040012/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 18:00:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus episode #074 - Memories of a marathon Episode description In this week&amp;rsquo;s bonus episode, Andrew recounts the story of running in the Gyeongju Marathon. Listen along to hear about the highs and lows of the experience, including getting stuck in a traffic jam, being caught on live TV in an embarrassing moment, smashing a personal record, and feeling too old to celebrate!
Study with the interactive transcript: click here</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #183 – Regions of the USA | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040013/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:35:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040013/</guid><description>Podcast Description As you can imagine, a country as large as the United States has many regions with their own distinct personalities. In this episode, Andrew and Kassy chat about all of the different regions in the United States. They discuss things like food, culture, accents, natural features, and demographics. If you’d like to learn more about culture in the United States, then this episode is for you!
Fun facts The United States contains a multitude of dialects.</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode #073 – History lesson | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040014/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 21:18:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus episode #073 - History lesson Episode description In this episode, Andrew talks about the history of Culips from its early days as one of the first English-language education podcasts, to where it’s at today! Plus, he answers a very frequently asked question: What does the word “Culips” mean?
Become a Culips member: click here
Study with the interactive transcript: click here
Join the Culips Discord server: click here</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #182 – Time versus money | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 20:39:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join Andrew and Kassy as they discuss the timeless debate of Time vs. Money. They share their perspectives, talk about how age changes our views on that matter, and discuss what they prefer to spend money on. Also, they chat about what they would do if there were more than 24 hours in a day in the bonus part of the episode.
Fun facts Recent studies show that, after the pandemic, more people prefer spending their money on experiences rather than material possessions.</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode #072 – Cherry on top | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 01:05:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus episode #072 - Cherry on top Episode description In this episode, Andrew discusses a moment of truth and recounts a comical visit to a local clinic in his neighborhood. Plus, in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you about the expression, &amp;ldquo;the cherry on top.&amp;rdquo;
Become a Culips member: click here
Study with the interactive transcript: click here
Join the Culips Discord server: click here
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #181 – Doin’ the chores | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040017/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 19:26:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nobody likes to do chores, but we all have to do them. In this episode, Andrew and Kassy discuss how they split chores in their households, and chat about cleaning services while sharing some useful cleaning tips and life hacks. Join in to improve your listening and speaking skills while picking up essential vocabulary!
Fun facts Most of us aren’t fans of doing chores, but there are actually numerous benefits to them.</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode #071 – Train to Busan | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 01:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus episode #071 - Train to Busan Episode description In this episode, Andrew talks about a trip he took over the weekend with his wife to Busan. Plus in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you about the expression “I’m on dinner duty.”
Become a Culips member: click here
Study with the interactive transcript: click here
Join the Culips Discord server: click here
Visit the Le Meets brunch cafe Instagram: click here</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #180 – Fast fashion | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:04:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrew and Kassy tackle a big topic in this episode – the problem with fast fashion. Fast fashion is when clothes are made quickly and cheaply, so people can buy new styles often and at low prices. Although this sounds like a good thing, it’s bad for the workers who make the clothing and it’s bad for the environment. Give this episode a listen and learn about the topic of fast fashion and Andrew and Kassy’s personal relationships to fashion.</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode #070 – A real nice surprise | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040020/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 18:36:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus episode #070 - A real nice surprise Episode description In this episode, Andrew shares a story about a surprise visit from an old friend. Plus, in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you about the idiom not your first rodeo.
Become a Culips member: click here
Study with the interactive transcript: click here
Join the Culips Discord server: click here
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Real Talk #059 – How to deal with noisy neighbours | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040021/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 03:16:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrew and Kassy discuss how to handle noisy neighbours in this Real Talk episode. Dealing with noisy neighbours can be challenging, but with the right approach you might be able to solve the problem without losing your cool. This episode features several useful expressions for bringing up topics that aren’t easy to discuss and for addressing conflict.
Fun facts There are often local laws called noise ordinances. These limit how much noise you are allowed to make at certain times of day, such as between 10 PM and 7 AM.</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode #069 – Goodbye King Pinky | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 22:39:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus episode #069 - Goodbye King Pinky Episode description In this episode, Andrew talks about saying goodbye to his pet dog, Pinky. Plus in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you the expression to set off your alarm bells.
Become a Culips member: click here
Study with the interactive transcript: click here
Join the Culips Discord server: click here
Bonus episode 57: click here
Culips Instagram: click here
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #179 – How Kassy spent her summer in Europe | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 19:46:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040023/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Kassy and Andrew talk about Kassy’s trip to Europe. Kassy shares her adventures in Sweden, Italy, and Scotland. During this trip, she visited her family, went hiking, stayed in a 15th-century castle, and volunteered at an Eco Lodge. Listen to this Simplified Speech episode to hear all the exciting details!
Fun facts Did you know that around 80% of Scandinavians speak English fluently? English is prioritized in their education, starting from a young age.</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode #068 – The sixth spot | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 02:21:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus episode #068 - The sixth spot Episode description The bonus series is back! Join Andrew as he shares a story about his recent adventure down south in Gwangju, where he caught up with friends and tackled a challenging half marathon along a scenic forest road. Plus, in the vocabulary lesson, Andrew will teach you a useful English idiom: &amp;ldquo;To snore your head off.&amp;rdquo;
Study with the interactive transcript here:</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #310 – The troubling world of deep fakes | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040025/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 18:19:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040025/</guid><description>Podcast Description In our modern world, technology is changing our lives all the time, and mostly, it’s making things better. But there are some tech innovations that can be a little worrying, even scary. In this episode, Andrew and Anna dive into the world of deepfakes. They explore their pros and cons and discuss how they might affect our future. If you’re interested in the world of modern technology and its hidden dangers, this episode is for you!</description></item><item><title>Catch Word #272 – Bear with me | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040026/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 21:13:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever found yourself in a situation where you needed someone to wait patiently while you handled something? In this Catch Word episode, Andrew and Kassy teach you two expressions you can use in such situations: bear with me and hang tight.
Catch Word is a Culips series that teaches you idioms, phrasal verbs, and expressions used in everyday life. With Catch Word, you learn common phrases used by native English speakers while listening to casual, natural conversations.</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode #067 – Early in the morning | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040027/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 03:59:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus episode #067 - Early in the morning Episode description Andrew talks about a new app that he’s become addicted to and how he used that app to make an early morning purchase. Plus, in the vocabulary lesson he teaches you how to use the idiomatic expression to put words in [someone’s] mouth.
Study with the interactive transcript here:
Listen to the interview with Indiana here:
Join the Culips Discord server here:</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #178 – Interview with Indiana | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040028/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 06:35:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040028/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Andrew interviews one of Culips’ study guide writers, Indiana! He asks her about how she got interested in languages, how she became an English teacher, and what her hobbies are. Plus, Andrew and Indiana share an exciting piece of news – a free Culips course that starts in October! Listen to this episode to find out more about this exciting English learning opportunity.
Join our first live course to study Simplified Speech episodes with a native English-speaking teacher for free!</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #066 – Let’s clear the air | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040029/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 04:14:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #066 - Let’s clear the air Episode description Andrew shares a story about a miscommunication, meeting up for lunch with his brother-in-law, a funny thing that happened at the Apple store, and more in this edition of the bonus episode. Plus in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you about the idiom to clear the air.
Study with the interactive transcript here:
Join the Culips Discord server here:</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #177 – Museums and galleries | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040030/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 19:54:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040030/</guid><description>Podcast Description How often do you go to museums and art galleries? In this episode, Andrew and Kassy chat about the different kinds of art exhibits they enjoy visiting. They also talk about some of the reasons they do not always enjoy spending time at art galleries, including anxiety and the behaviour of other gallery-goers.
Join the Culips Discord server here:
Fun facts Did you know that there is a special word in the United States to refer to museum tour guides?</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #65 – Sandwich day | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040031/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 02:40:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #65 - Sandwich day Episode description Andrew talks about forest fires raging in his hometown, marathon training, gifts from his mother-in-law, and more. Plus, in the vocabulary lesson, you’ll learn about the phrasal verb: to ramp up.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips member.
To sign up, visit Culips.com.
Study with the interactive transcript here:
Join the Culips Discord server here:</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #176 – Quality or quantity? | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040032/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 17:37:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you prefer quality over quantity, or the other way around? Your answer will probably vary depending on the situation. In this Simplifies Speech episode, Andrew and Kassy talk about the idea of quality versus quantity when it comes to making choices in life. They share their preferences and discuss when quality matters more than quantity, and vice versa. Listen in to find out more and learn useful vocabulary to express your thoughts on quality and quantity in English!</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #064 – The mushroom mystery | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040033/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 17:55:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #064 - The mushroom mystery Episode description Andrew talks about a fascinating and sad news story involving three deaths from eating poisonous mushrooms. Accident or crime? Listen to and decide for yourself! In the vocabulary lesson, you’ll learn about the phrasal verb to feel for (someone).
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips member.
To sign up, visit Culips.com.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #175 – Game changers | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040034/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:50:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever tried something new that completely changed the way you live your daily life? These new technologies and experiences are often called game changers. In this episode, Andrew and Kassy discuss game changers, such as having a GPS in your car, AI assistants like ChatGPT, and streaming services like Netflix.
Fun facts When you call something a game changer, it usually sounds positive. However, it can also be used neutrally or negatively.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #063 – Heat wave | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040035/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 04:49:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #063 - Heat wave Episode description In this edition of the bonus episode, Andrew talks about his weekend of cancelled plans. Plus, in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you about the word copycat.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips member.
To sign up, visit Culips.com.
Study with the interactive transcript here:
Join the Culips Discord server here:
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #309 – Quiet quitting | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040036/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 20:33:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040036/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Chatterbox episode, Andrew and Anna discuss quiet quitting. This term gained popularity during the COVID pandemic, and it refers to a situation where workers do the bare minimum of their employment responsibilities and do only the job that they’re being paid to do. Through this, employees refuse to engage in hustle culture. The question is, is quiet quitting a problem or a solution? Tune in to find out what our hosts think about it!</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #62 -Tourist in your town | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040037/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 05:09:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #62 - Tourist in your town Episode description In this edition of the bonus episode, Andrew talks about the trip he took without even leaving the city! Intrigued? Listen to find out the details. Plus in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you about the idiomatic expression to rub shoulders with someone
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips member.</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #308 – The life and legacy of Alan Turing | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040038/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 18:21:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040038/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Chatterbox episode, Andrew and Anna explore the fascinating life of Alan Turing, a visionary mathematician and codebreaker whose genius has shaped our modern world of technology. Join our hosts as they discuss the remarkable achievements and personal struggles of this legendary figure.
Chatterbox is the Culips series designed for intermediate and advanced English learners, featuring two native English speakers having natural conversations. Learning with Chatterbox will help you improve your listening and speaking skills and expand your cultural awareness.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #061 – Cake quest and marathon test | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040039/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 05:34:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #061 - Cake quest and marathon test Episode description In this edition of the bonus episode, Andrew shares two stories about what he did last week. The first is about his wife’s birthday party and the second is about starting to train for a marathon. Plus, in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you about a useful English idiom: to put your money where your mouth is. Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips member.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #174 – What do you think about remakes? | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040040/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 18:03:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you like remakes, or do you believe that nothing can beat the original? In this Simplified Speech episode, Andrew and Kassy discuss remakes of movies and video games, and whether the remakes can be better than the originals of our childhoods. They also talk about why remakes have become so popular lately and share their own opinions on this matter. Tune in to find out what they think while improving your English conversation skills!</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode #60 – Round 2 | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040041/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 02:06:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus episode #60 - Round 2 Episode description In this week’s edition of the bonus episode, Andrew talks about teaching Korean for the first time, catching COVID for the second time, and how he spent his 5-day bedroom quarantine. Plus in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you about the expression: to chalk [something] up to [something].
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips member.</description></item><item><title>Catch Word #271 – Seen better days | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040042/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 22:19:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040042/</guid><description>Podcast Description There are many different ways to talk about things that are old and worn out in English. In this episode, Andrew and Suzanne teach you two idiomatic expressions you can use to describe these things: seen better days and worse for wear.
Catch Word is the Culips vocabulary series designed for intermediate and advanced English learners. This series teaches you how to use everyday expressions, idioms, and slang to improve your speaking and listening skills.</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #307 – Setting boundaries | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040043/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 05:53:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040043/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Chatterbox episode, Andrew and Anna talk about the concept of setting boundaries. Setting boundaries means creating limits between ourselves and others. For instance, one example of a boundary you could set is to not respond to work-related calls after dinner time. You can set boundaries for yourself, your friends, family, and even your coworkers and boss. Setting boundaries is an important way to take control in your life and show respect for yourself.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #059 – Books and buddies | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040044/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 06:16:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #059 - Books and buddies Episode description In this week’s edition of the bonus episode, Andrew talks about having some guests over to his house, professional development, and a new book by one of his favorite writers. Plus, in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you about the expression to stay on your toes.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips member.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #173 – Kassy’s European summer | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040045/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 21:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040045/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Andrew and Kassy discuss Kassy’s plans for the summer. Kassy and her husband are going to Europe to volunteer at an Eco Lodge in Scotland. Tune in to find out all the details!
Simplified Speech is a Culips series that features two native English speakers having clear and natural conversations about fascinating topics. These episodes are designed to help you improve your English listening and speaking skills in a fun and exciting way.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #058 – One step forward, two steps back | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 02:57:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #058 - One step forward, two steps back Episode description In this week’s edition of the bonus episode, Andrew talks about some trials and errors he went through when trying to upgrade the storage drive in his old computer. Plus in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you about the phrasal verb to swap out.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member.</description></item><item><title>Catch Word #270 – Bottom of the barrel | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040047/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 03:42:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040047/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’ve all been in situations where our options were limited, and we had to accept something less than what we wanted. In this episode, Andrew and Kassy explain two idiomatic expressions that you can use to describe these situations, bottom of the barrel and slim pickings.
Catch Word is the Culips vocabulary series designed for intermediate and advanced English learners. By listening to these audio lessons, you can learn idioms, expressions, and phrasal verbs that native speakers use all the time.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #057 – The good, the bad, and the ugly cry | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040048/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 02:41:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #057 - The good, the bad, and the ugly cry Episode description In this week’s edition of the bonus episode, Andrew talks about what he’s been up to over the last couple of weeks, including moving to his new house and a health scare with his pet dog Pinky Boy. Listen, learn, and improve your English fluency with real-life stories.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #172 – What kind of web surfer are you? | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040049/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 05:52:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you use tabs a lot? Do you prefer to use keyboard shortcuts or mouse clicks? In this episode, Andrew and Suzanne talk about the different ways to browse the internet. They share their different styles of surfing the internet and explore the pros and cons of each approach.
Simplified Speech is the Culips series for beginner and intermediate English language learners that features easy to understand conversations about everyday topics.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #056.5 – Status update | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040050/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 22:59:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #056.5 - Status update Episode description Andrew quickly checks in to give you a status update about what’s new at Culips this week.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member. To sign up, visit Culips.com.
Join the Culips Discord server here:
Watch the Discord tutorial here:
Listen to Chatterbox #306
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #306 – Stepping outside your comfort zone | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040051/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 05:18:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stepping outside of your comfort zone can be scary, but it helps you grow as a person. In this episode, Andrew and Anna explore the science of stepping outside of your comfort zone, talk about why it’s important to push yourself, and share their own stories of personal growth and overcoming challenges.
Culips’ Chatterbox series is designed for intermediate and advanced English learners. Chatterbox episodes feature two native English speakers having natural conversations.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #056 – False alarm | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040052/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 00:08:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #056 - False alarm Episode description In this week’s bonus episode, Andrew makes a big announcement about the new Culips Discord server. Plus, he tells you a story about a false alarm and teaches you the idiomatic expression ‘like a champ.’
Study with the interactive transcript here:
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member. To sign up, visit Culips.</description></item><item><title>Real Talk #058 – How to compliment someone’s appearance | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040053/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 04:45:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040053/</guid><description>Podcast Description It feels great to give compliments, but do you know how to do it in English? When done correctly, it can help you create warm connections with others. In this Real Talk episode, Andrew and Kassy guide you through effective and easy-to-understand ways to compliment someone&amp;rsquo;s appearance.
By learning these expressions, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to make your friends feel good and appreciated while also improving your own English fluency and cultural understanding.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #055 – Rain, shine, and moving time | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040054/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 01:53:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #055 - Rain, shine, and moving time Episode description In this week’s bonus episode, talks about celebrating his anniversary and getting ready for his upcoming move. Plus, he teaches you a useful English expression that will improve your listening and speaking, ‘to be in flux.’
Study with the interactive transcript here:
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member. To sign up, visit Culips.</description></item><item><title>Catch Word#269 – Move mountains | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040055/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 04:40:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever had to move mountains to achieve something? In this episode, Andrew and Suzanne teach you two useful idiomatic expressions that mean to work extra hard: to bend over backwards and to move mountains. Give this episode a listen to learn how to use these expressions!
Catch Word is the Culips vocabulary series for intermediate and advanced English language learners. With this series you will learn idioms, expressions, and phrasal verbs that will help improve your English listening and speaking skills.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #054 – Pioneers of the Continuum | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040056/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 02:16:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #054 - Pioneers of the Continuum Episode description In this week&amp;rsquo;s bonus episode, Andrew chats with Alastair Budge. Alastair is the creator of the English for Curious Minds podcast. They discuss an exciting new audio drama that Alastair has created called Pioneers of the Continuum, which features voice actors from the English language podcast community.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #171 – What’s your house like? | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040057/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 04:45:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040057/</guid><description>Podcast Description What’s unique about your home? In this Simplified Speech episode, Andrew and Suzanne take Culips listeners on an audio tour of their homes. They discuss size, rooms, amenities, renovations, and memories. How do you think a Korean apartment in the middle of Seoul will compare to a duplex in Montreal? Listen and find out!
Fun facts If you want to buy an apartment in Seoul, the average cost in 2023 is over one billion won (or over $750,000).</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #053 – Dark horse | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040058/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 04:39:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #053 - Dark horse Episode description In this week’s bonus episode, Andrew talks about a dead mic, a failed recording session, and a new technology. Plus, he and Kassy teach you two interesting idiomatic expressions, black sheep and dark horse.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member. To sign up, visit Culips.com.
Study with the interactive transcript here.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #170 – The little joys in life | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040059/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 18:05:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Daily life can often feel hectic and stressful. It’s easy to get caught up in the chaos and focus on your responsibilities and the future. However, it’s also important to slow down once in a while and reflect on the little joys in life. In this episode, Andrew and Suzanne do just that—they chat about the small but lovely things they enjoy during daily life, such as the smell of coffee in the morning and gazing at a bouquet of fresh-cut flowers.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #052 – The anniversary episode | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040060/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 05:07:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #052 - The anniversary episode Episode description In this week’s bonus episode, Andrew talks about how he spent the weekend celebrating Children’s Day and Parents’ Day. And in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you a useful English expression: R and R.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member. To sign up, visit Culips.com.
Study with the interactive transcript here.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #169 – Andrew and Kassy catch up | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040061/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 18:09:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040061/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Andrew and Kassy have a catch-up and share what’s been happening in their lives lately. They talk about reading challenges, useful reading and productivity apps, and Kassy’s recent sports adventures.
The Simplified Speech series features native speakers having clear, natural, and easy-to-understand conversations. By studying with this Simplified Speech episode, you’ll improve your English listening skills, increase your vocabulary, and learn how to talk about recent events happening in your life.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #051 – There’s an app for that | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040062/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 23:04:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #051 - There’s an app for that Episode description In this bonus episode, Andrew talks about playing the drums and selling furniture. Plus he talks about the awesome Culips member live stream from last week and teaches you a useful idiomatic expression: to be in the market for something.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member. To sign up, visit Culips.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #168 – The ballet | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040063/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 21:09:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you like ballet? In this episode, Andrew and Suzanne talk about this unique style of dancing. They discuss its origins and characteristics, and explain some specific vocabulary along the way. Suzanne, a former professional dancer, shares her own story and what ballet means to her.
Simplified Speech is a Culips series that features two native English speakers having clear, natural, and easy-to-understand conversations about interesting topics. These episodes are designed to help you improve your English listening and speaking skills in a fun and exciting way.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #050 – The lost episode | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040064/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 04:39:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #050 -The lost episode Episode description Join Andrew as he tells a story about a surprising discovery he found while organizing some files on his hard drive last week. Then after the story, Andrew teaches you a must-know phrasal verb that will improve your English fluency: to get around [something].
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member. To sign up, visit Culips.</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #305 – Online anonymity | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040065/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 21:17:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040065/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Chatterbox episode, Anna and Andrew talk about online anonymity. They share their own stories about using the internet and discuss the pros and cons of being anonymous online. They discuss how being anonymous can help people talk honestly but can also cause problems like cyberbullying and false information.
Chatterbox is the Culips series designed for intermediate and advanced English learners. The series features fascinating conversations between native English speakers, covering a variety of topics such as culture, current events, everyday life, and more.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #049 – Lamp, lamb, luck | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040066/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 04:31:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #049 - Lamp, lamb, luck Episode description Join Andrew as he talks about how a normal day doing some errands with his wife had a surprise ending. Along the way, he’ll also give you some updates about what’s new at Culips and teach you a helpful English idiom, to weigh your options.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #167 – Emotional support animals | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040067/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 20:51:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrew and Suzanne discuss emotional support animals (also known as ESAs). They chat about Suzanne’s process with registering her dog as an ESA for her upcoming travel plans. This is a great episode for listeners interested in learning more about the ESA registration process and practicing pet and air travel vocabulary!
Simplified Speech is the Culips series for beginner and intermediate English learners. It includes easy-to-understand conversations between two native speakers, helping you build vocabulary and improve your listening skills in English.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #048 – Walking and talking | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040068/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 18:49:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #048 - Walking and talking Episode description In this week’s bonus episode, Andrew talks about the last-moment trip he took to Jeju Island to meet up with one of his oldest and best friends. Plus, in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you about the useful English idiom to throw a wrench into [someone’s] plans.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member.</description></item><item><title>Catch Word #268 – I cracked under the pressure | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040069/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 04:01:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever been so nervous or stressed about a presentation that you forgot everything you had prepared? Have you ever performed well during sports practice but made mistakes during the big game? There are lots of great idioms to describe these nightmare scenarios in English and, in this episode, Andrew and Kassy introduce listeners to two of the most common ones: to crack under the pressure and can’t take/handle the heat.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #047 – Big plans, little oven | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040070/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 05:32:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #047 - Big plans, little oven Episode description In this week’s bonus episode, Andrew shares two stories about his ongoing house renovation, one that’s funny and one that’s interesting. In the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you about the idiom to butt heads.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member. To sign up, visit Culips.com.
Study with the interactive transcript here.</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox#304 – Burnout | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040071/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 03:57:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you ever feel exhausted and overwhelmed with work or other aspects of your life? If so, you&amp;rsquo;re not alone. Burnout is a common experience that can happen to anyone. In this episode, Andrew and Anna explore what burnout is, how to recognize it, and most importantly, what you can do to prevent it.
Chatterbox is a series for intermediate and advanced English learners that features native English speakers having natural conversations on interesting topics.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #046 – Dinner party | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040072/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 18:02:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #046 - Dinner party Episode description In this week’s bonus episode, Andrew talks about a unique dinner party he had with his friends over the weekend. Along the way, he teaches you about some interesting expressions like: to tip your hat to somebody, to let something slide, and to be shouldered with something
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #166 – Table manners | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040073/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 04:47:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Table manners are an important part of many different cultures. Something that may be considered rude in one country may actually be polite in another. In this episode, Andrew and Suzanne talk about what is generally considered polite in the U.S., Canada, and U.K., their personal opinions on table manners, and a few horror stories about some really uncomfortable eating situations.
Fun facts If you have the opportunity to enjoy a meal at a fancy restaurant in the U.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #045 – Talking with strangers | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040074/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 20:21:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #045 - Talking with strangers Episode description In this week’s bonus episode, Andrew talks about an interesting conversation he had while riding the bus in Canada. He also gives you some exciting updates about some projects were working on at Culips. Along the way, he teaches you the vocabulary: a handful of something, to bite, curt, blunt, and to play favorites.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member.</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #303 – Could you live in a micro apartment? | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040075/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 21:54:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever considered living in a micro apartment or tiny home? In this episode, Andrew and Anna discuss the rising trend of micro apartments in the real estate and housing industry. They explore why tiny living is becoming more popular and share their opinions on the matter.
Chatterbox is a series designed for intermediate and advanced English learners where you can listen to native English speakers having natural conversations on fascinating topics.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #044 – He speaks! | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040076/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 23:28:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #044 - He speaks! Episode description In this week’s bonus episode, Andrew talks about a shocking event his wife witnessed this week. He also gives you some Culips updates, and teaches you about the idiomatic expression to rub someone the wrong way.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member. To sign up, visit Culips.com.
Study with the interactive transcript here.</description></item><item><title>Real Talk #057 – How to apply for a part-time job | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040077/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 05:31:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Applying for a part-time job can be stressful, and it’s always a good idea to be prepared before you walk into a store and ask for an application. In this episode, Andrew and Kassy teach you some of the common phrases and etiquette involved with applying for a part-time job in person. The example conversation presented by our hosts is applicable to many different kinds of part-time jobs, including food service, retail, or hospitality.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #043 – Pizza Parlor | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040078/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 19:02:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #043 - Pizza Parlor Episode description In this week’s bonus episode, Andrew talks about a cool aspect of big city life and shares some stories about what he did last week. Along the way, he teaches you some useful English vocabulary like to congregate, to pass the baton, and to be taken aback.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #165 – What were you like as a teenager? | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040079/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 05:45:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040079/</guid><description>Podcast Description We all have stories about our teenage years – some funny, some awkward. In this episode, Andrew and Kassy take a look back at their teenage selves and share their personal stories. Tune in to find out more!
Simplified Speech is the Culips series designed for beginner and intermediate English language learners. The series features natural, easy-to-understand conversations between two native speakers. By following along, you&amp;rsquo;ll increase your vocabulary and improve your listening skills in English.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #042 – Whistle while you work | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040080/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 03:39:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #042 - Whistle while you work Episode description In this week’s bonus episode, Andrew lets you know what he’s been up to over the last week and how he’s getting ready for spring. Along the way, he teaches you some interesting vocabulary and expressions, like menial, in the pipeline, and to be on a [something] kick.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member.</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #302 – What is cancel culture? | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040081/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 18:28:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040081/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Chatterbox episode, Andrew and Anna discuss the controversial topic of cancel culture. Cancel culture refers to the recent culture of mass criticism and ostracization of people in power after they have said or done something offensive. Because of social media, word spreads quickly when famous people commit a crime or even simply say something inappropriate. The responses to these behaviours can happen so fast that an actor could go from beloved celebrity to hated figure overnight.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #041 – Back to life, back to reality | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040082/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 03:49:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #041 - Back to life, back to reality Episode description In this week’s bonus episode, Andrew talks about his battle with jet lag and how his house renovation project is going. Plus, in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you about the expression to be thrown out of whack.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member. To sign up, visit Culips.</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #301 – Queen Elizabeth II | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040083/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 05:18:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Queen Elizabeth II was an important figure both in Britain and around the world. She was the longest-reigning monarch in British history and died at the age of 96 on September 8th, 2022. In this episode, Andrew and Anna talk about the Queen’s life and her legacy. Tune in to learn more about one of the most famous women in the world!
Chatterbox is a series for intermediate and advanced English learners in which native English speakers have natural conversations about interesting topics.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #040 – There’s no place like home | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040084/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:14:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #040 – There’s no place like home Episode description Join Andrew for the thrilling conclusion to his visit to Canada and his journey back to Seoul! He shares some stories about his brother’s birthday party and how he kept himself entertained on the plane. Plus, in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you about the expression to float your boat.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #164 – Socializing with coworkers | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040085/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 22:21:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever gotten together with your coworkers on the weekend? In this episode, Andrew and Kassy talk about their experiences spending time with their colleagues socially. They discuss the kinds of activities they participate in, cultural differences regarding socializing with coworkers, and the idea of drinking alcohol with the boss. What do you think English teachers living abroad do for fun with their colleagues? Give this episode a try and find out!</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #039 – Two days, two doughnuts | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040086/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 05:40:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #039 – Two days, two doughnuts Episode description Join Andrew for an exciting update on his travels and adventures in this bonus episode! He&amp;rsquo;ll share some stories of his latest adventures, from exploring Vancouver and Victoria, to creating unforgettable memories.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member. To sign up, visit Culips.com.
Study with the interactive transcript here.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #163 – Kassy’s trip to Korea | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040087/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 04:45:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040087/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this special episode, Kassy and Andrew get the chance to meet and chat in person! Our reunited hosts discuss Kassy’s unexpected three-week trip to South Korea and how she has been spending her time there. Be sure to check this one out if you’d like to hear stories about funny travel mishaps, different kinds of cuisine, and extreme weather conditions.
Fun facts Did you know that Incheon International Airport offers live music performances to visitors of the airport in different terminals throughout the day?</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #038 – On the road | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040088/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 18:35:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #038 – On the road Episode description In this bonus episode, Andrew gives an update from the road and shares a few stories about what he’s up to during his trip back home to Canada.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member. To sign up, visit Culips.com.
Study with the interactive transcript here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #300 – The metaverse | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040089/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 04:51:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is the metaverse our future reality or just a dystopian fantasy? In this episode, Andrew and Anna talk all about virtual reality and share their opinions on how they see the future of the metaverse.
Chatterbox is a Culips series designed for intermediate and advanced English learners. This series features native speakers having natural conversations about fascinating topics that help you improve your English listening and speaking skills. Plus, you might learn something interesting along the way!</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #037 – Silly hamster | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040090/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 20:50:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #037 – Silly hamster Episode description In this bonus episode, Andrew talks about buyers remorse and his regret for buying a phone case. Plus in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you a useful idiomatic expression: To check all your boxes.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member. To sign up, visit Culips.com.
Study with the interactive transcript here.</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #299 – Brain drain | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040091/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 00:18:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brain drain sounds like a mental health condition, but it actually means the mass migration of educated and skilled people from one place to another. In this Chatterbox episode, Andrew and Anna have a discussion about some of the reasons for this phenomenon. The hosts describe some of the brain drain trends they’ve witnessed in Canada, the UK, South Korea, and more. Check out the episode and learn why nurses are moving from Canada to the United States!</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #036 – A chance encounter | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040092/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 00:34:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #036 – A chance encounter Episode description In this bonus episode, Andrew shares a story about seeing a couple from a reality TV dating show at a coffee shop in his neighbourhood. He also talks about his upcoming trip to Canada. In the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you the idiomatic expression to put two and two together.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #162 – What do your facial expressions say about you? | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040093/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 18:17:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you consider yourself an expressive person? Can you usually tell how someone feels by looking at their face? In this Simplified Speech episode, Andrew and Kassy chat about how people communicate with facial expressions.
Simplified Speech is a Culips series designed to help beginner and intermediate English language learners improve their listening skills. In this series, you can listen to native speakers having natural conversations about everyday topics using language that is clear and easy to understand.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #035 – Skate time! | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040094/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 22:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #035 – Skate time! Episode description In this bonus episode, Andrew talks about going ice skating with his wife. Plus, in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you a useful English idiom: to set the bar high/low.
Study with the interactive transcript here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Catch Word #267 – Burst your bubble | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040095/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 20:20:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nobody likes to be disappointed, but it happens to all of us at some point of our life, so it’s good to know how to talk about it. In this episode, Andrew and Kassy teach you two useful expressions used when talking about disappointing someone.
Catch Word is the Culips vocabulary series designed for intermediate and advanced English learners. With this series you’ll learn common everyday idioms and expressions and improve your listening and speaking skills.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #034 – Bye, ‘22! | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040096/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 05:19:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #034 – Bye, ‘22! Episode description In this bonus episode, Andrew looks back on 2022 and talks about his goals and plans for 2023. Are you ready to seriously improve your English in 2023? We’re here to help you reach your goal.
Become a Culips member now: Study with the interactive transcript here:
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #033 – Biennial health check | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040097/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 19:33:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #033 – Biennial health check Episode description In this bonus episode, Andrew talks about going for a health checkup. Plus, in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you a useful idiomatic expression: a shock to your system.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member. To sign up, visit Culips.com. Study with the interactive transcript here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #298 – Christmas in Canada and the UK | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 19:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040098/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s the most wonderful time of the year – it’s Christmas! There are many different traditions and ways to celebrate this holiday around the world. In this episode, Andrew and Anna talk about the way they used to celebrate Christmas in their home countries and how they do it now that they live abroad.
Chatterbox is the Culips series designed for intermediate and advanced English learners. This series features native English speakers having natural conversations about fascinating topics.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #032 – Attending a funeral | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040099/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 23:50:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #032 – Attending a funeral Episode description In this bonus episode, Andrew talks about what it’s like to attend a funeral in South Korea.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member. To sign up, visit Culips.com. Study with the interactive transcript here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #161 – Do you practice self-care? | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040100/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 22:12:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Self-care is a term that has been around for a long time. However, it has become more popular recently because people are paying more attention to taking care of their physical and mental health in a fast-paced world. In this Simplified Speech episode, Andrew and Kassy chat about their personal self-care routines and some tips for listeners. If you’ve been feeling stressed out lately, then this is a great episode to check out!</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #031 – A sweet mystery | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040101/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 05:53:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #031 – A sweet mystery Episode description In this bonus episode, Andrew talks about a mystery he has discovered in his neighborhood and about visiting a Christmas market in Seoul. Plus in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you the expression to not hold water.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member. To sign up, visit Culips.com. Study with the interactive transcript here.</description></item><item><title>Catch Word #266 – Not make a dent in it | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040102/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 19:03:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you the type of person who gets work done quickly and easily? Sometimes we may work on a task for a long time but still not make a lot of progress on it. In this episode, Kassy and Andrew teach two expressions you can use in situations where you’re stuck or not making progress. These expressions are to not make a dent in something and to go round in circles.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #030 – 34 days of music | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040103/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 20:18:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #030 – 34 days of music Episode description In this bonus episode, Andrew talks about the music he listened to this year. Plus, he teaches you about a useful English expression, to reign supreme.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member. To sign up, visit Culips.com. Study with the interactive transcript here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #297 – Personal finance | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040104/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 06:21:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you a saver or a spender? In this episode, Andrew and Anna share their experiences handling finances and give some tips on how to spend less money. If you’re interested in personal finance, be sure to give it a listen!
Chatterbox is a series that features natural conversations between native speakers. This series is designed for intermediate and advanced learners. Listening to our Chatterbox series is a great way to improve your vocabulary and listening skills.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #029 – For the best | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040105/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 17:15:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #029 - For the best Episode description In this bonus episode, Andrew shares the story about how his half marathon went last week. He also talks about the World Cup and who he’s cheering for. Plus in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you the expression slim to none.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member. To sign up, visit Culips.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #160 – Amusement parks | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040106/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 15:55:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Most children in the U.S. and Canada have had at least a few experiences visiting amusement parks. In this Simplified speech episode, Andrew and Kassy describe their childhood experiences going to amusement parks and theme parks. They discuss their opinions on them and offer several tips on getting the most fun out of your visit. Listen to the episode and decide for yourself whether you think these classic summertime destinations sound like fun!</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #028 – Come back to haunt me | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040107/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 03:06:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #028 - Come back to haunt me Episode description In this bonus episode, Andrew talks about a decision he made in the past that has come back to haunt him. He also shares a story about a website that helped him to relive some childhood memories. Plus, in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you about the expression to pay the price.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #159 – Kassy’s new hobbies | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040108/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 04:21:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040108/</guid><description>Podcast Description It is always a great time picking up a new hobby! In this episode, Kassy talks with Andrew about some new hobbies of hers. Listen in to find out what they are!
Simplified Speech is a Culips series where native speakers have natural conversations about everyday topics using clear and easy to understand language. These episodes are designed to help beginner and intermediate English language learners improve their listening skills.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #027 – A dumpster fire | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040109/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 19:57:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #027 - A dumpster fire Episode description In this bonus episode, Andrew talks about the drama that’s unfolding at Twitter. Plus, he gives you some behind the scenes updates about some new things happening at Culips and teaches you a funny idiomatic expression: a dumpster fire.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member. To sign up, visit Culips.com. Study with the interactive transcript here.</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #296 – Anna’s trip to Scotland | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040110/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 20:24:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever travelled abroad during summer vacation? Depending on where you travel, summer can be one of the best times to take a trip. In this episode, Andrew and Anna talk about Anna’s trip to Scotland during the summer. Listen to this Chatterbox episode to hear about the food, sites, weather, and more that Anna experienced on her trip.
Chatterbox is a series of natural conversations between two native English speakers about diverse and interesting topics.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #026 – My strong suit | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040111/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 18:37:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #026 - My strong suit Episode description In this bonus episode, Andrew talks about why his dog Pinky is a conversation starter and shares some stories about what he did over the weekend. Plus, in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you the idiomatic expression to be someone’s strong suit.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member. To sign up, visit Culips.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #158 – Have you ever been in an emergency? | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040112/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 07:14:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emergencies can be extremely stressful, but they certainly make for some good stories. In this Simplified Speech episode, hosts Andrew and Kassy recount several stories from their childhoods about emergency situations. You’ll hear stories about stubborn children, bee stings, and getting stuck in theatre chairs. Listen to their tales and find out if you’ve gone through anything similar!
Simplified Speech is a Culips series that features easy to understand conversations that help beginner and intermediate English learners improve their listening skills.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #025 – A fixer-upper | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040113/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 02:57:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #025 - A fixer-upper Episode description In this bonus episode, Andrew talks about some exciting news! Plus in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you a useful English expression: a fixer-upper.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member. To sign up, visit Culips.com. Study with the interactive transcript here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #295 – Life as a digital nomad | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040114/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 19:53:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Where is your office? Is it located in a big building owned by the company you work for, or are you a digital nomad, able to work anywhere in the world? Andrew and Anna talk about what it must be like being a digital nomad and discuss the good and the bad that comes with this lifestyle.
Culips’ Chatterbox series is designed for intermediate and advanced English learning. All Chatterbox episodes feature natural conversations between two native English speakers.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #024 – Pick up where you left off | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040115/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 19:21:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #024 - Pick up where you left off Episode description In this bonus episode, Andrew talks about getting a 24-hour bug, visiting an industrial office tower, and failing the exercise portion of the Sober October Challenge. Plus in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you an idiomatic English expression: To lose it.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member. To sign up, visit Culips.</description></item><item><title>Real Talk #056 – Calling 911 in an emergency | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040116/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 22:53:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040116/</guid><description>Podcast Description No one ever expects to be in an emergency, but sometimes we may be in a situation where we need to call for help. In this Real Talk episode, Andrew and Kassy teach you common expressions you can use when talking to a 911 dispatcher.
Real Talk is a series that helps you learn practical English expressions that you can use in every day natural conversations. Be sure to listen carefully to this episode for all the useful expressions!</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #023 – A glimmer of hope | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040117/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 01:14:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #023 - A glimmer of hope Episode description In this bonus episode, Andrew shares a few stories about what he got up to last week. Plus, in the vocabulary lesson he teaches you about the expression a grind.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member. To sign up, visit Culips.com. Study with the interactive transcript here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #294 – The highs and lows of living abroad | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040118/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 20:28:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever thought about living abroad? That’s the discussion topic for this Chatterbox episode. Join Andrew and Anna as they share their experiences of living in a foreign country and talk about the ups and downs of living abroad.
Chatterbox is a series for intermediate and advanced English learners in which native English speakers have natural conversations on interesting topics. This series is designed to help you improve your English listening and speaking fluency in a fun way.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #022 – Sober October | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040119/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 21:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #022 - Sober October Episode description In this bonus episode, Andrew talks about the Sober October challenge and shopping for new shoes. Plus, he teaches you a useful idiomatic expression out of pocket.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member. To sign up, visit Culips.com. Study with the interactive transcript here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Catch Word #265 – Take the fifth | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040120/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 18:33:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever found yourself in a situation where it was best to just remain quiet? In English, there are many ways to say, “I don’t want to talk about it”. In this episode, Andrew and Kassy teach you two idiomatic expressions you can use to talk about being quiet and not talking.
The Catch Word series helps intermediate and advanced English language learners understand idioms, phrasal verbs and expressions that you may encounter in daily life.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #021 – French hotdog | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040121/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 17:47:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #021 - French hotdog Episode description In this bonus episode, Andrew talks about visiting an international festival in his neighborhood and about trying some cuisine from a couple different countries. Plus, in the vocabulary lesson he teaches you about the idiom for the time being.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member. To sign up, visit Culips.com. Study with the interactive transcript here.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #157 – Adjusting to life as a newlywed | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040122/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 21:16:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040122/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is life like after marriage? Andrew and Kassy have both had their weddings recently and, in this episode, they talk about adjusting to married life and share their experiences dealing with it.
In our Simplified Speech series, native speakers have natural and easy to understand conversations about everyday topics. These episodes are designed to help you improve your listening skills and expand your vocabulary.
Fun facts According to New Statistics, 53% (20 million) of marriages that happen around the world are arranged.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #020 – Mosquitos and juice | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040123/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 23:52:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #020 - Mosquitos and juice Episode description In this bonus episode, Andrew shares talks about getting attacked by mosquitos and a near disaster. Sound intriguing? Listen to the episode to learn the whole story. Plus in the vocabulary lesson, you’ll learn how to use the adjective stricken to describe negative situations.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member. To sign up, visit Culips.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #156 – First impressions of Thailand | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040124/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 23:41:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Greetings from Thailand! Kassy and her husband have finally arrived in Thailand and are starting to get settled in Bangkok. In this episode, Kassy tells Andrew about her first impressions of the new country and shares a couple of funny and interesting stories from her first days there. Tune in to hear about Kassy’s adventures in Bangkok.
Simplified Speech is the Culips series that is designed to help you improve your English listening and speaking fluency in a fun and exciting way.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #019 – Flexing my detective skills | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040125/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 21:08:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #019 – Flexing my detective skills Episode description In this bonus episode, Andrew shares some stories about what he got up to last week, including searching for his wife’s wallet and selling his PS4. He also tells you about an awesome new Culips feature, the interactive transcript. Then, in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you a great phrasal verb: to piece [something] together.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #155 – Getting ready for an international move | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040126/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 21:21:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever wanted to pack up and move to a whole new country? Kassy recently did just that, moving from South Korea to Thailand. In this episode, Andrew and Kassy talk about her recent move and share their stories about what it’s like to prepare for an international move.
Simplified Speech episodes are designed to help you improve your English listening and speaking skills. Listen as two native English speakers have a natural conversation using clear and easy to understand language.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #018 – A roller-coaster week | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040127/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 19:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #018 – A roller-coaster week Episode description In this bonus episode, Andrew talks about commuting to work in a typhoon, celebrating Chuseok, and the passing of Queen Elizabeth. Plus, in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you how to use the expression to go into [something] mode.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member. To sign up, visit Culips.com.</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #293 – The history and culture of tea in the UK | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040128/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 21:49:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who doesn’t love a hot cup of tea? Most countries have some kind of tea culture. However, the British think of tea as especially important to their culture. In fact, many people think of tea when they think of elements of British culture. In this Chatterbox episode, Anna talks with Andrew about her country’s relationship with tea and how important it is. So put the kettle on and sit back for an interesting conversation!</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #017 – Goodbye, summer! | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040129/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 21:00:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #017 – Goodbye, summer! Episode description In this bonus episode, Andrew talks about some of the highlights from the past week and teaches you a useful expression you can use when you’re tired: wiped out.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member. To sign up, visit Culips.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #154 – Kassy’s trip home | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040130/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 19:32:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040130/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Kassy and Andrew talk about Kassy’s trip home to the United States of America. On this trip, she finally got a chance to spend some time with her family and friends that she had not been able to see in person for years. Kassy talks about how she and her husband got to travel to different states, visiting attractions, eating local delicacies, and most importantly, partying at their long-planned second wedding reception.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #016 – Let the games begin | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040131/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 20:57:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #016 – Let the games begin Episode description In this bonus episode, Andrew shares some stories from the monster of a week he had last week. Plus in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you a useful English expression: on point.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member. To sign up, visit Culips.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Catch Word #264 – In stitches | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040132/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 22:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who doesn’t like to have a good laugh? In this Catch Word episode, Kassy and Andrew teach you some useful expressions that help you to talk about comedy and things in your life that make you laugh a lot.
Catch Word is the Culips vocabulary series for intermediate and advanced English language learners that will help you improve your listening and speaking skills. At the same time, you’ll be able to increase your vocabulary by learning some useful and important expressions that English speakers use in their everyday lives.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #015 – A really random day | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040133/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 21:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #015 – A really random day Episode description In this week’s bonus episode, Andrew talks about a random day he had last week where he registered his marriage and got an IV drip. Plus in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you an extremely common idiomatic expression: for good.
Support Culips and take your English to the next level by becoming a Culips Member. To sign up, visit Culips.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #153 – Zombies! | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040134/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 03:59:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Zombies are everywhere! From movies and TV shows to video games and more, zombies are supernatural monsters that appear in almost every culture’s folklore. In this episode, Andrew and Kassy talk about everything they know about these undead creatures.
Simplified Speech episodes feature two native English speakers having clear, natural, and easy-to-understand conversations about interesting topics, like zombies. Studying with this series helps you to improve your English listening skills and speak English naturally.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #014 – A week in bed | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040135/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 20:47:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #014 – A week in bed Episode description In this week’s bonus episode, Andrew talks about how he kept himself entertained while being sick at home with COVID. Plus in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you an expression you can use when you regret saying something: to eat your words.
For information about becoming a Culips Member, visit Culips.com
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #292 – Let’s get physical and talk about HIIT | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040136/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 21:51:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever heard of high intensity interval training? That’s quite a mouthful, isn’t it? Luckily, we usually just call this type of workout HIIT. It’s a training style that has recently gained a lot of popularity. In this Chatterbox episode, hosts Andrew and Anna explain the entire concept of HIIT and share their stories related to it.
Chatterbox is a Culips series where two native English speakers have a quick and natural conversation about interesting topics.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #013 – Don’t cry over spilt milk | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040137/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 19:14:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #013 – Don’t cry over spilt milk Episode description In this week’s bonus episode, Andrew talks about why he had to cancel his trip to Canada at the last moment. Plus in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you a useful expression for telling bad news: all around.
For information about becoming a Culips Member, visit Culips.com
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Catch Word #263 – Turn a blind eye | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040138/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 21:45:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040138/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s always someone in a friend group that’s not very observant. Maybe it takes them too long to understand a joke, or maybe they always say the wrong thing at the wrong time. There are many different phrases in the English language to describe these oblivious kinds of friends. Today, Kassy and Andrew explain two of these expressions: tone-deaf and turn a blind eye.
Culips’ Catch Word series teaches you idioms, phrasal verbs, and expressions that help improve your English listening and speaking skills.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #012 – Heading home | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040139/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:06:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #012 – Heading home Episode description In this week’s bonus episode, Andrew shares some stories about what he got up to last week and talks about his upcoming trip to Canada. Plus he teaches you a useful expression: to wait it out.
For information about becoming a Culips Member, visit Culips.com
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #152 – Do you celebrate any international days? | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040140/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 21:36:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Everyone knows about Christmas and Valentine’s Day, but do you know there’s a Strange Music Day and a Burger Day? In this Simplified Speech episode, Andrew and Kassy explore the wonderful world of international days. Give it a listen and you might discover a special day just for you!
Simplified Speech is a Culips series where our hosts have a clear and natural conversation designed to help beginner and intermediate English language learners improve their skills.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #011 – The birthday cake experiment | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040141/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 22:09:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #011 – The birthday cake experiment Episode description In this week’s bonus episode, Andrew shares a story about celebrating his wife’s birthday and baking her a cake. Plus in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you how to use a common idiomatic expression: to have your work cut out for you.
The Culips Member July live stream is happening on Tuesday July 26th, at 7:30PM KST. To join the live stream, follow this link: For information about becoming a Culips Member, visit Culips.</description></item><item><title>Real Talk #055 – How to order flowers in English | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040142/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 21:42:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040142/</guid><description>Podcast Description A beautiful flower arrangement can help to change the whole look of a room. But how do you order flowers at a flower shop in English? Don’t worry! In this Real Talk episode, hosts Andrew and Kassy walk you through the expressions and vocabulary you will need when buying flowers to decorate your home or give to a loved one.
Real Talk is the Culips series for beginner and intermediate English learners, which teaches you practical English expressions for real-world situations.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #010 – A quick trip south | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040143/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 23:11:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #010 –A quick trip south Episode description In this week’s bonus episode, Andrew talks about a short road trip he took to a small city at the southern tip of South Korea called Tongyeong. Plus in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you how to use a common idiomatic expression: to bad-mouth [someone]. Visit Culips.com to get the 100% free transcript for this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #151 – What’s your most prized possession? | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040144/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 20:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040144/</guid><description>Podcast Description Everyone owns special and precious things, things they think of as valuable and unique. In this episode, Kassy and Andrew get together to talk about the things that they value the most and, in fact, can’t imagine their lives without. Listen in to learn about what things both Andrew and Kassy consider to be their most prized possessions.
Simplified Speech episodes feature two native English speakers having clear, natural, and easy to understand English conversations about interesting topics.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #09 – Movie marathon | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040145/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 22:49:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #09 – Movie marathon Episode description In this week’s bonus episode, Andrew shares some stories about what he did last week. Plus, he teaches you a useful and common idiomatic expression that native speakers use all the time: to be at the top of your game.
Visit Culips.com to get the 100% free transcript for this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #291 – Decision paralysis | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040146/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 21:00:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Making decisions isn’t always easy, especially these days, when there are so many options for us to pick from. If you’ve ever felt stuck when faced with choices, you’re not alone! This sensation is called decision paralysis and many people face it, including Culips hosts Andrew and Anna. Listen in as they talk about this sensation and how they work through it.
Culips’ Chatterbox series is designed for intermediate and advanced English learners.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #08 – The search for the lost ring | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040147/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 21:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #08 – The search for the lost ring Episode description In this week’s bonus episode, Andrew tells a story about losing his wedding ring. Plus, he teaches you an idiomatic expression that native speakers use all the time: on and off.
Visit Culips.com to get the 100% free transcript for this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #150 – Have you ever been obsessed with something? | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040148/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 20:00:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040148/</guid><description>Podcast Description There are things that we like, and then there are things we really obsess over! But watch out: you don’t want your obsession to turn into an addiction. In this Simplified Speech episode, hosts Andrew and Kassy explore expressions dealing with our obsessions.
Simplified Speech is a series featuring easy and natural English conversations. Both beginner and intermediate language learners can benefit from this series. So be sure to go through our full catalogue online!</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #07 – Here comes the rain | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040149/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 05:12:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #07 – Here comes the rain Episode description In this week’s update episode, Andrew shares some stories about the monsoon season and dog sitting a poodle! Plus, he teaches you about an extremely useful phrasal verb: to stick with [something].
Visit Culips.com to get the 100% free transcript for this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Catch Word #262 – Doomscrolling | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040150/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:16:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040150/</guid><description>Podcast Description At some point, we’ve all found ourselves scrolling through the news or social media for hours on end. Sometimes the things we discover make us feel good (cute puppy videos!), and other times we find things that makes us feel bad (most news article about the world nowadays!). In this episode, Andrew and Kassy teach you two idiomatic expressions that you can use to talk about spending time on the Internet.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #06 – Spontaneous photo shoot | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040151/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 21:12:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #06 – Spontaneous photo shoot Episode description In this week’s update episode, Andrew shares a story about getting his picture taken in a photo booth. Plus, in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you a useful expression: unbeknownst to [someone].
Visit Culips.com to get the 100% free transcript for this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #290 – Is bread the world’s favourite food? | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040152/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 19:38:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bread is a staple around the world. Every culture has its own version or style, from India’s naan to Brazil’s pão de queijo. In today’s episode, Andrew and Anna chat about bread and what makes it so delicious (and popular).
The Chatterbox series is designed for intermediate and advanced English learners. Each episode features natural, unedited conversations between native speakers, so you can build your English vocabulary while learning about interesting topics, like bread.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #05 – Adventures in cooking | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040153/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 21:00:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040153/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #05 – Adventures in cooking Episode description In this week’s update episode, Andrew shares a story about the highs and lows of learning how to cook Korean food. Plus, in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you a useful expression: there’s never a dull moment.
Visit Culips.com to get the 100% free transcript for this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #289 – What’s your MBTI? | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040154/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 19:28:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you really know yourself? Sometimes you think you know your own personality, but you might think differently after taking the Myers-Briggs Type Indicator! The MBTI is a test designed to evaluate what kind of personality you have, based on 8 sets of traits.
In this Chatterbox episode, Andrew and Anna explore the MBTI as they talk about their own test results! Give it a listen. The results may surprise you!</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #04 – Presents from the island | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040155/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 05:20:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #04 – Presents from the island Episode description In this week’s update episode, Andrew talks about all the wonderful things his wife brought back for him from her trip to Jeju Island. Plus, in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you a useful idiomatic expression: to go to town.
Visit Culips.com to get the 100% free transcript for this episode. Note: The transcript has been edited for clarity.</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #288 – What’s your favourite quote? | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040156/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:18:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Words can inspire us. Everyone has that moment when they read something, or hear something, that just makes sense. So much so that we want to share these quotes with the world. In this episode, Andrew and Anna talk about inspirational quotes and share the ones they feel have influenced their lives in some way.
Our Chatterbox series is designed for intermediate and advanced English learners. Podcasts and audio lessons are a great way to improve your English listening skills.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #03 – Holding down the fort | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040157/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 23:02:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040157/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #03 – Holding down the fort Episode description In this week’s update episode, Andrew talks about holding down the fort while his wife is away for the week. Plus, in the vocabulary lesson, he teaches you a useful phrasal verb: to take on [somebody/something].
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #149 – Kassy’s wedding story | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040158/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 03:51:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040158/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here comes the bride! Kassy recently got married and in this episode, she tells Andrew all about her big day.
In our Simplified Speech series, native English speakers have natural conversations about everyday topics. These episodes are designed to boost your English listening skills and increase your vocabulary. On occasion, our hosts share their personal stories, making it easy to listen to these English audio lessons.
Fun facts Due to the COVID pandemic, the number of weddings that occurred in 2020 fell by nearly 20%, the lowest since the 1960s.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #02 – Broken tape player | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040159/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 06:32:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #02 – Broken tape player Episode description Andrew talks about how he spent the last week and about how his vintage cassette player broke. He also teaches you how to use the expression to slack off on doing something and gives an update about what you can expect this week from Culips.
Visit Culips.com to get the 100% free transcript for this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Catch Word #261 – Finger on the pulse | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040160/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 20:10:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040160/</guid><description>Podcast Description Everyone knows someone who seems to know about all the trends or the latest news before everyone else. You might even be that person among your friends! In today’s Catch Word episode, Andrew and Kassy explain two idioms that you can use to describe these people, finger on the pulse and ahead of the curve.
Catch Word English audio lessons are designed for intermediate and advanced English learners. Through natural conversations, you’ll learn idioms, phrasal verbs, and expressions that will help improve your English listening and speaking skills.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode #01 – Andrew’s whirlwind weekend | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040161/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 21:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040161/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode #01 – Andrew’s whirlwind weekend Episode description Andrew talks about his super busy weekend that included not only celebrating his birthday but also celebrating his first wedding anniversary. He also teaches you how to use the expression to pull out all the stops and gives a preview of the next Culips episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #148 – Where did you grow up? | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040162/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 19:32:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040162/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hometowns: everyone has one! In today’s Simplified Speech episode, hosts Andrew and Kassy talk about where they grew up. One of them grew up in Canada, and the other grew up in the United States. You will hear about the interesting similarities and differences the two have to share with you. Come and join them!
Simplified Speech is a Culips series with easy to understand conversations designed to help beginner and intermediate English learners improve their listening skills.</description></item><item><title>Catch Word #260 – Pay through the nose | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040163/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 21:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever wished there were an expression that perfectly fit how you feel about just how expensive something is? You’re in luck because, in English, there is! Today, Andrew and Kassy share two idiomatic expressions used when talking about buying something that is overpriced or, in your opinion, too expensive.
The Culips Catch Word series explains idioms, phrasal verbs, and expressions used in everyday life. Listening to our Catch Word audio lessons helps improve your English listening and speaking skills while also giving you new ways to talk about pricey or expensive things.</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #287 – Pub culture in the UK and Canada | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040164/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 21:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040164/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pubs are very common in the United Kingdom and Canada. However, there are differences between the two countries and their respective cultures. In this Chatterbox episode, Andrew and Anna discuss how important pubs are in their cultures and compare their traditions and customs.
Chatterbox is a series where native English speakers have a natural conversation on an interesting topic. In this episode, our hosts talk about pub culture in the UK and Canada.</description></item><item><title>Catch Word #259 – Back in the saddle | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040165/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 21:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040165/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Catch Word episode, Andrew and Kassy teach you two idiomatic expressions you can use when talking about something returning to normal: back in the saddle and back in business. Study with this vocabulary lesson and improve your English listening and speaking.
Catch Word is the Culips vocabulary series where you can learn idioms, expressions, and phrasal verbs that native speakers use all the time. Improve your English fluency with Catch Word!</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #147 – Andrew’s diggin’ and Kassy’s almost married! | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040166/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 04:55:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040166/</guid><description>Podcast Description Curious about what’s new in the lives of Culips’ podcast hosts? Listen in as Andrew and Kassy have another one of their famous catch-up calls.
Simplified Speech episodes feature two native English speakers having clear, natural, and easy to understand English conversations about interesting topics. By listening to Andrew and Kassy chat about their hobbies, you’ll improve your English listening skills and increase your vocabulary.
Fun facts The very first 12-inch long-play (LP) vinyl record produced was a recording of Beethoven’s Symphony No.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #146 – Kassy’s big move | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040167/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 00:38:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kassy shares her big news: she’s moving to Thailand so she can pursue her dream job teaching in a new country! Moving can be stressful. Moving to a new country is even more stressful. Andrew and Kassy discuss the process and everything that Kassy needs to do to prepare for her big move.
In this episode, two native English speakers talk about moving to a new country. This English audio lesson is designed to help you improve your English listening and speaking fluency.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #145 – Have you ever won a contest? | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040168/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 20:36:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever won a contest? That’s the discussion question that Andrew and Kassy talk about in this episode. Join them as they teach you the differences between draws, contests, sweepstakes, and lotteries. Then listen in as they share some stories about the different contests they’ve won in the past.
Simplified Speech episodes are designed to help you improve your English listening and speaking skills. During these episodes, two native English speakers discuss interesting topics, like winning contests, using clear and easy to understand language.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #144 – Buying and selling used things | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040169/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 02:47:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever bought or sold something used online? That’s the question that Andrew and Suzanne discuss in this Simplified Speech episode. Andrew talks about some sales he’s made recently, and Suzanne shares some crazy stories about different experiences she’s had as both a buyer and a seller.
Simplified Speech episodes feature two native English speakers having clear, natural, and easy-to-understand conversations about interesting topics, like buying and selling used things.</description></item><item><title>Catch Word #258 – Sweating bullets | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040170/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 00:08:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040170/</guid><description>Podcast Description “I was so nervous. I was sweating bullets!” That might sound a bit strange, but it’s a common English expression. Sweating bullets means to be very stressed or nervous. Does that happen to you sometimes? In this Catch Word episode, Andrew and Kassy teach you two idioms with the word sweat: no sweat and sweating bullets. After this episode, you’ll know how to use these expressions perfectly!
Catch Word is the Culips vocabulary series that teaches you idioms, expressions, and phrasal verbs that are useful in everyday life.</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #286 – Beauty filters | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040171/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 21:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040171/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you like the way you look in photos? Considering the huge market for online filters for photographs, there must be a lot of people who prefer embellishing their pictures instead of keeping them natural. Is that a problem? In this Chatterbox episode, hosts Andrew and Anna discuss the pros and cons of online beauty filters.
Chatterbox is a series featuring native English speakers carrying on a natural conversation.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #143 – Kassy’s acing tests and Andrew’s drumming away | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040172/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 22:00:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040172/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Simplified Speech episode, Andrew and Kassy give some updates about what’s going on in their lives these days. Kassy tells us the results of a big math test she took recently and talks about choosing a wedding dress and last-minute wedding planning. Andrew shares about why he started playing drums again and talks about growing herbs at home.
In our Simplified Speech series, native English speakers have natural conversations about interesting topics.</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #285 – Life hacks | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040173/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 18:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040173/</guid><description>Podcast Description What are some of your favourite life hacks? That’s the topic of discussion for this Chatterbox episode. Join Andrew and Anna as they share some of their favourite shortcuts for optimizing and organizing their lives and work.
Chatterbox is the Culips series for intermediate and advanced English learners. Each episode features a natural conversation between native speakers about a fascinating topic. By learning English with Chatterbox, you’ll be able to build your fluency, listening skills, and vocabulary.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #142 – Fake meat and meat alternatives | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040174/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 22:00:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040174/</guid><description>Podcast Description Plant-based meat alternatives have gained in popularity over the past decade. People following vegan and vegetarian diets now enjoy better, tastier fake meats. Today, Andrew and Kassy talk about this new, controversial food trend.
This episode is part of Culips’ Simplified Speech series. It features natural, easy‑to‑understand English conversations about interesting topics, like fake meat. Listening to native English speakers having natural conversations will improve your listening skills and increase your vocabulary.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #141 – Are you a big playlist person? | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040175/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 19:28:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040175/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you a big playlist person? That’s the question that Andrew and Suzanne discuss in this Simplified Speech episode. Join them as they chat about the kinds of playlists they make, how they make them, and when they like to listen to them.
Simplified Speech is perfect for intermediate-level English learners who are looking to improve their English fluency. Each episode features clear and natural conversations about an interesting topic.</description></item><item><title>Real Talk #054 – Joining a gym | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040176/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 21:26:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040176/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joining a new gym can be intimidating. There are a lot of things you need to think of. You have to ask about their membership fees. You have to ask about the length of their membership contracts. And you also need to see if their environment is a good fit for you. Fortunately, in this Real Talk episode, Andrew and Kassy help you with all those questions and more!</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #140 – Kassy’s kombucha | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040177/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 03:51:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040177/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever heard of kombucha? For some people, it’s an amazing tea full of health benefits. For others, it’s a weird-tasting beverage that only strange people drink! In this Simplified Speech episode, Andrew asks Kassy about her kombucha brewing lifestyle. They talk about the various steps of Kassy’s brewing process.
Simplified Speech is a series that features easy and natural conversation designed for listeners of all levels. In this episode, our hosts Andrew and Kassy talk about the fascinating world of kombucha brewing!</description></item><item><title>Catch Word #257 – Hightail it out of there | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040178/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 22:23:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040178/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is your favourite way to say, “I have to leave now, and fast”? In this episode, Andrew and Kassy explain two common English expression that mean to leave quickly: duck out and hightail it out of there.
The Culips Catch Word series explains idioms, phrasal verbs, and expressions used in everyday life. Today’s audio lesson is designed to help you improve your English listening and speaking skills while also giving you new, fun ways to say that you’re leaving.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #139 – Wedding traditions in France | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040179/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 05:12:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Did you know that every country has their own special wedding traditions? Recently, Suzanne travelled to France to start planning her wedding. In this episode, Suzanne tells Andrew about the wedding traditions she discovered there.
In our Simplified Speech series, native English speakers have natural conversations about common topics. These episodes are designed to boost your English listening skills and increase your vocabulary. On occasion, our hosts share their personal stories, making it easy to listen to these English audio lessons.</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #284 – The cult of overwork | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040180/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 00:00:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040180/</guid><description>Podcast Description In many countries, there is a cult of overworking and people are expected to work long hours. In fact, working long hours can be seen as a sign of good moral ethics. However, overworking is also a big problem for workers, as it puts a lot of stress on them. In this Chatterbox episode, Andrew and Anna discuss the cult of overworking and their experiences with this phenomenon.</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #283 – Plogging | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040181/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 19:53:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you heard about the newest trend that combines a daily walk or jog with picking up litter? If not, you’re not alone. It’s called plogging, and in this Chatterbox episode Andrew and Anna explain it, how it came to be called plogging, and why it’s becoming a popular activity for many people around the world.
The Chatterbox series is designed for intermediate and advanced English learners. Podcasts and audio lessons are a great way to improve your English listening skills.</description></item><item><title>Catch Word #256 – The different ways English speakers use damn | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040182/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 05:33:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040182/</guid><description>Podcast Description Damn! I can’t wait to listen to the new Culips episode. This is just one of the many ways you can use the word damn. You may have heard people say this word in films, TV, and music, but never truly understood all of the many meanings of the word. Listen to this Catch Word episode to learn some of the different definitions and how you can use the word like a native English speaker.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #138 – What do you think about online trolls? | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040183/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 22:08:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040183/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trolls. No, we’re not talking about mean mythical creatures who live under bridges. We’re talking about online trolls. They are very real and very mean people who like to anger others by posting nasty and cruel comments online. This has become a big problem associated with social media.
In this Simplified Speech episode, hosts Andrew and Kassy discuss the various ways online trolls operate, and how you can deal with them in your own way</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #137 – Kassy’s board game club | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040184/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 00:09:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040184/</guid><description>Podcast Description Board games are a fun way to spend an evening with friends. In this episode, Kassy talks with Andrew about her board game club and shares how it helps her meet new people, despite the pandemic.
Simplified Speech episodes feature two native English speakers having clear, natural and easy to understand English conversations about interesting topics, like board games with friends. By listening to Andrew and Kassy chat and following along with the transcript and study guide, you can improve your English listening skills and increase your vocabulary</description></item><item><title>Happy 2022!! BONUS EPISODE | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040185/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 20:45:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040185/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy 2022!! BONUS EPISODE Episode description Happy 2022! In this short episode, Andrew and the Culips team pass on the greetings and wishes for the new year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #136 – How was your 2021? | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040186/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 02:12:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040186/</guid><description>Podcast Description For some, 2021 was a lot better than 2020. However, that is not the case for everyone. We’re all still dealing with the COVID pandemic. In this episode, the Culips team looks back at some of the highs and lows of the last year.
Simplified Speech is a series meant for intermediate English language learners. This series is designed to help you improve your English skills with interesting and easy to listen to episodes.</description></item><item><title>Real Talk #053 – Visiting the dentist | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040187/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 19:15:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040187/</guid><description>Podcast Description Making a dental appointment, finding the time to go, and paying for dental insurance can all be quite the hassle. But of course, the main part of the whole experience is talking with your dentist about dental health. In this Real Talk episode, hosts Andrew and Kassy help you with the English you can expect to hear in the dentist chair.
In this episode, our hosts go over how to respond to the doctor’s polite requests.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #135 – Suzanne’s trip to France | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040188/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 06:07:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040188/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Suzanne tells us about her experience of flying internationally during the pandemic, which didn’t go as smoothly as planned. If you are thinking about taking a trip abroad, listen to this episode to get some useful tips on how to avoid problems at the airport.
The Simplified Speech series is the perfect way to learn from native speakers who use easy-to-understand English. In this study guide, there are detailed expressions to explain the more difficult words and phrases you hear, with examples to improve your understanding.</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #282 – The future of podcasting | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040189/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 19:17:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040189/</guid><description>Podcast Description Podcasts are evolving. From the technology used to the companies producing them and everything in between, the podcasting industry is seeing a lot of new, exciting changes. In this episode, Andrew and Anna talk about the changes they’ve seen, and discuss what it might mean for the future of podcasting.
The Chatterbox series is designed for intermediate and advanced English learners. Podcasts and audio lessons are a great way to improve your English listening skills.</description></item><item><title>Catch Word #255 – We just clicked | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040190/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 03:45:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040190/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever wished there was another way to describe how friendly you are with certain people? In this Catch Word episode, Andrew and Kassy share a couple ways native English speakers refer to their relationships with others.
The Culips Catch Word series explains idioms, phrasal verbs, and expressions used in everyday life. Listening to our Catch Word audio lessons helps improve your English listening and speaking skills while also giving you new, fun ways to talk about how well you get along with your friends.</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #281 – Do you prefer reading paper or e-books? | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040191/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 05:48:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040191/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Andrew and Anna debate the pros and cons of reading paper books and digital e-books. They also discuss their experiences with reading online and talk about the daily distractions that prevent them from reading properly.
Our Chatterbox series is the perfect way to learn English with our Culips hosts who discuss interesting and contemporary topics using everyday English. If you want to learn how to talk like a native speaker, then this is the podcast series for you!</description></item><item><title>Catch Word #254 – In for a rude awakening | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040192/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 18:50:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040192/</guid><description>Podcast Description Would you like to have a bombshell dropped on you? That sounds pretty bad, but don’t worry, our hosts Andrew and Suzanne are here to explain expressions you can use when you’re shocked at hearing big news. In this Catch Word episode, the two main expressions are to drop a bombshell and a rude awakening. Do you think you know what they mean? Give the episode a listen and find out!</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #134 – Buffet restaurants | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040193/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 00:34:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040193/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you the type of person who loves food and wishes your plate would never go empty? Going to a buffet restaurant means you can eat as much as you want. In this Simplified Speech episode, Andrew and Suzanne give us their opinions on buffets.
The Simplified Speech series helps you to learn English naturally with easy-to-understand conversations on current topics. Make sure you’ve eaten before listening to this episode, as it might make you hungry!</description></item><item><title>Catch Word #253 – Just chill | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040194/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 00:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040194/</guid><description>Podcast Description To calm down, hang out, relax, be easygoing: native English speakers use the word chill in many ways. In this Catch Word episode, Andrew and Kassy explain how to use this versatile word in four different situations.
The Culips Catch Word series explains idioms, phrasal verbs, and expressions used in everyday life. Listening to our Catch Word audio lessons helps improve your English listening and speaking skills. So, get ready to chill out as you listen to this natural conversation between two native English speakers.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #133 – Moving to a foreign country | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040195/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 21:04:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040195/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever lived or thought about living in a foreign country? If so, hit play and listen to Andrew and Suzanne’s perspectives about living in a foreign country. In this episode, Andrew and Suzanne talk about the ups and downs of living in a foreign country. Tune in to hear this interesting conversation full of natural English expressions and vocab
Fun facts An expat is someone who does not live in the country they hold citizenship in.</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #280 – Say goodbye to grey hair? | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040196/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 00:00:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040196/</guid><description>Podcast Description What? Another grey hair? If we’re fortunate enough to grow old, finding grey hairs will be a common occurrence for sure. In this Chatterbox episode, hosts Andrew and Anna talk about their relationship with grey hairs and a surprising new study on the topic. Apparently, your grey hairs can grow back to their natural colour. Imagine that!
Chatterbox is a series for intermediate to advanced English language learners. Our hosts speak in an easy-to-understand and natural way about a topic chosen to keep you interested.</description></item><item><title>Catch Word #252 – Do you have deep pockets? | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040197/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 19:18:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040197/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you know how to describe rich people and companies in English? In this Catch Word episode, Andrew and Kassy teach you two idiomatic English expressions that you can use to do just that. Upgrade your vocabulary and make your English sound more natural by learning with this lesson. Catch Word is the Culips vocabulary series for intermediate and advanced English language learners. In each episode, you’ll learn expressions, idioms, slang, phrasal verbs, and more that will help you become a better English listener and speaker.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #132 – Kassy’s getting married! | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040198/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 23:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040198/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kassy has joined the Culips wedding club! Many of the Culips hosts and listeners have gotten married these past few years, and Kassy is engaged to become the next! Listen to this Simplified Speech episode where Kassy talks about the events leading up to her engagement to her boyfriend.
Simplified Speech is a series where you can follow Culips hosts speaking in an easy-to-understand way. Also, we have a transcript and study guide designed to help you follow along with each episode.</description></item><item><title>Chatterbox #279 – Shrinkflation | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040199/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 21:09:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040199/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you noticed your usual grocery items are smaller than they used to be, but cost the same? You may not have heard of shrinkflation before, but it’s something that’s affecting everyone and people aren’t happy about it!
In this Chatterbox episode, Andrew and Anna discuss the issue of shrinkflation. Culips’ Chatterbox series helps you learn English from native speakers, with detailed expressions you can add to your own vocabulary that will surely impress your English-speaking friends!</description></item><item><title>Simplified Speech #131 – Squid Game | Culips Everyday English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9029040200/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 22:57:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9029040200/</guid><description>Podcast Description Squid Game on Netflix is a Korean show that has become extremely popular around the world. In this episode, Andrew and Kassy talk about the show, sharing their thoughts on the plot, story, and characters. If you liked Squid Game or are thinking about watching it, you shouldn’t miss this Simplified Speech episode!
Simplified Speech episodes feature two native English speakers having clear, natural, and easy-to-understand conversations about interesting topics, like popular TV shows.</description></item></channel></rss>