<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Round Table China on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/round-table-china/</link><description>Recent content in Round Table China on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 05:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/round-table-china/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Some colleagues and universities to stop providing accommodation | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750207/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750207/</guid><description>Podcast Description Some colleagues and universities say they will stop providing accommodation to specific groups of students pursuing postgraduate studies. Will this affect your decision to get a master&amp;rsquo;s degree? / The Hainan Island International Film Festival kicked off over the weekend (19:51). On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Brandon Yates
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What changes can tourism bring to rural areas? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750208/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750208/</guid><description>Podcast Description A recent report from a leading online travel agency reveals a significant surge in orders for rural tourism in China during the first three quarters of 2023, surpassing levels recorded in the pre-pandemic year of 2019. We&amp;rsquo;ll discuss the prospect of rural tourism. On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Brandon Yates
Transcript</description></item><item><title>International performers shine on stages in China | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750205/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750205/</guid><description>Podcast Description 2023 has been a total blast for the arts scene in China! We&amp;rsquo;re talking about global performances landing right on our doorstep, and our homegrown talents captivating audiences on world stage. In what ways have these cultural exchanges become instrumental in strengthening the bonds between China and other countries? / Round Table&amp;rsquo;s Happy Place (21:40)! On the show: Heyang, Xingyu &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Young people redefining retirement dreams | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750206/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750206/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;ll take a deep dive into the topic of retirement planning. China has got a one-year-old private pension initiative in the mix. We discuss how the younger crowd is turning the tables on retirement expectations. On the show: Heyang, Xingyu &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>'The Queen of News' - The rise, rewards, and risks of occupational drama | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750201/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750201/</guid><description>Podcast Description We step into the fast-paced universe of media professionals, where every headline is a battle, and every broadcast could hold the key to success. Hong Kong TVB&amp;rsquo;s latest sensation &amp;lsquo;The Queen of News&amp;rsquo; has got many in the audience hooked! What makes occupational drama series so irresistible? On the show: Heyang, Li Yi &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>China is the world's largest food importer! | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750202/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750202/</guid><description>Podcast Description Did you know that China is not only the ultimate foodie haven but also snagged the title of the world&amp;rsquo;s BIGGEST food importer? You won&amp;rsquo;t believe the numbers or flavors hitting Chinese dinner tables! It&amp;rsquo;s not just about a nice meal; it&amp;rsquo;s practically a world tour on a plate! So get ready to salivate. We are cooking up a storm and serving it right into your ears! On the show: Heyang, Li Yi &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill</description></item><item><title>Are American CEOs overpaid? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750203/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750203/</guid><description>Podcast Description American CEOs are often paid hundreds of times more than their company employees. Is that a problem? / Young Chinese explore uninhabited islands (21:35). On the show: Heyang, Xingyu &amp;amp; Brandon Yates
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Underwear market in China now bigger than ever | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750204/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750204/</guid><description>Podcast Description The bra and underwear market in China has grown bigger than ever, with domestic brands quickly taking over the intimate wardrobes of a new generation of Chinese women. We discuss the recipe to success of these companies. On the show: Heyang, Xingyu &amp;amp; Brandon Yates
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Are restaurant dances a hit or a miss? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750001/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ever been to a restaurant where the waitstaffs don’t just serve up delicious dishes but might also break into spontaneous dance moves? We dive into the debate of: Are these restaurant dances a cringe-fest or entertainment gold? / Dragon mascots got rizz. (21:44) On the show: Heyang, Yushun &amp;amp; Gao Junya
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A reality check on China's express delivery industry | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750002/</guid><description>Podcast Description A whopping 120 billion parcels crisscrossing the nation annually! We go beyond the speedy deliveries to look at the logistics behind these province-and-border-hopping parcels, and explore how the industry is stepping up its game on the green front. On the show: Heyang, Yushun &amp;amp; Gao Junya
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What does popularity of the Vietnamese version of a Chinese reality show imply? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chinese reality shows are getting excellent ratings in Vietnam, reaching the Vietnamese audience in different forms and formats. What does the success of a few shows say about the relationship between our two peoples? / Motivational Monday (19:15)! On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Li Yi
Transcript</description></item><item><title>2023 in review through the echoes of buzzwords | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750004/</guid><description>Podcast Description The buzzwords popping up everywhere on social media and in our everyday discourse can say a lot about our lives in the past year. Let&amp;rsquo;s review 2023 through the unique lens of buzzwords. On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Li Yi
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bookstores diversify as cultural spaces | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750005/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750005/</guid><description>Podcast Description You must be familiar with brick-and-mortar bookstores having a tough time in the era of online shopping. Well, bookshops are now trying something different to stay alive and relevant. Are we witnessing a revolution in retail, or is there something deeper at play? / Round Table&amp;rsquo;s Happy Place (18:56)! On the show: Heyang, Yushun &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Teaching digital literacy to digital natives | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750006/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today&amp;rsquo;s spotlight on RoundTable unveils the exciting quest for learning in a digital world. Join us as we explore the task of teaching digital natives, crack the code of cyber security in education, and navigate the vast digital frontier together. On the show: Heyang, Yushun &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Should we master first-aid skills? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750007/</guid><description>Podcast Description The percentage of Chinese people who have mastered first-aid skills stands at a dangerously low rate. Both the central government and regional authorities have taken actions to improve the situation, but satisfactory results are yet to be seen. What more needs to be done? / Will gossip against a third-party foster deeper friendship between two people (20:16)? On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Brandon Yates
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Opportunities and challenges faced by cities amidst social media frenzy | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750008/</guid><description>Podcast Description It seems Chinese cities are taking turns grabbing public attention over the internet. Beginning with the city of Zibo in east China&amp;rsquo;s Shandong Province, more and more cities have become internet sensations as people share tips and reflections about how best to enjoy a nice city tour. Today on Round Table, we discuss what makes a city sensational. On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Brandon Yates
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What makes soundtracks and music scores tug at our heartstrings? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750009/</guid><description>Podcast Description When music in movies and TV drama series is played exceptionally well, it has the ability to latch onto our nostalgic heartstrings. We go down our playlists of timeless favorites and try to answer this question: do recent music scores and soundtracks hold up to the same standard as their predecessors? On the show: Heyang, Xingyu &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why are celebs leaving the livestream selling scene? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;re spotlighting a captivating new trend in ecommerce – celebrities bidding adieu to the livestream selling scene. Are they exiting in grace or being booted out? / A dad gives a speech at a school meeting beaming with pride at his son, despite his son&amp;rsquo;s mediocre grades. Why has the video gone viral (19:12)? On the show: Heyang, Xingyu &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The rise of morning workouts among Chinese youth | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750011/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rise and shine, or hit snooze and recline? We dive into the fascinating rise of morning workouts among China&amp;rsquo;s youth - unpacking the why, the how, and whether it&amp;rsquo;s worth it to trade sunrise stretches for a few extra winks. / Keeping warm in wintertime (22:37) On the show: Heyang, Li Yi &amp;amp; Ding Heng
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Crafting your ideal TV experience in the streaming era | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750012/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Traditional cable TV has been witnessing a steady decline in subscribers for over a decade, as consumers increasingly shift towards streaming services. In our exploration of television viewing services, we delve into the areas that could welcome some improvements. Can a new industry standard address all these concerns? On the show: Heyang, Li Yi &amp;amp; Ding Heng
Transcript</description></item><item><title>China has banned the use of so-called 'fresh lamps' | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750013/</guid><description>Podcast Description China&amp;rsquo;s market regulator has recently put a stop to the use of the so-called &amp;ldquo;fresh lamps&amp;rdquo; in grocery stores and supermarkets which butchers have been using to cast their products in favorable lighting. We will discuss this new regulation to see whether it is achieving its intended results. / Motivational Monday (19:12)! On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Brandon Yates
Transcript</description></item><item><title>China's skiing frenzy continues with the arrival of a new snow season | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Skiing participation already was on the rise before the 2022 Winter Olympics in Beijing. Now with COVID-19 out of the way, businesses expect and are experiencing strong growth. And amidst all this skiing frenzy, we&amp;rsquo;ve spotted some new trends that we hope to share with you. On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Brandon Yates
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Might there just be such a thing as a free lunch? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hungry minds out there, listen up! Have you ever wished for a free lunch? Well, hold on to your chopsticks because we&amp;rsquo;re about to dish out the details on a trend called &amp;ldquo;eat and run meals. &amp;ldquo;/ Round Table&amp;rsquo;s Happy Place (17:23)! On the show: Heyang, Li Yi &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Anticipating more climate actions at COP28 | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750016/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are in the thick of the 28th UN Climate Change Conference, COP28, already in full swing in Dubai. World leaders have converged in the UAE, fueled by a collective mission to tackle climate change head-on. We&amp;rsquo;ll explore what ambitious climate actions might be on the horizon, with expert opinions from Derek Elsworth, Professor of Energy and Geo-Environmental Engineering at Pennsylvania State University, adding depth and clarity to the discussion.</description></item><item><title>Decoding the date: What lies behind 'near-expired foods?' | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750017/</guid><description>Podcast Description We take behind-the-scenes look at the industry of close-to-expire food! Are near-expired foods a budget-friendly buffet for foodies or a scheme that businesses use to deal with the ticking expiry clock. From a seller&amp;rsquo;s hustle to your kitchen – we&amp;rsquo;re talking about the money, the ethics, and everything in between. / Clearing the air: debunking respiratory myths for winter warriors (19:52). On the show: Niu Honglin, Xingyu &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill</description></item><item><title>China holds first supply chain expo | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750018/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750018/</guid><description>Podcast Description We step into the heartbeat of global commerce as the first China International Supply Chain Expo is underway here in Beijing. How are global supply chains affecting our daily lives? What are some highlights that one would not want to miss? On the show: Niu Honglin, Xingyu &amp;amp; Li Yunqi
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Do you talk more like a zoomer or a boomer at work? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750019/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;lsquo;Slay,&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;I&amp;rsquo;m dead&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;yass queen&amp;rsquo; are just a few phrases that Gen Z have snuck into the American workplace. But for older colleagues not keeping up with the latest trends, those phrases might just fly over their heads. Or worse yet, their meanings might be misinterpreted. We take a look at the generational differences in how we talk at work! On the show: Heyang, Yushun &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill</description></item><item><title>Why are short drama videos gaining global appeal? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get ready for a wild ride into the world of short drama videos, that&amp;rsquo;s unabashedly tacky, clichéd, and yet, undeniably beloved. From forbidden alphas to reborn wives, these short video series may seem over the top, but with skyrocketing viewing numbers, it&amp;rsquo;s clear that the world secretly loves drama. Buckle up, drama lovers – it&amp;rsquo;s about to get so bad, it&amp;rsquo;s good! On the show: Heyang, Yushun &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill</description></item><item><title>Why do employees hate hot-desking? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750021/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2023, hot-desking means sharing on-site workspaces between employees who work remotely most of the time but occasionally need to come to the office. Why do a third of American employees in a survey hate it? / Should I sit in the front row of the lecture hall (21:06)? On the show: Heyang, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Yushun
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Latest weight-loss drug hardly the fix for obesity | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ozempic and a popular new class of medications like it are transforming the medical approach to obesity, challenging traditional perspectives on weight and its treatment. However, this drug, initially designed for diabetes management, is facing a global shortage due to its popularity among weight-loss enthusiasts. Using drugs to stop cravings - isn&amp;rsquo;t that a bad thing? Are there any side effects that we should be aware of? On the show: Heyang, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Yushun</description></item><item><title>Living legacies of intangible cultural heritage | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750023/</guid><description>Podcast Description ‘Intangible Cultural Heritage’ represents the essence of a community’s identity. In a fast changing world, it’s important to ensure the preservation and protection of these invaluable cultural assets. In China, many localities are trying out an approach by blending cultural heritage with tourism. How can we strike a harmonious balance between sharing these treasures with the world and safeguarding them for generations to come? On the show: Heyang, Li Yi and Dr.</description></item><item><title>Can genetic testing predict talent? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750024/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can genetic testing predict a child&amp;rsquo;s talents? Is it a crystal ball into their future abilities, or should we approach it with caution? / Round Table&amp;rsquo;s Happy Place (23:33)! On the show: Heyang, Ding Heng &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Are seniors the new growth catalyst for e-commerce? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750025/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750025/</guid><description>Podcast Description The increasing presence of senior consumers in the online world could reshape the ecommerce marketplace. How can we optimize the online shopping experience for the elderly to ensure that they can navigate it with ease? On the show: Heyang, Ding Heng &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Are baked goods becoming overpriced? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750026/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750026/</guid><description>Podcast Description As some bakeries push the boundaries of creativity, their prices are also becoming more and more jaw-dropping. Are these treats reaching new heights in taste and quality, or are we witnessing a dough dilemma as prices soar? Are the prices worth the treat? / Heart to Heart - please send your audio questions to ezfmroundtable@foxmail.com (20:43)! On the show: Niu Honglin, Li Yi &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Driving forces for maternal and infant industry upgrade | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750027/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a world where raising a child has transformed from a shared responsibility to a meticulous, sometimes high-tech endeavor, the maternal and infant industry stands as a testament to this paradigm shift. From the quest for the perfect diaper to the intricacies of high-end baby formula, join us as we decode the driving forces behind this parenting revolution. On the show: Niu Honglin, Li Yi &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill</description></item><item><title>Research publications not mandatory for PhDs in a few Chinese universities | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750028/</guid><description>Podcast Description A few Chinese universities recently announced that research publications are no longer mandatory for their PhD students. Is this a good idea? / Where do you suppose all the good small phones have gone (19:10)? On the show: Heyang, Li Yi &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Spending power of men | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750029/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750029/</guid><description>Podcast Description In retail analysis in China, there&amp;rsquo;s a somewhat tongue-in-cheek observation: Men are often consigned to the bottom of the consumption hierarchy, falling even behind pet dogs and cats. But, maybe we&amp;rsquo;ve gotten it wrong all those years! On the show: Heyang, Li Yi &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What can we do to safeguard valuable heritage tucked away in narrow historic streets? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750030/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750030/</guid><description>Podcast Description As our cities rapidly urbanize, many people lament the loss of landmarks and historic streets that they grew up with. Should we wipe out every old building and every ancient street to make room for bigger, taller and more efficient high-rises? We discuss the approaches to sooth our nostalgia and preserve our culture. / Have you ever thought about a personality test for companies and businesses (21:02)? On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Yushun</description></item><item><title>What makes outdoor sports so popular? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750031/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Outdoor sports activities are picking up in popularity. What has been driving the increasing enthusiasm in the great outdoors and who are these people climbing mountains and hugging trees? What opportunities does this trend present to relevant industries? On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Yushun
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Community pharmacies become local health hubs | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750032/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750032/</guid><description>Podcast Description From handling minor illnesses to long-term conditions, we&amp;rsquo;ve got your back. Learn why community pharmacies are the neighborhood champions for health advice and support! / Motivational Monday(19:46)! On the show: Heyang, Li Yi &amp;amp; Yushun
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Do pop-up stores make your business pop? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750033/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750033/</guid><description>Podcast Description We explore the fascinating world of pop-up retail, or flash retailing. In my eyes, as a slightly less sympathetic observer, they&amp;rsquo;re like the wannabes of the retail scene, here one day and gone the next. Our discussion will go beyond the glossy facade of pop-up stores. On the show: Heyang, Li Yi &amp;amp; Yushun
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Are music festivals losing their creative edge? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750034/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750034/</guid><description>Podcast Description We share with you what made us happy this week in RoundTable&amp;rsquo;s Happy Place! / Music festivals used to be incubators for creativity in music, culture and fashion. Despite explosive popularity in the post-covid era, music festivals are now being questioned: Have they plateaued? Are music festivals no longer the breeding grounds for new and groundbreaking ideas in music and fashion (16:18)? On the show: Heyang, Yushun &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill</description></item><item><title>Bring back 10-minute recess to schools | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750035/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750035/</guid><description>Podcast Description The &amp;lsquo;10-minute recess&amp;rsquo; getting too quiet in elementary schools? The Internet is buzzing with criticism! Why are some students losing their playtime, and what does it mean for their well-being? On the show: Heyang, Yushun &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>From shopping to experiencing: the resurgence of wet markets in China | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750036/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750036/</guid><description>Podcast Description As we plan our journeys to new cities, the search for authentic experiences becomes increasingly important. Some might follow the new style of city walk, while others seek help from the locals. However, some young Chinese travelers have figured out a third option: visiting the traditional wet markets. Today we&amp;rsquo;ll explore this fascinating travel trend. / &amp;lsquo;Shy Girl Workouts&amp;rsquo; Trend on Tiktok (20:35). On the show: Niu Honglin, Fei Fei &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill</description></item><item><title>Young Chinese adults opt for evening classes after work | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750037/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750037/</guid><description>Podcast Description While blinking neon lights of Shanghai paint the city in dazzling glows, a different kind of radiance has captured the attention of many of its young residents. Night schools have become a sensation, attracting swarms of eager learners fresh out of their cubicles. Round table takes you to discover the allure of Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s nocturnal learning revolution. On the show: Niu Honglin, Fei Fei &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cultural exchanges between China and the U.S. | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750038/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750038/</guid><description>Podcast Description We explore the remarkable cultural exchanges between China and the U.S., focusing on the unique experiences of artists and scholars who have been bridging these two nations. In a world where cultures intertwine, creativity knows no borders, and art becomes a universal language. We can all have faith in a better future. / Yushun&amp;rsquo;s one-day tour in NYU Shanghai (39:29). On the show: Niu Honglin, Xingyu, Allan Denis Naymark &amp;amp; Yushun</description></item><item><title>EU bans microplastics to combat plastic pollution | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750039/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750039/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a significant stride towards a cleaner future, the European Commission introduced a ban on microplastics. How significant is the microplastic problem? What is China doing to tackle plastic pollution? / What are the factors behind the yawning gap in personal energy levels (19:27)? On the show: Niu Honglin, Xingyu &amp;amp; Brandon Yates
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Navigating the Sweet Dilemma - World Diabetes Day Special | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750040/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750040/</guid><description>Podcast Description As we observe World Diabetes Day, we delve into the complex landscape of diabetes in China and beyond. From skyrocketing cases to the influence of lifestyle, we dissect the sweet dilemma that millions face daily. Join us as we examine the multifaceted factors that contribute to the rise of diabetes, question how the world can collectively combat the silent epidemic of diabetes. On the show: Niu Honglin, Xingyu &amp;amp; Brandon Yates</description></item><item><title>Why young people crowd the lower levels in shopping malls | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750041/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750041/</guid><description>Podcast Description At the moment, the spotlight is cast on young consumers and their inclination to shop on underground levels, rather than immersing in the glamour and serenity of the upper decks. Why has it turn into a thing that deserves so much attention and discussion over the internet? / Motivational Monday(19:54)! On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Li Yi
Transcript</description></item><item><title>10 years on: World Internet Conference Wuzhen Summit | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750042/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750042/</guid><description>Podcast Description The advent of the internet and the onslaught of AI technologies have introduced more complexities to our lives in the cyberspace. Today, we investigate the efforts of online community-building as a recent annual gathering of the internet industry sheds some light on business development in China and around the world. On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Li Yi
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A sneak peek into the future: interview with designer Alexander Brandt | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750043/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Heyang interviews visionary designer, Alexander Brandt, chief designer of the record-setting Shanghai Astronomy Museum, and the brilliant mind behind &amp;ldquo;AI&amp;rsquo;s Dreams&amp;rdquo;. They discuss the controversies of AI &amp;amp; tech, the future of immersive education, and how to stay creative in today&amp;rsquo;s fast-changing world.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>WeWork doesn't work. Now what? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750044/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Office-sharing company, WeWork, once a venture capital darling valued at 47 billion USD, has filed for bankruptcy on November 6th. What went so wrong in this company that was once one of America&amp;rsquo;s most valuable start-ups? On the show: Heyang, Yushun &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Plus-size travelers on public transport | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750045/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750045/</guid><description>Podcast Description A video about a plus-size girl trying to squeeze herself into her seat in public transport sparked a wave of controversy. What infrastructure do we need in public places both in our physical world and in the cyberspace? / Some frequent travelers claim there are now less movie options when they fly with commercial airlines. Is that true (19:22)? On the show: Laiming, Li Yi &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill</description></item><item><title>China releases white paper on development of distant-water fisheries | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750046/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750046/</guid><description>Podcast Description A white paper sheds some light on the development of China&amp;rsquo;s distant water fishing industry. Why should the average listeners of Round Table care about what&amp;rsquo;s going on hundreds of thousands nautical miles off China&amp;rsquo;s coast? How does it affect our lives? On the show: Laiming, Li Yi &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>RT special: Seeds of Change - Through urban gardening to a greener city | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750047/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Round Table&amp;rsquo;s Heyang continues her trip in Shanghai. This time, she visits a rooftop experimental farm at NYU Shanghai, in the middle of the bustling metropolis! She talks to professors about how creativity and cultivation intersect with urban farming, art, and the city development.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>RT special: Shanghai Shines – CIIE Sparks Innovation and Connections | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750048/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Round Table&amp;rsquo;s Heyang is in Shanghai amid one of the most important events taking place in the city - the China International Import Expo (CIIE). Together with Professor Chen Yuxin, Dean of Business at NYU Shanghai, and Eric Zheng, President of the American Chamber of Commerce in Shanghai, she explores the impact created by the Expo. Today&amp;rsquo;s show is a journey into the heart of trade, innovation, and global connections.</description></item><item><title>RT special: Global Lens - Insights from the CIIE 2023 Opening Day | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750049/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750049/</guid><description>Podcast Description The world once again looks to Shanghai as the 2023 China International Import Expo kicks off in a spectacular fashion. #RoundTableChina shares remarkable highlights of this year&amp;rsquo;s Expo on its opening day. What sets it apart from the precious iterations? How does it symbolize China&amp;rsquo;s commitment to high-level openness and international collaboration? Join us and take a closer look at this global economic extravaganza.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why young audiences enjoy breakup movies | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750050/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750050/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a world where love can be as unpredictable as the weather, we&amp;rsquo;ve all been through the ups and downs of relationships. While a happy ending is what most would appreciate for a good love story, more and more young audiences start to develop a special taste for breakup movies. Why is that? / Heart to Heart - please send your audio questions to ezfmroundtable@foxmail.com (19:24)! On the show: Niu Honglin, Xingyu &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill</description></item><item><title>How to make a city walkable? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750051/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750051/</guid><description>Podcast Description As Chinese cities continue to swell with inhabitants, the concept of walkability has stepped into the limelight. In the meantime, rapid urbanization has brought forth challenges such as traffic jams, pollution, and urban sprawl. Our discussion today focuses on the significance of walkable cities in solving these urban issues. On the show: Niu Honglin, Xingyu &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Employment background checks: Where are the boundaries? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750052/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750052/</guid><description>Podcast Description In an era where even your digital footprint might impact your career, the question of where employment background checks should begin and end is more relevant than ever. Today, on Round Table, we embark on a journey through the complexities of this practice. / Emotional intelligence test attracts young adults in China (17:57). On the show: Niu Honglin, Fei Fei &amp;amp; Yushun
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Following others vs. treading your own path, what's for you? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750053/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750053/</guid><description>Podcast Description In life&amp;rsquo;s pivotal moments, we often grapple with the age-old question: should we follow the well-worn paths tested out by tradition and others&amp;rsquo; experiences, or shall we dare to blaze our unique trail into the unknown? The choices we make at these moments can significantly impact our lives and our futures. Today, Round Table takes you to discover the pros and cons of both approaches. On the show: Niu Honglin, Fei Fei &amp;amp; Yushun</description></item><item><title>Why are grownups playing hide-and-seek? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750054/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hide-and-seek is one classic childhood game, for kids under the age of 10, I would think. But in Chinese cities nowadays, Gen-Z adults are also playing hide-and-seek and are proud of doing so. Hear this one out: Playing Hide and Seek with Strangers may seem a bit childish for kids around ten, but is just right for adults in their twenties. What gives? / Chinese musicians turn everyday objects into music magic (22:08).</description></item><item><title>Online shopping vs. In-store: Who's winning the price game? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750055/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750055/</guid><description>Podcast Description E-commerce is a huge part of our economy. China boasts almost 900 million online shoppers who are actively engaged in the vibrant online marketplace, filled with countless product options, all touting affordability. But here&amp;rsquo;s the question: Is online shopping still the wallet-friendly choice, or are brick-and-mortar stores winning the price war? On the show: Heyang, Yushun &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The power of default | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750056/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750056/</guid><description>Podcast Description The biggest-ever antitrust case in US tech history is unfolding right now, starring Google as its defendant. At the heart of this courtroom clash is a little word with big implications: default. Why don&amp;rsquo;t users change their tech default settings? How powerful is it to be a consumer&amp;rsquo;s first choice? / Pain-free mountain hike (20:00). On the show: Heyang, Li Yi &amp;amp; Brandon Yates
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Digital solutions for smarter cities | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750057/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750057/</guid><description>Podcast Description As cities get smarter, the plan is for them to become more livable and responsive. In China, various levels of government have been pushing for smart cities. We are now just seeing a preview of the marvels of technology in the urban environment. But as we all know, new tech brings its own set of problems. We discuss the pluses and pitfalls of smarter cities! Can we make smart cities wiser too?</description></item><item><title>What has Beijing Marathon witnessed since its inception in 1981? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750058/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750058/</guid><description>Podcast Description 30,000 runners took part in the Beijing Marathon over the weekend. What is special about the foot race and why can it attract such a large following? / Motivational Monday (21:56)! On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Fei Fei
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Urban development with youth in mind | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750059/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750059/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are starting a special series this week looking at the world around us through the unique lens of cities. In China and around the world, urbanization continues to provide new incentives for economic growth and social development. As such, cities and their residents deserve special attention. Today, in the first episode of the series, we look at urban development with young people in mind. On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Fei Fei</description></item><item><title>What does it take to correct pet behavior? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750060/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750060/</guid><description>Podcast Description The recent news of an unleashed Rottweiler dog attacking a toddler has prompted local authorities to tighten regulations on owning oversized dogs and promote responsible pet ownership. To help dogs behave better, a new generation of pet parents is sending their furry friends to school for training. How can we better control pet dogs in public? / Quirky profile photos show work moods (18:00). On the show: Heyang, Li Yi &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill</description></item><item><title>The 2023 concert boom | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750061/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to the Concert Boom of 2023! But here&amp;rsquo;s the catch - getting a ticket is like trying to catch a shooting star. One has to win a race to get a seat! We take a look at the incredible &amp;amp; irreplaceable live music experience and the economic impact of live concerts! On the show: Heyang, Li Yi &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>From clicks to experiences: China's 'local life service' | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750062/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750062/</guid><description>Podcast Description What if I told you that discounts and great deals are just a click away for your next dinner date or spa retreat? That&amp;rsquo;s the magic of &amp;ldquo;local life services&amp;rdquo; in China! We peel back the curtain to reveal the secrets of this thrill-seeking trend. / Heart to Heart - please send your audio questions to ezfmroundtable@foxmail.com (19:28)! On the show: Niu Honglin, Yushun &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Unmasking Life Coaches | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750063/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750063/</guid><description>Podcast Description With China&amp;rsquo;s highly competitive job market and a lack of enough career guidance in universities, life coaches are stepping in to fill the void and help the latest wave of graduates navigate their career choices. Today, Round Table invites you to delve into the world of life coaching. On the show: Niu Honglin, Yushun &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chinese nail-care sets its sight on international markets | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750064/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750064/</guid><description>Podcast Description The nail-care industry has been taking off big time in China for years. From nail tips and kits to nail salon services, there&amp;rsquo;s a whole ecosystem of small businesses thriving on the beauty treatment of nails. Companies have set their eyes on the international market. / Why do celebrities change their names (17:10)? On the show: Heyang, Junya &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Moving out is getting increasingly difficult for young Americans | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750065/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750065/</guid><description>Podcast Description A new Bloomberg survey has found that it&amp;rsquo;s getting a lot harder for young Americans to leave their parents&amp;rsquo; nest. And when you look around the world, renting a place on your own as an adult, seen in some cultures as an important step to independence and adulthood, just isn&amp;rsquo;t as easy as it used to be. We delve into changes in the housing market, and perceptions towards independence and the self-made ideal.</description></item><item><title>The success and challenges of IP-driven theme parks | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750066/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Recently, a popular Chinese toy maker has launched its first theme park in Beijing. Our discussion unlocks the magic of immersive experiences, as we explore the rewards and hurdles of IP-driven theme parks. / Surfing app changes how people surf (19:59). On the show: Heyang, Xingyu &amp;amp; Brandon Yates
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Will the future of work be hybrid? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750067/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750067/</guid><description>Podcast Description The pandemic has shown us the pros and cons of remote work. Now in a post-pandemic world, a hybrid system of allowing employees days of working both from office and from home has taken hold in some companies in the US, UK, New Zealand and so on. But it&amp;rsquo;s still less common in the Chinese workplace. Why the discrepancy? On the show: Heyang, Xingyu &amp;amp; Brandon Yates
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The rise of ethnic-themed photography among Chinese tourists | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750068/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Young Chinese tourists have recently embarked on a journey where photos aren&amp;rsquo;t merely mementos, but a bridge to understanding and celebrating the country&amp;rsquo;s ethnic diversity. We&amp;rsquo;ll find out what&amp;rsquo;s so special about ethnic-themed photography. / The 2023 Hugo Awards were a night to remember at Chengdu Worldcon on October 21st. Roundtable has caught up with some people in the know for exciting insights (15:30). On the show: Niu Honglin, Laiming &amp;amp; Fei Fei</description></item><item><title>From tradition to technology: supporting seniors on Double Ninth | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750069/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750069/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this year&amp;rsquo;s Double Ninth Festival, we gather at Round Table to shed light on the mental and emotional well-being of our seniors, from their cultural experiences and social interactions to the impact of the digital age, to better understand and meet the emotional needs of our elderly, making their later years truly fulfilling. On the show: Niu Honglin, Laiming &amp;amp; Fei Fei
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What happens to all the unsold clothes? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750070/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750070/</guid><description>Podcast Description About 70 percent of clothes in malls don&amp;rsquo;t get sold. What happens to all that inventory? How to be fashionable without hurting the planet? Let&amp;rsquo;s find out how our individual choices as consumers can change the future of the planet. (01:04) / Round Table&amp;rsquo;s Happy Place! (20:22) On the show: Heyang, Li Yi &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>More people go for online psychological support | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750071/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Feeling down? Ever considered paying to chat with a stranger online in the hopes of feeling better? Well, lots of folks are giving it a try in China. But there are worries too. Join us as we take a peek into the world of online counseling that&amp;rsquo;s just getting started. On the show: Heyang, Li Yi &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The good and bad of curiosity | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750072/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Human beings have an innate desire to close the &amp;ldquo;curiosity gap&amp;rdquo; and solve riddles every day. However, it curiosity always good? We discuss: curiosity, the good, the bad, and the double-edged sword. / Heart to Heart - please send your audio questions to ezfmroundtable@foxmail.com (21:48)! On the show: Heyang, Yushun &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chinese science fiction boom &amp; Chengdu Worldcon | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750073/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750073/</guid><description>Podcast Description All eyes of science fiction enthusiasts worldwide are now focused on Chengdu. As the 2023 World Science Fiction Convention or Worldcon kicks off on October 18th in the southwest Chinese city. Get ready for the scoop on Chengdu Worldcon and a deep dive into the buzz around the Chinese Science Fiction Boom. On the show: Heyang, Yushun &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Round Table presents 'CGTN Townhall – The New Silk Road' | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750074/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750074/</guid><description>Podcast Description 2023 marks the 10th anniversary of the Belt and Road Initiative. CGTN invites dozens of college students, together with experts and national news networks from Pakistan and Malaysia, to jointly review the achievements of the initiative over the past decade and explore its future potential. In this show, we are joined by Li Qiuyuan, CGTN Anchor; Zhong Shi, CGTN Anchor; Harvey Dzodin, Senior Fellow of Center for China and Globalization; Amine Hammadi, Chief Analyst for the African Chamber of Commerce; Zoon Ahmed Khan, Research Fellow of the BRI Strategic Institute of Tsinghua University; and John Gong, Vice President of Research and Strategy University of International Business and Economics - Israel.</description></item><item><title>Weal and woes of 'part-time children' | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750075/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Part-time children or full-time offspring? We discuss how young adults navigate relationships with aging parents. / To sweat or not to sweat, which is the indication of health (21:37)？On the show: Heyang, Xingyu &amp;amp; Brandon Yates
Transcript</description></item><item><title>'Dumb phones' for digital detox? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750076/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750076/</guid><description>Podcast Description More young people are now opting for old-fashioned dumb phones, without smart features most of us have become so dependent on. Is dumb the new smart? We discuss the return of &amp;lsquo;dumb phones&amp;rsquo;. On the show: Heyang, Xingyu &amp;amp; Brandon Yates
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Round Table presents '2023 Youth Talks- My Silk Road' | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750077/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750077/</guid><description>Podcast Description As we mark the 10th anniversary of the &amp;ldquo;Belt and Road Initiative&amp;rdquo;, how can global youth seize opportunities for cooperation and exchange? How should Generation Z integrate themselves into this grand vision and jointly sketch out the Silk Road blueprint for the new era? In this episode, Niu Honglin, together with CGTN commentator Huang Jiyuan, Pakistani researcher Zoon Ahmed Khan, and European policy officer Giorgia Maset, will delve into these questions.</description></item><item><title>Is packaging fee for takeout food over-priced? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750078/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are we being overcharged for takeout food that comes in plastic boxes wrapped in plastic bags? What is the economic and environmental cost of food delivery? / Round Table&amp;rsquo;s Happy Place (16:51)! On the show: Laiming, Gao Junya &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to make carbon neutral zones sustainable? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750079/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Before the whole planet hits the finishing line with carbon neutrality, small battles and skirmishes will have to be won. The building of zero-carbon zones constitutes small steps toward the final victory. Today we take a look at the construction and operation of carbon neutral zones, to see whether we&amp;rsquo;ve found sustainable ways to save our environment. On the show: Laiming, Gao Junya &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Uni-talk Challenge: Round Table's rising stars! | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750080/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you ready to unleash your inner voice in thought-provoking discussions? Join us in “Uni-talk Challenge”, where you and your friends can team up to record a mini-English talk show on whatever topic that sparks your interest and encourages inspirational discussions. Submit your entry to: ezfmroundtable@foxmail.com and get ready to become Round Table&amp;rsquo;s rising stars!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A tale of China's two great cities: Beijing &amp; Shanghai | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750081/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cities in the same country can be friendly rivals with different strengths. Their differences add to the uniqueness of the country. We take the pair of Beijing and Shanghai and see in what aspect does one outshine the other? / How to navigate a long-distance relationship (20:43)? On the show: Heyang, Yushun &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Opportunities and challenges of recycling EV batteries | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750082/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Around the world, Electric Vehicles are expected to play a vital role in reducing air pollution and meeting climate change goals. While EVs emit less CO2, their batteries are tough to recycle. What happens when your electric car&amp;rsquo;s battery pack reaches the end of its life? On the show: Heyang, Yushun &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Do social media 'friend recommendations' truly expand our friend circles? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750083/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Recommendation Systems are used to suggest things to users, from things to buy, songs to listen to, and even strangers we could befriend. Do social media &amp;lsquo;friend recommendations&amp;rsquo; truly expand our friend circles? / Quirky profile photos show work moods (20:21). On the show: Heyang, Li Yi &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Younger generations are now the primary target of online fraud | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750084/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Recent research reveals that young people are falling victim to internet scams more frequently than their older counterparts nowadays. Why is this happening and how can we better protect both the young and old? On the show: Heyang, Li Yi &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The odyssey of seafarers: rewards and realities of life at sea | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750085/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750085/</guid><description>Podcast Description The maritime industry in China is undergoing a transformation as the number of new seafarers is on the rise, but so is the complexity of this profession. We’ll unravel the intricate tapestry of seafaring life. / Breaking free from wedding gift money traditions (19:32). On the show: Niu Honglin, Li Yi &amp;amp; Ding Heng
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Unraveling the childhood obesity puzzle in rural China | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750086/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750086/</guid><description>Podcast Description In China, a recent study unveiled some surprising findings – the height gap between rural and urban children is narrowing, suggesting improvements in overall health of children living in the countryside. Yet, lurking beneath this positive trend is a growing concern. Obesity among rural youth is on the rise and may soon surpass that of their urban counterparts. What are the reasons behind this surge in childhood obesity? On the show: Niu Honglin, Li Yi &amp;amp; Ding Heng</description></item><item><title>What has caused the general uproar about kids having pre-cooked meals every day? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750087/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pre-cooked meals are the latest fashion in China&amp;rsquo;s catering business, but when businesses seek to expand its reach into school cafeterias, they met strong backlash from parents. What&amp;rsquo;s going on? / Motivational Monday (20:05)! On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Yushun
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A look-back at the Hangzhou Asian Games | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750088/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750088/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 19th Asian Games wrapped up last night in China&amp;rsquo;s southern city of Hangzhou. Today, we look back at the weeks-long competition events to relive the most exciting and touching moments. On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Yushun
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Round Table presents 'Connected,' ep5: Gabriella Bonino | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750089/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750089/</guid><description>Podcast Description RT presents the latest edition of a special series called &amp;ldquo;Connected.&amp;rdquo; This series offers a glimpse into the lives of ordinary individuals whose paths intersect with the ancient Silk Road, as well as the modern-day Belt and Road Initiative. Today, we share the captivating story of the &amp;ldquo;Contemporary female Marco Polo.&amp;rdquo; Gabriella Bonino, from Italy, has followed fellow predecessor Marco Polo&amp;rsquo;s footsteps and retraced the Silk Road.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The pursuit of happiness from multiple dimensions | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750090/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750090/</guid><description>Podcast Description The pursuit of happiness often proves capricious. However, therein lies a subtle truth – anchoring our happiness solely in one place can leave us exposed to life&amp;rsquo;s inescapable ebbs and flows. We explore a potential defense mechanism: the cultivation of happiness from multiple dimensions. Can it provide alternative ways of being happy? On the show: Heyang, Yushun &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Round Table presents 'Connected,' ep4: Li Mengyang and Zhao Yun | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750091/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750091/</guid><description>Podcast Description RT presents the latest edition of a special series called &amp;ldquo;Connected.&amp;rdquo; This series offers a glimpse into the lives of ordinary individuals whose paths intersect with the ancient Silk Road, as well as the modern-day Belt and Road Initiative. China and Mongolia have deepened corporation within the framework of the Belt and Road Initiative. Here&amp;rsquo;s the story of Li Mengyang and Zhao Yun, which shows that exchanges of goods and medical supplies, known as the &amp;ldquo;gifts of sheep and tea,&amp;rdquo; strengthen the bond between the two countries.</description></item><item><title>The hidden strength of weak social ties | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750092/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750092/</guid><description>Podcast Description A recent survey found that something as simple as &amp;lsquo;saying hello to neighbors&amp;rsquo; can boost one&amp;rsquo;s wellbeing. Researchers arrived at the conclusion that &amp;lsquo;causal social ties make us happier.&amp;rsquo; We unravel the impact of &amp;lsquo;weak social ties&amp;rsquo; on our well-being. On the show: Heyang, Xingyu &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Round Table presents 'Connected,' ep3: Simon Abbe and Jiang Keyu | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750093/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750093/</guid><description>Podcast Description RT presents the latest edition of a special series called &amp;ldquo;Connected.&amp;rdquo; This series offers a glimpse into the lives of ordinary individuals whose paths intersect with the ancient Silk Road, as well as the modern-day Belt and Road Initiative. Dancers Simon Abbe from Cameroon and Jiang Keyu from China are not only partners on stage but also a loving couple in life. Join us in this episode to explore how their artistic journey has fostered a living bond between China and Africa.</description></item><item><title>Let's talk about love | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750094/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about love. From the adventurous voyage of &amp;ldquo;master-dating&amp;rdquo; to the unconventional recourse of relationship &amp;ldquo;wakeup&amp;rdquo; calls, a new generation of young people cast their gaze upon romantic love through a new prism. Does romantic love still hold its traditional significance? On the show: Heyang, Yushun &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Round Table presents 'Connected,' ep2: Jin Zhaoyu | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750095/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750095/</guid><description>Podcast Description RT presents the latest edition of a special series called &amp;ldquo;Connected.&amp;rdquo; This series offers a glimpse into the lives of ordinary individuals whose paths intersect with the ancient Silk Road, as well as the modern-day Belt and Road Initiative. Today, we delve into the story of Jin Zhaoyu, a Chinese restorer who has helped with the restoration of the splendid Ta Keo Temple, one of the major temples at the UNESCO world heritage site of Angkor in Cambodia.</description></item><item><title>How can art help invigorate the countryside? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750096/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750096/</guid><description>Podcast Description In recent years, there has been a wave of creative initiatives bringing modern art into rural communities. One example is the Art at Fuliang project. Part of the Art Field China Project, it has turned a small village in east China&amp;rsquo;s Jiangxi Province into an art gallery under the sun. How can art help invigorate the countryside? On the show: Li Yi &amp;amp; Chen Xiyu, Communication Director of the Art Field China Project &amp;amp; Teng Huimin, Chief of Operation of Art at Fuliang.</description></item><item><title>Round Table presents 'Connected,' ep1: Zhang Yiqing | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750097/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750097/</guid><description>Podcast Description RT presents the latest edition of a special series called &amp;ldquo;Connected.&amp;rdquo; This series offers a glimpse into the lives of ordinary individuals whose paths intersect with the ancient Silk Road, as well as the modern-day Belt and Road Initiative. In this episode, we hear the story of Zhang Yiqing, a professional builder who has taken part in construction projects in many countries over the past 13 years.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>New travel trends for National Day holiday | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750098/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Started on October 1, the Chinese National Holiday period is now in full swing. This year, the holiday stretches to include an additional day compared to the typical week, thanks to the Mid-Autumn Festival. People are making the most of this precious time off, by embarking on trips or opting for a tranquil staycation. On today&amp;rsquo;s show, we bring you the latest insights into new travel trends for this National Holiday week.</description></item><item><title>Round Table's Mid-Autumn Festival Special: Hangzhou Rendezvous | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750099/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750099/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Mid-Autumn Festival is a time for getting together with loved ones, rejoicing in bountiful harvest, and embracing the romance of a luminous full moon. For thousands of years, China&amp;rsquo;s Hangzhou has been adorned as the &amp;ldquo;City of Heaven&amp;rdquo; and has attracted travelers, artists, and litterateurs from both home and abroad. Celebrate the holiday with us at &amp;lsquo;Hangzhou Rendezvous,&amp;rsquo; a show featuring poetry, music, stories and more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Can 'sound healing' ease stress? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750100/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Heart to Heart - please send your audio questions to ezfmroundtable@foxmail.com! / What is &amp;lsquo;sound healing&amp;rsquo; therapy? Can it really ease stress (15:21)? On the show: Heyang, Xingyu &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chinese home cooked dishes for a lighter diet | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750101/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750101/</guid><description>Podcast Description In recent years, the concept of light meals or light foods, known as Qingshi in Chinese, has won the approval of many urban dwellers. With a quick browse you&amp;rsquo;ll notice that every shopping mall comes with a light meals restaurant. Now, Chinese home cooked light meals are gaining traction. On the show: Heyang, Xingyu &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Summer cool drink - sour plum juice with TCM ingredients | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750102/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sour plum juice, with a TCM twist, stands at the juncture of traditional Chinese medicine and busy urban lifestyle. It is the latest favorite drink of Chinese Gen Z. What&amp;rsquo;s given rise to this new beverage trend? / Heart to Heart - please send your audio questions to ezfmroundtable@foxmail.com (15:47)! On the show: Heyang, Fei Fei &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Shopping malls go digital | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750103/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shopping malls, those brick and mortar retail spaces, have undergone a digital transformation in China. We take a look at how shopping malls welcome the combination of bricks and clicks. On the show: Heyang, Fei Fei &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why do people follow study influencers? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750104/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750104/</guid><description>Podcast Description China&amp;rsquo;s young internet users are following a new type of influencers, diligent learners who do livestreams or upload content showing their spartan studying marathons, sometimes exceeding 10 hours a day. Users say they find inspiration from these hardworking content providers, but what do the influencers get in return? / Do we all use visual aids on some levels when watching TV or videos (21:19)? On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Yushun</description></item><item><title>How can ancient Chinese philosophy help address modern global challenges? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750105/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750105/</guid><description>Podcast Description What makes Confucius a good figure to represent China in a dialogue between different civilizations? What good comes from having common ground in values shared by mankind? On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Yushun
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How props matter in film and TV productions | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750106/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Making a successful TV series takes a confluence of factors, including an outstanding cast, a great script, directorial efforts, post-production prowess, and of course, props fitting of the period and the needs of every scene. We take a look at the unsung heroes of TV and movie production, prop masters&amp;rsquo; responsibilities and their role in show biz. / Motivational Monday (19:55)! On the show: Heyang, Ding Heng &amp;amp; Xingyu</description></item><item><title>Hangzhou hosts largest-ever Asian Games | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750107/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750107/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 19th Asian Games are in full swing in the city of Hangzhou, China. What are some of the highlights of the Asian Games so far and exciting matches and spectacles to look forward to? On the show: Heyang, Ding Heng &amp;amp; Xingyu
Transcript</description></item><item><title>China embraces Farmers' Harvest Festival | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750108/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750108/</guid><description>Podcast Description September 23 marks China&amp;rsquo;s sixth Farmers&amp;rsquo; Harvest Festival, a time to celebrate farmers&amp;rsquo; hard work and shed light on agriculture. In 2019, China joined forces with the United Nations&amp;rsquo; Food and Agriculture Organization (FAO) on a project focused on enhancing agricultural industry development in 16 impoverished Chinese villages. Four years later, we discuss the successful results from this endeavor and more. On the show: Heyang, Li Yi &amp;amp; Dong Le, program officer from FAO&amp;rsquo;s China Office</description></item><item><title>World Alzheimer's Day: Never too early, never too late | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750109/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750109/</guid><description>Podcast Description September 21 marks World Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s Day. This year&amp;rsquo;s theme, &amp;ldquo;Never too early, never too late,&amp;rdquo; aims to underscore the role of identifying risk factors and adopting proactive risk reduction measures to delay and potentially prevent the onset of dementia. On the show: Heyang, Xingyu &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Round Table presents 'Radio Documentary: Aging in China: Living with Alzheimer's' | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750110/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750110/</guid><description>Podcast Description We present a CGTN Radio documentary dedicated to this World Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s Day, called, Aging in China: Living with Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Golden Panda Awards - RT's Choice ep5 | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750111/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 05:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750111/</guid><description>Podcast Description The first Golden Panda Awards is being held in the southwestern Chinese city of Chengdu on Sep. 19-20. It showcases top-notch films, TV programs, documentaries and animations by participants from around the world. In our special series, we introduce some great contents featured at this year&amp;rsquo;s event. For this episode, we present to you the Chinese amination Yao-Chinese Folktales and the documentary Miss Holocaust Survivor. On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Ding Heng</description></item><item><title>Chinese museums say "No" to private guides | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750112/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750112/</guid><description>Podcast Description It is not uncommon for tour guides to bring up or even invent fun anecdotal stories to entertain their tour groups. But the National Museum of China says this is not permissible on its premise. Is there a reason why it is being so strict? On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Ding Heng
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What kind of driving school and instructor do we want? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750113/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Car ownership and driving have become commonplace across Chinese cities. Many young people choose to learn to drive and take their driver&amp;rsquo;s test over the summer holiday. However, the training part is not always pleasant. Let&amp;rsquo;s listen to some complains in this regard. On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Ding Heng
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Golden Panda Awards - RT's Choice ep4 | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750114/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 05:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750114/</guid><description>Podcast Description The first Golden Panda Awards is being held in the southwestern Chinese city of Chengdu on Sep. 19-20. It showcases top-notch films, TV programs, documentaries and animations by participants from around the world. In our special series, we introduce great contents featured at this year&amp;rsquo;s event. For this episode, we present to you the Chinese archaeological documentary Sanxingdui: Rediscovering a Lost Civilization and the British TV Series All Creatures Great and Small.</description></item><item><title>"Back street" businesses near universities have seen better days… | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750115/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Businesses selling food, booze and books tucked away in the back streets of university campuses rake in big bucks. Year after year, new students come in and bring with them high demand for just such services, normally. Things are looking a bit shaky this time around. A fair number of business owners have experienced a dip in foot traffic. What&amp;rsquo;s behind this change? On the show: Heyang, Li Yi &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill</description></item><item><title>Preserving the Great Wall of China | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750116/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750116/</guid><description>Podcast Description We take a look at the complex endeavor of preserving the Great Wall of China. What challenges await the mission to safeguard this historical wonder? And how might we enhance our efforts to protect its invaluable legacy (21:53)? / Pu&amp;rsquo;er&amp;rsquo;s Old Tea Forests join world heritage ranks. On the show: Heyang, Li Yi &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Golden Panda Awards - RT's Choice ep3 | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750117/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 05:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750117/</guid><description>Podcast Description The first Golden Panda Awards is held in the southwestern Chinese city of Chengdu on Sep. 19-20. It showcases top-notch films, TV programs, documentaries and animations by participants from around the world. In our special series, we introduce some great content featured at this year&amp;rsquo;s event. For this episode, we present to you the Chinese drama film The Shadowless Tower and the American animation Hotel Transylvania 4. On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Yushun</description></item><item><title>Why would university professors serve as primary school vice principals? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750118/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750118/</guid><description>Podcast Description In central China&amp;rsquo;s Anhui province, some professors from universities have been appointed vice principals of primary schools. What can they bring to kids just starting their academic life? On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Yushun
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The journey of lost relics returning home | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750119/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750119/</guid><description>Podcast Description A short fiction series about artifacts escaping the British Museum has gone viral, as countries around the world call on the London institution to repatriate items from other countries. On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Yushun
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Golden Panda Awards - RT's Choice ep2 | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750120/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 05:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750120/</guid><description>Podcast Description The first Golden Panda Awards is held in the southwestern Chinese city of Chengdu on Sep. 19-20. It showcases top-notch films, TV programs, documentaries and animations by participants from around the world. In our special series, we introduce some great content featured at this year&amp;rsquo;s event. For this episode, we present to you the Chinese historical drama A Dream of Splendor and Jojo Rabbit, a 2019 comedy-drama film. On the show: Laiming, Xingyu &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill</description></item><item><title>Should games detach from reality in an effort to become entertaining? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750121/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750121/</guid><description>Podcast Description A simulation game captures the harsh side of the lives of Ph.D. students. Is the game being unreasonably pessimistic? Or does it really shed some light on the lives of Ph.D. students? On the show: Laiming, Xingyu &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Inland seafood" gains in popularity in China | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750122/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Aquatic products from Xinjiang Autonomous Region has definitely taken people by surprise and curiosity abounds. Will seafood from inland aquatic farms carve up a big share of the market just at a time when treated radioactive wastewater from Japan&amp;rsquo;s Fukushima nuclear plant deals a blow to the fishing industry in the pacific? On the show: Laiming, Xingyu &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Golden Panda Awards - RT's Choice ep1 | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750123/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 05:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750123/</guid><description>Podcast Description The first Golden Panda Awards is held in the southwestern Chinese city of Chengdu on Sep. 19-20. It showcases top-notch films, TV programs, documentaries and animations by participants from around the world. In our special series, we introduce some great content featured at this year&amp;rsquo;s event. For this episode, we present to you the Chinese TV Series A Lifelong Journey and the American TV Series 1923. On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill</description></item><item><title>Shanghai introduces sugary beverage labelling system | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750124/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750124/</guid><description>Podcast Description To raise awareness of the health implications (or the unhealthy impact) of sugary drinks, a pilot program has been launched in Shanghai to label the sugar content in beverages. Is sugar consumption that much of a problem now and will this program achieve its goals? On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>China encourages reemployment of retired teachers | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750125/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750125/</guid><description>Podcast Description China seeks to encourage more retired teachers to come back to the classrooms. What is the purpose of this move and who will benefit? On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chinese version of TikTok takes actions on its anxiety-mongering content | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750126/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750126/</guid><description>Podcast Description China&amp;rsquo;s version of TikTok is now trying to address the rampant anxiety-mongering content on its platform. Will it help make school life just a little easier (22:39)? / A &amp;ldquo;silent&amp;rdquo; café changes the lives of hearing-impaired bakers in Beijing. On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Steve Hatherly
Transcript</description></item><item><title>China's new rule on generative AI has taken effect | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750127/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750127/</guid><description>Podcast Description China has become one of the first countries to respond to the rise of generative artificial intelligence. With the introduction of a set of interim guidelines, the country hopes to install safety belts to ensure relevant businesses make headways on the right track. What does the regulation entail and what impact will it have on the industry? On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Steve Hatherly
Transcript</description></item><item><title>'When will my husband start picking up trash?' | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750128/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750128/</guid><description>Podcast Description When your husband or wife doesn&amp;rsquo;t clean up their own messes, you probably feel like a housekeeper, an unpaid one at that! You&amp;rsquo;re not alone! How can we inspire our partner to start helping a bit around the house (21:40)? / Buffets are back in the US, and better than ever. On the show: Heyang, Ding Heng &amp;amp; Li Yi
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Can a college degree help domestic workers battle social stigma? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750129/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750129/</guid><description>Podcast Description We can probably agree that domestic workers such as housekeepers and nannies don&amp;rsquo;t receive as much of the social recognition they deserve. We discuss how to squash the undeserving stigma in domestic work. Will a college degree help? On the show: Heyang, Ding Heng &amp;amp; Li Yi
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How will AI change radio and broadcast? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750130/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Generative AI that can generate new text, image and video with a simple line of instruction also known as prompt, has taken the Internet by storm since the later part of last year. What&amp;rsquo;s next in AI? How will it change radio and broadcast? In answering these questions and exploring further into the subject at this Radiodays Asia international conference on September 6, Heyang joined a panel of guest speakers Abe Thomas, Aaron Pinto &amp;amp; Paul Kaye, moderated by Francis Currie.</description></item><item><title>Round Table wins "Radio Podcast of the Year"! | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750131/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750131/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are back from Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia, where this year&amp;rsquo;s Radiodays Asia international conference took place. And guess what! RoundTable won &amp;ldquo;Radio Podcast of the Year&amp;rdquo; at the Asian Podcast Awards! Heyang, Laiming and Niu Honglin share their thoughts on the event, the latest development of AI in the media field, the importance of international exchange, and some Malaysian delights! On the show: Heyang, Laiming &amp;amp; Niu Honglin</description></item><item><title>RT's Inner Mongolia Special ep3: Pushing the boundaries of clean energy (classic) | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750132/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Note: This episode originally aired on July 28, 2023
Ulanqab is many things. It is nicknamed China&amp;rsquo;s yoghurt capital, potato capital and wind energy capital. The region&amp;rsquo;s abundant solar and wind energy resources have encouraged development in the new energy sector. Round Table shares first-hand observation from the team&amp;rsquo;s trip to a solar power plant, a wind turbine manufacturer and a research base on energy storage. Hopefully, this can shed some light on the state of development in China&amp;rsquo;s pursuit of clean energy and carbon neutrality.</description></item><item><title>What does urban resilience mean? (classic)​ | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750133/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Note: This episode originally aired on July 12, 2023
Global temperatures in early July this year were the highest ever recorded for this time of the year. More &amp;ldquo;hottest days ever&amp;rdquo; are coming. We take a look at how cities cope with climate change and other environmental challenges. On the show: Heyang, Yushun &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Decode the digitalization of Dunhuang | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750134/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750134/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 6th Silk Road Intl. Cultural Expo is held in the enchanting city of Dunhuang. Among the many highlights is relic digitalization. Why is it important? What are the latest applications? How are technologies enhancing the protection and restoration of our precious cultural heritage? On the show: Niu Honglin Yushun &amp;amp; Zhao Chenchen
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to cope with climate anxiety? (classic) | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750135/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Note: This episode originally aired on August 17, 2023
It&amp;rsquo;s hard not to feel stressed and helpless when we are bombarded with news of extreme weather conditions and disasters around the world. We also need to face the evidence that what we’ve been witnessing are real consequences of climate change. What can we do to deal with the stress and anxiety? / Heart to Heart - please send your audio questions to ezfmroundtable@foxmail.</description></item><item><title>CIFTIS: Embracing a digital future | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750136/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750136/</guid><description>Podcast Description We continue our exploration in the vibrant world of CIFTIS. In our last episode, we delved into an exhibitor&amp;rsquo;s perspective, but today, it&amp;rsquo;s about you - the real audience. Not only will we give you a glimpse into the fair&amp;rsquo;s trends but we&amp;rsquo;ll also discuss how they&amp;rsquo;re reshaping our daily lives. On the show: Niu Honglin, Xingyu &amp;amp; Dou Hongyu
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Worst NYC air pollution on record &amp; Parts of the world endure hottest summer ever (classic) | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750137/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Note: This episode originally aired on June 13, 2023
The wildfire smoke shrouding New York City has made taking a breather more challenging, as the air quality in the city hits an all-time low. Parts of the world, including a dozen of Chinese cities, are bracing for another searing summer, with temperatures already at unprecedented levels. We take a look at abnormal weather conditions that humanity has to face.</description></item><item><title>CIFTIS: Opening up to a wider world | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750138/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750138/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we transport you to the current hotspot in Beijing, the 2023 China International Fair for Trade in Services, also known as CIFTIS. This annual event is not just a trade show but also a window into the future of services, technology, and innovation. On the show: Niu Honglin, Xingyu &amp;amp; Yawen
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Should kids be welcomed in fancy restaurants? (classic) | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750139/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Note: This episode originally aired on July 3, 2023
Recently, a fine dining restaurant in Beijing has stopped serving children under the age of 12. The move has reignited a longstanding debate about children in restaurants. Should kids be welcomed in fancy restaurants? / Motivational Monday (21:01)! On the show: Heyang, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Pearl
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Shanghai adopts new electricity pricing scheme to save energy (classic) | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750140/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Note: This episode originally aired on July 3, 2023
In an effort to secure electricity availability for Shanghai residents, local governments have churned out new policies and measures for another very hot summer, including subsidies for off-peak usage and virtual power plants, to name a few. We take a look at effective measures aimed at better managing soaring power consumption in China. On the show: Heyang, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Pearl</description></item><item><title>Are class reunions worth it? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750141/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750141/</guid><description>Podcast Description High school reunions offer a great way to reconnect with old friends and classmates. But they can kick up some unhappy memories, or become a competition game you never signed up for. Is it worth going? / Round Table&amp;rsquo;s Happy Place (20:21)! On the show: Heyang, Yushun &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Obsessed about being in control, over everything? Learn the power of letting go | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750142/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Being in control of your life sounds like a positive thing, but too much of a need for being in control can lead to heightened stress, reduced flexibility (and not to mention strained relationships). We discuss the idea of letting go of control, at least some, and maybe that’ll free up some headspace. On the show: Heyang, Yushun &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Young people find love through job recruitment apps | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750143/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Some people find it easy to fall in love. Others&amp;hellip; not so much. Maybe they’ve been looking in the wrong places. Could job-seeking apps be the way to go, finding employment and romance at the same time? / Heart to Heart - please send your audio questions to ezfmroundtable@foxmail.com (20:44)! On the show: Heyang, Xingyu &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Summer movie market soars | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750144/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750144/</guid><description>Podcast Description Moviegoing has made a mega-comeback this summer! Viewers have been embracing a diverse slate of films with domestically made movies leading in box office performance! What brought audiences back into the red velvet seats? On the show: Heyang, Xingyu &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is tipping out of control in North America? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750145/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750145/</guid><description>Podcast Description To tip or not to tip, and how much to tip, that is something one needs to find out when visiting a foreign country. And if you happen to be paying a visit to North America, the answers might not be so straightforward anymore? Do self-checkout machines deserve a tip too? / What have you stopped buying after 35 (18:51)? On the show: Heyang, Gao Junya &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill</description></item><item><title>Big move for biodiversity conservation | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750146/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Biodiversity is the foundation for human life as well as for mother nature. From conservation projects to innovative policies, what has China been doing to preserve biodiversity? On the show: Heyang, Gao Junya &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why have teambuilding events become such a dread? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750147/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teambuilding is supposed to be about strengthening bonds and encouraging cooperation. But why do most employees consider it a dread? / Capybaras are taking over social media, and we&amp;rsquo;re the better because of it (21:45)! On the show: Heyang, Ding Heng &amp;amp; Pearl
Transcript</description></item><item><title>An obesity map of China | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750148/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750148/</guid><description>Podcast Description We start off today&amp;rsquo;s show with a map, a China Obesity Atlas. This map offers a province-by-province look at adult obesity rates in China. Which region in China has the highest occurrence of obesity? On the show: Heyang, Ding Heng &amp;amp; Pearl
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Art museums stand at crossroads | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750149/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Museums and exhibitions are experiencing a period of strong growth in China. But excessive crowds are also posing a challenge to management. Is this surge in museum craze sustainable? (20:51) / Motivational Monday! On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Li Yi
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chinese lab builds bridges for human connection with nature | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750150/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750150/</guid><description>Podcast Description As societies in China and around the world continue to urbanize, our exposure to nature diminishes and this may lead to consequences both immediate and long-term. Education about nature is a means to bridge the gap and efforts along this line are being made cross cultures. Today we look at some typical examples in nature education. On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Li Yi
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Listening to the ocean… | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750151/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Round Table’s Happy Place! (1:42) / The oceans are teeming with wildlife and mystery. To plumb its depths is to discover a world filled with creatures and activities beyond our imagination. It&amp;rsquo;s no wonder that scientists have been studying the oceans for decades. They have also been collecting the sounds of the sea. (11:54) On the show: Heyang, Xingyu and Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Timeless Traditions: “Guofeng” Music | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750152/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750152/</guid><description>Podcast Description We invite you to ride with us the waves of &amp;ldquo;Guochao&amp;rdquo; and enjoy the contemporary reinterpretations of China’s timeless traditions! We bring you the final installment of this special series, in which we zero in on the growing trend of “guofeng music”. This is where contemporary tunes are being integrated into traditional Chinese music. On the show: Heyang, Xingyu and Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Do we need a workplace persona? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750153/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750153/</guid><description>Podcast Description The word “persona”, or “人设” in Chinese, comes with slightly negative connotations, as it means the conjuring up of a certain image. Is it really useful though, especially in the workplace? (00:59) / Heart to heart. (19:00) On the show: Heyang, Li Yi and Josh Cotterill Transcript</description></item><item><title>Timeless Traditions - Chinese Fashion Trends | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750154/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750154/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the latest installment of our special series &amp;ldquo;Timeless Traditions: Riding the Waves of Guochao&amp;rdquo;, we take a look at how Chinese traditional elements coalesce beautifully with trendy renditions. Chinese fashion is in! What are the biggest trends? On the show: Heyang, Li Yi and Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Timeless Traditions: "Guochao" Cosmetic and Beauty | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750155/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750155/</guid><description>Podcast Description We invite you to ride with us the waves of &amp;ldquo;Guochao&amp;rdquo;, and enjoy the contemporary reinterpretation of China&amp;rsquo;s timeless traditions! Traditional beauty aesthetics has found resonance among the younger generation of Gen Z. On the show: Heyang, Li Yi &amp;amp; Brandon Yates
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Has the online fitness industry passed its peak? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750156/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750156/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s not in the distant past when global interest gravitated towards home workouts during the pandemic lockdowns. However, as we reemerge into gyms, dance studios, and outdoor cycling groups, can the online fitness industry maintain its relevance? On the show: Heyang, Li Yi &amp;amp; Brandon Yates
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Timeless Traditions: Riding the Waves of "Guochao" - Chinese ACG | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750157/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750157/</guid><description>Podcast Description We invite you to ride with us the waves of &amp;ldquo;Guochao&amp;rdquo; and enjoy the contemporary reinterpretation of China&amp;rsquo;s timeless traditions! Chinese ACG, anime, comic and game, has become a tour de force, home and abroad. We trace the rise of Chinese ACG! / Cool Robots at World Robot Expo (24:57) On the show: Heyang, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Pearl
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Romance on Chinese Valentine's Day | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750158/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750158/</guid><description>Podcast Description August 22nd marks this year&amp;rsquo;s Qixi Festival, also known as the traditional Chinese Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day. Love is in the air. We only need to be reminded of it now and then. On the show: Heyang, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Pearl
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Timeless Traditions: Riding the Waves of "Guochao" - Food and drinks! | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750159/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chinese traditional culinary culture has become a new growth engine in China&amp;rsquo;s market for food and beverages. There are tremendous businesses opportunities in tastes that probably would have shocked and puzzled our ancestors. What led to the changes in the marketing landscape? / Motivational Monday (21:25)! On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Yang Guang
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Young Chinese tap into elderly care market | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750160/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750160/</guid><description>Podcast Description An increasing number of young people are joining the senior care industry. What can they bring to the industry? On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Yang Guang
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Local coffee brands rise in domestic market | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750161/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750161/</guid><description>Podcast Description China&amp;rsquo;s coffee market is red hot, with a homegrown brand eclipsing the influence of international coffee juggernauts for the first time. What did it get right? / Round Table&amp;rsquo;s Happy Place (17:46)! On the show: Heyang, Yushun &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Saver vs. Spender. How to strike a balance? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750162/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750162/</guid><description>Podcast Description When it comes to personal finance, are you a big saver or spender? What factors shape our spending habits? On the show: Heyang, Yushun &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to cope with climate anxiety? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750163/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750163/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s hard not to feel stressed and helpless when we are bombarded with news reports of extreme weather conditions and disasters around the world. We also need to face the evidence that what we’ve been witnessing are real consequences of climate change. What can we do to deal with the stress and anxiety? / Heart to Heart - please send your audio questions to ezfmroundtable@foxmail.com (20:44)! On the show: Laiming, Li Yi &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill</description></item><item><title>Local chronicles - the tale of a city | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750164/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750164/</guid><description>Podcast Description Local chronicles make up an important part of Chinese cultural heritage. The oldest of such documents date back to about 2,000 years and this ancient form of literature and history still provide good values for education and governance purposes in the modern time. Today on Round Table, we discover the modern relevance of local chronicles. On the show: Laiming, Li Yi &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why does livestream shopping have high return rates? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750165/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Livestream shopping has taken e-commerce by storm in China in recent years. However, its high rate of returns for purchases reveals a different aspect of livestream shopping. / Heart to Heart - please send your audio questions to ezfmroundtable@foxmail.com (21:44)! On the show: Heyang, Xingyu &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>UNESCO advocates global ban on smartphones in schools | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750166/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750166/</guid><description>Podcast Description With smartphones now such a pervasive part of our lives, we have been following how technology has been transforming the world of education. Now UNESCO says smartphones should be banned in schools. Do you agree? On the show: Heyang, Xingyu &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Raptor rescue and birding | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750167/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750167/</guid><description>Podcast Description This August 15 marks China&amp;rsquo;s first National Ecology Day. We discuss the rescue and rehabilitation of raptors, or birds of prey, share birdwatching perks and the balancing of urban space with wildlife. How can we better promote animal welfare and wildlife conservation? Heyang is joined by Ma Chenyue, program manager of International Fund for Animal Welfare (IFAW), and birder Lin Shaowen for this discussion.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>China drafts rule on restricting the use of facial recognition technology | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750168/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750168/</guid><description>Podcast Description China is collecting public opinion on a new rule governing facial recognition technology. If passed, the policy will require individual consent before this technology can be used. / Motivational Monday (21:57)! On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Pearl
Transcript</description></item><item><title>China's installed renewable energy capacity surpasses coal | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750169/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750169/</guid><description>Podcast Description China&amp;rsquo;s installed capacity for renewable energy has surpassed that of coal-fired power plants. How much will this affect our lives and contribute to worldwide efforts against climate change? On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Pearl
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Discounted blind food boxes - a hit with young buyers | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750170/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Discounted blind food boxes have recently become a hit with young buyers across Chinese cities. And these boxes often contain unsold food from bakeries, cafes and restaurants before the end of the day. Is this an effective solution to the problem of food waste? / Did you finish your bottled water at conferences (21:57)/ Round Table&amp;rsquo;s Happy Place! On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Li Yi
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How does protected agriculture impact the way we grow and eat? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750171/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750171/</guid><description>Podcast Description China hopes to tap the potentials of protected agriculture to safeguard food security, encourage spending and investment in rural areas and boost its overall economic competitiveness. Today, we decipher China&amp;rsquo;s formula for agricultural growth in the coming decade. On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Li Yi
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Vibrant night markets gain traction among young Chinese | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750172/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Night markets in China have long been a haven of all-you-can-eat street food. These markets are back all over the country in summer of 2023, injecting vitality to the night economy. What does a night market mean to the locals and tourists alike? / Are &amp;ldquo;photobombs&amp;rdquo; hilarious or offensive (22:38)? On the show: Heyang, Ding Heng &amp;amp; Xingyu
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Changing attitudes toward weddings | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750173/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750173/</guid><description>Podcast Description Most wedding traditions go far back into the past. And in today&amp;rsquo;s world, where things change with incredible speed, young people rewrite the rules on their big day. But in other ways, they can stay surprisingly loyal to some traditions. What wedding traditions do young people favor and what do they dislike the most? On the show: Heyang, Ding Heng &amp;amp; Xingyu
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Will handwritten notes become obsolete? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750174/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750174/</guid><description>Podcast Description What&amp;rsquo;s the best way to take notes? &amp;lsquo;Paper vs. Digital&amp;rsquo; has long been central in the debate. Now an AI power note-taking app is available. Is it time to put away your pen and pencil, for good? / Heart to Heart - please send your audio questions to ezfmroundtable@foxmail.com (16:43)! On the show: Heyang, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Yushun
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The allure of lesser-known Chinese cities | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750175/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750175/</guid><description>Podcast Description While big Chinese cities are often in the limelight, plenty of off-the-radar cities are also worth visiting. These lesser-known cities have successfully grabbed tourists&amp;rsquo; attention this summer. How to leverage a city&amp;rsquo;s unique features and bring in tourist revenue? On the show: Heyang, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Yushun
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What skills are expected of a 5-star tour guide? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750176/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750176/</guid><description>Podcast Description Having a great tour guide can certainly boost one&amp;rsquo;s travel experience and customer satisfaction. But such talents can be hard to come by. During the peak summer travel season, we discuss how tour guides can contribute to tourism development. / Study confirms that having a pet is good for one&amp;rsquo;s health (22:50). On the show: Heyang, Ding Heng &amp;amp; Pearl
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The best from Chengdu World University Games | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750177/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750177/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 31st Summer World University Games are set to close on August 8th in southwest China&amp;rsquo;s Chengdu City, after 12 days of fierce competitions. We take a look at the highlights of this celebration of youth, friendship and sportsmanship. On the show: Heyang, Ding Heng &amp;amp; Pearl
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Young people getting more from traveling | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750178/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750178/</guid><description>Podcast Description Summer vacation has inspired a new round of growth for tourism in China. Besides the much-talked about special forces-style travel, which grabbed our attention earlier this year, people are travelling in all kinds of styles this summer. Today we study the latest trends in summertime tourism. / Motivational Monday (21:17)! On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Fei Fei
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The '15-minute life circle' creates new trend of urban life | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750179/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750179/</guid><description>Podcast Description The concept of a 15-minute city is shared in Europe and north America and inspiring new ways of urban planning in China. What would the future of our neighborhoods look like if we model our cities after this line of thinking? On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Fei Fei
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Fresh fruit industry benefits from speedy logistics network | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750180/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Round Table&amp;rsquo;s Happy Place! / With increasing consumer demand for a wide variety of fresh fruits, the volume of fresh produce being moved across China rises every year. However, moving fresh produce on this scale is no mean feat. We take a look at how stakeholders overcome a number of challenges across the value chain in managing this immensely challenging task (13:14). On the show: Heyang, Yushun &amp;amp; Pearl</description></item><item><title>Cruise vacations attract a younger crowd | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750181/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Recent data shows that more young people in China are choosing cruise vacations as their preferred style of travel and leisure. What makes cruising so appealing to younger consumers? Are cruise vacations as perfect as advertised? On the show: Heyang, Yushun &amp;amp; Pearl
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What's so great about Chinese bathhouses? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750182/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750182/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why stay in a hotel when you get more of the experience with less money in a bathhouse with hot springs? We take a look at the hot new trend of bathhouses in China, with a modern twist. / Daytime power naps may help our brains age slower. On the show: Heyang, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Fei Fei
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Anyone can drown, but no one should | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750183/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750183/</guid><description>Podcast Description Drowning is the third leading cause of unintentional injury death worldwide. It could happen to anyone who has access to water. Summer vacation is here at last and it&amp;rsquo;s time for our discussion on how to keep outdoor fun safe. On the show: Heyang, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Fei Fei
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dopamine dressing and Barbiecore | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750184/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750184/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s probably no coincidence that the fashion trend of dopamine dressing has been on the rise after the global pandemic. And now Barbiecore has arrived with its hot pink invasion. So it looks like it&amp;rsquo;s time to ride along this season&amp;rsquo;s bravest trend. Come on. Let&amp;rsquo;s go party. On the show: Heyang, Ding Heng &amp;amp; Pearl
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cool summer getaways | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750185/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750185/</guid><description>Podcast Description We go through some great summer travel ideas with never-ending fun things to do, and you know what&amp;rsquo;s most important, staying cool! Have you planned your summer getaway yet? What are China&amp;rsquo;s most sought-after destinations to escape from the scorching heat? On the show: Heyang, Ding Heng &amp;amp; Pearl
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Student-athletes from across the globe gather in Chengdu | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750186/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750186/</guid><description>Podcast Description The city of Chengdu in southwest China has rolled out the red carpet to welcome young athletes from around the world at the 31st World University Games. We shall look at the myriad of fun things that athletes and observers can do at the event. On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Fei Fei
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Young professional farmers inject new energy into rural revitalization | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750187/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750187/</guid><description>Podcast Description More and more young people choose to start their careers and lives in the rural areas. Being a fulltime farmer is often associated with hard manual labor, high tech, local government support and social network challenges. There is definitely a future for young, educated young folks in agriculture in this new era, but what more can we do to help them succeed? On the show: Laiming, Niu Honglin &amp;amp; Fei Fei</description></item><item><title>Food loss during production and transportation | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750188/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750188/</guid><description>Podcast Description A recent report found that China faces 300 million tons of food loss per year, throughout the production, post-harvest, processing and storage stages. That&amp;rsquo;s all before food even meets the eye of the consumer. Why and how does all the losses take place? How can we stop this huge loss of food (02:13)? / Experts suggest strengthening the anti-addiction system of online gaming (27:39). On the show: Heyang, Ding Heng &amp;amp; Pearl</description></item><item><title>RT's Inner Mongolia Special ep3: Pushing the boundaries of clean energy | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750189/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750189/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ulanqab is many things. It is nicknamed China&amp;rsquo;s yoghurt capital, potato capital and wind energy capital. The region&amp;rsquo;s abundant solar and wind energy resources have encouraged development in the new energy sector. Round Table shares first-hand observation from the team&amp;rsquo;s trip to a solar power plant, a wind turbine manufacturer and a research base on energy storage. Hopefully, this can shed some light on the state of development in China&amp;rsquo;s pursuit of clean energy and carbon neutrality.</description></item><item><title>RT's Inner Mongolia Special ep2: What makes a modern village? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750190/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750190/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Inner Mongolia&amp;rsquo;s villages, Round Table finds examples of initiatives that have boosted incomes and quality of life for farmers. From adopting new farming techniques that increase crop yields and incomes to job creation programs, these efforts are making real differences in people&amp;rsquo;s lives. Stories from these villages illustrate tangible progress in China&amp;rsquo;s rural transformation and provide lessons that can help more communities. On the show: Laiming, Li Yi &amp;amp; Yushun</description></item><item><title>RT's Inner Mongolia Special ep1: Tastes of transformation | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750191/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750191/</guid><description>Podcast Description Round Table is on the move again! This time to Ulanqab of central Inner Mongolia Autonomous Region. From smoked chicken that would satisfy any meat lover to fresh yogurt made from milk of grass-fed cattle, Inner Mongolia is devoted to developing new pillar industries. As we sit down to sample the diverse delicacies, we explore how these emerging food businesses contribute to the preservation and promotion of Inner Mongolia&amp;rsquo;s culinary heritage while carving out new economic opportunities for locals.</description></item><item><title>Robotaxi rides in major Chinese cities | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750192/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750192/</guid><description>Podcast Description China has pushed itself to the forefront of the self-driving industry. Now the capital city has given some companies the go-ahead for allowing driverless taxis on the road. How does the public feel about getting into a robotaxi (02:01))? / Are gaps in employment bad (27:59)? / Making public toilets better by setting up a national standard (47:23). On the show: Heyang, Guo Yan &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Can one's personality be defined by a test? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750193/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750193/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;Are you an &amp;lsquo;i-person&amp;rsquo; or an &amp;rsquo;e-person&amp;rsquo;?&amp;rdquo; This has become a popular ice breaker for many young people making friends these days. It stems from the popularity of MBTI personality tests. We take a stab at explaining the mysterious popularity of (possibly meaningless) personality assessment tests (01:54). / Putting your phone in silent mode does NOT reduce phone use (27:23). / Motivational Monday (50:05)! On the show: Heyang, Li Yi &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill</description></item><item><title>Online medical services see rapid development in China | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750194/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750194/</guid><description>Podcast Description The pandemic juiced the growth of online medical services, and a slew of companies have ramped up their resources in spearheading the telemedicine area. We take a pulse check on the rapidly developing sector of online medical services (01:53). / Breathing new life into old trees (29:25) / Youth hostels reject customers above the age of 35 (48:29)? On the show: Heyang, Ding Heng &amp;amp; Pearl
Transcript</description></item><item><title>E-commerce for agriculture going big | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750195/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750195/</guid><description>Podcast Description We take a look at the advantages and challenges that a farm, food or agriculture business faces when selling through e-commerce. How does e-commerce reshape the way we grow, sell and consume food (01:41)? / Are you embarrassed to look attractive (27:42)? / Motivational Monday (49:54)! On the show: Heyang, Fei Fei &amp;amp; Pearl
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Discover the charm of city walks | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750196/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750196/</guid><description>Podcast Description Taking walks around the city has become the latest popular leisure and travel activity among young people in China. Related threads on social media platforms have garnered hundreds of millions of views. What&amp;rsquo;s the charm in taking walks around the city (01:39)? / What is antagonistic personality? How shall we deal with it (27:16)? On the show: Heyang, Yushun &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>AI robots rise to the challenge of eldercare | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750197/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750197/</guid><description>Podcast Description As China&amp;rsquo;s population ages rapidly, the country faces a severe shortage of health and social care workers. Now, can we bet on platoons of AI-enabled robots to bridge the gap (01:45)? / More people embrace the healing power of trees (27:09). / Heart to Heart - please send your audio questions to ezfmroundtable@foxmail.com (42:28)! On the show: Heyang, Li Yi &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What is urban resilience? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750198/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750198/</guid><description>Podcast Description Global temperatures in early July were the highest ever recorded for this time of the year. More &amp;ldquo;hottest days ever&amp;rdquo; are coming. We take a look at how cities cope with climate change and other environmental challenges (02:38). / Is pizza losing its appeal among Chinese consumers (27:29)? On the show: Heyang, Yushun &amp;amp; Josh Cotterill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>China steps up in building a barrier-free living environment | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750199/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750199/</guid><description>Podcast Description The living environment we all share should be fully accessible and usable for everyone, including people living with disabilities. A new law puts this goal front and center (01:00). / Lifelike robot babies give students a taste of parenthood (26:17). / Why are fewer people wearing sandals in summer (46:09)? On the show: Heyang, Ding Heng &amp;amp; Pearl.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to better address domestic violence? | Round Table China</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8250750200/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8250750200/</guid><description>Podcast Description China&amp;rsquo;s top court has disclosed details on ten typical domestic violence cases. Will these examples be able to deter the violent members of the society and provide reference to regional courts across the country (01:48)? / Chinese cities ramp up efforts on child-friendly urban planning (27:05). / Motivational Monday (48:05)! On the show: Laiming, Fei Fei &amp;amp; Niu Honglin
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>