<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cancelled with Tana Mongeau on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/cancelled-with-tana-mongeau/</link><description>Recent content in Cancelled with Tana Mongeau on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/cancelled-with-tana-mongeau/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>OUR EMBARRASSING DRUNK NIGHT AT THE VMAS - Ep. 65 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630067/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630067/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of the Cancelled Podcast we are joined by the lovely Trevi Moran. We reminisce on the time we went to the VMA’s and open up about addiction.
Control Body Odor ANYWHERE with @lumedeodorant and get $5 off off your Starter Pack (that’s over 40% off) with promo code CANCELLED at https://LumeDeodorant.com! #lumepod
Download the DraftKings Casino app NOW and sign up with promo code CANCELLED and play FIVE DOLLARS to get ONE HUNDRED DOLLARS IN CASINO CREDITS!</description></item><item><title>HOW TANA LOST HER TOOTH IN HAWAII - Ep. 64 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630001/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630001/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of Cancelled Tana loses a tooth and Brooke goes off on Matt Rife.
Use code TANA for $20 off your first SeatGeek order. https://seatgeek.onelink.me/RrnK/TANA
Tana Mongeau Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/tanamongeau/ Tana Mongeau Twitter: https://twitter.com/tanamongeau Tana Mongeau TikTok: https://www.tiktok.com/@tanamongeaulol
Brooke Schofield Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/brookeschofield/ Brooke Schofield Twitter: https://twitter.com/BroookeAmber Brooke Schofield TikTok: https://www.tiktok.com/@brookeschofield1 Brooke Schofield YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCzCVovj7tfqnV2lIkaVk35A
To listen to the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.ly/CancelledYouTube
Don’t forget to subscribe to the podcast for free wherever you&amp;rsquo;re listening or by using this link: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>Matt Rife is CANCELLED… again - Ep. 63 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630002/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630002/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of the Cancelled podcast it&amp;rsquo;s all about that bass, we are joined by the lovely Meghan Trainor and Chris Olsen. We cover a range of topics from motherhood, to love lives, to meeting Kris Jenner and releasing her upcoming song with Jimmy Fallon. Get 20% Off and Free Shipping with the code TANA at https://Manscaped.com Download the DraftKings Casino app NOW and use code CANCELLED. New players can deposit FIVE DOLLARS or more and get a match of UP TO FIVE HUNDRED DOLLARS IN CASINO CREDITS.</description></item><item><title>Meghan Trainor Opens Up: Kris Jenner, Jimmy Fallon, and the Cancellation Saga - Ep.62 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630003/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630003/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of the Cancelled podcast it&amp;rsquo;s all about that bass, we are joined by the lovely Meghan Trainor and Chris Olsen. We cover a range of topics from motherhood, to love lives, to meeting Kris Jenner and releasing her upcoming song with Jimmy Fallon. Download the DraftKings Casino app NOW and use code CANCELLED. New players can deposit FIVE DOLLARS or more and get a match of UP TO FIVE HUNDRED DOLLARS IN CASINO CREDITS.</description></item><item><title>Tana Found Love in Hawaii - Ep. 61 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630004/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630004/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of the Cancelled podcast Tana recaps her trip to Hawaii, where she finds the love of her life. Brook tells us her blackout experience with Brianna Chickenfry.
Control Body Odor ANYWHERE with @lumedeodorant and get $5 off off your Starter Pack (that’s over 40% off) with promo code CANCELLED at https://www.lumedeodorant.com! #lumepod
USE MY CODE TANA FOR $20 OFF TICKETS AT SEATGEEK. THAT’S $20 OFF YOUR FIRST PURCHASE WITH PROMO CODE TANA.</description></item><item><title>Unpacking Trauma, Death, and Childhoods - Ep.60 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630005/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630005/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of Cancelled we discuss Sam and Colby which brings up childhood trauma and friends that passed away. https://adamandeve.com Order is 50% off almost any item + FREE SHIPPING + RUSH PROCESSING Code is TANA Tana Mongeau Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/tanamongeau/ Tana Mongeau Twitter: https://twitter.com/tanamongeau Tana Mongeau TikTok: https://www.tiktok.com/@tanamongeaulol
Brooke Schofield Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/brookeschofield/ Brooke Schofield Twitter: https://twitter.com/BroookeAmber Brooke Schofield TikTok: https://www.tiktok.com/@brookeschofield1 Brooke Schofield YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCzCVovj7tfqnV2lIkaVk35A
To listen to the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>TANA AND BROOKE ARE FIGHTING OVER THE SAME GUY - Ep. 59 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630006/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630006/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of Cancelled the girls recap halloween week and Tana&amp;rsquo;s party. They touch up on mental health and being over the influencer / LA scene. They end the episode off covering current events in the media.
Control Body Odor ANYWHERE with @lumedeodorant and get $5 off off your Starter Pack (that’s over 40% off) with promo code CANCELLED at https://lumepodcast.com! #lumepod Tana Mongeau Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/tanamongeau/ Tana Mongeau Twitter: https://twitter.</description></item><item><title>TANA GOT CHEATED ON AND STARTED HER VILLAIN ORIGIN STORY - Ep. 58 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630007/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 18:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630007/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of Cancelled we discuss sobriety and dating preferences, acknowledging the benefits of a sober lifestyle but expressing concerns about compatibility. We discuss getting cheated on, Trisha Paytas, and our overall tour experience.
Download the DraftKings Casino app NOW, sign up with promo code CANCELLED, and new customers get a deposit match up to ONE HUNDRED DOLLARS in casino credits when you deposit $5 or more! Only on DraftKings Casino with promo code CANCELLED.</description></item><item><title>Surprising Brooke with Josh Peck - Ep. 57 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630008/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630008/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of Cancelled, Tana surprises Brooke with Josh Peck. They talk about being a child star and Josh’s role in the blockbuster Oppenheimer. Follow Josh on Insta: @shuapeck or on Twitter: @ItsJoshPeck Tana Mongeau Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/tanamongeau/ Tana Mongeau Twitter: https://twitter.com/tanamongeau Tana Mongeau TikTok: https://www.tiktok.com/@tanamongeaulol
Brooke Schofield Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/brookeschofield/ Brooke Schofield Twitter: https://twitter.com/BroookeAmber Brooke Schofield TikTok: https://www.tiktok.com/@brookeschofield1 Brooke Schofield YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCzCVovj7tfqnV2lIkaVk35A
To listen to the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>Brooke's New Man is Homeless? - Ep.56 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630009/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630009/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this Episode of Cancelled Tana and Brooke talk about, finishing their Live Tour, NFL Boys, and Crazy Plastic Surgery. Control Body Odor ANYWHERE with @lumedeodorant and get $5 off off your Starter Pack (that’s over 40% off) with promo code CANCELLED at https://lumepodcast.com! #lumepod Adam and Eve is offering 50% off just about any item! Plus FREE SHIPPING which includes RUSH PROCESSING! htttps://Adamandeve.com Code is TANA Tana Mongeau Instagram: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Tana’s Hinge date is harassing her (VOICE MEMOS) - Ep. 55 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630010/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630010/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of Cancelled Tana and Brooke go over icks, their dating life and apologize to Trisha Paytas for Jojo Siwa comments.
Tana Mongeau Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/tanamongeau/ Tana Mongeau Twitter: https://twitter.com/tanamongeau Tana Mongeau TikTok: https://www.tiktok.com/@tanamongeaulol
Brooke Schofield Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/brookeschofield/ Brooke Schofield Twitter: https://twitter.com/BroookeAmber Brooke Schofield TikTok: https://www.tiktok.com/@brookeschofield1 Brooke Schofield YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCzCVovj7tfqnV2lIkaVk35A
To listen to the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.ly/CancelledYouTube
Don’t forget to subscribe to the podcast for free wherever you&amp;rsquo;re listening or by using this link: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>THIS FIGHT ALMOST ENDED OUR FRIENDSHIP - Ep. 54 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630011/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630011/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of Cancelled Tana and Brooke talk about a fight that happened on tour that almost ended their friendship. They touch on their dating life, wanting to move to New York and dealing with stalkers.
Control Body Odor ANYWHERE with @lumedeodorant and get $5 off off your Starter Pack (that’s over 40% off) with promo code CANCELLED at https://lumepodcast.com! #lumepod
Tana Mongeau Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/tanamongeau/ Tana Mongeau Twitter: https://twitter.</description></item><item><title>Jojo Siwa’s WILD interaction with Miley Cyrus, How much money she makes, and more! - Ep.53 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630012/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 23:28:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630012/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of Cancelled we are joined by the multi talented Jojo Siwa. We discuss how much money she makes, coming out, meeting Miley Cyrus and Elton John and much more! Tana Mongeau Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/tanamongeau/ Tana Mongeau Twitter: https://twitter.com/tanamongeau Tana Mongeau TikTok: https://www.tiktok.com/@tanamongeaulol
Brooke Schofield Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/brookeschofield/ Brooke Schofield Twitter: https://twitter.com/BroookeAmber Brooke Schofield TikTok: https://www.tiktok.com/@brookeschofield1 Brooke Schofield YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCzCVovj7tfqnV2lIkaVk35A Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description></item><item><title>Tana’s EMBARRASSING interaction with her gamer crush… - Ep. 52 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630013/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630013/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of the Cancelled, we discuss our experiences at the Streamys and the frenzy surrounding our previous episodes. We talk about the excitement of having Trisha on the show and the frustrations Tana has to face when people mistake her for being drunk. Brooke shares a coincidence with a guy she saw at a park and later matched with on Hinge. We discuss the role of PR teams and our experiences at the gym.</description></item><item><title>First Annual Cancelled Awards - Ep. 51 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630014/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630014/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of Cancelled&amp;hellip;In honor of the Streamy&amp;rsquo;s being last week Tana and Brooke go down the ranks and award the best and worst from in relation to the Cancelledsphere of people.
https://Adamandeve.com Order is 50% off almost any item + FREE SHIPPING + RUSH PROCESSING Code is TANA
Go to https://ShipStation.com and use code CANCELLED today and sign up for your FREE 60-day trial.
Tana Mongeau Instagram: https://www.</description></item><item><title>The TRISHA PAYTAS Episode - Ep. 50 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 17:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630015/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of Cancelled we are joined the the queen her self, Trisha Paytas. We talk about the YouTubeshpere of creators from our pasts, PR stunts, and find out how much money Trisha has spent making videos. As a special offer for listeners, new customers GET $5 OFF a Lume Starter Pack with code CANCELLED at https://LumeDeodorant.com. That equates to over 40% off your Starter Pack when you visit https://LumeDeodorant.</description></item><item><title>Tana and Bryce Hall are NOT FRIENDS - Ep. 49 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630016/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of Cancelled Tana and Brooke discuss Bryce Hall, Dillon Danis, a jealous date, and everything that went down on tour. Go to https://ShipStation.com and use code CANCELLED today and sign up for your FREE 60-day trial. Tana Mongeau Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/tanamongeau/ Tana Mongeau Twitter: https://twitter.com/tanamongeau Tana Mongeau TikTok: https://www.tiktok.com/@tanamongeaulol
Brooke Schofield Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/brookeschofield/ Brooke Schofield Twitter: https://twitter.com/BroookeAmber Brooke Schofield TikTok: https://www.tiktok.com/@brookeschofield1 Brooke Schofield YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCzCVovj7tfqnV2lIkaVk35A Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Confronting Trevor Wallace for dating BOTH of us - Ep.48 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630017/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 00:14:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630017/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of Cancelled we are joined by Trevor Wallace. Tana tells us a juicy hook up story while traveling abroad. Trevor gets confronted about his clip on Howie Mandel’s podcast where he discussed him and Tana seeing each other. Trevor confronts Brooke about going on a date with him after another date that day. This episode is full of laughs and advice about what to do on tour.</description></item><item><title>Tana’s Apology to KSI - Ep.47 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630018/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630018/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of Cancelled we are joined by Mike Majlak and Jeff Wittek, we discuss Logan and Jake Paul’s argument on Impaulsive, Tana confronts Mike about enabling her to scam KSI and the Sidemen, Tana apologizes to KSI and can Aliens become lovers? Get a 60-day free trial at https://www.shipstation.com/cancelled Thanks to ShipStation for sponsoring the show! As a special offer for listeners, new customers GET $5 OFF a Lume Starter Pack!</description></item><item><title>Tana got in a FIST FIGHT in France - Ep.46 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630019/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630019/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of Cancelled, Tana and Brooke discuss Tana’s eventful European trip, a DM that lead to a feud, fear of a stalker, police frustrations, a strange incident with sidewalk defecation, and much more.
Get a 60-day free trial at https://www.shipstation.com/cancelled. Thanks to ShipStation for sponsoring the show!
Tana Mongeau Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/tanamongeau/ Tana Mongeau Twitter: https://twitter.com/tanamongeau Tana Mongeau TikTok: https://www.tiktok.com/@tanamongeaulol
Brooke Schofield Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/brookeschofield/ Brooke Schofield Twitter: https://twitter.</description></item><item><title>Brooke’s hookup with Harry Jowsey EXPOSED - Ep. 45 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630020/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 17:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630020/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of Cancelled Tana and Brooke are in two separate continents giving us one long two part episode. On the first half Tana goes to London to film a video with KSI and the Sidemen. Brooke stays at home and brings on Imari as a guest. https://www.adamandeve.com Get 50% off almost any item + FREE SHIPPING + RUSH PROCESSING Code is TANA Tana Mongeau Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/tanamongeau/ Tana Mongeau Twitter: https://twitter.</description></item><item><title>Tana made $ 160,000 in 3 minutes doing THIS TikTok trend - Ep. 44 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630021/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 17:46:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630021/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of Cancelled Tana talks about wanting to take a break from drinking and partying, gives her thoughts on London, her ex responds to her lastpodcast and they discuss Tiktok trends and other current events OUR LISTENERS WILL RECEIVE ACCESS TO CEREBRAL’S STRONG START PACKAGE WHICH ALLOWS YOU TO SAVE UP TO 160 DOLLARS WHEN YOU BUY 2- OR 4-MONTHS OF CARE IN ADVANCE, DEPENDING ON PLAN SELECTION.</description></item><item><title>Tana’s Exes are Dating - Ep 43 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630022/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of Cancelled Tana talks about her exes dating each other. They also talk about guy that stalked her’s response to the last episode. They give their take on Jonah Hill, Trisha Paytas, and Colleen Ballinger situations. Tana Mongeau Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/tanamongeau/ Tana Mongeau Twitter: https://twitter.com/tanamongeau Tana Mongeau TikTok: https://www.tiktok.com/@tanamongeaulol
Brooke Schofield Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/brookeschofield/ Brooke Schofield Twitter: https://twitter.com/BroookeAmber Brooke Schofield TikTok: https://www.tiktok.com/@brookeschofield1 Brooke Schofield YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCzCVovj7tfqnV2lIkaVk35A Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>What Really Happened On Tana’s Birthday Trip | Ep 42 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 20:45:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630023/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of Cancelled Tana and Brooke hash out the discrepancies of their life in the pop culture world. They talk about Tana’s “hook up” with Trevor Wallace, Tana gets a song written about her, Brooke get’s broken up with, react to Colleen Ballinger’s apology and they recap the incident that happened on Tana’s birthday week vacation. As a special offer for listeners, new customers GET $5 OFF a Lume Starter Pack with code TANA at LumeDeodorant.</description></item><item><title>Brooke’s brutal BEEF with a TikTok girl | Ep 41 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630024/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 17:20:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630024/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of Canceled Tana recaps her trip to Cabo, running in to her ex boyfriendbad hinge dates, Facetuned private parts and Brooke having beef with a tiktoker. Tana Mongeau Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/tanamongeau/ Tana Mongeau Twitter: https://twitter.com/tanamongeau Tana Mongeau TikTok: https://www.tiktok.com/@tanamongeaulol
Brooke Schofield Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/brookeschofield/ Brooke Schofield Twitter: https://twitter.com/BroookeAmber Brooke Schofield TikTok: https://www.tiktok.com/@brookeschofield1 Brooke Schofield YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCzCVovj7tfqnV2lIkaVk35A Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Whitney Cummings Gender Reveal Ep. 40 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630025/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630025/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of Cancelled the girls are joined by the talented Whitney Cummings. Theydiscuss Whitney’s Pregnancy announcement, give dating and period advice. They talk abouttheir attraction to bald men, magicians, and attraction David Blane. OUR LISTENERS WILL RECEIVE ACCESS TO CEREBRAL’S STRONG START PACKAGE WHICH ALLOWS YOU TO SAVE UP TO 160 DOLLARS WHEN YOU BUY 2- OR 4-MONTHS OF CARE IN ADVANCE, DEPENDING ON PLAN SELECTION. LET’S DO THIS TOGETHER - MAKE A STRONG START TO A BETTER YOU.</description></item><item><title>Sofia Franklyn on her fallout with Alex Cooper Ep. 39 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630026/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630026/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of Cancelled we have Sofia with an F on. They discuss Tana accidentally throwing shade at her via twitter. They go over their sex lives and where they fall on a kink scale and toxic relationships. They discuss how she met Alex Cooper and how Call Her Daddy came to be and much more! Adamandeve.com Odder is 50% off almost any item + FREE SHIPPING + RUSH PROCESSING Code is TANA</description></item><item><title>Matt Rife On Why He'll Never Be Cancelled Ep. 38 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630027/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matt Rife joins the show today. They discuss cancel culture, touring as a comedian, trauma and glowing up. OUR LISTENERS WILL RECEIVE AN EXCLUSIVE 50% OFF YOUR FIRST MONTH OF THERAPY BY GOING TO CEREBRAL.COM/CANCELLED
Tana Mongeau Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/tanamongeau/ Tana Mongeau Twitter: https://twitter.com/tanamongeau Tana Mongeau TikTok: https://www.tiktok.com/@tanamongeaulol
Brooke Schofield Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/brookeschofield/ Brooke Schofield Twitter: https://twitter.com/BroookeAmber Brooke Schofield TikTok: https://www.tiktok.com/@brookeschofield1 Brooke Schofield YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCzCVovj7tfqnV2lIkaVk35A Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>EXPOSING HOW MUCH MONEY TIKTOKERS MAKE with Leo Skepi Ep 37 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630028/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 17:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630028/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Cancelled we are joined by TikTok icon Leo Skepi. They discuss social media strategies, their personal lives, and a fight that broke out at a bar. The overall tone of the this episode is light-hearted and funny, with them discussing personal matters and their take on issues. That’s 20% off with free shipping at manscaped.com, and use code [TANA]. Don’t forget that you came from your dad’s balls.</description></item><item><title>Tana responds to Idubbz’ Apology Ep. 36 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630029/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 22:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tana and Brooke talk about flirting within the friend group leading to awkward situations. Tana is paying to look for love on dating apps, possibility of being homeless, and responding to Idubzzz apology.
Adamandeve.com is offering 50% off just about any item! Plus FREE SHIPPING! This is an exclusive offer specific to this podcast so be sure to use this code TANA to get your discount, 100% Free Shipping and get it fast with Rush Processing - Code TANA!</description></item><item><title>Jeff ANGRILY accuses Tana of hooking up with his employee (MAJOR FIGHT) Ep. 35 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630030/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff Wittek joins the podcast today. They talk about their dating life, touring, mental health, and Tana&amp;rsquo;s alleged hook up with one of the Jeff FM boys.
Get 20% Off + Free Shipping, with the code[TANA] at Manscaped.com
Control Body Odor ANYWHERE with @lumedeodorant and get $5 off off your Starter Pack (that’s over 40% off) with promo code TANA at lumedeodorant.com/TANA! #lumepod
Tana Mongeau Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/tanamongeau/ Tana Mongeau Twitter: https://twitter.</description></item><item><title>A PSYCHO FAN IS STALKING TANA…Ep 34 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630031/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tana and Brooke recap their wild adventure from encountering a crazy fan, getting seduced by their flight attendant, to how their live show went. Tana realizes might have a s*x addiction and much more on this episode of Cancelled!
Go to AdamAndEve.com and use code TANA at checkout. This is exclusive offer specific to this podcast so be sure to use this code TANA to get your discount, 100% Free Shipping and get it fast with Rush Processing - Code TANA!</description></item><item><title>Hannah Berner on Ozempic, Dating Comedians, and Facetune Ep. 33 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630032/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630032/</guid><description>Podcast Description The girls bring on their second guest, Hannah Berner. They discuss a range of topics, from the filthiness of their podcast couch to the pressure to be perfect. They touch on their experiences with men and relationships, and the male-dominated space of stand-up comedy. They express their love for collaborating with women and their desire to normalize failure and imperfection. Despite their humorous tone, the friends touch on serious topics, including anxiety and the pressures of growing up in high-stress environments.</description></item><item><title>Tana and James Charles Coachella Reunion Ep. 32 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630033/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630033/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Tana and Brooke discuss Tana’s first week off 75 hard. Tana reveals she was left at the Redrocks in Vegas. They have Ari join in to recap and rate Coachella outfits. Finally Billy McFarland calls in to announce his plans for Fyre Fest 2.
Watch the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.ly/CancelledYouTube
Don’t forget to subscribe to the podcast for free wherever you&amp;rsquo;re listening or by using this link: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>Brooke Finally Breaks The Silence On Her Ex-Boyfriend EP 31 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630034/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 18:37:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tana talks about completing 75 days of sobriety and expresses her fear of drinking again. They discus their plans for Coachella and how much money tana spent spent on the event in the past. The two talk about the lineup and their feelings about certain artists. Brooke mentions that she wants to try molly at the festival. Brooke shares her feelings towards her last relationship and leaving her toxic ex.</description></item><item><title>Tana Has BEEF With Jojo Siwa EP 30 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630035/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tana and Brooke express their fears and nightmares. The two share their opinions on people who use their clout or fame to their own benefit in certain situations. Tana shares a story of a person falsely claiming she acted stuck up at a theme park. Brooke chimes in with a story of a troll on TikTok who has made multiple viral videos with bad takes, including one about Alabama Barker.</description></item><item><title>Tana and Brooke Are BACK and Hooking Up With the Same Guy EP 29 | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630036/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tana and Brooke have finally reunited for the second season of &amp;ldquo;Cancelled,&amp;rdquo; where they update listeners on their lives and experiences since the last episode. This episode features discussions about their hookup encounters with the same guy, experiences with their toxic exes, the latest pop culture tea (such as Tyga and Avril’s relationship and the Hailey/ Selena drama),and show off their extensive history knowledge in a game of trivia.</description></item><item><title>Episode 28: A Formal Apology From Us | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630037/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 07:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630037/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Tana and Brooke discuss the Dave Portnoy incident, Joe moving on, Tinx&amp;rsquo;s cancellation, Coachella and more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 27: She Hooked Up With Her Cousin for OnlyFans | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630038/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630038/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Tana and Brooke are joined by Stella Barey aka The Anal Princess. They discuss sex parties, anal, having intercourse with homeless people, and how Stella&amp;rsquo;s sexual relationship with her cousin skyrocketed her OnlyFans.
This episode is sponsored by Favor (http://www.heyfavor.com/cancelled), and Noom (http://www.noom.com/tana), Cerebral (http://www.cerebral.com/tana) and Adam &amp;amp; Eve (http://www.adamandeve.com offer code Tana). Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 26: Tana's Ex Hacked Her Netflix Account with Imari | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630039/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 07:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630039/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Tana and Brooke are joined by Imari Stuart. They discuss Coachella, grooming privates, Facetune and DJ&amp;rsquo;s passing. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 25: Mike Majlak on Addiction, Fame and Anxiety | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 00:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630040/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Tana and Brooke are joined by Mike Majlak. They discuss Mike&amp;rsquo;s book, addiction, anxiety, Anthony Bourdain and more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 24: Brooke Embarrassed Herself In Front of The Migos | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630041/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 19:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630041/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Tana and Brooke discuss Tana&amp;rsquo;s wild party, Lilah getting banned from all LA nightclubs, and the rumor about John Mayer.
This episode is sponsored by Adam &amp;amp; Eve (http://www.adamandeve.com offer code Tana), Lucy ( http://www.lucy.co promo code Cancelled), Bloom (http://www.bloomnu.com/tana), and Current (http://www.current.com/tana). Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 23: Why Tana Fired Her Assistant | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630042/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630042/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Tana and Brooke are joined by Imari Stuart. They discuss why Tana fired her assistant, Brooke&amp;rsquo;s night with Tyga, Pete, her split with Brad Souza, and Tana&amp;rsquo;s experience on SeekingArrangement. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 22: The Roast of Bryce Hall Got Us in Trouble | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630043/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 07:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630043/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Tana and Brooke discuss the Roast of Bryce Hall, Brooke&amp;rsquo;s run in with Brody Jenner, and they play Are You Smarter than a Fifth Grader? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 21.5: Brooke's Major Lie to the Vlog Squad | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630044/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630044/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Tana and Brooke are joined by Lilah Gibney. They discuss the roast of Bryce Hall, Brooke&amp;rsquo;s lie to the vlog squad and more Lilah stories&amp;hellip; Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 21: Planning Tanacon 2 with Tim Dillon | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630045/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630045/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Tana and Brooke are joined by Tim Dillon. They discuss the Hype House Netflix show, Joe Rogan, David Dobrik, their feud with Impaulsive, and a romantic entanglement with O.J. Simpson. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 20: Tana Had Sex in Hunter's Bed | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630046/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 05:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630046/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Brooke, Tana and Hunter discuss their hectic 2022, Bryce Hall, Miley Cyrus, and whether Olivia Rodrigo is a Cancelled listener. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 19: Brooke's Beef with Logan Paul | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630047/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 08:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630047/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Brooke and Tana discuss their hectic December, New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve in Vegas, and Brooke&amp;rsquo;s Beef with Logan Paul.
This episode is sponsored by Cerebral (http://www.cerebral.com/tana), Noom (http://www.noom.com/tana), and Adam &amp;amp; Eve (http://www.adamandeve.com offer code Tana). Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 18: One of Us Got Peed On | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630048/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 21:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630048/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode I am joined by Ari Aguirre. We discuss Tana&amp;rsquo;s impending conservatorship, Ari&amp;rsquo;s hookup with Bryce Hall, and his near near fatal attraction to Brooke.
This episode is sponsored by Cerebral (http://www.cerebral.com/tana), Shipstation (http://www.shipstation.com/ promo code Tana) and Adam &amp;amp; Eve (http://www.adamandeve.com offer code Tana). Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 17: The Imari and Ashly Episode | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630049/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 18:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630049/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode I am joined by Imari Stuart and Ashly Schwan. We discuss my solution for making sure someone didn&amp;rsquo;t hook up with my ex, why Ashly doesn&amp;rsquo;t live with us, how they rank all my exs and the real story behind my breakup with Somer.
This episode is sponsored by Manscaped (http://www.manscaped.com promo code Tana), Adam &amp;amp; Eve (http://www.adamandeve.com offer code Tana), and Noom (http://www.noom.com/tana). Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Episode 16: Tana's Stalker is Stalking Brooke | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630050/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 03:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630050/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Tana and Brooke discuss Brooke&amp;rsquo;s encounter with Tana&amp;rsquo;s Stalker, the Reality House controversy, and more Lilah sugar baby stories.
This episode is sponsored by Pill Club (http://www.thepillclub.com/cancelled), Cerebral (http://www.cerebral.com/tana) and Country Heat Weekly Podcast (https://music.amazon.com/podcasts/8b0cf1f8-ea72-4ee7-ad89-39ec6474ee87/country-heat-weekly). Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 15: Tana Is Shaking Things up with Bella Thorne | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630051/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630051/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Tana and Brooke are joined yet again by Bryce Hall. They discuss clapping back at &amp;ldquo;that girl&amp;rdquo;, Tana&amp;rsquo;s reunion with Bella Thorne, being invited as a date to Jake Paul&amp;rsquo;s upcoming fight, and more.
This episode is sponsored by Shipstation (http://www.shipstation.com/ promo code Tana), Buffy (http://www.buffy.co promo code Tana), Adam &amp;amp; Eve (http://www.adamandeve.com offer code Tana), and Simplisafe (http://www.simplisafe.com/tana)
Room 13 x Tana Collection: https://room13.la/collections/tana-x-13 Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Episode 14: Jeff Wittek Only Kissed Me Because He's Blind | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630052/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 22:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630052/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode I am joined by Jeff Wittek. We discuss jail, why he&amp;rsquo;s never dated in the spotlight, our hookup, the barbershop, and his accident.
This episode is sponsored by Noom (http://www.noom.com/tana), Buffy (http://www.buffy.co promo code Tana), and Pill Club (http://www.thepillclub.com/cancelled).
Room 13 x Tana Collection: https://room13.la/collections/tana-x-13 Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 13: Tana's Single Shenanigans | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630053/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 21:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630053/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Tana and Brooke discuss Tana&amp;rsquo;s breakup, their epic show, the dangers of CarPlay, and Tana&amp;rsquo;s stalker.
This episode is sponsored by Manscaped (http://www.manscaped.com promo code Tana), Pill Club (http://www.thepillclub.com/cancelled) and Storyworth (http://www.storyworth.com/tana). Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 12: One of Us was Roofied | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630054/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 19:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630054/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Tana and Brooke discuss Chris getting roofied, a food delivery gone awry, an update on crazy IV lady, Chris getting Tana tattooed on him and Brooke&amp;rsquo;s chaotic evening.
This episode is sponsored by Adam &amp;amp; Eve (http://www.adamandeve.com offer code Tana), Simplisafe (http://www.simplisafe.com/tana), Cerebral (http://www.cerebral.com/tana). Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 11: Zane and Heath's Vlog Squad Threesome | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630055/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630055/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Tana and Brooke are joined by Zane Hijazi and Heath Hussar. They discuss TikTok&amp;rsquo;s Couch Guy, friendship, and all the Vlog Squad tee.
This episode is sponsored by Glamnetic (http://www.glamnetic.com.tana) and Pill Club (http://www.thepillclub.com/cancelled)
Zane &amp;amp; Heath&amp;rsquo;s 100th Unfiltered Episode with Tana: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oBZylPl93ew Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 10: Why We Kicked Hunter Off the Podcast | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630056/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 09:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630056/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Tana and Brooke are joined by Lilah Gibney. They discuss New York, sugar babying, Hunter&amp;rsquo;s faux paux, the IV girl, and much more!
This episode is sponsored by Manscaped (http://www.manscaped.com promo code Tana) and Simplisafe (http://www.simplisafe.com/tana). Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 9: Ethan Cutkosky | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630057/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630057/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Tana and Brooke are joined by Ethan Cutkosky. They discuss Shameless, Raya, acting, the opportunity of social media and much more.
This episode is sponsored by Noom (http://www.noom.com/tana) , Blue Chew (http://www.bluechew.com offer code Tana), and Cerebral (http://www.cerebral.com/tana).
Ethan Cutkosky Linktree: https://linktr.ee/ekat19 Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 8: The Dallas Episode | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630058/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 23:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630058/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Tana, Hunter and Brooke discuss Dallas, the Harry Jowsey controversy, and the Los Angeles restaurant scene&amp;rsquo;s dirty secret. This episode is sponsored by Simplisafe (http://www.simplisafe.com/tana), Cerebral (http://www.cerebral.com/tana) , Buffy (http://www.buffy.co offer code Tana), and Raycon (http://www.buyraycon.com/tana). YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCcseTnvS6CC-mkIcwKfi-1A
Hosts Social Media Tana Mongeau Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/tanamongeau/ Tana Mongeau Twitter: https://twitter.com/tanamongeau Tana Mongeau TikTok: https://www.tiktok.com/@tanamongeaulol Hunter Moreno Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/huntermoreno/ Hunter Moreno TikTok: https://www.tiktok.com/@huntermorenoo Hunter Moreno Website: https://www.huntermoreno.com/ Make Sure Your Friends Are Okay: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Episode 7: Hunter's Crazy Ex Made Tana Mad | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630059/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 16:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630059/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Tana, Hunter and Brooke discuss their new house, Hunter&amp;rsquo;s wild encounter with his ex, and Tana&amp;rsquo;s crazy rideshare driver. This episode is sponsored by Cerebral (http://www.cerebral.com/tana) Parade (http://www.yourparade.com/tana), Apostrophe (http://www.apostrophe.com/tana), and Blue Chew (http://www.bluechew.com offer code Tana) Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 6: Harry Jowsey Hooks Up with All of Us | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630060/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630060/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Tana, Hunter and Brooke are joined by Harry Jowsey. They discuss their various hookups, Harry&amp;rsquo;s secret sex routine, Too Hot to Handle, boxing plans, and and all of Harry&amp;rsquo;s firsts. This episode is sponsored by Adam &amp;amp; Eve (http://www.adamandeve.com offer code Tana), Parade (http://www.yourparade.com/tana), Noom (http://www.noom.com/tana) &amp;amp; Apostrophe (http://www.apostrophe.com/tana). Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 5: Tana's Celebrity Orgy | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630061/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 06:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630061/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Tana, Hunter and Brooke discuss secret LA poker games, quick marriages to millionaires, and Tana&amp;rsquo;s recent orgy proposition. This episode is sponsored by Raycon (www.buyraycon.com/tana), Parade (www.yourparade.com/tana), Apostrophe (www.apostrophe.com/tana), and Blue Chew (www.bluechew.com offer code Tana). Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 4: Tana Hooked Up With Bryce Hall | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630062/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 07:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tana Mongeau and Brooke Schofield are joined by Bryce Hall. They discuss boxing, sexuality, his legal battles with Austin McBroom, the truth about Riley Hubatka, and his sexual history with Tana. This episode is sponsored by Raycon (www.buyraycon.com/tana), Parade (www.yourparade.com/tana), Buffy (www.buffy.co offer code Tana), and Blue Chew (www.bluechew.com offer code Tana). Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 3: The Ex Episode | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630063/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 08:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630063/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Tana, Hunter and Brooke discuss the Mindy fiasco, their trip to see Beiber, Tana&amp;rsquo;s past relationship with Mod Sun as well as much more. This episode is sponsored by Adam &amp;amp; Eve (www.adamandeve.com offer code Tana) Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 2: The Trisha Paytas Episode | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630064/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 06:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tana Mongeau and Hunter Moreno are joined by Trisha Paytas. They discuss Gabbie Hanna, the dissolution of Frenemies, struggling with mental illness and OnlyFans. This episode is sponsored by Adam &amp;amp; Eve (www.adamandeve.com offer code Tana), Raycon (www.buyraycon.com/tana), and Noom (www.noom.com/tana). Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 1: Beefing with the Kardashians | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630065/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 06:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630065/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the first episode of Cancelled, Tana Mongeau is joined by co-hosts, Hunter Moreno and Brooke Schofield. They discuss their beef with the Kardashians, living in David Dobrik&amp;rsquo;s house, Chris D&amp;rsquo;Elia, Bryce Hall and more. This episode is sponsored by Adam &amp;amp; Eve (www.adamandeve.com offer code Tana), Raycon (www.buyraycon.com/tana), and Noom (www.noom.com/tana). Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cancelled with Tana Mongeau | Cancelled with Tana Mongeau</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6681630066/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 21:14:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6681630066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cancelled with Tana Mongeau Teaser Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>