<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Idea to Startup on SWIEST - Transcripts 路 Screenplays 路 Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/idea-to-startup/</link><description>Recent content in Idea to Startup on SWIEST - Transcripts 路 Screenplays 路 Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 09:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/idea-to-startup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to be Different, Part 1 (feat. The Personal Venn Diagram Method) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll help you build a system to be different. We dive into the Persona Venn Diagram Method - a tool designed to help you identify and capitalize on your unique strengths - and we&amp;rsquo;ll talk through how the path you might think holds the least risk actually guarantees the most. This is the first in a series of episodes on the Methods we use at Tacklebox to help our founders build differentiated businesses.</description></item><item><title>Testing Another Startup Idea Live Part 1: Picking the Idea, Nudging the Boulder | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll kick off a new series where we&amp;rsquo;ll start an idea live on the pod. Actually, we&amp;rsquo;ll start two. One in the healthcare space, one in the AI space. The hope is that you&amp;rsquo;ve got an idea and can follow along with us. Today we&amp;rsquo;ll cover when your idea is ready to start, how to structure the first couple of weeks, and how to think about the giant boulder sitting in front of you.</description></item><item><title>The Quest for an Identity | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we&amp;rsquo;ll help you find an identity. An identity is something unique that you can organize your business beneath. A north star that can act as a lens for every decision you make. We talk through how to use category shifts and first principles to find and evaluate possible identities, and when to stick with an identity vs. when to jump ship. We use a bunch of examples - from an Italian restaurant to a skincare company called Jolie to the 1994 Arkansas Razorbacks basketball team.</description></item><item><title>How to Find a Differentiator (ITS Classic) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we&amp;rsquo;ll outline two frameworks that&amp;rsquo;ll help you find a meaningful differentiator. We&amp;rsquo;ll use a bunch of examples to show how Inversion + Before and After can change your business. A baseball academy, Krispy Kreme, and Nutrisystem help show us the way to a product your customers will happily overpay for.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Customers Speak Problem, But Youre Speaking Solution | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about why so many entrepreneurs can&amp;rsquo;t effectively explain what they&amp;rsquo;re doing to their customers. The short answer is they speak the wrong language. Customers speak Problem, entrepreneurs speak Solution. It&amp;rsquo;s like two people trying to have a conversation when one only speaks Latin and the other only speaks Dutch.
We go through how to start speaking Problem, and show the power of Problem Language through a live idea test - two landing pages for an AI bot to help people get out of debt: one with Solution Language, one with Problem Language.</description></item><item><title>An SOP for Testing a Startup Idea | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll help you build an SOP for testing startup ideas. We&amp;rsquo;ll use an example from a listener - a startup in the homeschooling space - as a guinea pig. The best way to have a great startup idea this time next year is to test out a bunch of ideas in the interim. This SOP will help you do it, and scale the process.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Ways to Approach Your Startup Idea Like A Pro (ITS Classic) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about pros and amateurs. Pros build businesses that have a shot - amateurs never leave the starting gate. Unfortunately, most amateurs don&amp;rsquo;t know they&amp;rsquo;re approaching their idea the wrong way.
We talk through your vision and your internal system - the internal process you&amp;rsquo;ll build, automate, and scale to help you execute that vision. We do it with a little help from the best run solo business I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered (an interior designer), and the best tool for your internal system (Zapier).</description></item><item><title>Writing Persuasive Copy to Test an Idea | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we talk through how to write compelling copy. We go through a few counterintuitive archetypes you can use to dramatically increase the clarity of your messaging, which will allow you to increase your conversion rate and get more people involved earlier in the process. Copywriting is an idea-testing superpower.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to Embrace Risk, Uncertainty, and Chaos | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll help you embrace risk, uncertainty, and chaos. The only way to get asymmetric results in life is to spend a lot of time in what we call the &amp;ldquo;chaos&amp;rdquo; zone - the uncomfortable place where you&amp;rsquo;re finding things no one else has yet. This type of work (life) is uncomfortable and stressful, so people don&amp;rsquo;t do it. But, it&amp;rsquo;s where all the potential asymmetric value is. So, we go through tactics to make this stage feel safer, allowing you to spend more time in it and increasing the chances you pull a life changing business out of it.</description></item><item><title>The Three Types of Problems Worth Your Time to Solve | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we talk through the three types of problems that deserve a solution. We start off with a few higher level thoughts about problems and startups - specifically around achievement incentives and how some bad early decisions usually can&amp;rsquo;t be salvaged by good decisions later on. Then we talk through Hole Problems, Teleporter Problems, and Status Level Jump Problems.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to Find Your Wedge, feat. Bleeding Neck Problems (ITS Classic) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220011/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you can&amp;rsquo;t get traction, you likely need a wedge. Today, we talk through how to find one. We leverage a few frameworks we use at Tacklebox - the Bleeding Neck Problem, Productizing the First Step, and the 100 Character Landing Page. The goal is to solve an immediate, painful problem that&amp;rsquo;ll build trust and allow you to pitch your bigger, North Star vision. Wedges get you started, and life is 100x harder without them.</description></item><item><title>Are you a Freelancer or an Entrepreneur? | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll help you think through a deceptively tough question - are you a freelancer or an entrepreneur? Every decision you make needs to nest neatly below this core decision for your business to work, but tons of founders are either trying to do both simultaneously or think they&amp;rsquo;re one when they&amp;rsquo;re really the other.
We clarify the difference between freelancer and entrepreneur, help you decide which will make you happier, and get you started on the path for whichever you choose.</description></item><item><title>A System to Relish the Uncomfortable Stuff | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we help you become the type of founder who relishes uncomfortable things that lead to successful startups. There are no real secrets in the startup world - the hard, proactive, uncomfortable work leads to businesses that matter. This work doesnt happen without a system.
Today we help you build that system, using The Costanza Swap, The Three Levers of Resilience, and The Failure Case.
Hoo ahh.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to Identify and Kill Bad Startup Ideas Masquerading As Good Ones | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll lay out a framework to help you identify and kill bad ideas. It&amp;rsquo;s hard to objectively evaluate your idea early on - this framework helps you rise above your idea to do it effectively. A side-effect is that the framework will help you find and pursue the good ideas.
We talk through 1) Finding and Evaluating the Real Risk, 2) Predicting Organic Growth Potential, and 3) Predicting the Likelihood of Converting Early Customers, using a startup idea from a listener as an example.</description></item><item><title>A System to Test and Build Your Startup (Part III - Implementing Your System This Weekend) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today is the last episode in the three-part series on an internal operating system for people working on startup ideas. We talk through the core pillars - Projects, Areas, Inbox - and the multipliers (like Keystone Actions) that&amp;rsquo;ll make sure you&amp;rsquo;re focused on the things that could be differentiators for your business. After today, you&amp;rsquo;ll have everything you need to build your own system.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>An Operating System to Help You Move Faster By Focusing On Less - Part 2 (feat. a monkey reciting Hamlet) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today is part 2 of our series helping you build an internal operating system. We identify the four things you&amp;rsquo;ll need to have happen for your startup to gain momentum, then we organize those into a system that&amp;rsquo;ll help you move fast based on inertia.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Weekly System to Keep Entrepreneurs With Jobs Moving Fast (Part 1 - Strategy) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll kick off a series that&amp;rsquo;ll help people with jobs and startup ideas build an internal system that&amp;rsquo;ll help them track progress and build momentum. Too many founders have no strategy or measurement system around how they pursue and test an idea - this series will help you do it.
In part 1, we go through what a strategy should look like and the three counterintuitive benefits to creating one.</description></item><item><title>The One Thing That Matters - How to Find a Differentiator That'll Support a Business | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll help you find a differentiator powerful enough that it can support your business. We&amp;rsquo;ll talk through what a differentiator actually allows you to do, five prompts to help you uncover and test one for your business, and Brian&amp;rsquo;s favorite current differentiator - Popup Bagels.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to Stop Being Your Startup's Bottleneck | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll help you get out of your own way. We subscribe to the Charlie Munger school of &amp;ldquo;instead of trying to be smarter, try to be less dumb,&amp;rdquo; and this episode digs into three ways to simplify your startup so that you can move faster. We talk through how to actually implement jobs to be done, how to build systems to amplify your willpower 100x, and how to be more courageous.</description></item><item><title>A Framework for Building Wildly Useful Startups | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll help you make sure the thing you&amp;rsquo;re building is wildly useful. Most startups fail because founders build stuff that customers don&amp;rsquo;t care enough about to change their behavior for. We&amp;rsquo;ll use The Usefulness Framework to ensure you don&amp;rsquo;t do that, with help from Habit Kangaroo, a startup Brian ran back in 2014, and a GMAT training program his friend built to help people get into Harvard.</description></item><item><title>Four Characteristics of Great Startup Ideas | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we talk through four characteristics of great startup ideas (with a bonus fifth Brian thought of post-recording). We discuss organic growth, market innovation vs. product innovation, growing markets, product swaps, and happiness. The goal of this episode is to help shape fuzzy ideas and give you new ideas.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Organic Growth Equation - Why People Share and How to Pick Ideas that'll Grow | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we talk about organic growth. Your startup won&amp;rsquo;t be successful if your first customers aren&amp;rsquo;t compelled to tell people about how you&amp;rsquo;ve helped them. Luckily, organic growth is straightforward. There are ways to predict it and ideas better suited for it. We talk through an equation for organic growth and dig in on why people share.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A System to Help You Become Wildly Creative | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll help you build a system for creativity. We&amp;rsquo;ll start by defining creativity as an equation to make it more accessible. Then, we&amp;rsquo;ll develop a system that focuses on the inputs of the creativity equation. We talk through the Commonplace Book, Commencement Speeches, a sports writer and the movie Sahara. Then, we get into the weeds on how to set up and implement your own personal creativity system.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 165 - Should You Niche? | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about the big question - should you start with a focused niche? There are pros and cons to the approach, but the perceived cons - &amp;ldquo;what if I get tired of the niche in a few years?&amp;rdquo; , &amp;ldquo;what if the niche doesn&amp;rsquo;t lead to a bigger market?&amp;rdquo; , &amp;ldquo;isn&amp;rsquo;t a niche just hiding from the bigger problem I want to solve?&amp;rdquo; have gotten louder lately.</description></item><item><title>Why You Didn't Build a Product Last Weekend (feat. A Framework to Seek Out Discomfort) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll talk through why you didn&amp;rsquo;t get a product live last weekend despite an episode that walked you through a step-by-step process to do it. Last week, we ignored the emotional stuff. The inertia and discomfort that keep people from doing something new. Today, we tackle it. We give you a framework to lean into discomfort and answer the questions that nag at you and hold you back from putting stuff live.</description></item><item><title>How to Build the First (Magical) Version of Your Product This Weekend | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we&amp;rsquo;ll help you get the first version of your product up and out. We use a three-part framework to help you focus in on the one core feature you&amp;rsquo;ve got to nail. We also find your customers inertia and ride that wave to make it easier to use your product than not. We get help from an airbnb for lawn equipment startup and move the ball forward on the chronic pain idea.</description></item><item><title>Choose The Right Quest | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220027/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll talk through how to identify and pursue the big, consequential ideas - what we&amp;rsquo;ll call Quests. We go through how to identify them, how to wrap our arms around them, and what to do when you (inevitably) feel intimidated. We&amp;rsquo;ll do it with a little help from the 90 Yard Mistake, a ghost kitchen idea, and some chronic pain interviews. Quest (drink).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>INTERVIEW: Seth Godin Thinks Through Startup Ideas in Real-Time | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, Seth Godin (!!) virtually dropped by to talk through a bunch of startup ideas. He gives his opinion on how hed start everything from a pasta truck to an updated CSA program. We dive into risk, emotion, tension and doing things that matter. Seth talks about the distinction between entrepreneurs and freelancers and the danger of thinking youre one when youre really the other. We talk about marketplaces and domain expertise and knowing what it is youre actually selling.</description></item><item><title>When to Pivot and When to Stick (aka How Pros Deal w/ Distractions) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220029/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about one of the most common hurdles entrepreneurs run into - getting tempted by a new idea a few months into working on a different idea. We lay out a framework to identify the first principles of the new idea fast so you can decide if it&amp;rsquo;s worth a pivot. We also dig in on why the urge to pivot shows up, procrastination, and how to win a baking contest.</description></item><item><title>How to Use Landing Page Tests to Find Your Beachhead Customer (feat. the One Person Landing Page and the ELU Framework) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220030/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll talk through a landing page system that&amp;rsquo;ll help you find a great initial customer - one that can anchor your business. We&amp;rsquo;ll talk through the circle framework, as well as the One Person Landing Page and the Emotion / Logistics / Urgency flow. This will help you identify the right customer to focus your product building efforts on.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ideation, Finding a Wedge, Seeding a Marketplace and How to Scale Yourself with an EA - with Jonathan Swanson, cofounder of Thumbtack, Athena, and Powerset | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220031/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we chat with Jonathan Swanson, cofounder of Thumbtack, Athena, and Powerset. We cover a ton of ground - starting with the Sunday idea club that led to Thumbtack, how to scale a marketplace, and how to choose ideas you&amp;rsquo;d happily spent a decade on. Next, we jump into the science of delegation - the idea at the core of Athena. Jonathan talks through how to delegate to an EA, when to start with one, a system of delegation that creates asymmetric upside and what type of founders should consider it.</description></item><item><title>The Law of The Startup Wedge (feat. circadian rhythms and trust transactions) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220032/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to talk about one of the fundamental laws of startups - The Wedge. It&amp;rsquo;s the best way to build trust when you have a product that&amp;rsquo;s got a longer feedback loop or requires a lot from your early customers. We&amp;rsquo;ll show a few examples and build out a framework to help guide you when you&amp;rsquo;re looking for, and implementing, a wedge.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to Separate Yourself from Your Idea (feat. the five immutable laws of cold emails) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220033/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about people. An old boss of Brian&amp;rsquo;s said the best way to see into the future is to see the present in higher resolution than anyone else. Understanding people - yourself and your customer - will let you understand their behavior. This will let you better predict how they&amp;rsquo;ll act than anyone else and build for it.
We talk through a cold email that&amp;rsquo;ll get you customers to speak with and a method to make sure you&amp;rsquo;re unbiased in what you hear.</description></item><item><title>Testing a Startup Idea Live, Part 2: An Organizing Principle and A Structure to Move Fast | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220034/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today is week two of testing out a startup idea live on the show. We&amp;rsquo;re pushing and pulling on the chronic pain idea, setting up the system to get interactions with customers and establishing our organizing principle for the first phase of the business: speed.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Testing a Startup Idea Live, Part 1: The Idea, The Goldfish Cleanse, J.O.A.S. | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220035/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll kick off a series where Brian is going to test out a startup idea live. We begin the way every idea should begin - by figuring out why the thing will fail and building in systems to avoid that fate.
Brian touches on Thrust and Drag, The Goldfish Cleanse, Journal of a Startup, and exactly what you should do to get to first principles for your startup idea.</description></item><item><title>When to Quit on your Startup Idea, and When to Stick It Out (feat. the systemic vs. solvable checklist and the idea growth curve) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220036/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll talk through the hardest decision an early-stage entrepreneur has to make - quit on your idea or stick it through? This decision rarely has enough information and the entrepreneur never has enough context to make it. Lots of entreprenuers quit right before their idea was about to get interesting or stick with ideas that never had a chance for years.
This pod lays out a decision framework to help with the quit or stick question.</description></item><item><title>How to Find and Solve Hard Problems (feat. a used car startup and The Problem Hunters) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220037/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hard problems are the only problems worth your time. Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about how to identify them and build a business around them. We&amp;rsquo;ll dig in on decisions customers avoid and using those decisions to anchor early traction. We&amp;rsquo;ll talk through Brian&amp;rsquo;s favorite current business - a guy who buys used cars for you - and how to approach helping people with chronic pain.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to Build Trust in Six Seconds (Thrust + Drag Part 2, feat. an elephant and the bus stop exercise) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220038/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll finish up on Thrust and Drag. This time, we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about building trust with your customer in six seconds - creating thrust that&amp;rsquo;ll buy you another six seconds, and another after that. There&amp;rsquo;s art and science to getting people&amp;rsquo;s attention in such a short period of time, and we&amp;rsquo;ll talk through both.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Thrust and Drag Part 1: A System to Keep Momentum | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about thrust and drag, the components of momentum. Momentum is the lifeblood for startups, but most people leave it to chance. By focusing on the inputs of momentum - thrust and drag - you can build systems to ensure you keep moving forward. Gaps kill startups. This system removes them.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What if the problem you're solving isn't "painful" or "urgent"? What if it's just something you think people will want? Should you still pursue it? (feat. Linguini) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll hit on the most asked question in our now functional podcast question submission list. What if the thing you&amp;rsquo;re building isn&amp;rsquo;t solving a bleeding neck problem? What if it&amp;rsquo;s just something you think people will want? Something that&amp;rsquo;ll improve their life, but not something they loose sleep over? Should you still pursue it? How?
We&amp;rsquo;ll talk through Linguini, Yeti, gross margins and status level jumps and land on the answer - is that type of business worth your time?</description></item><item><title>How to Create Useful Content (feat. the "creating content by not creating any content" method) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220041/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about content. Two of the most asked questions we get are &amp;ldquo;should I create content?&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;if I should&amp;hellip; what the heck should I say?&amp;rdquo;
Creating content feels daunting until you realize the best way to create content is to not create content. We go through how to do that, leaning on a few examples and a content generating framework. We also crown the best burrito in NYC.</description></item><item><title>How to stack risk early, tackle the cold start problem, and compete by understanding incentives with Jareau Wad茅 | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we speak with Jareau Wad茅 - currently the founder of Batch Processing, previously the co-founder of Balanced (acquired by Stripe), head of growth at Tilt Pro (acquired by Airbnb), and Chief Growth Officer at Finix.
We spoke with Jareau about the early days of Balanced - how they prioritized, gained trust with initial customers, and competed with companies like Stripe and PayPal. Jareau talks through a bunch of different heuristics and models he uses to evaluate risk (stack it early), tackle the cold start problem, synthesize feedback, figure out the technical side of your business early on, and manage the mental side of starting a business.</description></item><item><title>15 Min(ish) Skill: Script the Start and End aka How to Consistently Do Uncomfortable Things | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about one very specific method you can use to tackle your hardest, most uncomfortable work.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Three More Ways to Approach Your Business Like a Pro (feat. anti-marketing, Frank Sinatra, and an Uber comedian) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll dig in on three approaches that separate how pros and amateurs build businesses. We&amp;rsquo;ll talk through how pros leverage existing infrastructure, how they use anti-marketing to build trust with strangers, and how they don&amp;rsquo;t leave luck and serendipity to chance - they orchestrate it. We&amp;rsquo;ll do this with help from stories about Frank Sinatra, a comedian in an Uber, and a founder starting a GMAT course for people looking to score 800 (and for those people only).</description></item><item><title>The Trust to Risk Ratio (feat. Soona + a four-step risk framework) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220045/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll help you get your first customers. We&amp;rsquo;ll do it by learning how to use the trust to risk ratio - a way to identify the big risks that are holding your customer back and shoulder those risks early on to build trust. We talk through risk and trust with Find Your Lobster, Soona, and a finicky water pump.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Ways to Approach Your Startup Idea Like A Pro (feat. an interior designer + Zapier) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220046/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about pros and amateurs. Pros build businesses that have a shot - amateurs never leave the starting gate. Unfortunately, most amateurs don&amp;rsquo;t know they&amp;rsquo;re approaching their idea the wrong way. We talk through two things entrepreneurs can do to give themselves the best chance to build something that matters.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Testing an AI Coaching Tool in a Month (feat. The 5 Startup Idea Non-Negotiables) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220047/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll tell the story of an idea a friend of Brian&amp;rsquo;s pursued over the past month. It came about through flashy new tech, but the process shows what&amp;rsquo;s actually valuable.
This is a reps episode. A way to vicariously watch someone else test an early idea so that it&amp;rsquo;s easier for you to do the same.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to Build a Product People Will Share | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220048/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll talk through a way to ensure people will share what you&amp;rsquo;re building (ideally before you decide to build it). We&amp;rsquo;ll break down a few baby products that&amp;rsquo;ve been shared with Brian dozens of times the past few weeks to understand the incentives and drivers that made those products so shareable. Finally, we&amp;rsquo;ll look at three questions that&amp;rsquo;ll ensure you&amp;rsquo;re on the right track.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Regret Minimization Framework (feat. Alone + The Big Reveal) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220049/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll talk through a regret minimization framework that&amp;rsquo;ll help you reset for the new year. Then, we&amp;rsquo;ll use the show Alone to show how entrepreneurs need to stack risks early to give themselves the best chance at success.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>HOLIDAY CLASSIC: The Three Characteristics of a Startup Idea That's Worth Your Time | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220050/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll revisit another one of the top-listened to episodes of the year. We&amp;rsquo;ll reflect on the three core characteristics our fastest growing startups all share. We&amp;rsquo;ll talk about how to identify these characteristics, test for them, and leave ideas that don&amp;rsquo;t have them. We&amp;rsquo;ll talk through the 4x rule and level jumping. And we&amp;rsquo;ll be back next week with new episodes 
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Holiday Classic: Four Questions to Help You Start Your Idea (Feat. Penne Vodka Pete ) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220051/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today&amp;rsquo;s episode is one of the most shared of the year. We start a business using four questions, hit on problems and opportunities, and meet the cult favorite Penne Vodka Pete.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to Take Yourself Seriously feat. Your Entrepreneurship Handbook | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220052/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Most people&amp;rsquo;s startup approach is haphazard. It&amp;rsquo;s a combination of instincts and reactions and luck or happenstance. People who succeed are far more purposeful. Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll help you take your idea and yourself seriously. We&amp;rsquo;ll build your entrepreneurship handbook - the thing that&amp;rsquo;ll let you make tough decisions at scale.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Build a System to be Different in 2023 (feat. pessimistic squirrels and majestic lions) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220053/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll help you build a system to be different. The well-traveled paths don&amp;rsquo;t get you anywhere interesting and common inputs won&amp;rsquo;t give you uncommon output. But, acting different is difficult. There&amp;rsquo;s external and internal pressure and biases, so we need a system. We talk through the Venn Diagram Method and the cataloging and reflection needed to make decisions that&amp;rsquo;ll help you reach your potential.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to Test the Startup Idea You Had Over Thanksgiving in 7 Minutes | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220054/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll run a 7-minute test on a startup idea I had over Thanksgiving. It&amp;rsquo;s tackling a massive topic - email - but breaking it down into a manageable first customer and use case. You probably had a startup idea over the break, too, and you should use this framework to test it. The secret to startups is that there is no secret - you&amp;rsquo;re more likely to have a successful business if you try out lots of ideas.</description></item><item><title>How to Productize Your Customer's First Step (feat. The Family Operating System and a 3am Pitch) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220055/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we&amp;rsquo;ll dig in on productizing your customer&amp;rsquo;s first step. This is the best path to building a product that generates revenue immediately so that you&amp;rsquo;ve got some runway and flexibility to build. We&amp;rsquo;ll walk through a few examples, including a Family Operating System that came in at 3am last Thanksgiving from a listener.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Frameworks to Help Find Your Differentiator (feat. Inversion and the Before and After Method) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220056/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll outline two frameworks that&amp;rsquo;ll help you find a meaningful differentiator. We use a bunch of examples to go through Inversion and the Before and After pic method, including a baseball academy, Krispy Kreme, and Nutrisystem. The goal is a product your customers will happily, willingly overpay for.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to Think Bigger (feat. Mattress Mack and Asymmetric Upside) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220057/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Most entrepreneurs spend the majority of their time doing things that, even if they work, won&amp;rsquo;t make a meaningful difference. Our default state is reactive, iterative work. To be a successful founder, you need to do things with the potential for asymmetric upside. Today, we talk about how to identify and incorporate tasks each day that - if they work - will fundamentally change your business. Today, we teach you how to think big.</description></item><item><title>20(ish) Min Skills: How to Find Your Wedge (feat. Bleeding Neck Problems) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220058/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220058/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you can&amp;rsquo;t get traction, you likely need a wedge. Today, we talk through how to find one. We leverage a few frameworks we use at Tacklebox - the Bleeding Neck Problem, Productizing the First Step, and the 100 Character Landing Page. The goal is to solve an immediate, painful problem that&amp;rsquo;ll build trust and allow you to pitch your bigger, North Star vision. Wedges get you started. Life is 100x harder without a wedge.</description></item><item><title>Start a Startup in an Hour a Day (Part 3 of 3): Taking the System for a Spin (feat. You've Got Mail and Curious Ruby) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220059/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today is the last in our three-part series on how to start a startup in an hour a day. Brian talks through an idea he&amp;rsquo;s working on on the side - VR for chronic pain - and sets up and executes a two-week, hour a day sprint. We dig in on the three pillars of the system - The Big Question, Tactics, and Structure, how to use friction and leverage, and how to organize your startup life around being curious.</description></item><item><title>Start a Startup in an Hour a Day (Part 2) - Founder Archetypes and a Two-Week Sprint Rhythm | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220060/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220060/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the second episode of the series, we&amp;rsquo;ll talk through the type of founder you are - Storyteller, Builder, or Manager. We&amp;rsquo;ll then help you build out a two-week sprint cadence to test and grow your idea dependent on which type of founder you are. We get a little help from Brian&amp;rsquo;s grandma and an offsite event startup for businesses trying to get their remote employees to feel some camaraderie.</description></item><item><title>Start a Startup in an Hour a Day (Part 1 of 3) - Reflection + A Lifestyle Debt Audit + Finding a Free Hour | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220061/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today is the first of a three part series on setting up an operating rhythm for building a startup while you&amp;rsquo;ve got a full-time job. We lay out a system to help you make serious progress in an hour a day. We focus on reflection - specifically, your lifestyle debt - in an attempt to free up an hour of your time for the startup work. A startup won&amp;rsquo;t be sustainable if it&amp;rsquo;s layered on top of everything you&amp;rsquo;re doing now.</description></item><item><title>20(ish) Min Skills: How to Write Direct, Persuasive Copy (feat. The Four Keys to Writing) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220062/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about the biggest gap in most entrepreneurs skillsets - writing compelling copy. We&amp;rsquo;ll go through the Four Keys to Writing which idiot-proof writing compelling copy that&amp;rsquo;ll convert customers from landing pages, ads, and cold emails. Implement this stuff and you&amp;rsquo;ll give your startup a much better chance at success.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to Start a Community-Based Startup - or Tack a Community Onto Your Existing Business (feat. Monks and Lonely Dads) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220063/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about community. What a good community looks like, the mistakes people make around communities, and how to test an idea for a community fast. We&amp;rsquo;ll test out a community for lonely dads, dive into an example about a freelancer community, and check in on a couple of Monks walking through Central Park at night.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>20(ish)-Minute Skills: The Concierge MVP | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220064/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today&amp;rsquo;s episode discusses the Concierge MVP, an indispensable tactic early stage entrepreneurs can use to get the feedback of a full product without the money and time required to build one. We go through the 4-step method that&amp;rsquo;ll get you data from customers you can use to raise funding, hire, or recognize the opportunity actually isn&amp;rsquo;t worth your time.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to Spot Promising Startup Ideas (feat. The Hard Startup Myth and The Hassle Premium) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220065/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we&amp;rsquo;ll help you find and choose the right startup idea. We&amp;rsquo;ll use a couple of frameworks to help you evaluate startup ideas you&amp;rsquo;ve got and find startup ideas other people miss. We talk through the Hard Startup Myth and The Hassle Premium, two mental models that&amp;rsquo;ll make sure your next idea has legs. We&amp;rsquo;ll also evaluate Tinder for Jobs and learn a lesson from the great Frank Prisinzano.</description></item><item><title>How to Raise Money from Angel Investors with Angela Lee (37 Angels, Columbia Business School) ((And we start a $100mm taco company the last 15 minutes)) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220066/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Awesome chat with Angela Lee (37 Angels, Columbia Business School) about angel investing. We talk through what angels are looking for, who should try to raise from them, what&amp;rsquo;ll happen if they do, and what the other options are.
Then, we spend the last 15 minutes starting a $100mm Taco company. Angela walks through the process goals and financial milestones she&amp;rsquo;d want to hit in a fascinating startup exercise.</description></item><item><title>How to Get the World to Work For You (feat. pickleball and the greatest marketing campaign of all time) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220067/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220067/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you understand how the world works, you can let it do some serious heavy lifting for your business. If you ignore how it works, your business is as good as dead. Today we talk through three universal truths - forces that you can put behind your business to dramatically accelerate it. We&amp;rsquo;ll use three examples - the best marketing campaign Brian&amp;rsquo;s ever seen, the most magical product, and the mind-blowing growth of pickleball.</description></item><item><title>Three Ways to Build Trust (feat. parking valets and a cure for baldness) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220068/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220068/</guid><description>Podcast Description We spend a bunch of time on business fundamentals. These are important, obviously, but they&amp;rsquo;re only relevant if you can build enough trust with customers to convince them to give you a chance in the first place.
Today we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about why people hand their keys over to random strangers on the street in New York City, how a person selling cures for baldness converts 80% of the people he speaks with, and how you can build a strategy to cultivate trust with your customers, too.</description></item><item><title>A 20(ish) Minute Startup: Airbnb Referrals | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220069/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll start a business in 20(ish) minutes. We&amp;rsquo;ll talk through the idea, figure out assumptions, run a test, and make a decision. We leverage a three step process to figure out if the idea is worth our time: Whisper Ideas vs. Rooftop Ideas, Rivers and Dams, and a Hypothesis Test.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What Kind of Company Do You Want to Build? (feat a 3-part framework to help you figure it out and Shaggy) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220070/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220070/</guid><description>Podcast Description I meet far too many unhappy entrepreneurs. The whole point of this thing is to build a business that makes you happy. It needs to work, but it also can&amp;rsquo;t make you miserable. Lots of entrepreneurs set themselves on a bad path from day one by ignoring critical early decisions. We talk through them today. And if you&amp;rsquo;re not happy building what you&amp;rsquo;re building, it&amp;rsquo;s not too late.</description></item><item><title>A Podcast Figuring Out Your Value (featuring an aperol spritz startup and a magician) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220071/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we&amp;rsquo;ll help you sink your teeth into value. We&amp;rsquo;ll help you understand what people will actually pay for, talk through a framework to ensure you&amp;rsquo;re creating enough value to anchor a business, and look at examples of a few startups doing this well and poorly. There&amp;rsquo;s also a magician.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Mental Model to Reduce Complexity: The River (featuring a papaya) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220072/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220072/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode digs into how to reduce complexity and choose the right path through a mental model we call the river. You identify the dams that stop your customer and break them down, focusing on just them to bring focused, explainable, shareable value. Plus, the papaya. Which you&amp;rsquo;ll have to listen to understand.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to Start a Startup Accountability Group | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220073/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220073/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;ve spent a ton of time recently on tactics and strategies. Today, we talk about how to build a group to make sure you&amp;rsquo;re implementing them. Here&amp;rsquo;s how to build a 4 person startup accountability group that&amp;rsquo;ll meet weekly. We talk through who should be in the group, what you should focus on, and why it&amp;rsquo;ll help. There&amp;rsquo;s absolutely no better way to get started.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Three Pillars of a Startup That's Worth Your Time (feat. Markets, The 4x Rule, and Level Jumping) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220074/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we reflect on the three core characteristics our fastest growing startups shared. We break each down and talk through how to check for them and optimize for them. We also realize that startup ideas without these characteristics aren&amp;rsquo;t worth your time to build.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A 20(ish) Minute Startup: An App That Cures Chronic Pain | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220075/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we think through an idea for an app that treats chronic pain. We&amp;rsquo;ll use the Three Level system to figure out what we know, what we need to learn, and whether the business has enough potential for us to spend our time filling in the gaps.
And, if you&amp;rsquo;re a freelance designer, podcast producer, or in video production, and you&amp;rsquo;re interested in working on and growing ITS, contact team@gettacklebox.</description></item><item><title>A Framework to Get You Unstuck (featuring an Airstream startup) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220076/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about how early-stage entrepreneurs can get themselves unstuck. It&amp;rsquo;s easy to get paralyzed when the things you do don&amp;rsquo;t lead to the outcomes you want. The key is understanding that in the startup world, results and decisions don&amp;rsquo;t always go hand in hand. Separating them and focusing on stacking good decisions while understanding that the results might be a lagging indicator is your best bet. That&amp;rsquo;s hard to do.</description></item><item><title>20(ish)-Min Skills: Sales 101 For Entrepreneurs That Hate Sales | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220077/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220077/</guid><description>Podcast Description A 20(ish) minute skills episode on sales 101 for entrepreneurs who hate sales. We go through three tactics and a bunch of examples to help you build a system for sales that&amp;rsquo;ll help you grow without making you feel slimy. We set up sales for a sabbaticals as a service startup. And we talk through why entrepreneurs hate sales and how to reframe the whole thing.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Weekly Prioritization and Audit Framework to Help Entrepreneurs Make Great Things | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220078/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Most entrepreneurs struggle with prioritization. When you need to do everything, where do you start? Today we lay out a three-part framework to make sure you&amp;rsquo;re spending your time on the most important stuff. It includes a calendar, a weekly audit, and an environment makeover. Best of all, it works. Hat tip to Finland for the inspiration.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to Test If Your Idea Can Grow Before You Build It (featuring a meeting agenda startup) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220079/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we talk through testing and getting to an idea that can grow before you invest time and money to build it. We do this through the lens of a meeting agenda startup, plus revisit Brian&amp;rsquo;s basketball lesson business and the NYC speakeasy, Please Don&amp;rsquo;t Tell.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What Makes a Great Product? | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220080/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we break down a tough question: What makes a great product? We look at Brian&amp;rsquo;s two favorite products to tease out themes and characteristics we can leverage to build a great first product at a smaller scale.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Strategies for a Crowded Market: Breaking Down Three Coffee Startups | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220081/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Operating in a crowded market with a ton of potential is tempting - and tough. Today, we evaluate companies taking very different approaches to the coffee market. We go deep on Blank Street, Cometeer, and Nguyen Coffee Supply and pull out everything we can learn that&amp;rsquo;ll help you build your business.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to Build The Right Thing (Introducing the Product Pyramid Framework) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220082/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today&amp;rsquo;s episode introduces the Product Pyramid Framework, a tool entrepreneurs who have never built products before can use to make sure they build the right thing. The three part system ensures you&amp;rsquo;re focused on features that&amp;rsquo;ll move the needle and translate into organic growth.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Thing To Do This Weekend If You're Working on a Startup | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220083/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lots of people carve out time to work on their startup ideas. Most people spend that time doing things that don&amp;rsquo;t matter. Today, we talk about something you can do this weekend that&amp;rsquo;ll actually matter for your startup. Like, way more than anything else you could do. We get a little help from Martin Scorsese, a golf startup, and a restaurant that only serves French Dip.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to Become a Startup Idea Machine | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220084/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Getting to a startup idea worth starting is active, not passive. The idea won&amp;rsquo;t just show up - you&amp;rsquo;ll need to find it. And it likely won&amp;rsquo;t be the first idea you&amp;rsquo;ve got. The way to get a great startup idea is to get lots of startup ideas so you&amp;rsquo;ve got context and practice. The way to get lots of startup ideas&amp;hellip; well, that&amp;rsquo;s what the episode is about.</description></item><item><title>How to Evaluate and Choose an Idea Worth Pursuing with Alex White | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220085/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here at Idea to Startup we&amp;rsquo;re obsessed with the process of filtering through and choosing ideas. Today we&amp;rsquo;re joined by Alex White, previously the founder of The Next Big Sound (acquired by Pandora) and current founder of Subcity, and someone with as thoughtful and rigorous an approach around ideation as you&amp;rsquo;ll find. We dig in on how to think through an idea, how to pursue it, and how to decide if it&amp;rsquo;s worth your time.</description></item><item><title>How to Write Great Copy for your Startup | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220086/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Writing copy for a startup is hard, especially when you&amp;rsquo;re thinking it up from scratch. This episode goes through five frameworks that&amp;rsquo;ll help you write copy that converts customers. We&amp;rsquo;ve got a bunch of examples in here and Brian has a sore throat so he &amp;ldquo;sounds pretty cool, actually&amp;rdquo; - his words.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>INTERVIEW: Jonathan Hunt-Glassman, founder @ Oar Health | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220087/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 17:06:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we talk with Jonathan Hunt-Glassman, the founder of Oar Health. Oar Health makes safe, effective medication and convenient care for people who want to drink less or quit drinking altogether. Jonathan went through Tacklebox a few years back and created a path a lot of entrepreneurs with jobs would love to follow - validating, building, and growing before quitting his job to transition to Oar full-time. Since, he&amp;rsquo;s raised funding, grown the team, and is tackling addiction in a unique and highly effective way.</description></item><item><title>Start a Startup in 7(ish) Minutes: Solving Parking in NYC  | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220088/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we&amp;rsquo;re going to start yet another startup in 7(ish) minutes. We&amp;rsquo;ll flesh out an idea and figure out how to test it using four key questions. The problem we&amp;rsquo;ll solve is parking in NYC. As always, if anyone wants to run with this - please do. Reach out if you do. This problem needs a solution.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 100 : How to Design Your Life to Support Building a Startup on the Side | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220089/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 11:38:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220089/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 100th episode of Idea to Startup dives into the most important thing our entrepreneurs with jobs have done to make progress - purposefully designing their lives so that inertia pulls them towards growth, not inaction. We go through how you can design your life to make progress on your startup the norm with a little help from Brian&amp;rsquo;s grandfather, Poppy.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to Stand Out: Differentiate your Startup with Categories | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220090/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220090/</guid><description>Podcast Description The best entrepreneurs choose what they compete against. They stack the deck so their product is overwhelmingly better than the alternative. The key to this is choosing the category your customer sees you in. Choose the category and you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to dictate your competitors and ensure you have a good chance to win. Today we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about choosing categories with a little help from e-bikes, protein bars, and a mattress.</description></item><item><title>How to Guarantee Word of Mouth Growth for Your Startup | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220091/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Your startup will only grow if you design for and facilitate word of mouth. The big mistake people make is thinking their business will generate that WoM growth - the key is making sure the conversation is already happening before you build a product. We&amp;rsquo;ll talk through strategies for this today, with a little help from a wine investing platform and a product to help a two year old sleep.</description></item><item><title>The Three Pillars of an Idea That Can Grow Huge | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220092/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about finding ideas that are primed to grow fast and grow big. As we dug in, we realized this was a great approach for any sized business. There are three pillars for this type of idea, and we&amp;rsquo;ll go through each with a little help from Coke and Pepsi and my grade school friend, Aaron.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Start a Startup in Ten Days using Four Questions: Kitchen Organizer Edition | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220093/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we&amp;rsquo;ll talk through how to test out and build a startup idea in ~10 days by answering four questions. We&amp;rsquo;ll use an idea that&amp;rsquo;s oddly popped up a bunch lately: Kitchen Organizer. We do this with a little help from a story about a poker player and my good friend, Penne Vodka Pete.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Perfect is the Enemy of the Good: Startup Product Edition | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220094/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Simple products win. You probably already knew this, but creating a simple product is harder than it should be. The reason is that a simple product has nothing to do with the product itself. Today we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about Customer Deltas - the most important piece of the puzzle for a simple product that you can build fast and is primed for growth.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to Conquer Irrational Fear as a Startup Founder | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220095/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about the irrational fears that keep entrepreneurs from doing the things they need to do to be successful. We&amp;rsquo;ve got stories about Barney Greengrass, a six year old pedaling on a Peloton with his hands, and a tourist ending up with the perfect order. And, a system to ensure you don&amp;rsquo;t get caught making irrational decisions that hamstring your startup.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Most Interesting Startups are Boring (and how to make sure yours is, too) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220096/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Building a great startup usually isn&amp;rsquo;t rocket science - it often comes down to just trying more things than anyone else does. The hard part about this is the repetition and the mindset - building a system will push you through. Today we talk about that system with a little help from a prolific writer and a startup idea about sabbaticals.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to Build a Startup in a Crowded Market | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220097/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Entrepreneurs are told all the time to avoid crowded markets. There&amp;rsquo;s too much competition, there&amp;rsquo;s too much venture funding, you&amp;rsquo;ll get squashed like a bug. I&amp;rsquo;m not so sure. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot to like about crowded markets - this episode talks through how to carve out your own space and benefit from all the great things crowded markets have to offer.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Formula for Creating Moments Your Customers Will Share | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Creating moments your customers will share is how your startup will grow early on. This episode will teach you how to orchestrate and plan those moments before you&amp;rsquo;ve built a product. Your business will rely on these moments for growth, so we need to figure them out early. Featuring bagels, noodles, and a dog training app.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Don't Bail On Your Startup Idea Right When It's Getting Interesting | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220099/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220099/</guid><description>Podcast Description There&amp;rsquo;s an epidemic of talented entrepreneurs bailing on their startup ideas right before those ideas are about to get interesting. We talk about why and how to avoid it, with a little help from Splash Mountain and a Tacklebox alum.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Startup Practice | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220100/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 13:36:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220100/</guid><description>Podcast Description People are too precious with ideas. The idea you&amp;rsquo;ve got is probably wrong, but the only way you&amp;rsquo;ll get to the right one is working on the wrong one - not waiting for the right one to magically appear. But how do you do that? This episode is about startup practice - how to find and test ideas on the side that&amp;rsquo;ll eventually lead to the one that&amp;rsquo;ll hopefully change your life.</description></item><item><title>Storytelling 101 for Entrepreneurs | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220101/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220101/</guid><description>Podcast Description A storytelling primer for entrepreneurs. Marketing is storytelling, and in this pod we lay out a three step framework for telling exceptional stories that convert customers. This is idiot-proofing - you don&amp;rsquo;t need to be a great marketer or writer or storyteller. You can build effective messaging campaigns if you understand and execute this process.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>BONUS STORY: The Monster and The Girl | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220102/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 16:13:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220102/</guid><description>Podcast Description A bonus short episode for a snowy Friday. A story that might light a bit of a fire under your ass for 2022.
And don&amp;rsquo;t worry, we&amp;rsquo;ll get back to our tactical episodes next Wednesday .
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Secret Pod | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220103/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Startups work best when they&amp;rsquo;re anchored around a secret. A great secret has three characteristics, and Brian goes through those, as well as examples of a few secrets that can anchor a business, in this week&amp;rsquo;s pod.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sell the Position (Brian's favorite episode of the year) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220104/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220104/</guid><description>Podcast Description The last episode of 2021 is Brian&amp;rsquo;s favorite - sell the position. It&amp;rsquo;s rare that a piece of advice truly changes your life. This advice did.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to Not Waste Your Life (most listened to episode of the year) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220105/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220105/</guid><description>Podcast Description How to Not Waste Your Life. This was the most listened to episode of 2022, so we&amp;rsquo;re running it back with a special intro. It&amp;rsquo;s the lesson we all need to hear going into the New Year .
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to Find Problems Worth Solving (and a request for a startup) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220106/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 12:56:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220106/</guid><description>Podcast Description We lay out a framework for finding and evaluating problems and dig into a problem worth solving: single-use plastic from takeout food orders. If you&amp;rsquo;re working on this - reach out.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>You need a bouncer | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220107/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220107/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;re all lugging around metaphorical backpacks. These backpacks are filled with tasks, shoulds, and IOUs. The problem isn&amp;rsquo;t that they exist, it&amp;rsquo;s how easily other people are able to lob things in and how hard it is for us to get them out. This episode talks about how to create a bouncer - to ensure that the only things taking up your consciousness are things you&amp;rsquo;ve chosen, things that will help you move towards your goals.</description></item><item><title>How to get counterintuitive startup ideas | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220108/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220108/</guid><description>Podcast Description If lots of people think your startup idea makes no sense, it&amp;rsquo;s got a much higher likelihood of succeeding. Counterintuitive ideas will buy you time to build, test, and flesh out your product before competitors catch on. Today, we talk through how to come up with and grow counterintuitive ideas while looking at a bonkers business Brian can&amp;rsquo;t get enough of.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Three Things Entrepreneurs Should Do Over Thanksgiving Break | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220109/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we talk through three things entrepreneurs can do over Thanksgiving break - and the next six weeks - to differentiate themselves in 2022. Stories about the fireplace delusion, rainfall in Bermuda, and how to tell sexual partners you&amp;rsquo;ve got chlamydia will help us out.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to create your own MBA in entrepreneurship | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220110/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 12:59:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220110/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you were building an MBA in entrepreneurship from scratch, how would you do it? We built out a framework to design your own program - and just about any other program you&amp;rsquo;d like - on today&amp;rsquo;s pod.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Story 3: How to sell wood for $10 when everyone else sells it for $5 | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220111/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about a guy in the Adirondacks who sells wood for $10 when everyone else around him sells it for $5. He sells 10x more wood than all his competitors and it&amp;rsquo;s all due to being able to answer one question really well. We&amp;rsquo;ll dig into that question and how you can leverage it to build your business on this week&amp;rsquo;s Idea to Startup.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Story 2: How to motivate people | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220112/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220112/</guid><description>Podcast Description The apartment I live in was on the market for a year without a bid, then sold in a bidding war for well above ask in a week. What the heck happened? Today&amp;rsquo;s episode breaks down why people took action (and a framework to create it).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Three Stories To Get You Unstuck - Story 1: Sell The Position | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220113/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220113/</guid><description>Podcast Description People keep telling us they&amp;rsquo;re stuck. The next three pods are stories that&amp;rsquo;ll get your juices flowing. It&amp;rsquo;ll be impossible to be stuck after them. Today&amp;rsquo;s is about Selling The Position - it&amp;rsquo;s probably the most helpful single concept we&amp;rsquo;ve ever discussed on the pod.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to Quit Your Job and Pursue Your Startup Idea | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220114/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lots of people come into our orbit because they&amp;rsquo;d like to get their startup to a point where they can quit their full-time job and transition over. Here&amp;rsquo;s what you need to do before you quit - and what&amp;rsquo;ll happen to you and your idea once you do. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a kick in the ass, this might be it.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to Motivate Customers (and People) feat. Airstreams | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220115/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220115/</guid><description>Podcast Description We leverage Yu-kai Chou&amp;rsquo;s Octalysis Framework to think through motivating customers. We test it out using a startup idea that&amp;rsquo;s come across Brian&amp;rsquo;s desk recently: a network of Airstream trailers, dropped on people&amp;rsquo;s property, that digital nomads can subscribe to. How would we motivate these people to take action? What can we test? The framework leads the way as we kickstart the business.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MAILBAG PART 2: Testing a pasta startup, how niche is too niche, and a structure for dealing with founder stress | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220116/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220116/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two of our Mailbag series, Brian answers listener questions on how to run lean, inexpensive, fast tests on an idea that seemingly has big up front costs (we launch tests for the pasta startup), how niche is too niche, and a framework to deal with stress as a founder.
As always, thank you for the questions, and if you&amp;rsquo;d like to submit a question, email it to team@gettacklebox.</description></item><item><title>MAILBAG: Listener questions on a startup ethos, great marketing, a travel company for couples, and nootropics (sorta) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220117/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brian answers emails from listeners on a startup ethos, examples of great marketing - leveraging behavioral economics to remove friction and The Rent Is Too Damn High guy, nootropics (sort of), and the best inputs for the best outputs. We also start a travel company for couples.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Treading Water Startup (feat. Scorpions and Frogs) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220118/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lots of entrepreneurs spend their time trying to figure out if their startup idea is &amp;ldquo;good.&amp;rdquo; They wonder if they can raise funding and build a team. But so much of our idea evaluation ignores the most fundamental building block of a startup - the magic moment that will spur organic growth. There is no funding or team or business without that initial magic, so maybe the best route is to reverse engineer a business from that moment?</description></item><item><title>Hidden Lottery Tickets | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220119/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you finding your startup&amp;rsquo;s hidden lottery tickets? What are the opportunities hiding in plain sight that will drastically amplify your output? We talk through Bumble, vertical farms, poker, and derivatives trading, and set up prompts for you to identify hidden lottery tickets that&amp;rsquo;ll catalyze your startup.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Vertical Farms, Robert Frost, and Growth | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220120/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220120/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are BACK.
We talk through how to approach a startup idea in a space you aren&amp;rsquo;t in expert in, how to build momentum and make decisions fast, and the problem mindset. We also talk through how everyone was wrong about Robert Frost&amp;rsquo;s The Road Not Taken and what that means for Brian&amp;rsquo;s vertical farm startup.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>INTERVIEW: Jeff Sheldon, Founder @ Ugmonk | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220121/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff Sheldon is the founder of Ugmonk, a company I have an enormous amount of admiration for. It&amp;rsquo;s a thoughtful, purposeful, highly effective business that creates and curates beautifully designed products. Jeff has run and grown the business slowly and sustainably (without funding), building an incredibly engaged customer base. This strong customer affinity allows him to launch products through crowdfunding campaigns without a massive marketing budget.
We talk through how he built Ugmonk, how he thinks about curation and design, and we go deep on his most recent Kickstarter campaign - a ~half million dollar raise for Analog.</description></item><item><title>How to Not Waste Your Life | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220122/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 12:32:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220122/</guid><description>Podcast Description The past 15 months kicked our butts. We all picked up some terrible habits, and we get a pass for it. But now it&amp;rsquo;s time to dig ourselves out of the hole.
This episode goes through three questions that&amp;rsquo;ll help you refocus, tactics to find your North Star, and a framework to reset your inputs. There&amp;rsquo;s never been a better time to build a startup, and if you haven&amp;rsquo;t got an idea or are deciding between a few - this is the place to start.</description></item><item><title>Inertia - The Only Thing That Matters | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220123/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Inertia is the tendency to not change. Everyone is on a path driven by inertia, which leads just about everyone to always repeat the same things. Which is a problem if you&amp;rsquo;re starting a startup, since you need people to do something different (buy your thing).
In this episode we talk through inertia and how to build startups that leverage it vs. fight it, with cameos from Javier the Hot Air Balloon Guy, Erin Andrews, and Donald Trump.</description></item><item><title>INTERVIEW: Tom Eisenmann (HBS) on Why Startups Fail | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220124/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we&amp;rsquo;ve got Tom Eisenmann on the pod. He&amp;rsquo;s an entrepreneurship teacher at HBS and the author of the white-hot startup book &amp;ldquo;Why Startups Fail.&amp;rdquo; We had a blast talking through all the mistakes startups make and the best ways to avoid them. We also talk through how to validate when you&amp;rsquo;ve got big up front costs, when domain experts are important (and when they&amp;rsquo;re not), and how to start the gig-economy version of the private chef.</description></item><item><title>How to Choose the Right Customer (ITS Classic) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220125/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Theres one decision that early stage founders make that can drastically tip the tables in their favor. This is a tactical episode, helping you push through the critical question of what customer segment to target first. We delve into a framework to help you identify and evaluate customer segments as your startup evolves.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is Your Startup Idea Good? (ITS Classic) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220126/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220126/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week&amp;rsquo;s ITS Classic covers whether your startup idea is any good. We talk through a failed startup Brian ran called Find Your Lobster, present a framework to ensure you choose the startup idea that best matches your skillset, and how to stay away from the dreaded Whisper Idea.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How To Be A Great Storyteller (ITS Classic) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220127/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220127/</guid><description>Podcast Description I recently asked a good investor friend of mine what he thought the most underrated but important skill for entrepreneurs in 2021 was. He responded quickly - storytelling. The amount of compelling copy a startup needs to write in 2021 is astounding - from ads to emails to socials to pitch decks - and the base rate has gotten extremely high. A startup can only be as successful as it&amp;rsquo;s messaging, and that all starts with a founder&amp;rsquo;s ability to tell the story of their customer and their product.</description></item><item><title>How to Prioritize and Build a Personal Operating System (ITS classic) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220128/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220128/</guid><description>Podcast Description We revisit an episode from the early days of the podcast on an operating system for founders. Not everything I say here has stuck, and not everything I do I recommend. But the bones of this podcast are rock solid. Being thoughtful about how you work and what you work on is the key for building a startup in the margins. And, everyone has more margins now. If you&amp;rsquo;re one of the people who isn&amp;rsquo;t going to have to commute again, this is your chance.</description></item><item><title>How to lose 1.8 billion dollars in 10 days | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220129/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Predicting a startup will fail is like betting every number on the roulette wheel except that green double zero and then puffing out your chest when one of your numbers hits. It&amp;rsquo;s just not impressive to predict that something going up against overwhelming odds won&amp;rsquo;t beat those odds.
And yet&amp;hellip;. Sometimes people build startups like horses asses. And in that case, they need to be called out.
This podcast originally aired the day Quibi launched back in April of 2020 and gave the company 18 months to survive.</description></item><item><title>Curiosity and Space | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220130/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220130/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;re told the curious entrepreneurs are the most successful. But we&amp;rsquo;re also told we need to be experts for our startups to work. How do you balance being curious and learning with being seen as an expert?
Today, we explore curiosity through one of the best founders to ever go through Tacklebox, and through another founder just getting started building something in the Space&amp;hellip;space.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Survivorship Bias, Base Rates, and Librarians | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220131/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220131/</guid><description>Podcast Description You get startup advice constantly. Your ears probably perk up when it comes from an entrepreneur that&amp;rsquo;s been successful. But what should you listen to? What&amp;rsquo;s still relevant? How can you evaluate if the tactics an entrepreneur suggests are right for you?
Today we talk through how to take advice, how to check base rates, and how to decide on the right strategies for your startup. Plus, librarians, salespeople, and adultery.</description></item><item><title>Let It Go | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220132/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about how to pick what you work on - we need to ensure you&amp;rsquo;re spending your time on things that&amp;rsquo;ll actually matter. We&amp;rsquo;ll do it through the lens of the greatest company ever built.
We also wrap up Problems + Opportunities and get some guidance from Peter Drucker.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>This Too Shall Pasta (Vision + Part II of Problems vs. Opportunities) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220133/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last week, we laid out the Problems vs. Opportunities (PVO) framework. This week, we dive deeper into the &amp;ldquo;vision&amp;rdquo; part of the framework, helping you identify and follow your North Star.
We use This Too Shall Pasta, a gluten free DTC pasta company, to dig deeper into the PVO process.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Problems and Opportunities | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220134/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we&amp;rsquo;re talking about problems vs. opportunities. It&amp;rsquo;s easy for entrepreneurs to spend their time putting out fires - they&amp;rsquo;re often the only ones who will. But it&amp;rsquo;s far more important to block off time to identify and pursue opportunities that&amp;rsquo;ll create asymmetric value.
We discuss a framework for identifying, prioritizing, and pursuing opportunities. Also, Steph Curry and how to say &amp;ldquo;razorblades&amp;rdquo; with a flawless Australian accent.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Case For Now | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220135/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Three numbers and a story show the path for startups during a uniquely difficult but opportunity filled time. The goal of today&amp;rsquo;s podcast is grounding and motivation. And pizza dough.
We talk through opportunities for compound interest, knowledge growth, and the $32 trillion dollars that will change the startup market.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What To Do About Competition (The Gift of "Which") | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220136/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220136/</guid><description>Podcast Description What do you do when you stumble upon, or get smacked in the face by, a competitor? How do you react? What do you focus on? What do you stop doing?
Can you still&amp;hellip; exist?
We talk through exactly what to do with competitors and discuss the &amp;ldquo;Gift of Which.&amp;rdquo;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to Sell A Protein Bar in Seven(ish) Minutes | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220137/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220137/</guid><description>Podcast Description What if you&amp;rsquo;ve got a product and no customer? We go through an email from a listener who makes the world&amp;rsquo;s best protein bars but has absolutely no idea who to sell them to. We use storytelling archetypes to find the best possible customer to catalyze the business.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mini Series Ep 3: A Bunch of Tests and an Epiphany | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220138/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220138/</guid><description>Podcast Description The third in our mini-series where we&amp;rsquo;re starting a startup live on the pod. Today, we take what we learned from customer interviews and synthesize it into tests in real life. Step by step on customer, channel, landing page, and call-to-action.
Plus, why atheists don&amp;rsquo;t sell their soul and York Peppermint Patties.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mini Series Ep 2 - We're Starting a Startup - Making Customer Interviews Doable | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220139/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode Two of our miniseries &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re Starting a Startup&amp;rdquo; details our first seven days after we decided to pursue an idea live. We talk customer interview strategy and stack, get a bunch of lukewarm feedback, and play clips from some of the interviews we ran. We also talk about Baked By Melissa cupcakes an uncomfortable amount.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mini Series Kickoff - Picking The Startup Idea We'll Start | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220140/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220140/</guid><description>Podcast Description It was bound to happen. We&amp;rsquo;re starting a startup idea on&amp;hellip; Idea to Startup. Someone reached out basically daring us to, and we couldn&amp;rsquo;t say no.
Today, we&amp;rsquo;ll run three startup ideas through our Idea Resume framework that evaluates an idea at the earliest stages. Then, we&amp;rsquo;ll pick the one we&amp;rsquo;ll start over the next set of episodes.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How To Get Your First 1,000 Customers (feat. Pizza) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220141/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Getting your first 1,000 customers is hard, particularly when you&amp;rsquo;re thinking about it wrong.
We talk through how Push for Pizza and Slice took different approaches to growth in the pizza space.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Sasquatch Problem (Are You Passionate Enough About Your Startup Idea?) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220142/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220142/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;re told we need to be head over heels passionate about our startup for it to succeed. Is that&amp;hellip; true? What if we haven&amp;rsquo;t found something we&amp;rsquo;re that passionate about - does that mean we shouldn&amp;rsquo;t start it? How do you find something you&amp;rsquo;re passionate enough about to build a company around? Is Sasquatch Real?
The answers to these and more on this week&amp;rsquo;s Idea to Startup Pod.</description></item><item><title>Three Stories for People Starting Startups in 2021 | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220143/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220143/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;ll look back on 2021 as the best year to start a startup in the past 50. The world we&amp;rsquo;re returning to will be a lot different from the one we left, and people will start meaningful companies to bridge that gap. Hopefully, one of those people is you.
Here are three stories that&amp;rsquo;ll help you position yourself and your startup to succeed in 2021.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Make A Billion Dollars | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220144/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220144/</guid><description>Podcast Description That title is even spammier than last week. But it isnt. Today, well talk about how thinking through how to build a billion dollar business is actually a really useful exercise, too.
Today, were going to fix Goodreads and drink a bunch of egg nog. Lets see how that goes.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Make $1,000 Today | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220145/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220145/</guid><description>Podcast Description That title sure does sound spammy. But it isnt. Today, well talk about how thinking through how youd make $1,000 today is the best way to actually start a startup.
This episode is for people who are stuck - people who want to start something but cant figure out the best way to go about doing it. People who are overwhelmed by what starting a startup might entail.</description></item><item><title>The Holiday Mailbag | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220146/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we take a bunch of questions from ITS listeners. We talk through startup ideas for 2021, founder superpowers, and hutzpah.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Counterintuitive Way To Get Your First Customers | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220147/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220147/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode focuses on the 4 best emails written on Black Friday, and the framework each used to break through the clutter.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Will I Know? | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220148/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 16:03:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Entrepreneurs favorite questions all begin with how will I know..
The real answer is, you never know anything for sure. This podcast is about the process of entrepreneurship - how to set up and run lightweight tests to get a unique perspective no one else does.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Do The Thing (Motion vs. Action) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220149/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Its easy to do everything but the thing that matters. Today we talk about how to identify the thing that matters and how to combat all of our instincts that tell us to push back against real reflection.
We go through a few examples, including Ro.co, business school, and writing books, focusing on Motion vs. Action.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Are You Good Enough? | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220150/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Imposter syndrome kills more startups than not finding a cofounder, competition, or funding ever could.
Today, were talking about whether youre good enough to compete in the startup world. Can you really turn this into your livelihood? Can you thrive?
What happens if you dont?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to be Resilient (feat. IOUs) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220151/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Founders need to be resilient. Its beaten into our heads over and over. But what resilience is - and how to be resilient - is misunderstood.
Today well talk about all the IOUs you consciously and unconsciously write all day, and how theyre sapping you of your best work. Well finish with tactics to combat these IOUs. Go get em.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to Differentiate Your Startup (feat. Crabs + Running Shoes) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220152/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Meaningful differentiation is hard to come by. Most startups pay lip service to differentiation and pay the price through higher customer acquisition costs and lower retention rates. A truly differentiated product is necessary for a healthy funnel - acquisition, conversion, retention, referral.
Today we talk through questions thatll help you differentiate your startup with the help of On, an apparel company that leveraged business model innovation to create a truly differentiated product in a crowded space.</description></item><item><title>Start a Wine Company in 17 Minutes | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220153/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220153/</guid><description>Podcast Description Transcript</description></item><item><title>Whisper Ideas | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220154/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220154/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you ever find yourself whispering your startup idea at a coffee shop, this podcast is for you.
We dig in on what a good startup idea actually looks like and how to find the right idea for you.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to test a startup idea in 7 minutes | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220155/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to get a customer to choose you (and bagels) | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220156/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 10:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220156/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the first episode of season 3 we talk through the paradox of choice, how to facilitate decisions in your customers, how to build a brand, and bagels.
We touch on Dan Arielys book Predictably Irrational, digging in on how architecting the environment for your customers will drastically increase your chances at conversion.
We also talk about the two bagel shops that were next to each other in NYC, and why each wound up with a far stronger brand because the other existed.</description></item><item><title>INTERVIEW: Daina Trout on building Health-Ade from a kombucha-making operation in her kitchen to one of the fastest growing beverage brands in the U.S. | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220157/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 10:00:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220157/</guid><description>Podcast Description Weve had lots of conversations with successful entrepreneurs, but Im not sure Ive ever been more impressed than I was after speaking with Daina. Great entrepreneurs have a bias towards action. Dainas action-based philosophy is incredible and eye-opening. She talks through how to build a massive brand in a competitive space, how to make decisions in the face of uncertainty, and how she was able to turn three friends with a weekly entrepreneurship club into a company reportedly valued at over a half billion dollars.</description></item><item><title>How to lose $1.8 billion dollars in 10 days | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220158/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 10:00:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220158/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about Quibi. A company that raised nearly $2 billion dollars before launching a product earlier this April. Quibi made the same foundational mistakes most founders make and won&amp;rsquo;t be around in 18 months. We&amp;rsquo;ll talk through those mistakes - and how you can avoid them - on this week&amp;rsquo;s Idea to Startup.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>INTERVIEW: Jennifer Goggin on building Startle, a tech studio that bridges the gap between research and impactful companies. | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220159/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 10:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer Goggin, whos founded multiple startups in the food space and now runs Startle - one of the coolest companies Ive heard about in a while - stopped by.
Startle is a tech transformation studio that partners with researchers in the food tech space to bridge the gap between research and help build impactful companies.
We get into what that is and how that works, what Jennifer looks for in super early stage companies, what she learned from building her previous startups and exiting Pippin Foods, and ton more.</description></item><item><title>INTERVIEW: Marc and Ashley Merrill on building Riot Games and Lunya, the role of a leader during times of uncertainty, and their perspectives on how to build a business. | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220160/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 10:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220160/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marc and Ashley Merrill are married, have kids, and both run fast growing businesses. The thought of handling all that makes my head hurt, but they&amp;rsquo;ve done it incredibly well. They talk through how they built these businesses, how to prioritize time and effort, how to be steady during times of uncertainty, and how to validate and disprove ideas. It&amp;rsquo;s an awesome conversation that taught me a ton.</description></item><item><title>INTERVIEW: Christoph Bertsch on building Vejo (and multiple other startups) and how to manage the long-game of entrepreneurship. | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220161/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220161/</guid><description>Podcast Description Christoph Bertsch, founder of Vejo among multiple other startups, stops by in what is one of my favorite conversations yet. He talks through what it really takes to start a company, the differences between b2b and b2c, fundraising vs. not, supply chain management, and team building. This is a wonderful, fun conversation that&amp;rsquo;ll brighten your day. Heads up for some curses - they flow pretty freely from Christoph :)</description></item><item><title>Ladders and Lobsters | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220162/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220162/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;Chaos isn&amp;rsquo;t a pit, chaos is a ladder.&amp;rdquo; Coronavirus is an inflection point that will change all sorts of behavior and create all sorts of opportunity for startups. This podcast looks at the opportunities that&amp;rsquo;ll be created and how you should approach them within the startup world.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>INTERVIEW: Agatha Kulaga on building Ovenly, turning your creative outlet into a scalable business, and baking the best cookies I've ever tasted. | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220163/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Agatha Kulaga - co-founder of Ovenly, an award-winning retail and wholesale bakery with a global footprint - stops by to talk through the early days. How do you turn your creative outlet into a business? How do you scale high quality? How do you build a distinct brand as a wholesaler? A great conversation with a very smart and talented founder.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to Evaluate a Startup Idea | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220164/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220164/</guid><description>Podcast Description What should it look like when you have a startup idea? What do you do first? How do you know if it&amp;rsquo;s a good idea for you? We go through seven archetypes of innovation, then go through a framework to understand if you&amp;rsquo;re uniquely positioned to pursue that idea. We then apply it all to a startup idea Brian has. This is the first of a few episodes testing out an idea Brian has in the food space.</description></item><item><title>INTERVIEW: Brian Linton on building United By Blue, removing millions of pounds of trash from the ocean, and scaling a purpose-driven brand. | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220165/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brian Linton, founder of outdoor apparel and accessory brand United By Blue, stops by to tell the story of how he built a purpose-driven brand that&amp;rsquo;s removed over 2 million pounds of trash from the ocean. He talks through the earliest days - how driving up and down the east coast selling t-shirts gave him the foundation to build an omni-channel brand - and the tradeoffs necessary to build a profitable brand that also has a clear philanthropic North Star.</description></item><item><title>The Selfish Score: How to build a great customer acquisition funnel | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220166/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220166/</guid><description>Podcast Description To build a great company, you need to build a healthy customer acquisition funnel. You need a consistent flow of customers coming in the top, tactics to engage them as you build your brand and story, &amp;amp; urgency to get them to pull the trigger. The way to measure how effective your startup can be at this is to measure how selfish you can be with customers. How often can you contact them before they get pissed?</description></item><item><title>INTERVIEW: Rob Petrozzo on building Rally Rd, how to test startup ideas before you quit your job, storytelling, leveraging personas for brand and marketing, raising money, and differentiation. | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220167/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rob Petrozzo, co-founder of Rally Rd, stops by for an awesome interview that at it&amp;rsquo;s core is about storytelling. Rally Rd is growing incredibly fast, but the early days were tougher to navigate. Rob talks through how building storytelling into the DNA of the product laid the groundwork for future growth, and how early stage founders can do the same. We touch on personas, customer segmentation, fundraising, growth, team building and composition, design, and more.</description></item><item><title>Two mental models that'll make or break your startup + a mystery company that can't stop growing because of them | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220168/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220168/</guid><description>Podcast Description There&amp;rsquo;s a mystery company that is one of the 10 best performing stocks since 2010. You&amp;rsquo;ve heard of them. You&amp;rsquo;ve eaten (hint) their product. You&amp;rsquo;d never in a million years guess who they are.
They&amp;rsquo;ve grown because of two mental models, and we break down how you can leverage them for your startup.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>INTERVIEW: Ashley Merrill on building Lunya, the beauty of capital-constrained businesses, true differentiation, and self-doubt | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220169/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ashley Merrill, the founder of premium sleepwear brand Lunya, stops by and delivers a masterclass on how to build a brand in the DTC era. She talks about the earliest days, about what differentiation in a crowded space really looks like, about pricing and business model, brick and mortar, focus and prioritization, and self-doubt.
If you&amp;rsquo;re a startup founder interested in brand, or trying to start a DTC company, get a notebook ready.</description></item><item><title>The Secret Formula to Hot Ones' Success | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220170/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hot Ones is a show on Youtube that you&amp;rsquo;ve probably heard of. A host interviews guests while they each eat 10 progressively hotter hot wings. The growth is preposterous - episodes routinely get over 10 million views. Hot Ones structure is brilliant - it creates and drives the growth - and it&amp;rsquo;s something you can (and better) implement in your startup.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>INTERVIEW: Marc Merrill on building Riot Games (League of Legends), prioritization frameworks, and focused growth | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220171/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220171/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marc Merrill, founder of Riot Games, joins the podcast to talk about building League of Legends into a cultural phenomenon (with over $20bn in revenue).
We discuss the early days - how he built a complex product for customers with high expectations, fundraising, managing people, growth, prioritization, and more. It&amp;rsquo;s an amazing conversation with one of the sharpest and most thoughtful people I&amp;rsquo;ve met. Enjoy!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>You Should Start a Startup in 2020 | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220172/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fewer new businesses were started in 2019 than in 1970. That&amp;rsquo;s terrible. We look at the two cognitive biases holding you back, and lay out a framework to help you overcome them and start your startup.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Idea to Startup Season 2: Build Your Startup in 2020 | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220173/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220173/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fewer companies were started in 2019 than in 1970. Thats preposterous. This is the single best time in human history to start a company - so why arent more people doing it? Season Two of Idea to Startup digs into why. Brian speaks with successful founders about how they navigated the tricky early stages, and delivers solo episodes on tactics founders can implement to start something in 2020. This is the year to start your company, and this is the podcast to help you do it.</description></item><item><title>INTERVIEW: Dave Idell on building Croissant, a flexible coworking company competing with giants. | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220174/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220174/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dave Idell is the founder of Croissant, a flexible coworking company beloved by freelancers and entrepreneurs around the world. We talk about the early days - how he tested the idea, how they grew with some counter-intuitive and aggressive decisions, and how he thinks about growth. We also talk through his thoughts on early stage founders and the stuff they should nail down early. Enjoy!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>INTERVIEW: Rich Fulop on Building Brooklinen, the Internets Favorite Sheets | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220175/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220175/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rich and Vicki Fulop built Brooklinen after realizing there wasnt an easy way to find and buy high quality sheets. There were no strong brands, no transparency into manufacturing - nothing they valued in a product.
This interview is about how two founders turned that core insight and little else (no textile background, no knowledge of the bedding industry, etc.) into a global brand and the sheets I happily sleep on every night (and would whether Rich came on the podcast or not).</description></item><item><title>How to Leverage Storytelling Archetypes for Your Startup | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220176/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220176/</guid><description>Podcast Description People probably wont remember your startup, but theyll remember a story. Today we lean on Pixars 22 Rules of Storytelling to help you tell a story that breaks through to your customer and changes behavior.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>INTERVIEW: Kim Kaupe on Building Superfan with No Funding | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220177/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220177/</guid><description>Podcast Description Were speaking with Kim Kaupe, the founder of Superfan, a company built to give fans unparalleled opportunity for engagement, working with clients like the Red Sox, Shawn Mendes, Carrie Underwood, Paul McCartney &amp;amp; way more.Kim has built Superfan over the past 8 years with no funding. Shes built a powerful personal brand that has her LinkedIn startup videos amassing 10s of thousands of views. She talks personal brand, how to build a startup without funding, making tough decisions &amp;amp; much more.</description></item><item><title>INTERVIEW: Leo and Oliver Kremer on Building a Burrito Empire at Dos Toros | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220178/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220178/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, were talking burritos. Leo and Oliver Kremer founded Dos Toros in 2009 because they couldnt find the Mission-style burritos they grew up with on the west coast anywhere in NYC. However, they werent cooks and had never been in the restaurant or food space.
We talk to them about the early days - about validating the need, creating the supply chain, getting into brick and mortar, creating a culture, and growth.</description></item><item><title>How Do You Find Founder/Startup Fit? | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220179/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220179/</guid><description>Podcast Description You need two things to build a great startup: specific knowledge and a lever to amplify that knowledge. On todays pod, well start a CBD startup with specific knowledge and leverage mind, and hear how Tejas, founder of Via (a Tacklebox founder) was able to build a great business on the back of a mental model.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>INTERVIEW: Elizabeth Yin, founder &amp; GP @ Hustle Fund, where they invest in hilariously early founders | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220180/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Elizabeth Yin is a founder and general partner at Hustle Fund, where she invests in hilariously early founders. Prior to Hustle Fund, she ran the accelerator program at 500 Startups, started Launchbit (acq. 2014), and she writes my favorite VC blog @ http://elizabethyin.com.We cover a lot of ground, including who should and shouldnt raise funding, how to build a customer base pre-product, how to find angel investors, and how to prioritize during the early stages of your startup.</description></item><item><title>How to Prioritize as an Early-Stage Startup | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220181/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Entrepreneurs can do anything, but they cant do everything. How do you prioritize early on? How do you differentiate? This episode presents a framework thatll ensure you work on the things that give your startup its best chance at success.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>INTERVIEW: Ben Conniff on Building Lukes Lobster | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220182/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220182/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ben and Luke, the founders of Lukes Lobster, knew how to make a killer lobster roll when they decided to start Lukes Lobster, a lobster shack in the East Village in 2009. They didnt know much else. Ben talks through how they were able to build an incredible company with locations all over the globe while keeping sustainability as a top priority. We focus on the early days, discussing tactics and learnings that will be extraordinarily helpful for our early stage founders.</description></item><item><title>How to Choose the Right Customer | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220183/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 12:43:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220183/</guid><description>Podcast Description Theres one decision that early stage founders make that can drastically tip the tables in their favor. This is a tactical episode, helping you push through the critical question of what customer segment to target first. We delve into a framework to help you identify and evaluate customer segments as your startup evolves.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>INTERVIEW: Katherine Krug on Building BetterCo | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220184/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 12:34:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220184/</guid><description>Podcast Description We chatted with Katherine Krug, founder of BetterCo. This conversation is packed with insight - you&amp;rsquo;ll need a notebook handy as you listen. Katherine takes us through the tactics and tools she used to ideate and develop BetterBack, a product that raised over $3mm on Kickstarter (first solo female founder to do so). We then touch on validation techniques, not raising funding, life design frameworks, and prioritization. She also gives an amazing answer to the &amp;ldquo;Taco Truck&amp;rdquo; question.</description></item><item><title>Is Your Startup Idea Good? | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220185/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 19:29:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220185/</guid><description>Podcast Description A walk down memory lane checking in on Brian&amp;rsquo;s past startups and how you can make sure you&amp;rsquo;re starting a company that has a shot at working out.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>INTERVIEW: Joey Cofone on Building Baron Fig | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220186/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 13:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220186/</guid><description>Podcast Description We chatted with Joey Cofone, founder of Baron Fig, about the early days of building the company. He touches on a bunch of helpful topics, from breaking through to your customer with his archetype of the Attention Pie, to how non-designers can prioritize design, to building a company without outside funding.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Start Here | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220187/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220187/</guid><description>Podcast Description Most startups fail. Entrepreneurs assume there are a bunch of reasons for this, but there&amp;rsquo;s really only one. Your startup will fail because of customer indifference.
This episode explores in detail a few examples of startups that have avoided this fate, and lays out a pragmatic approach to avoiding it with your idea.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Idea to Startup Teaser | Idea to Startup</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7120220188/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 15:18:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7120220188/</guid><description>Podcast Description Less than 1% of all businesses raise Venture Capital money. Yet that&amp;rsquo;s all we hear about. How can you raise money? How can you build something attractive to VCs?
This podcast is for entrepreneurs that want to build real businesses. Businesses that are profitable, businesses that customers love, and businesses that will transform the founder&amp;rsquo;s life.
We&amp;rsquo;ll focus on early tactics that allow you to go from idea to initial product without relying on funding.</description></item></channel></rss>