<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Martin Lewis Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-martin-lewis-podcast/</link><description>Recent content in The Martin Lewis Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 17:49:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-martin-lewis-podcast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The terrible human cost of scams, and finally, a cheap energy deal | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 17:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610001/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week’s episode, Martin gives listeners his advice on how to spot a scam and hears the terrible experience of ‘Lisa’, who was scammed by criminals using Martin’s name. Martin also has some energy saving deals to share, and answers more of your questions on personal finance.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to understand: Pensions, APRs, Economy, Tax, Energy, Insurance, Shares &amp; more | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 16:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610002/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week, it’s a “Tell Us” special with Martin. He answers your personal finance questions on everything from pensions to tax, and energy to APRs. Plus Nihal makes his way out of the 5 Live show and into Martin’s podcast-only space for a special Mastermind. Can he finally get to grips with Martin’s question? Listen to find out.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Call centre staff secret tips &amp; unpleasant issues: wills, power of attorney &amp; more | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Martin hears about how to get the best service from call centres from those who’ve worked in them. He also talks about the importance of setting up a will and power of attorney, and finally finds out if Nihal has done his.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Beat the 5% energy price hike? Autumn Statement practicals &amp; Richard Osman! | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610004/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks podcast, Martin discusses the 5% energy price hike and gives his reaction to the Autumn Statement. Plus a surprise Mastermind appearance from a special guest!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to get a free flight upgrade and how to cut credit card costs even if rejected for 0% | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 17:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Martin talks about how to get free flight upgrades and how to cut your credit card interest even if rejected for 0%. He also has tips on how you and a friend can ear £50 each for switching energy providers and the best way your kids can get an 'actual' letter from Santa this Christmas.
02.36 Flight upgrades 05.10 Inflation rate 11.32 More flight upgrades 20.35 Credit card interest rates
36:00 Matin's tips on how you and a friend can make £50 by switching energy companies 37:28 Martin's tips on how your kids can get an 'actual' letter from Santa 39:54 More flight upgrades 44:12 Mastermind: how much interest can your children earn before it is taxable?</description></item><item><title>How £1 could make 1st time buyers £1,000s… | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Martin talks about Lifetime ISAs and how you can time your energy usage to make you money. He has tips on the most cost-effective bank cards to use abroad as well as some of the best deals on some Christmas drinks. And this week’s ‘Tell Us’ focusses on great customer service.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Wallet workout, admin anxiety and acts of financial kindness | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610007/</guid><description>Podcast Description He also quizzes Nihal on where he is up to with making a will, and they discuss how to deal with financial anxiety. Plus, this week’s ‘Tell Us’ is all about acts of financial kindness.
03:22 Nihal’s Will
13:30 Wallet Workout
27:10 Administration anxiety 43:50 Mastermind
50:30 Tips
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Can you reclaim PPI again &amp; 1m+ owed money back on student loans | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 18:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610008/</guid><description>Podcast Description All former students with student loans should check if they can reclaim £100s or even £1,000s. Martin explains who is eligible and how to reclaim.
Also PPI reclaiming is back. New legal action means you could you reclaim £1,000s (even if you were paid before) if you had a loan, credit card, car finance, catalogue debt etc. Listen to find out if you are eligible to reclaim and how to get the money if you are.</description></item><item><title>Car insurance up 41% on average, home insurance too, how to beat the hikes | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 17:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Martin talking about insurance and his advice on what to do about a cost we know is climbing at the moment. He has tips on how to get the best deals on your car and home insurance renewals.
He also looks at financial education in schools.
01:21 Nihal’s Will 03:04 Financial education in schools
09:05 Cost of Insurance 26:28 Life in you thirties
41:51 Mastermind
48:37 Podcast Tips</description></item><item><title>Free Wills and a Brown Trouser phone in… | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 17:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Martin explains how to get a free solicitor-drafted will and Nihal’s rap career showcases the importance of having a pension.
He also looks at the importance of having a power of attorney, he answers your questions and has some tips on where to find cheap toys and cheap make up.
02:21 Tell Us 03:55 How to get a free solicitor drafted Will 14:51 Brown Trouser phone in 23:25 More Tell Us 29:18 Mastermind 38:08 Podcast-only tips</description></item><item><title>Cut energy bills, fix savings and free Greggs | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 18:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Martin is back with a bumper episode. Find out the savings account you need to know about, why even though energy prices are lower some people could be paying more this winter and also the action that you need to take this weekend to keep your bills as low as possible. Plus how you could be paid to insure your phone, free Greggs and Martin finds out the financial nuggets that older people would love to tell their younger, working selves.</description></item><item><title>Teen money special: Lessons for everyone | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Martin joins the 5live Teen 23 Summit to give financial advice to teenagers and students, with a guide to savings, inflation, credit cards and money that apply to everyone.
00:00 Introduction
05:58 Maintenance loans and top uni tips
22:34 Tell Us
27:05 Questions from teens
34:17 Podcast-only tips, National Trust and more
36:54 More teen questions
43:19 More Tell Us
45:23 Mastermind
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Make £100s in time for Christmas, and state pension boosting | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 19:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610013/</guid><description>Podcast Description With around 100 days until Christmas, Martin looks at the financial opportunities to make some more money to pay for it – and how to cut costs. And with the pensions 'triple lock' in the news again we look at how to boost your state pension – more than 800,000 people could be missing out on extra pension credits. Plus you ‘tell us’ the strangest things you found left behind, when you moved in to a new home.</description></item><item><title>Huge best buy savings, and are you due flight compo? | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 17:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Martin is back to talk about the best savings accounts out there at the moment. Advice on how to get your money back if your flight is delayed or cancelled. And you ‘tell us’ your childhood money memories.
01:36 Intro
09:07 Saving Accounts
16:20 Flight Compensation
44:10 Mastermind
49:37 Podcast Tips
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Are cash ISA’s ni-sa? &amp; will lower inflation mean cheaper mortgages? | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 16:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Martin explains why Inflation is down and whether mortgage rates will follow, why you should open or reopen a cash ISA and Mortgage Charter help, should you access it and how do you do it?
PLUS what is a day?... (When you’re holiday roaming on your phone)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Top 10 holiday tips &amp; energy switches are back | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 09:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Martin Lewis gives you some top tips on how to save money when going on holiday. Energy switches are back - Martin talks you through all you need to know.
Plus, you 'tell us' your experiences of living abroad and how it compares to life in the UK.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Uni costs to increase 50% – Everything you need to know | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 18:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Martin Lewis explains all you need to know about student finance including the changes coming THIS September with a new plan (Plan 5)
Martin is joined by three prospective university students from Westminster Kingsway College and parents concerned about funding their children through university. AND a warning for anybody on a fixed rate energy tariff as well as good news for First Direct customers. PLUS Martin is featured in Succession… sort of.</description></item><item><title>Are you missing out on £100,000+? Meter reading week and Dead Ringers.... | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 17:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Martin Lewis live from LORDS! He responds to the Chancellor’s mortgage charter announcement and talks about what else the government could do to cut the cost of living. 4 ways you may be missing out on THOUSANDS of pounds!
PLUS how to reduce your water bill and of course… many, many cricket puns.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>My mortgage meet with the Chancellor, should you overpay? – and travel tips | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 15:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Martin comes to the podcast straight from Number 11 after an emergency meeting with The Chancellor over mortgages. So Martin talks mortgages rates and whether you should overpay your mortgage with savings or extra cash AND some very important bonus travel tips if you’re planning a holiday abroad. PLUS Nihal throws a twist in the show with some Mastermind antics and you ‘tell us’ your favourite free activities to do with your kids over the summer.</description></item><item><title>Pay up to £800 get £6,000 – HUGE boost to your state pension. | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 18:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610020/</guid><description>Podcast Description The deadline for buying back National Insurance contributions to boost your state pension has been extended to 2025. Martin explains why the deadline has been extended, how to check if you should be doing it and shares the success stories of those who have already done it, got £1,000s and transformed their finances. And in Mastermind the stakes are higher than ever as Martin DOUBLES the points… will Nihal be able continue his winning streak under the pressure?</description></item><item><title>Mortgage mayhem, energy fixes, car insurance &amp; Tesco tips | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Martin talks your through how to beat the current mortgage mayhem, with help from Andrew Montlake, Managing Director of the mortgage brokerage Coreco.
Can you get a fix on your energy bills and should you? How to triple your Tesco Clubcard credit AND podcast exclusive tips to help drive down car insurance costs. PLUS You ‘tell us’ your tales of the financial kindness of strangers…
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Energy Price Cap Decoded (&amp; new 4.25% savings) | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 16:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610022/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Martin talks you through everything you need to know about the latest energy price cap. What will you pay? How does it work? Are fixes coming back? Plus standing charges, switching and pre pay help!
You ‘tell us’ how your energy usage has changed over the last two years.
AND will Nihal finally get a Mastermind right, or will he go off the rails?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Are you due new energy compensation? Plus renters rights (&amp; wrongs)… | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 17:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610023/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you’re struggling to pay your rent, Martin shares his top tips. Plus how to check if you are due compensation from your energy firm and - is the energy price cap coming down in July? It’s National Numeracy Day too, so Martin explains why you should shy away from numbers. And you ‘tell us’ the WORST gifts you’ve been given…
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to check if you’re owed £100s of energy credit and are 100% mortgages good? | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 17:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is your electricity and gas provider sitting on £100’s of YOUR money? Martin explains why May is the PERFECT TIME to get that money back! Have you been considering a 100% mortgage? Martin explores whether it could help you get on the property ladder. You ‘tell us’ your best birthday presents and Martin reveals Nihal’s ‘secret commercial venture’ in this weeks’ Mastermind. Plus FINALLY podcast producer Lillie-Mae gets an official nickname!</description></item><item><title>Scam-busters, the best debit card and is cash king? | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 17:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610025/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Martin Lewis podcast is here and it’s an emotional one. As it is announced that the UK is to ban all cold calls selling financial products as part of a national crackdown on scams, Martin reveals that a relative of his was the victim of a scam call earlier this week – while he was in discussions with the government about the policy. Did you know 41% of crime in the UK is now fraud?</description></item><item><title>Are your savings safe in the bank? (and paying to squeeze blackheads) | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 17:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610026/</guid><description>Podcast Description With some uncertainty in the banking world, Martin talks you through how safe your savings are and how to make the most of the savings you have.
Martin also answers your questions including ‘What is better: a Help to buy ISA or a Lifetime ISA?’ and ‘What should I do with my inheritance?’ and you ‘tell us’ about the strangest thing you’ve ever paid for… Plus some podcast exclusive tips on how to get a discounted family pass for National Trust sites and how you can get your hands on a free baked potato and beans!</description></item><item><title>10 ways to pimp your pension (&amp; warranty schmarranty) | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610027/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 17:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610027/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Martin Lewis Podcast is here - he tells you the ten things you MUST know about your pension, from how to find lost money in old pensions, to when you can opt in for extra pension contributions from your employer. PLUS when to ignore your warranty and still get what you want… Elsewhere in the podcast, Martin reacts to the latest inflation figures, you ‘tell us’ your summer holiday bargains and Martin is challenging YOU to come up with a nickname for new podcast producer Lillie-Mae…</description></item><item><title>Finally you can fix your energy bill - but should you? And more… | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 16:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610028/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Martin Lewis Podcast is here and energy bills are once again top of the agenda. For the first time in a long time you can fix your energy bills – but the question is should you? At the moment there’s only one company offering a fixed rate but there could be more to come. Martin and Nihal discuss the pros and cons of fixing and whether we really will see our energy bills drop considerably by the end of the summer.</description></item><item><title>Budget special: energy, tax, childcare, pension and Help to Save | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610029/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610029/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Martin Lewis Podcast is here – and it’s a Budget 2023 special. Founder of Money Saving Expert, Martin Lewis reacts to Chancellor Jeremy Hunt’s Spring Budget. Free childcare of 30 hours a week for working parents in England is being expanded to cover one and two-year-olds, but will only be fully implemented by September 2025. Currently, working parents with three and four-year-olds are eligible for 30 hours of free childcare per week.</description></item><item><title>ISAs, ISAs, baby... cheap flights and pensions boost | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610030/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 17:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610030/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Martin Lewis Podcast is here. Founder of Money Saving Expert, Martin Lewis answers your ISA questions. Interest rates are up, so ISAs are back for many, although you need to sort them by 5 April or sooner. Martin shares his key ISA need-to-knows.
Elsewhere in the podcast, you Tell Us what’s the oldest, working object you have in your home that you never use. Plus, when did you last use it?</description></item><item><title>Energy bill help, free wills and super service | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610031/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 17:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610031/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Martin Lewis Podcast is here – founder of Money Saving Expert, Martin Lewis joins BBC Radio 5live’s Nihal Arthanayake to answer your energy questions. The Energy Price Cap will fall by 23% in April 2023, to £3,280/year for a typical household, but energy bills are currently controlled by the Energy Price Guarantee (EPG) – and this is set to rise by 20% from 1 April. This is why Martin has been urging Chancellor Jeremy Hunt to postpone the rise – a plea now backed by more than 85 other organisations.</description></item><item><title>Council tax, £1000s back? Money-piphany, energy bills | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610032/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 18:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610032/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Martin Lewis Podcast is here. Founder of Money Saving Expert, Martin Lewis answers your financial questions. In this episode we look at how to check if you could save on your council tax, ahead of the 5% rise due for many of us in April. Plus, the council tax discount many people can apply for - that they may know nothing about. Elsewhere in the podcast you Tell Us your best ‘Money-piphany’ - that moment when your eyes were opened to how something in debt or budgeting worked, which changed your approach to finances forever.</description></item><item><title>How to turn £800 into £5,500 - Part Two | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610033/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 12:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Long: The Martin Lewis Podcast is here. Founder of Money Saving Expert, Martin Lewis answers your questions on buying national insurance contribution years to top up your state pension.
As the buy-back deadline is fast approaching, Martin has an urgent plea for those aged between 45 and 70. They could be missing years off their state pension worth £1,000s, so check yours and your family and friends now.</description></item><item><title>Beat water bill increases, student finance &amp; biggest ever savings | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610034/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 18:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610034/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Martin Lewis Podcast is here. Founder of Money Saving Expert, Martin Lewis answers your financial questions, including several queries on upcoming changes to student finance. Water bills could rise by 7.5% from April for households in England and Wales - the largest increase for nearly 20 years. The industry body Water UK says the rise due in April could take average water bills to nearly £450 a year because of rising energy costs.</description></item><item><title>Uni costs doubling, holiday must-dos and money fails | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610035/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610035/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Martin Lewis Podcast is here. Founder of Money Saving Expert, Martin Lewis answers your financial questions. You Tell Us your most embarrassing money fail, Nihal takes on Martin’s Money Mastermind and is quizzed on Section 75.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Haggling help, LISAs, free cash for teens? And more… | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610036/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 18:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610036/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Martin Lewis Podcast is here. Founder of Money Saving Expert, Martin Lewis answers your financial questions. Elsewhere in the podcast, you Tell Us your best haggle. How much did you save, and what are your top haggling tips? Nihal takes on Martin’s Money Mastermind and is quizzed on Child Trust Funds. Martin confirms 14% broadband and mobile price hikes due April. He warns that for those in contract there's little you can do, except take note when that contract ends, and act then.</description></item><item><title>Underpaid cash ISAs, broadband hike, WHAT-ER saving | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610037/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 08:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marin Lewis and Nihal Arthanayake's regular weekly dive into the world of money saving tips. This week Martin explains why you could be missing out if you have a cash ISA, how to beat inflation when it comes to your mobile phone and broadband and why a water meter could save you money.
Plus bonus money saving tips that you can only hear on the podcast, Nihal tries his luck at Mastermind and you tell us about your positive money surprises.</description></item><item><title>24,630 steps to sorting your debts, kid finance gurus and more | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610038/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 18:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Martin Lewis joins Nihal Arthanayake to answer your debt-related questions. In this week’s “tell us” Martin asks how your kids have helped you with your finances. Plus Martin’s podcast-only money saving tips, including how to save on cinema tickets.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Will energy prices rise or fall? 1p challenge and cash ISAs | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Martin Lewis answers your financial questions including what are my rights if my parcel isn’t delivered? Why are wholesale gas prices falling but bills aren’t? Elsewhere in the podcast, ‘Tell Us’ what were your new year’s financial resolutions last year. Did you keep to them? How long did they last? Did it work? BBC Radio 5live’s Nihal Arthanayake takes on Martin’s Money Mastermind – he’s quizzed on savings and cash ISAs.</description></item><item><title>Money Mastermind Special | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 16:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610040/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Martin Lewis Podcast is here and this week is a festive special. In a compilation of the year’s best Money Mastermind questions, Martin tests BBC Radio 5live’s Nihal Arthanayake’s financial knowledge.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Consumer right &amp; wrongs, dictionary corner, advice to 18yr old self… | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610041/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 17:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610041/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Martin Lewis Podcast is here. Founder of Money Saving Expert, Martin Lewis answers your financial questions including when is the £200 payment for homes that use heating oil, have an LPG boiler or biomass boiler due?
In the 12 months to November 2022 the inflation figure was 10.7% but what does inflation mean? Why is inflation so high? When will inflation go down?
This week, Martin has an urgent reminder for people to check if they are eligible for pension credit as the deadline for the Cost of Living payment of £324 is this week.</description></item><item><title>Energy cost cutters, Mortgages, 7% and Will he or won’t he? | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 17:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610042/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week’s podcast Martin and Nihal Arthanayake share their energy saving tips, Martin’s got an update on a mortgage summit he’s involved in with the Chancellor, and there’s a bonus podcast-only tip for savers too!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to turn £800 into £5,500 | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 17:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610043/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Martin Lewis Podcast is here. Founder of Money Saving Expert, Martin Lewis answers your financial questions including is a dehumidifier a cost effective way to dry clothes? Is it cheaper to use an oven, air-fryer or microwave? This week, Martin has an urgent plea for those aged between 45 and 70. As you could be missing years off your state pension worth £1,000s, so check now. Elsewhere in the show, ‘Tell Us’ have you re-gifted gifts.</description></item><item><title>Black Friday ‘best’ deals – are they worth it? | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610044/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 11:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610044/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Martin Lewis Podcast is here – founder of Money Saving Expert, Martin Lewis answers your financial questions. What is Grey Friday? When is Cyber Monday? Martin reveals whether Black Friday is any good. He shares the best and the worst type of deals – plus his take on pre-Xmas, Boxing Day and January sales. But before you get pulled into an impulse buy, Martin coaches us in his ‘Money Mantras’ and ‘Black Friday shopping memo’.</description></item><item><title>Budget Analysis, Credit, Christmas and Jeremy Hunt’s Fiscal Drag Show | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610045/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610045/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Martin Lewis Podcast is here – founder of Money Saving Expert, Martin Lewis joins BBC Radio 5 live’s Nihal Arthanayake to answer your questions – such as is Black Friday a good deal? Also this week, Martin has an urgent plea for anyone who can’t afford to clear their credit card debit: get a 0% balance transfer. And there’s Martin’s analysis of the key announcements in Chancellor Jeremy Hunt’s autumn statement.</description></item><item><title>Savings boost, Christmas pre-NUPPs &amp; baboon bums | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610046/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 18:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who gets the cost of living payment? When is the second cost of living payment? The Martin Lewis Podcast is here – and Martin has an urgent plea for anyone who hasn’t receive their £150 council tax rebate.
Martin and BBC Radio 5live’s Nihal Arthanayake talk returns, ‘pre-NUPPs’ and baboon bums.
They ask whether it is possible to cut back at Christmas?
Plus Martin’s advice on how to best protect your savings from inflation and what to do if you have an order with furniture site Made.</description></item><item><title>Preparing for death, divorce &amp; dementia | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610047/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Martin Lewis on why it’s financially crucial to prepare death, divorce and dementia. But don’t be down, there’s also advice on energy, cheap train travel and free beer.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mortgages: Stick or Twist? | The Martin Lewis Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4099610048/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4099610048/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Martin Lewis Podcast is here, with a brand new sound. Martin and Nihal Arthanayake talk mortgages as listeners ask if they should stick with a longer fix or take a chance on variable rates. Martin’s got some special tips on how you might be able to top up your state pension and how to get some extra cash in time for Christmas. Plus, have you ever found a bone fide second-hand bargain?</description></item></channel></rss>