<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Wiser Than Me with Julia Louis-Dreyfus on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/wiser-than-me-with-julia-louis-dreyfus/</link><description>Recent content in Wiser Than Me with Julia Louis-Dreyfus on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/wiser-than-me-with-julia-louis-dreyfus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>EXTRA: A Peek Behind the Scenes | Wiser Than Me with Julia Louis-Dreyfus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5701950001/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5701950001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Julia surprises the one-and-only Judith Bowles (aka her mom) with some very exciting news! And did you know her mom isn't the only one of Julia’s relatives who's part of Wiser Than Me? Julia shares some behind-the-scenes info about how the show is actually a family affair and how she is so grateful to all of you out there who have been listening to Wiser Than Me. Finally, stay tuned for season 2, which returns this spring!</description></item><item><title>Julia Gets Wise with Carol Burnett | Wiser Than Me with Julia Louis-Dreyfus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5701950002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5701950002/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the season finale of Wiser Than Me, Julia sits down in person with 90-year-old groundbreaking actress, comedian, and writer Carol Burnett. Carol tells Julia how she learned to accept rejection, what Lucille Ball taught her about being a boss, and how a spontaneous ride on a beer truck led to her landing a CBS special with Julie Andrews. And Carol gives Julia a compliment that makes Julia cry, which leads to a touching conversation between Julia and her mom Judith.</description></item><item><title>Julia Gets Wise with Rhea Perlman | Wiser Than Me with Julia Louis-Dreyfus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5701950003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5701950003/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Wiser Than Me, Julia spends time with 75-year-old actress Rhea Perlman, who recently became a grandmother for the first time. Julia and Rhea trade stories of being pregnant on set and reminisce about working together 40 years ago on Saturday Night Live. Then, Julia tells her mom Judith that Rhea has read a lot of Buddhist monk Thich Nhat Hanh’s work, which inexplicably prompts a laugh-out-loud funny story from Judith.</description></item><item><title>Julia Gets Wise with Amy Tan | Wiser Than Me with Julia Louis-Dreyfus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5701950004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5701950004/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of Wiser Than Me, Julia sits down with 71-year-old author Amy Tan. Amy tells Julia how she’s learned to deal with the expectations following her successful debut novel The Joy Luck Club, the power of an apology, and the practical ways she’s preparing for getting older. And Julia and her mom Judith recall the disastrous first time Judith met Julia’s future husband Brad.
Follow Julia on Instagram and Twitter @officialjld.</description></item><item><title>Julia Gets Wise with Gina McCarthy | Wiser Than Me with Julia Louis-Dreyfus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5701950005/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5701950005/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this edition of Wiser Than Me, Julia is joined by 69-year-old environmental advocate Gina McCarthy, the former EPA Administrator and first-ever White House national climate advisor. Gina and Julia share their experiences of being the only woman in the room at work, trying different tactics to get the outcome you want, and going gray surprisingly young. And Julia and her mom Judith contemplate ways to get people personally invested in the climate crisis and discuss Julia and Gina’s plans to go shopping together.</description></item><item><title>Julia Gets Wise with Diane von Furstenberg | Wiser Than Me with Julia Louis-Dreyfus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5701950006/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5701950006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today on Wiser Than Me, Julia sits down with 76-year-old fashion icon Diane von Furstenberg. In this conversation, Diane tells Julia why she’s always looked forward to getting older, the one piece of clothing she thinks every woman should have in her closet, and how she says her mother made her fearless. Plus, Julia and her mom Judith debate a questionable fashion choice Julia nearly made.
Follow Julia on Instagram and Twitter @officialjld.</description></item><item><title>Julia Gets Wise with Darlene Love | Wiser Than Me with Julia Louis-Dreyfus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5701950007/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5701950007/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Wiser Than Me, Julia is joined by 81-year-old Rock and Roll Hall of Fame singer Darlene Love. From her early days singing gospel music in her father’s church to backing up icons like Elvis Presley to finally going solo at age 40, Darlene is a case study in never giving up on your dreams. She tells Julia about raising her sons while building her career, how to balance being strong and kind, and what motivates her to give her best performances.</description></item><item><title>Julia Gets Wise with Ruth Reichl | Wiser Than Me with Julia Louis-Dreyfus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5701950008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5701950008/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of Wiser Than Me, Julia gets enlightened by 75-year-old food writer, magazine editor, and author Ruth Reichl. From her infamous New York Times review of Le Cirque to greenlighting a controversial David Foster Wallace article in Gourmet, Ruth is as gutsy as they come. Ruth talks to Julia about living with a mom who has bipolar disorder, processing grief through food, and why you should always do things that scare you.</description></item><item><title>Julia Gets Wise with Fran Lebowitz | Wiser Than Me with Julia Louis-Dreyfus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5701950009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5701950009/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this edition of Wiser Than Me, Julia gets schooled by 72-year-old writer and legendary New York City resident Fran Lebowitz. This is an interview for the ages – literally. Fran gives Julia her best advice for plotting revenge, being a bad girlfriend, and avoiding modern technology at all costs. Plus, Fran shares what she learned about forgiveness from her late friend Toni Morrison. And Julia and her mom Judith reminisce about how Julia’s sense of humor got her in trouble in high school.</description></item><item><title>Julia Gets Wise with Isabel Allende | Wiser Than Me with Julia Louis-Dreyfus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5701950010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 07:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5701950010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today on Wiser Than Me, Julia gets schooled by 80-year-old award-winning author Isabel Allende (The House of the Spirits). Isabel teaches Julia about organic justice, letter writing, and blueberry weed edibles. The two compare notes on everything from postpartum experiences to otherworldly visits from the other side. Follow Julia on Instagram and Twitter @officialjld. Keep up with Isabel Allende on Instagram @allendeisabel. You can find out more about our show @lemonadamedia on all social platforms.</description></item><item><title>Julia Gets Wise with Jane Fonda | Wiser Than Me with Julia Louis-Dreyfus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5701950011/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5701950011/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the premiere episode of Wiser Than Me, Julia sits down with the one and only Jane Fonda. With a career spanning over six decades, Jane – now 85 years old – hits all the highlights: staying fit at any age, fantasizing about funerals, getting heckled on set by Katharine Hepburn…and something about a fake thumb.
Follow Julia on Instagram and Twitter @officialjld. Keep up with Jane Fonda on Instagram and Twitter @janefonda.</description></item><item><title>Wiser Than Me (Official Trailer) | Wiser Than Me with Julia Louis-Dreyfus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5701950012/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 21:59:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5701950012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Julia Louis-Dreyfus, the Emmy Award winning-est actress of all time, is diving into her first-ever podcast with touching, funny, personal conversations with wise, fascinating women who have lived long enough to know a thing or two about a thing or two. Tune in to laugh, cry and just maybe… get wise. Coming April 11.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>