<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Duolingo French Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/duolingo-french-podcast/</link><description>Recent content in Duolingo French Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 01:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/duolingo-french-podcast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Secret Life of Josephine Baker - Josephine: L’héroïne | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600001/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josephine embarks on perilous spy missions…and her wartime service brings her face to face with the man who inspired her to join the Resistance. With Ariana DeBose.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3QUR3sq.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Secret Life of Josephine Baker - Josephine, la résistante | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600002/</guid><description>Podcast Description With France under German occupation, Josephine takes refuge at her sanctuary, Les Milandes. Until the enemy comes knocking at the gates. With Ariana DeBose.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3QNcpIh.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Secret Life of Josephine Baker - Josephine, l'espionne | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600003/</guid><description>Podcast Description With war declared in France, Josephine braces for the conflict and wonders how she can help…until a member of the French secret service knocks at her door and she begins a new chapter of her life. With Ariana DeBose.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3MP6aBx.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Secret Life of Josephine Baker - Josephine, la cible | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josephine puts down roots in her beloved France while trying to find her place as an artist as the world teeters toward war. With Ariana DeBose.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3tM0mlu.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Secret Life of Josephine Baker - Josephine, l'icône | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600005/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josephine becomes an international sensation and adopts France as her home. But in neighboring Germany, Nazism is on the rise and threatens her newfound freedom. With Ariana DeBose.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/4010Hg5.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Secret Life of Josephine Baker - Josephine, la danseuse | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600006/</guid><description>Podcast Description 19-year-old Josephine Baker leaves her life in the U.S. behind and arrives in Paris to try her luck onstage. She falls in love with the city, but what will she have to do in order to succeed there? With Ariana DeBose.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/46I6I3s.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trailer Season 14 | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 15:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600007/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Duolingo French Podcast returns with a thrilling new season! Discover the untold story of 1920s icon Josephine Baker – not just a dancer, but a spy for the French Resistance. Featuring Academy Award-winner Ariana DeBose. This special season launches on October 11th, 2023. Catch the trailer now!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>La championne du fromage (Cheese Champion) - Revisited | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600008/</guid><description>Podcast Description In honor of Women’s History Month, we’re revisiting a story by Virginie Dhorne – a French cheesemonger with a fierce competitive streak. Stick around until the end to hear what Virginie’s been up to since this episode first aired.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/4202Hpg.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>38 gamins (38 kids) - Revisited | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600009/</guid><description>Podcast Description In honor of Women’s History Month, we’re revisiting a story by Loune Viaud, a public health expert from Haiti who rescued 38 children after the 2010 earthquake struck the country. Stick around until the end to hear what Loune and the children from the story have been up to since this episode first aired.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3H96ecn.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>La reine du codage (The Coding Queen) - Revisited | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600010/</guid><description>Podcast Description In honor of Women’s History Month, we’re revising a story by Matina Razafimahefa, a university student from Madagascar with an entrepreneurial spirit. Stick around until the end to hear what Matina has been up to since this episode first aired.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/41vlwjy.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rêves d’une karateka (Karate Dreams) - Revisited | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600011/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600011/</guid><description>Podcast Description In honor of Women’s History Month, we’re revisiting a story by Valérie Desroches, a karate student from Montreal. After learning she had Asperger's syndrome, Valérie’s new self-knowledge inspired her to work even harder toward achieving her karate dreams. Stick around until the end to hear what Valérie has been up to since this episode first aired.
A transcript of this episode is available at http://bit.ly/3zREXHc.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trouver sa voix (Speaking Out) - Revisited | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600012/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600012/</guid><description>Podcast Description In honor of Women’s History Month, we’re revisiting a story by Linh Lan Dao, who decided to pursue a career in journalism after encountering anti-Asian racism. Stick around until the end to hear what Linh Lan’s been up to since this episode first aired.
A transcript of this episode is available at http://bit.ly/3ZEze25.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Surfer au Sénégal (Senegal Surfer) - Revisited | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600013/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600013/</guid><description>Podcast Description In honor of Women’s History Month, we’re revisiting a story by Khadjou Sambe, a young woman who defied gender norms by taking up surfing, considered a men-only sport in her home country of Senegal. Stick around until the end to hear what Khadjou has been up to since this episode first aired.
A transcript of this episode is available at http://bit.ly/3KeOdLy.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Reconstruire le travail d'une vie (Rebuilding a Life's Work) - Revisited | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600014/</guid><description>Podcast Description In honor of Women’s History Month, we’re revisiting a story by Maya Husseini, a stained-glass artist who spent her career rebuilding churches in her hometown of Beirut. But after a devastating warehouse explosion in August 2020, she was faced with a question: could she help rebuild Beirut? Stick around until the end to hear what Maya has been up to since this episode first aired.
A transcript of this episode is available at http://bit.</description></item><item><title>Une chanson révolutionnaire (A Song of Revolution) - Revisited | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600015/</guid><description>Podcast Description In honor of Women’s History Month, we’re revisiting a story by Emel Mathlouthi, a singer whose music became a symbol of freedom during the seismic revolution that took place in 2010 in her home country of Tunisia. Stick around until the end to hear what Emel has been up to since this episode first aired.
A transcript of this episode is available at http://bit.ly/3JEFAd6.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trailer Season 13 | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600016/</guid><description>Podcast Description In honor of Women’s History Month, the Duolingo French Podcast is back for a special season celebrating exceptional women. We’ll revisit stories of powerful dreamers, visionaries, and truth-seekers from our archives — and share updates on their lives since their stories first aired. This special season starts March 14th, 2023. Tune in to the trailer now!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Paris - Le goût des pâtisseries | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Muriel Aublet-Cuvelier is a French pastry chef on a mission to share the art of pastry with the world. She takes us to visit some of Paris’ historic pastry shops and taste some of the city’s most iconic desserts.
A transcript of this episode is available at http://bit.ly/3kUYQZI.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Paris - Les Catacombes interdites | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600018/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Photographer Gaspard Duval has a growing archive of the historic Paris Catacombs, a network of tunnels and burial grounds underneath the city of Paris. He navigates the underground labyrinth to highlight his favorite spots, from the official tour area to secret chambers that are forbidden to the public.
A transcript of this episode is available at http://bit.ly/3XDWlK0.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Paris - Notre-Dame à travers le temps | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Olivier Chandez was the official clocksmith of the Notre Dame Cathedral. He tended to its antique central clock until a fire set the Cathedral ablaze in 2019. Olivier will take us back to a time before the fire for a special tour of one of the world’s most beloved Parisian landmarks.
A transcript of this episode is available at http://bit.ly/3WuvTAX.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Paris - Visite du Marais | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600020/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600020/</guid><description>Podcast Description A longtime resident of Paris, Pascal Fonquernie, walks us through his historic neighborhood, Le Marais, sharing its unique history and shining a light on the different communities who live there.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3X25hIQ.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trailer Season 12 | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600021/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Duolingo French Podcast is back for a new season. Our special trip to Paris, France starts January 2023. Listen to the trailer now!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>L’enfant prodige de la mode (The Fashion Prodigy) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alphonse Maitrepierre is a talented young designer who worked his way up to many established fashion houses in Paris. After learning from the best, he wanted to design clothes that reflected his vision and commitment to sustainability. But would the fashion world embrace him?
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3ThCPQh.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Un jour de commémoration (A day of remembrance) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600023/</guid><description>Podcast Description A doctor from Guadeloupe dedicates his life to honoring the memory of his island’s enslaved ancestors, and fights to make sure their names will not be forgotten.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3DRItUY.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>La chocolatière (The Chocolate Maker) - Revisited | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600024/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Growing up in Cameroon, Euphrasie Mbambae spent a lot of time on her grandfather’s cacao farm. But it wasn’t until she moved to Belgium that she tasted chocolate for the first time and understood the power of the fruits from her childhood. We recently reached out to Euphrasie and updated her story with new content.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3FnIsJk.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>La lutte pour une justice alimentaire (Fighting for Food Justice) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600025/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600025/</guid><description>Podcast Description A Montreal resident realizes people in his neighborhood of Saint-Henri West don’t have access to fresh and affordable food. So together as a community, they decide to take matters into their own hands and open a collective grocery store run by and for the people of Saint-Henri West.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3Sa4Ad9.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>La coureuse de Bamako (The Runner from Bamako) - Revisited | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600026/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600026/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a teenager in Mali, Djénébou Dante dodged a string of marriage proposals to pursue her running dreams and represent her country on the international stage. We recently reached out to Djénébou and updated her story with new content.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3MkQK6s.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>L'art de la Crêpe (The Art of the Crepe) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600027/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600027/</guid><description>Podcast Description A Parisian B&amp;amp;B host sets out on a journey to master the art of making the perfect traditional French crepe. He shares his findings with the world…one crepe at a time.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3CadWzG.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>La Seine à la nage (Swimming the Seine) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600028/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600028/</guid><description>Podcast Description After learning that cigarette butts are the most harmful pollutants of our oceans, Chloé decides to take action. She sets out on a daring journey to follow a cigarette butt's course from the Seine River to the sea, raising awareness and sparking change along the way.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3LJHGYx.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Le pouvoir des réseaux sociaux (The Power of Social Media) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600029/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600029/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a little person, Douchka Volaric didn’t grow up with any media representation of people like her. When she discovers TikTok, she decides to use it as a tool to educate others, spread a positive message, and be the change she wished to see.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3xDnYrn.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Les bébés au Festival de Cannes (Babies at the Cannes Festival) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600030/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600030/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a film programmer, Aurélie depended on going to the legendary Cannes Film Festival. But when she had her first child, she realized attending Festivals with a baby would be nearly impossible and she wondered, could anything be done to help working families?
A transcript of this episode is available at https://podcast.duolingo.com/french.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Le chasseur d’orages (The Storm Chaser) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600031/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ever since he was 10 years old, Serge Zaka was fascinated by the power and beauty of France’s most elusive thunderstorms. So he made it his life's mission to photograph the perfect storm to share with the world, but could he do it?
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3AUvkHQ.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trailer Season 11 | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600032/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 14:46:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600032/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Duolingo French Podcast is back with new episodes starting September 6, 2022. Listen to the trailer now!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Traditions iconiques - The Tour de France | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600033/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Le Tour de France is a legendary bicycle race in France. But to cycling enthusiast Claire Floret, there’s something terribly wrong with it: women aren’t allowed to compete. So in order to make things right, she created a brand new cycling challenge.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3zeMXTo.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Traditions iconiques - The Beret | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600034/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600034/</guid><description>Podcast Description The béret was once the most popular hat in France. But today, most French people see it as old-fashioned. Except for Valérie. As a native of southwest France – where bérets were invented – she wants to bring them back in style!
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3ajeGbM.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Traditions iconiques - A Kiss Hello | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600035/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600035/</guid><description>Podcast Description In France, greeting friends, relatives and co-workers with “la bise” — a kiss hello — is more than tradition. It’s essential. Yet Mathieu Avanzi was so baffled by the custom, it left him wondering: did others feel the same?
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3y59bp7.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Traditions iconiques - Fête de la musique | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600036/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Every year on June 21st, musicians across France take to the streets to celebrate la Fête de la musique. Growing up, Fanny’s birthday also happened to be on June 21st…and for a long time, she resented having to share her day with the popular French holiday. Until the tradition took on a special meaning for her…
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3O9Ieal.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Traditions iconiques - Beaujolais Wine | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600037/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600037/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the grand French tradition of winemaking, Beaujolais Nouveau wine was once the cool kid on the block. But when wine connoisseurs felt it went too mainstream, they turned their backs on it. So wine lover Anaïs Pertuizet decided to make a new kind of Beaujolais Nouveau, one that would win back their hearts.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3b4LLZb.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Traditions iconiques - Summer Vacation | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600038/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600038/</guid><description>Podcast Description The French love their long summer vacations, les grandes vacances. But they hate the massive traffic jams that go with them. To help vacation-bound drivers and passengers have some fun on the road, traffic radio host Francine Thomas has to get creative.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3GWrJM9.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Traditions iconiques - French Gastronomy | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600039/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Le repas gastronomique, the true French feast, is a unique part of French culture. Chef Stéphane Ranieri worked his way up the kitchen ranks in some of France’s most prestigious restaurants. Then one day, he decided to take fine dining to a completely different setting: the rugby stadium.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3NK17Qz.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Traditions iconiques - Perfume | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600040/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Perfume is France’s everyday luxury. French people love to wear it, to gift it, but also to create it. When one of France’s foremost perfumers realizes that the perfume-making tradition in his hometown of Grasse is in danger, he vows to defend it.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3lJuKpn.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trailer Season 10 | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600041/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600041/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Duolingo French Podcast is back with new episodes starting May 24, 2022. Listen to the trailer now!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>La course en solitaire (The Solo Race) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600042/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600042/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Kevin Escoffier entered one of the world’s most epic solo boating races, he faced long odds, dangerous waters, and stiff competition.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3iuoCQ2.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>La chocolatière (The Chocolate Maker) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600043/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Growing up in Cameroon, Euphrasie Mbamba spent a lot of time on her grandfather’s cacao farm. But it wasn’t until she moved to Belgium that she tasted chocolate for the first time, and understood the power of the fruits from her childhood.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3MVLnu7.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>La rameuse paralympique (The Paralympic Rower) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600044/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600044/</guid><description>Podcast Description A passionate rower trains to build her strength and perfect her technique for the Paralympics… But along the way she also learns the importance of maintaining her mental health.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/35BAMnE.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Pour l’amour du rap (For the Love of Rap) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600045/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ouafa Mameche didn’t speak French when she first arrived in France at the age of seven. But her passion for rap music led her to love the language and find her place in her adopted homeland.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3C46bKW.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Les tableaux volés (The Stolen Paintings) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600046/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600046/</guid><description>Podcast Description In March 2014, Richard Hardin received a phone call that would change his life and cause him to question everything he thought he knew about his family history.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/35iKeLP.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sauver la langue bretonne (Saving the Breton Language) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600047/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600047/</guid><description>Podcast Description A young woman from the region of Brittany falls in love with the local language, le breton. Through her passion for language learning, she decides to help save the Breton language from extinction.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3oQnABC.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Le messager des livres (The Book Messenger) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600048/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Luc was a maintenance technician in Parisian hotels who dreamed of becoming a bookseller. With little experience, but a lot of passion, he opened a new kind of bookstore, one aimed at serving the busy working people and immigrants living in his suburb outside Paris.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3HCNxfk.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rescue on Mont Blanc (Sauvetage sur le Mont Blanc) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600049/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600049/</guid><description>Podcast Description A mountain rescuer in the French town of Chamonix decides to go on one of the riskiest missions of his career.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3AOV9IV.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trailer Season 9 | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600050/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600050/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Duolingo French Podcast is back with new episodes starting February 1, 2022. Listen to the trailer now!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Final Escape - The Rebel Thief, Episode 6 | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600051/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600051/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the sixth and final episode of our series, Alexandre experiences life in France’s notorious overseas prison camp, le Bagne. Always the rebel, he attempts the riskiest of escapes… Meanwhile, in Paris, his mother Marie leads a tireless campaign for his release. Will either of them prevail?
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3IFrFzX.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Trial - The Rebel Thief, Episode 5 | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600052/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600052/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Episode 5 of this six-part series, the prosecutor of Alexandre Jacob’s trial makes his case. He hopes the Judge and jury will send the rebel thief to the guillotine. But will Alexandre’s impassioned speeches sway the jury…or will they send him to his doom?
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3tZ07lb.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>To Catch a Thief - The Rebel Thief, Episode 4 | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600053/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600053/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Episode 4 of this six-part series, Alexandre and two accomplices set out on a routine burglary. After being spotted, the three men flee into the French countryside with the police in hot pursuit. Alexandre has vowed never to use violence…but will he break his own rule?
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3G3N6sV.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Night Crew - The Rebel Thief, Episode 3 | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600054/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600054/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Episode 3 of this six-part series, Alexandre hones his skill as a master thief. He builds a team of anarchist thieves and strives to remain one step ahead of the police. But how long can his luck last?
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/34extBL.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The First Heist - The Rebel Thief, Episode 2 | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600055/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600055/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Episode 2 of this six-part series, Alexandre attempts his first heist. It's a clever, daring plan…but he has no experience as a burglar. Will he pull it off?
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3ADyX4G.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Making of a Thief - The Rebel Thief, Episode 1 | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600056/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600056/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Episode 1 of this six-part series, we meet Alexandre Marius Jacob, the young sailor who grew up to become one of France’s most daring and notorious thieves. At the turn of the 20th century, the injustices Alexandre witnessed ignited a desire to seek vengeance against the rich and the powerful…entirely on his own terms.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3u7errJ.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trailer Season 8 | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600057/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600057/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Duolingo French Podcast is back with new episodes starting November 9, 2021. Listen to the trailer now!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>La reine du codage (The Coding Queen) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600058/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Growing up in Madagascar, one of the poorest countries in the world, Matina Razafimahefa was upset that the majority of kids didn't have the same access to education as she did. So at 19, she took action…and launched a one-of-a-kind coding school.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3IDyFNR.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Le grand pari (The Big Gamble) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600059/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600059/</guid><description>Podcast Description At 23, Loïc was lost. After a severe accident, he’d lost his job, his home, and his dream of becoming a soccer player. But after entering a poker game as a card dealer, Loïc played the hand he was dealt, the chips fell where they did, and his life changed overnight.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3AwZ7pC.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Reconstruire le travail d’une vie (Rebuilding a Life’s Work) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600060/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Maya Husseini is a stained-glass artist who spent her career rebuilding churches in her hometown of Beirut. But after a warehouse explosion in August 2020, she’s forced to ask herself: Can she help rebuild Beirut again?
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/33UDa7R.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>La comédienne de balcon (The Balcony Performer) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600061/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600061/</guid><description>Podcast Description During the second Covid lockdown, the French President had declared that theaters weren’t "essential." But to Marie, theater was the essence of life. Could she do anything to safely bring theater to audiences?
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3rTnEkH.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>L’élève courageuse (The Courageous Student) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600062/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Laetitia Dubois felt trapped in the rigorous French school system but worried that dropping out would lead to a life of failure. Until one day, an eye-opening internship gave her the courage to find her own unique path.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/35sqqG8.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>La chanteuse des îles (The Island Singer) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600063/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600063/</guid><description>Podcast Description An R&amp;amp;B-loving teenager from the tiny island of Mayotte sees her world turned upside down when her mother signs her up for an amateur opera competition.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3H9YyED.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Changer de camp (Switching Sides) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600064/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andoh Ashu Rex thought he’d found his dream job working for an American company in Cameroon. But after learning that his employer might be harming his homeland instead of helping it, Rex decided to sacrifice his steady income and choose a different professional path.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3AIkXXm.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Le plus jeune maire de France (The Youngest Mayor in France) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600065/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can France’s youngest mayoral candidate in history revive public life in his sleepy village?
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3fYLzcO.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trailer Season 7 | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600066/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600066/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Duolingo French Podcast is back with new episodes starting July 20, 2021. Listen to the trailer now!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Une visite guidée du Paris noir (A Tour of Black Paris) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600067/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600067/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this special episode, we’re taking you on a guided audio tour through Paris to explore a unique side of the city: its Black history and culture! Join tour guide Kévi Donat in discovering the Black thinkers, artists, and leaders who helped make Paris the city it is today.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3o42VK1.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Polynésie, mon amour (Polynesia, My Love) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600068/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600068/</guid><description>Podcast Description When the son of a Polynesian fisherman discovers the threats affecting his beloved island’s coral reefs, he teams up with a surf buddy to do something about it.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3fXSLpJ.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mont-Saint-Michel, mon amour (Mont-Saint-Michel, My Love) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600069/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600069/</guid><description>Podcast Description François Saint-James’s first great love was not a person, but a place: le Mont-Saint-Michel, the iconic island fortress off the coast of Normandy. Working there was the chance of a lifetime, and living there a dream come true. But when his first love introduced him to the next one, he found himself forced to choose between the two…
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/32Avl6T.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Madagascar, mon amour (Madagascar, My Love) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600070/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600070/</guid><description>Podcast Description The first time Onja Razafindratsima stepped foot in the Madagascar rainforest, she fell in love with the unique plants and animals that call it home. But when she realized all these species could go extinct, she decided to protect her home country’s incredible biodiversity.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3tZ77OV.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lausanne, mon amour (Lausanne, My Love) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600071/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Renato Häusler felt out of place in modern life. He longed for a simpler, slower, more natural time. When he learned that his city, Lausanne, is one of the last in Europe to still have a lone night watchman, he made it his mission to preserve the centuries-old tradition.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3u1txPv.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lyon, mon amour (Lyon, My Love) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600072/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600072/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a free-spirited wanderer reluctantly takes a job as tour guide in Lyon, the last thing she expects is to fall in love with the city and its secrets…
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3rRYdjE.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Étretat, mon amour (Étretat, My Love) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600073/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600073/</guid><description>Podcast Description When the best crab fisherman in Étretat, Normandy gradually loses his eyesight, he does everything in his power to continue fishing along the coastline he loves.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3g0bdOx.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trailer Season 6 | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600074/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600074/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Duolingo French Podcast is back with new episodes starting April 13, 2021. Listen to the trailer now!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ask Me Anything — Your Listener Questions Answered | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600075/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600075/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this special episode, we answer your questions about the Duolingo French Podcast! Listen as host Ngofeen Mputubwele takes you behind the scenes of this one-of-a-kind podcast — with a little help from some friends.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3KI7cwt.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Les rebelles écolos (The Eco Rebels) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600076/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Benji was an idealistic young man full of hopes for his future…until the 2008 financial crisis left him jobless. At a loss for how to lead a good life and earn a living, he decided to join an alternative community, la ZAD, in the west of France.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3uiB5h9.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>La voix de la France (The Voice of France) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600077/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Simone Hérault had the gift of a unique voice, but as a child, she was too insecure to believe in it. Still, her talent and dedication would end up taking her places she never expected…until she became one of the most familiar and beloved voices in all of France.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/33Owbh1.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>La coureuse de Bamako (The Runner from Bamako) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600078/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600078/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a teenager in Mali, Djénébou Danté dodged a string of marriage proposals to pursue her running dreams and represent her country on the international stage.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3KJMR9Z.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>L’amour et les chevaux sauvages (Love and Wild Horses) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600079/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600079/</guid><description>Podcast Description At 30, Aliénor Le Gouvello set off to ride solo across Australia’s toughest trails. She gave herself one year to train wild horses and complete the journey. Riding ten hours a day, every day, Aliénor was determined not to quit — not for crocodiles, fire ants…not even for the handsome helicopter pilot she met along the way.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3HkGO9T.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>38 Gamins (38 Kids) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600080/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600080/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a devastating earthquake strikes Haiti in January 2010, one of the island’s most respected public health experts rushes to the aid of 38 abandoned children who have been left without a home. She decides then and there to take care of them, not knowing that the decision will change their lives — and hers — forever.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3o3Ox4e.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Les moines brasseurs (The Beer-Brewing Monks) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600081/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600081/</guid><description>Podcast Description At age 27, Matthieu Landri said goodbye to his family and shared one last beer with his friends…then began his new life as a Benedictine monk. He longed for a spiritual life of contemplation and prayer. But soon he found himself embarking on a new journey: reviving the lost French art of monastic beer-brewing.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/33OwCIb.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Les santons de Noël (The Little Christmas Figures) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600082/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600082/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Martine Gaussen’s childhood, traditional French santons — handmade nativity figures — were a key that unlocked the magic of Christmas. But decades after the magic has dulled and adult responsibilities have taken over, can Martine rediscover the curiosity and creativity that defined the holidays of her youth?
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3rRYymq.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Le petit apiculteur (The Beekeeper Kid) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600083/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600083/</guid><description>Podcast Description A young boy in the south of France discovers an unexpected passion for bees and beekeeping. But he’s not prepared for the heartbreak he’ll face when he leaves his little buzzing companions over the summer...
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3rS6R1w.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trailer Season 5 | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600084/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600084/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Duolingo French Podcast is back with new episodes starting December 15, 2020. Listen to the trailer now!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Le nom caché (The Hidden Name) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600085/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600085/</guid><description>Podcast Description After his grandparents’ deaths, 20-year-old Damien Bouché uncovers a family secret from World War II. He spends the next 10 years unearthing the past, from Vienna to the south of France, in a fight to regain his true family name.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3GZqStj.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Le caporal canadien-français (The French Canadian Corporal) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600086/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600086/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Vincent-Gabriel Lamarre joined the Canadian Armed Forces, he knew he had found his calling. But a few years into his service, he realized he could no longer ignore the discomfort he felt about his gender identity. Would a gender transition be accepted in the military? After the episode, learn more about Vincent-Gabriel’s journey here: https://vimeo.com/ondemand/tigars.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3HkH4pn.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>La joie du cancan (The Joy of Cancan) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600087/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600087/</guid><description>Podcast Description A young dancer discovers French Cancan in the 1960s, leading her to an exciting international career…and the love of her life. When a tragic loss rips the joy of dancing from her, cancan slowly helps her find a renewed sense of self.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3ACl2vK.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Défier un dictateur (Defying a Dictator) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600088/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600088/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a young attorney from Chad decided to take on the ex-dictator who terrorized her country, she knew she was going up against dark and powerful forces. But that didn’t stop her from dedicating her life to fighting for justice in her homeland.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3fXuAaY.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Le boulanger de l’Afghanistan (The Baker from Afghanistan) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600089/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Najib Nasary left his native Afghanistan in search of a fresh start in France. He had nothing, knew no one, and faced the threat of deportation. But when a village in France’s Cévennes mountains took him in, he finally found a new home…and a new passion for baking French bread.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3rMjM52.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>La course au sommet de la tour Eiffel (The Race to the Top of the Eiffel Tower) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600090/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600090/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Valérie Hirschfield lost her leg, she made a promise to her family that she would bounce back stronger than ever — a promise that would one day lead her to race up France’s most iconic monument.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3H41se7.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Une chanson révolutionnaire (A Song of Revolution) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600091/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emel Mathlouthi left her home country of Tunisia so that she could sing openly about bringing freedom to her people. But that didn’t stop her from participating in the seismic revolution that was taking place back home.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3AOkKSB.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trouver sa voix (Speaking Out) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600092/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Growing up in France as the daughter of Vietnamese immigrants, Linh Lan Dao felt uncomfortable speaking up when she encountered anti-Asian racism. But after becoming a journalist and finding a community of like-minded people, Linh Lan discovered the tools she needed to stand up for herself and others.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3u3wRK4.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trailer Season 4 | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600093/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600093/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Duolingo French Podcast is back with new episodes starting September 15, 2020. Listen to the trailer now!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dessiner un nouveau départ (Drawing a New Beginning) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600094/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Berthet One always loved drawing, but never saw a future in it. Until he wound up in prison and realized that drawing was the best chance he had at rebuilding his life.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3H40yhC.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Le Top Chef (The Top Chef) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600095/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gratien Leroy is a small-town accountant with big culinary dreams. But when France’s most popular cooking show announces an open call for the country’s best amateur cooks, does Gratien have what it takes to join the ranks of his country’s top chefs?
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3rSGPeD.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Surfer au Sénégal (Surfing in Senegal) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600096/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600096/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Khadjou Sambe’s home country of Senegal, surfing is considered a male-only sport. But that hasn’t stopped Khadjou from pursuing her surfing dreams, becoming the first girl in Dakar to rule the waves.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/34e0gpK.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rerun: Le pouvoir du foot (Soccer Power) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600097/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600097/</guid><description>Podcast Description In honor of Pride and LGBTQ people across the world, this week we're rerunning the story of Marine Rome and the French soccer team that rocked the Women’s World Cup in 2019.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3KMKz9Z.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>En scène avec Jacques Brel (In the Spotlight with Jacques Brel) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600098/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Arnaud Askoy has already had three different careers when, at age 43, he discovers his true calling: singing. But not his own music. Arnaud plans to launch a career impersonating Jacques Brel, one of the world’s most famous francophone musicians, and might just be crazy enough to pull it off.
Check out recordings of Arnaud’s live performances here (arnaudaskoy.org/video). We also made a Spotify playlist (spoti.fi/36MhU19) where you can kick back and listen to some of Jacques Brel’s greatest hits.</description></item><item><title>Rêves d'une Karatéka (Karate Dreams) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600099/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600099/</guid><description>Podcast Description For many years, Valérie struggled with feeling different from the other students at her karate school in Montreal. But after learning she had Asperger's syndrome, Valérie’s new self-knowledge inspired her to work even harder toward achieving her karate dreams.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/34goRKY.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>L’aquanaute (The Aquanaut) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600100/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fabien Cousteau, grandson of legendary ocean explorer Jacques Cousteau, was just a boy when he fell in love with a creature that most other people fear: sharks. But no one could have predicted that years later, Fabien would do the unthinkable…and decide to live among them.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3H7TErH.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trailer Season 3 | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600101/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 14:24:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600101/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Duolingo French Podcast is back with new episodes starting June 8, 2020. Listen to the trailer now!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>La championne du fromage (The Cheese Champion) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600102/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600102/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a young PhD student, Viriginie Dhorne dreamed of becoming a brilliant academic. But after starting a family and finding herself stuck working in her husband’s cheese business, Virginie began to realize that the world of cheese—a world she once hated—was rich with opportunities for people with brains, ambition… and a fierce competitive streak.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3KOzkh8.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Héros malgré eux (The Unlikely Heroes) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600103/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kilian Belamri’s loitering habits weren’t much appreciated among the residents of his housing project in Malakoff, south of Paris. But when his neighbors found themselves in grave danger late one evening, Kilian and his friends did the unexpected—and became heroes overnight.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/33RKOQo.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>L’amour après le deuil (Love After Grief) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600104/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600104/</guid><description>Podcast Description While on a day trip with his senior citizens club, Raymond Silvestrini survived one of the worst traffic accidents in France’s history. But after meeting Monique, a fellow survivor, his life took another unexpected turn -- this time, for the better.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3fWBX2u.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Le clown « undercover » (The Undercover Clown) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600105/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600105/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a nuclear engineer, David S. had a very serious job. But after discovering a passion for the French art of clowning, he decided to start leading a double life, doing everything in his power to keep his two different worlds from colliding.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3H4Wn57.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>La chasseuse de la particule (The Particle Hunter) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600106/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600106/</guid><description>Podcast Description After earning a PhD in nuclear physics in Europe, Dr. Rajaâ Cherkaoui El Moursli returned to her native Morocco to teach and raise a family. But when she learned her former colleagues were embarking on the scientific quest of the century, she hatched a plan to join them—and give her country the scientific credit it deserved.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/34ajsVI.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Le pouvoir du foot (Soccer Power) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600107/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 05:25:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ever since France won the World Cup in 1998, Marine Rome yearned to play soccer, but felt excluded from the field. When she finally found her dream team in Paris, they decided to take a stand for inclusion at the 2019 World Cup.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3KM5ERN.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Comment je m’appelle ? (What’s My Name?) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600108/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Growing up in France, Hong Dagognet rarely spoke with her adoptive parents about her childhood in Vietnam. But after receiving a surprising letter, she set out to reconnect with her family and finally unveil the mysteries of her past.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3r13beE.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>La mélodie de la Martinique (The Sound of Martinique) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600109/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600109/</guid><description>Podcast Description In everyday sounds, Christophe Chassol hears the makings of a song. That refined ear led Chassol to become a renowned musician, and develop a new genre of music. But it was only by returning to his parents’ birthplace in Martinique that he would be able to create his masterpiece.
A transcript of this episode is available at https://bit.ly/3u1MVMg.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trailer Season 2 | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600110/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 15:19:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600110/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Duolingo French Podcast is back with new episodes starting January 28, 2020. Listen to the trailer now!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Le surfeur sans limites (The surfer without limits) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600111/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eric Dargent devoted his life to surfing — the bigger the waves, the better. He wouldn’t let anything get in his way of his passion, not even a life-altering shark attack. After losing half of his leg, he set out to pursue a new dream, for himself and countless others.
Study materials and a transcript of this episode are available at https://bit.ly/3r2QU9t.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Le paysan (The Countryman) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600112/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cédric Herrou lived a quiet life as an olive farmer on the border between France and Italy until he began to offer shelter for hundreds of migrants struggling to cross into France. But when the French state took him to court for his actions, it would take Cédric and a small community of volunteers to convince a nation that freedom should know no borders.
Study materials and a transcript of this episode are available at https://bit.</description></item><item><title>Le vigneron rebelle (The Rebel Winemaker) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600113/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600113/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Oliver Cousin's grandparents passed away, he promised to honor the winemaking traditions they had passed down to him. But when the French state got involved with his product, he decided to fight to the end for his natural wine.
Study materials and a transcript of this episode are available at https://bit.ly/3KOuYa4.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Partir du paradis (Leaving Paradise) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600114/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Elodie Lauret yearned to discover what was beyond the island of La Réunion. But when she set off to Europe in search of better opportunity, she realized over time that the island would always be her place to call home.
Study materials and a transcript of this episode are available at https://bit.ly/35hcJcU.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Entre deux mondes (Between Two Worlds) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600115/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600115/</guid><description>Podcast Description For a long time, Paris was the only place Alexia Sena considered home. But when Alexia began to wonder how she would pass down her Cameroonian heritage to her mixed-race daughter born in France, she decided to move back to Cameroon with her family in search of the identity she thought she lost.
Study materials and a transcript of this episode are available at https://bit.ly/3G2NWGo.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Le magicien des baguettes (The Baguette Magician) | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600116/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mahmoud M’Seddi was born to bake. When M’Seddi was surprised to come in 7th place in the Grand Prix contest for Best Baguette in Paris in 2017, he knew that the next time, he had a chance to win. He would prove to his parents and an entire nation that he was meant to do this for the rest of his life.
Study materials and a transcript of this episode are available at https://bit.</description></item><item><title>Trailer Season 1 | Duolingo French Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4281600117/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 17:13:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4281600117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Deepen your language skills and knowledge of the French-speaking world through fascinating true stories in easy-to-follow French, with added English for context. From Duolingo, the world's #1 way to learn a language. Hosted by Ngofeen Mputubwele.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>