<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/free-state-with-joe-brolly-and-dion-fanning/</link><description>Recent content in Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 01:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/free-state-with-joe-brolly-and-dion-fanning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>POSH: The tongue twisting world of Dublin 4 with Paul Howard, Ross O’Carroll-Kelly &amp; Roddy Collins | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090057/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 01:01:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Roddy Collins and Paul Howard join Dion and Joe for the 'Free State' Christmas special.
They explain how Medjugorje is a good place to go on the lash, their time on the road together with Steve Collins and the rise of the D4 accent. And Joe is surprised to discover that a place he thought was a figment of Ross O’Carroll Kelly’s imagination actually exists.
Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning is a Gold Hat Production in association with SwanMcG.</description></item><item><title>Deep Fake, The Many Masks Of Al Foran: Part 2 | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 01:15:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090001/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s episode, Al Foran recalls the good and bad in the celebrities he has encountered. He takes us inside the mechanics of creating an impression and talks about the movie greats from Brando to Denzel Washington. Dion also recalls a day in Barnsley when Roy Keane went full Joe Pesci.
Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning is a Gold Hat Production in association with SwanMcG.</description></item><item><title>Deep Fake, The Many Masks Of Al Foran: Part 1 | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 01:01:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090002/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week's Free State welcomes figures from politics, sport and entertainment. From Donald Trump to Katie Taylor to Tyson Fury, Al Foran has an unparalleled ability to make people feel as if they are listening, not to an impression, but to the person themselves. Al joins Joe and Dion to talk about making it in a new media world, how he has to inhabit the people he mimics and what links Christopher Walken to Eamon Dunphy.</description></item><item><title>Fantasy: Ireland is in flames. Reality: Ireland is not in flames | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 04:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why has Ireland caught the attention of Steve Bannon, Tucker Carlson and Elon Musk? In today’s Free State, Joe and Dion look at how the stability of the state can be threatened by the powerful preying on the public’s irrational fears. And, as Conor McGregor continues to rain hate down on innocent people, Joe considers if there is a different path.
Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning is a Gold Hat Production in association with SwanMcG.</description></item><item><title>The Twilight Zone (An Imaginary World Where Ireland is At War) | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 01:01:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090004/</guid><description>Podcast Description What attracts people to conspiracy theories? In an uncertain world is it certainty or do they offer excitement missing in their lives?&amp;nbsp;In today’s Free State, Joe and Dion enter the twilight zone, the fantasy land where Ireland is at war with the other.
They look at what drives these theories, the anger of those who believe them and discuss one previously unknown fact uncovered by the conspiracy theorists: Did you know that Joe Brolly wanks dogs?</description></item><item><title>In Dublin's Fair City | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 01:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090005/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do we combat hate?&amp;nbsp;
What happened in the Dublin Riots was driven by far right agitators but how do we fight their message?&amp;nbsp;
Dion and Joe ask how should we treat those on the margins of the hate movement.
Finland has become a world leader in combating hate and misinformation using a curriculum that starts when their kids are five years old. Turns out kids don’t hate “others” unless they have been taught to hate them.</description></item><item><title>God save Ireland, said the heroes - Dublin Riots | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090006/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 01:01:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last Thursday, Joe Brolly was returning to the Stardust Inquest when he witnessed the events unfolding on Parnell Square.
On Free State today he talks about what he saw and how humanity and courage revealed themselves at this most frightening moment.
Dion and Joe reflect on the riots that followed, how the hate movement needs to be dealt with and why Conor McGregor has nothing to offer Ireland.</description></item><item><title>Derry Girls | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 01:15:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Five Derry girls went to the Stardust nightclub. Only four came home.
How do people keep going when their lives change tragically in a moment? What is it that defines the human spirit?
On today’s Free State Joe talks about the Stardust Inquest, the resilience of people in the worst of circumstances and the quiet heroism that has been revealed. Dion and Joe talk too about Hillsborough and the fight for justice when the British establishment tried to smear them.</description></item><item><title>The Thick Of It | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 01:01:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090008/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is more mind altering, a trip to Amsterdam or trying to track the lies and deception of the Tories in Britain?
On this week’s Free State, Joe has all the information on a hallucinogenic trip - maybe too much information - in Holland. The Covid Inquiry, Suella Braverman’s propaganda and the return of David Cameron tell us everything about the British establishment. Joe also can’t tell the difference between Dion and a humanoid just out of its box.</description></item><item><title>Wounded Child No Surviving Family - Part 2 | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 01:10:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090009/</guid><description>Podcast Description When did ‘ceasefire’ become a dirty word?
In the second podcast this week on the destruction of Gaza, Dion and Joe look at how language has been weaponised during the conflict. How did a desire for a ceasefire come to mean that you are, at best, hopelessly naive and, at worst, a Hamas sympathiser? The barbarity of what has been inflicted on the people of Gaza by the Israeli government is changing that view but too slowly.</description></item><item><title>Wounded Child No Surviving Family (WCNSF) | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 01:01:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Around the world people are marching in their millions for peace and calling for a ceasefire in Gaza. On Free State, Joe and Dion have a difficult conversation about war, peace and propaganda which reflects the difficult conversations people are having everywhere.
They ask why are these conversations so difficult and how did calling for peace become such a risky thing to do?
Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning is a Gold Hat Production in association with SwanMcG.</description></item><item><title>The Secret Life Of David Gough Part 2: Bewitched, Bothered And Bewildered | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 01:15:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090011/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Gough felt sure he would live a life where love was denied to him. But a poem changed his life.
In part 2 of Free State, David Gough talks about the sliding doors moment in his life and how it changed everything.
Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning is a Gold Hat Production in association with SwanMcG.
For more on Free State: https://freestatepodcast.com/
To get in touch with the podcast: info@freestatepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Blue Moon. The Secret Life Of David Gough | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090012/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 01:01:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090012/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Gough is the most famous and the best referee in Ireland.
He grew up in a religious and staunch GAA family and like everyone he wanted to fit in. He was an altar boy and a Gaelic footballer but one day, when he was 15, he saw the front page of a newspaper and it changed everything.
David is this week’s guest on Free State. He tells Joe and Dion about his journey.</description></item><item><title>The Unbearable Lightness Of Living. Michael Lewis talks life, love &amp; the death of his beloved daughter Dixie Lee. | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 01:15:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090013/</guid><description>Podcast Description During the rise of Sam Bankman-Fried, Michael Lewis got closer to him than anybody else. But the fall of the crypto baby gave the Moneyball author a different story. When people turned on Bankman-Fried, Michael Lewis knew they would turn on him too.&amp;nbsp;
In the second part of his interview on Free State, Michael Lewis talks about why he took on the story and what kept him going.</description></item><item><title>Who wants to be a billionaire? The rise and fall of crypto king Sam Bankman Fried | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 01:01:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090014/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week’s Free State, Michael Lewis, the author behind Hollywood blockbusters Moneyball, The Big Short and The Blind Side, joins Dion and Joe.&amp;nbsp;
Michael's new book Going Infinite charts the rise and fall of Sam Bankman-Fried who within two years of discovering crypto was worth $22 billion.&amp;nbsp;
In the first part of a two-part interview, Michael talks to Joe and Dion about why sport in America has become as violent as it was for gladiators in the Roman Empire and why he would give up sex before exercise.</description></item><item><title>Netenyahu And The Coffin Of Peace | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090015/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 00:02:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Where is the way out of the horror in Gaza? When the Shankill Road bomb killed ten people in Frizzell’s fish shop 30 years ago there seemed to be no way out of violence and destruction in the north. But a year later there was a ceasefire and by 1998 a peace process that was the envy of the world. It happened because world leaders like Bill Clinton and Tony Blair were resolute in working with those who wanted peace.</description></item><item><title>The Nuclear Tiger And The Hungry Alleycat | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 00:05:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090016/</guid><description>Podcast Description How much is enough? With the threat that things will worsen even more in Gaza, what will it take for those with influence to intervene. The US and President Biden are friends of Israel, as they should be, but now they need to be friends of Palestine too. What is stopping them?
On this episode of Free State, Joe and Dion look at what might be needed for peace and how it was lost a generation ago with catastrophic consequences.</description></item><item><title>Oh What A Lovely Genocide | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 00:01:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090017/</guid><description>Podcast Description The world is watching as terror and suffering come to the people of Gaza once more. In this terrible war, there is also a propaganda war. This war is waged to distract and deflect from slaughter and genocide. After the savagery of Hamas on Oct 7th, there is an understandable need among Israelis for a response but indiscriminate attacks on Palestinians will not destroy Hamas.&amp;nbsp;
On Free State this week, Dion and Joe discuss how Israel is breaching international law, anti semitism and why Joe Biden needs to speak truth to Benjamin Netanyahu.</description></item><item><title>The Israeli Death Star: The Tragedy Of Palestine, Gaza and Israel | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090018/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 00:15:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090018/</guid><description>Podcast Description As Israel commits war crimes in Gaza, can anyone persuade the country’s government to stop the slaughter?
On part 2 of this week’s Free State, Joe and Dion recall their own trips to Israel and their experiences in the country. It is a land where fundamentalism, hatred and fear have twisted all hopes for a peaceful existence. Within the country there are voices, even after the horrors of October 7th, calling for restraint.</description></item><item><title>Dancing Among The Corpses | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 00:01:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090019/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Israeli government - emboldened by politicians in the west - is committing war crimes. Gaza is a human catastrophe where the horrors will echo through history. There is a primal need within so many Israelis for action to avenge the horrific massacre of the innocents by Hamas. But how is the cycle of violence broken? In the bloodlust for revenge, sane voices in Israel and around the world are being drowned out.</description></item><item><title>On Her Majesty’s Secret Service - Part 2 | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:15:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090020/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the second part of 'On Her Majesty’s Secret Service', Peter Taylor discusses the attempts of the British establishment to censor &amp;amp; intimidate him. He describes the central importance of the hunger strike and how it changed everything.&amp;nbsp;
He recalls a day spent locked in a cell in the dreaded H Blocks with a young Eamonn McDermott &amp;amp; marvelling at his book collection. “How can an IRA man read Tolstoy &amp;amp; Hardy?</description></item><item><title>On Her Majesty’s Secret Service | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:01:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Late in the night following Bloody Sunday, a young reporter arrived in Derry. ‘If you want to know what’s going on here,’ John Hume told him, ‘he’s the person you should be talking to you. He’s called Martin McGuinness’. It was the first time this young reporter called Peter Taylor had heard the name.&amp;nbsp;
For 50 years Taylor made establishing the truth in the north his goal. He talked to everyone.</description></item><item><title>Fellas! Are you having any fun? | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 00:01:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090022/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the end, Pat Gilroy will remember the fun more than the winning. What is sport for except those moments shared among a team that will never be forgotten?&amp;nbsp;
In this episode of Free State, Joe and Dion talk to Pat about what is being lost in sport as backroom teams swell and&amp;nbsp;clubs and counties are being drained of finances by professional management teams who have no bond with them.</description></item><item><title>Derry Boys: Mickey Harte &amp; The Caravan Of Fools | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 00:01:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090023/</guid><description>Podcast Description When the news broke that Mickey Harte was the new manager of Derry, some accepted it as part of how the modern GAA operates. But for others it struck at the heart of the GAA.&amp;nbsp;
In a powerful and emotional episode of Free State, Pat Gilroy is back with Joe and Dion to talk about Mickey Harte and loyalty.&amp;nbsp;
What is the GAA about? What do we want? Is the association becoming a sham, where there are more barter accounts than at RTÉ?</description></item><item><title>Hate. The Shit Magnificent Seven - Part 2 | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090024/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 00:15:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matthew Collins was dead inside. This is where hatred led - to a library with mothers cowering in fear, sheltering from an attack from his far right group. The sound of hatred was the sound of a pregnant woman crying and begging for mercy
His life changed that day when he realised that violence is always where hatred leads. Hatred of asylum seekers, Jews, people of colour, the trans community, Muslims, librarians…anyone will do.</description></item><item><title>Hate. The Shit Magnificent Seven - Part 1 | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090025/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 00:15:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Once upon a time, Matthew Collins would have been standing with the mob outside Dáil Éireann erecting gallows and spitting hate.&amp;nbsp;
This unexceptional teenager fell under the spell of older Neo Nazis and became, in his own words, a vile violent hater, who wanted nothing more than to smash someone, anyone, in the face with a hammer.
Matthew joins Joe and Dion on Free State this week for a two-part interview.</description></item><item><title>Unquiet Graves - Part 2: Smiling Like You’ve Never Been Gone | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090026/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 00:15:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090026/</guid><description>Podcast Description For the families of those murdered by security forces collusion, the truth was all they had left.
In Part II of Unquiet Graves, Joe and Dion look at the fight for truth from the families affected by the Legacy Bill. The truth would not set them free but it would provide some peace. It would honour the memory of the dead. They hope to see them some day, walking in, smiling like they’ve never been gone.</description></item><item><title>Unquiet Graves - Part 1 | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090027/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 00:15:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090027/</guid><description>Podcast Description The past lives in everyone traumatised by the Troubles. The Legacy Bill has layered misery and anxiety on top of suffering and injustice. For the families who are haunted by the graves of their loved ones, the Act will bring only silence. The families want the truth about the past, the truth about state collusion and murder.
On Free State, Joe and Dion look at the stories of those families whose lifelong search for justice is in peril.</description></item><item><title>Wrap The Green Flag Round Me Boys - Part 2 | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090028/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 00:15:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090028/</guid><description>Podcast Description With around 35% of people north and south supporting the Sinn Fein movement, Dion &amp;amp; Joe wonder why there isn’t a single person from a Republican background in the mainstream Irish media
On Part 2 of ‘Wrap The Green Flag Round Me Boys’, we discuss how change is coming in Ireland and why politicians will be followers not leaders. Also can Joe Brolly be persuaded to agree with himself?</description></item><item><title>Wrap The Green Flag Round Me Boys - Part 1 | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090029/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 00:01:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is ‘Ooh Ah, Up the Ra’ the best the Irish establishment can do in the face of the existential threat posed by Sinn Fein?&amp;nbsp;In the week that Michéal Martin said Sinn Fein were “infecting” the people of Ireland, Dion and Joe discuss the FG/FF Culture wars against Sinn Fein. They reflect on the family dynasties that replaced the British in Ireland: WT Cosgrave in his top hat, Charlie Haughey on his stallion.</description></item><item><title>Who says there’s no talent in Longford? | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090030/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 00:01:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is the Rose of Tralee a national embarrassment or does it represent something precious? On this week’s Free State, Joe and Dion look at Irish culture and what makes it different. There’s also Pele’s (and Joe’s) lack of concern about erectile dysfunction as well as a cost busting alternative to Viagra.
Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning is a Gold Hat Production in association with SwanMcG.</description></item><item><title>Roddy Collins Is A Wanker - Part 2 | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090031/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 00:01:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090031/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Part Two of Roddy Collins is a W****r, Roddy Collins talks to Joe and Dion about his failed attempt at an IRA hold up as a teenager, his days going AWOL with Vinnie Jones and the love story that has shaped his life.
Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning is a Gold Hat Production in association with SwanMcG.
For more on Free State: https://freestatepodcast.com/
To get in touch with the podcast: info@freestatepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Roddy Collins Is A Wanker - Part 1 | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090032/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 00:01:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Don’t mess with the Cabra boys. In the first of a two-part interview, Roddy Collins joins Dion and Joe on Free State. He talks about the confidence trick they played on Chris Eubank, the deeply superstitious middleweight champion of the world. He remembers growing up in Cabra, his uncle Terry, Reggie Kray, banjoeing ‘The General’ Martin Cahill and much more.
Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning is a Gold Hat Production in association with SwanMcG.</description></item><item><title>Death On The Mediterranean | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090033/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:01:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stalin said one death is a tragedy, a million deaths are a statistic. On Free State this week, Dion and Joe discuss the tragedy of tens of thousands drowning in the Mediterranean. They wonder how we lost touch with our own humanity and why people fall for the same tricks of hate peddled for centuries. They also ask why did four of our own MEPs vote against&amp;nbsp;a resolution that would have ramped up search and rescue operations in the Mediterranean?</description></item><item><title>Hate, Housing &amp; Happiness - Pat Gilroy’s Roadmap to Utopia | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090034/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 00:01:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fresh from Dublin’s triumph in the All Ireland final, Joe and Dion welcome an old friend back to Free State. Pat Gilroy returns to talk about why the most vulnerable have always been a target throughout history and why inequality is at the root of society’s problems. Pat also explains what a GAA World Series would look like and outlines his radical solution to the Dublin housing crisis…</description></item><item><title>Don’t Cry For Me, Falkland Islands | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090035/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:01:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Donald Trump continues to demonstrate how reality can be hijacked by lies. This week Dion and Joe look at how America and Britain have been lost to populism while wondering why the Falkland Islands are more loved in Britain than Northern Ireland. Joe also undertakes not to sue his own podcast…
Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning is a Gold Hat Production in association with SwanMcG.</description></item><item><title>Unleash the superhero within: How to become a multi millionaire, a wonderful lover and a complete a**hole. | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090036/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:01:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can you sustain an orgasm for 15 minutes? Joe and Dion help you unleash the superhero within and they disagree about the power of the mind. Joe also remembers a fiery encounter with Enda McNulty
Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning is a Gold Hat Production in association with SwanMcG.
For more on Free State: https://freestatepodcast.com/
To get in touch with the podcast: info@freestatepodcast.com
Twitter: @dionfanning @JoeBrolly1993 @freestateirl</description></item><item><title>The Surprising Truth About Champions feat. Philly McMahon &amp; Ger Brennan | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090037/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 00:01:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090037/</guid><description>Podcast Description What makes a champion? Philly McMahon and Ger Brennan talk to Joe and Dion about what they were prepared to do as they helped to shape that great Dublin team. Philly tells the extraordinary story of his father’s life on the run while Ger explains why he was drawn to the priesthood before taking another path. They speak about hate and glory and the power in finding a thing - whatever it is - that is bigger than you.</description></item><item><title>RTÉ The Musical - Act 2 | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090038/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:01:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090038/</guid><description>Podcast Description You’ve got to pick a pocket or two...
You can say what you like about Ryan Tubridy but do not question his soul, his love for the decent people of Ireland and, in particular, the decent people of Louth.&amp;nbsp;In Act II of RTÉ The Musical, Joe and Dion look at the evidence the Toy Man, his agent Noel Kelly and the RTÉ executives provided to the Oireachtas committees. They also extend an invitation to Ryan Tubridy…</description></item><item><title>RTÉ The Musical - Act 1 | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090039/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:01:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Show me the (taxpayers) money...
What does the RTÉ scandal tell us about Ireland? Joe and Dion explain why this was always about more than Ryan Tubridy’s salary. The Late Late Show’s decline from the glory days of Gay Byrne shows how RTÉ has been captured and why it can’t be a public service broadcaster and an advertising agency at the same time.
Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning is a Gold Hat Production in association with SwanMcG.</description></item><item><title>The Inglorious 12th | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090040/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 00:01:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you know the words to The Sash? Is it culture or hate that sees effigies of politicians including Leo Varadkar burned on bonfires? This week Joe and Dion discuss the Twelfth of July, the role it plays in the siege mentality of the DUP and how to change it. Also is it better for RTE to have Gregory Campbell on the airwaves or Noel Kelly’s clients? And Dion finally persuades Joe to talk about cricket.</description></item><item><title>The Sportswriter | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090041/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 23:15:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Richard Ford, the Pulitzer Prize winning author, joins Joe and Dion on this week’s Free State.
Before he became a novelist, Richard was a sportswriter. He talks to Dion and Joe about why he will defend America when people attack it, his views on President Biden and an extraordinary and hilarious encounter with Muhammad Ali in 1969.
We also find out what happened to Joe’s own unfinished Great Irish Novel, a novel inspired by the works of Richard Ford.</description></item><item><title>The Ultimate Gunfighter | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090042/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 23:15:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Humans have always been drawn towards violence but is there a limit to the licence to thrill? Violence has always been a part of sport but now with events like Power Slap, sport is a tiny part of violence. Where will it end? Dion and Joe welcome back an old friend and ask, as Saudi Arabia takes over sport, could public executions one day become a pay per view event?</description></item><item><title>The Headless Men | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090043/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 23:15:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090043/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happens if you speak out against the tribe in Unionism? Is there only free speech for Catholics in Northern Ireland? Joe and Dion argue about commemorations and discuss the Irish language and the secret meeting Joe attended with concerned Protestants. Also do people in the south need to do more to make unionists welcome?
Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning is a Gold Hat Production in association with SwanMcG.</description></item><item><title>Our Friends in the North | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090044/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 00:01:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dion and Joe debate and disagree about friendships and links between the north and south. They recall some fascinating incidents from the Troubles, including the forgotten heroism of Major Mike Guerin of the Light Air Defence regiment of the Royal Artillery, a real life Bruce Willis. And if a young man gets an excruciating tattoo after losing a bet in Vegas, you might think he would do it for a greater cause than Joe Brolly.</description></item><item><title>The Reverse Cowgirl | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090045/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 00:01:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090045/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do you achieve the perfect orgasm without a sexual partner? What precisely is the reverse cowgirl? Where can you buy an orgasmatron? Dion &amp;amp; Joe explore these crucial questions. They also look at how a tiny group of Eton posh boys hijacked the U.K., handed out billions to their pals and used an entire kingdom as their reverse cowgirl. As a bonus, Joe gives an apology masterclass. Enjoy.</description></item><item><title>Searching For God | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090046/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:01:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090046/</guid><description>Podcast Description What does it mean to confront addiction? Do we still have a stereotype when it comes to imagining what somebody with a drink problem looks like? This week Dion and Joe talk about drink and what is left when you drain the pool. Dion takes Joe through his own story of recovery and explains why war stories are for amateurs.
Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning is a Gold Hat Production in association with SwanMcG.</description></item><item><title>The Roman Catholic Breeders Association | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090047/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 00:01:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Birds do it, bees do it, but nobody does it like northern catholics, even the educated ones. Once again the demographic changes in the north have been framed in terms of a trope that Catholics are out breeding Protestants. In this week’s Free State, Joe and Dion look at the history of the Unionist view of Catholics in the north, how it fed into the south and why it persists.</description></item><item><title>The Lonely Passion of Patrick Gilroy | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090048/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 00:01:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Before Dublin became the greatest Gaelic football team ever seen, they were the best known failures in Irish sport. Pat Gilroy was the manager who turned Dublin around. He joins Joe and Dion to talk about his years at Trinity with Joe, the players he wanted to dump who went on to become multiple All-Ireland winners and why he disagrees with Joe on the importance of psychology in sport.</description></item><item><title>The Trouble With Supremacists | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090049/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 00:01:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090049/</guid><description>Podcast Description What unites the US Republican Party, Brexiteers and the DUP? This week, Joe and Dion look at the magical thinking that has replaced reason among those who once believed they were born to rule in Washington and London - and how the DUP showed them the way.&amp;nbsp;Behind the three-word slogans, the bluster and the demonisation of minorities, what insecurities are driving the supremacists? And what would your reaction be if, as Joe once did, you answered the door to the Reverend Ian Paisley?</description></item><item><title>Curb Your Enthusiasm Father | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090050/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:01:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090050/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you were offered a lift on Air Force One would you take it? Joe talks to Dion about his time with Joe Biden in Ireland and the extraordinary empathy shown by the president when visiting end of life patients at the Mayo Roscommon Hospice. He also gives some fascinating insights into what happened behind the scenes during the president’s visit. Finally, brace yourself for a cringeworthy &amp;amp; hilarious encounter between Brolly and a priest in Dublin City centre.</description></item><item><title>Ooh Aah, Up Which Ra? - Part 2 | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090051/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 00:01:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090051/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the second part of Ooh Aah, Up Which Ra, Dion and Joe wonder what being honest about history really means and if Ireland wants to be Austria or Germany. Joe talks about Martin McGuinness and how many people were angered by what he wrote after McGuinness’s death and he also recounts an eye-opening experience at an Old Firm game.
Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning is a Gold Hat Production in association with SwanMcG.</description></item><item><title>Ooh Aah, Up Which Ra? | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090052/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 00:01:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090052/</guid><description>Podcast Description When the Irish women’s football team qualified for the World Cup, their achievement was overshadowed by a video of them singing ‘Ooh Aah, Up the Ra’. In this week’s episode Dion and Joe talk about why the song triggered such debate and if there are double standards involved, not just when certain groups are criticised and others aren’t, but in talking about the IRA itself. What does the issue tell us about Irish identity and how we understand our history?</description></item><item><title>The Nigerian Prince | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090053/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Charles Anyaegbunam had a privileged upbringing in Nigeria as a Nigerian prince. His first meeting with Joe Brolly took place either during an escapade around Ireland or an escapade around Florida. He talks to Dion and Joe about his son, the rapper Rejjie Snow, his own view on racism in Ireland and the time himself and Joe tried and failed to buy the Jacksonville Jaguars.
Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning is a Gold Hat Production in association with SwanMcG.</description></item><item><title>The Optimism Muscle | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090054/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 00:01:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you know where to find your optimism muscle? In this week’s episode Joe and Dion look at how the 21st century has become a factory and why a banal uniformity has invaded so many areas of life, including sport.&amp;nbsp;
With stories of John Morrison, Eamonn Coleman, Stan Bowles, Phil Lynott &amp;amp; Thin Lizzy, Dion and Joe wonder if all that was missing from their lives was an attitude of gratitude?</description></item><item><title>Smile Or Die | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090055/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:01:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Everybody wants to be happy but what if simply wanting to be happy is as crazy as simply wanting to live on Mars? In the first episode Dion and Joe examine how vulnerable people have been exploited by wellness gurus and in a time of uncertainty why those who offer easy and misleading answers have thrived. There's also an exiting executive position in the sporting world to discuss...</description></item><item><title>This is Free State Podcast | Free State with Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6567090056/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 15:43:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6567090056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Free State is a podcast for the curious that stimulates, provokes, challenges and entertains, while never taking itself too seriously. Free State covers topics from sport to politics, love to loss, the human condition and how to fix the world, with guests from across the planet including Nigerian princes, former Prime Ministers, ex convicts, footballers, boxers and extraordinary people from every walk of life.&amp;nbsp;
Free State is presented by Joe Brolly and Dion Fanning.</description></item></channel></rss>