<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Girls Uninterrupted on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-girls-uninterrupted/</link><description>Recent content in The Girls Uninterrupted on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-girls-uninterrupted/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Toenails, mingy eggs, daytime soaps and a sweet baby angel. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Honestly, when the three of us are in the same room, the wheels completely fall off.
I don't even know how to describe this podcast - it goes from clipping your toenails, to buffet breakfasts, to confirmation of a moustache, to a Slippery Susan and rounds out with a sweet baby angel.
We wish you well.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Big news (but low key), men sitting down to pee, and soup. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gracie may very well have low key slipped some news into the minutes today...
We probably talk for way too long about the mechanics of a man sitting down to pee.
We wonder who goes to a restaurant and orders soup?!
PDA at a concert?
Mouthwash?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Strapless Bras, sickbags and lava lamps. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Caitlin thinks there is indeed a good strapless bra that exists.
Have you ever spewed in a sick bag?
Remember K-Bars? They were a time weren't they?
What about lava lamps? Did you have one or were you not allowed?
All the big chats today folks.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mercury in the microwave, dresses over pants, and the "Xmas window". | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mercury is in the microwave folks but Gracie reckons Mercury Energy owes us money and quite frankly we are here for it.
Are you climbing in the Christmas window this year? Or are you staying out of it?
Dresses over pants. No.
And when your mate is being rude to your husband - what do you do?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Fiji!! Cute or hot or healthy? Flicking nipples and badly-packed mussels. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 04:59:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Not only are the three of us in the same room together, but it's our first podcast back together in about six weeks (she's a biggie)!!
We debrief about the glorious trip to Fiji, all thanks to the wonderful team at Tourism Fiji - we had a stunning time!
Caitlin tells us something she regularly does on the couch and we weren't expecting that.
Do you like being called cute or hot or healthy?</description></item><item><title>Shaving above the knee, thrifting and nipple bras | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 05:18:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Caitlin and Gracie fumble their way through another episode this week without B, who will be back next week! They talk about going make-up-free, Celine Dion, being back on the dating apps, Christmas Trees and losing yourself after having children. Also, Caitlin may be a creep at the gym…
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Caitlin’s European Adventures, Playing with Fire and Belly Buttons. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 02:22:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Caitlin is back and sharing all of her European stories (um, hot waiters…) baby travel tips from Gracie, daycare fun, belly buttons, hair ties and a bunch of other stuff including a listener tip on those pesky spag bol tupperware containers.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Solo female traveling yarns - with Alexa West | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610008/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week's guest host is an absolute VIBE.
Over a decade ago, Alexa West boarded a plane with $200 in her pocket and zero travel experience under her belt.
She's now a best selling travel author, has traveled all over the world and built a 6-figure travel empire.
Her mission: to show women how we can travel and work abroad without having a boyfriend or a big bank account.</description></item><item><title>The Beckhams, single pity, a surprise period and Stewart Island - Brodie's minutes. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 05:17:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Look, Caitlin's in Ibiza being fabulous and Gracie is having a beautiful family holiday, but I still had some minutes!
So I said them haha.
Enjoy!
Brodie x
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The "boyfriend experience", designer bags and running poles - with Morgan Penn | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610010/</guid><description>Podcast Description She's a juicy episode today as somatic sexologist Morgan Penn joins Brodie and we go everywhere from hairy or waxed or lasered, to getting out of a rut, to dealing with break ups, to normalising the slut era, to learning about the "Morgan Penn Boyfriend Experience" and then somehow we end on running poles. Yes, they are a thing thank you.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Holding hands, the "Pandemic Skip" and boy math. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 05:17:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610011/</guid><description>Podcast Description The fantastic Tegan Yorwarth joins Brodie for the week and it's a real rollercoaster of yarns.
Think Taylor Swift, Kim V Kourtney, having babies or not, politics and voting, Meg the Great White Shark from Stewart Island, buying houses, taking supplements because health, boy math and the "pandemic skip".
Told you it goes everywhere!
xxx
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We need to talk about Kevin (and stool samples and RARO and naughty kids)... | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Caitlin has pissed off the Jonas Brothers diehard fans by a a single Instagram caption...
We reminisce about RARO (does it still exist??) and going out and doing naughty things as teenagers.
Brodie has a traumatic experience with a stool sample.
Turns out she's not the only one struggling with stools this week (Frank's Corner)...
Gracie gives some amazing advice to a woman who's just found out she's pregnant and has mixed feelings about it.</description></item><item><title>A Girlie Roman Empire, Sydney Mara and, Crocs vs Birks, UP THE WAHS. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610013/</guid><description>Podcast Description UP THE WAHS!
The girls discuss the Roman Empire trend (because it's actually bloody funny) and realise that a lot of the girl versions are quite grim!
Brodie gives a Sydney Marathon debrief.
Caitlin is in the departure lounge.
Gracie has to make a HUGE decision...
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Woman wees, BJs and chats, shoplifting and chutney. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 06:31:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brodie's back and there's a lot to unpack from Bali...
Gracie had to deal with Frank shoplifting and choking in one day.
Caitlin is trying to get "pissfit" for Europe so we tell her that hangovers aren't the same over there.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kevin Jonas, Brain Worms and Short Kings | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 05:47:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610015/</guid><description>Podcast Description B is having a much-deserved break in Bali, so Gracie and Caitlin have taken the reins on this week's episode! Caitlin is oddly into Timothée and Kylie, Gracie has unlocked a new fear of worms on the brain, and they are both making sure they are enrolled to vote... Plus they discover just how lame they truly are with their coffee orders and how much they enjoy long walks.</description></item><item><title>Zoe Marshall Uninterrupted | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610016/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are so excited to have Zoe Marshall on the podcast this week, this is an episode you will NOT want to miss.
Zoe has been a broadcaster for over 12 years, and is the host and creator of the hugely successful podcast The Deep. From diving into Gloriavale, interviewing terminally ill parents, a madam, a lactating porn star and a man who has sex with dolls - there is quite possibly no one Zoe wouldn’t interview.</description></item><item><title>Taranaki Hardcore, Beekeeping age and the Unicorn... | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gracie spills the tea on all the sexy towns and regions of Aotearoa...
We learn about "beekeeping age" and Caitlin is not impressed...
We hear about what it means to be "the unicorn" and WOW.
And the girls are divided over when you should pack for a holiday - the night before or weeks out? See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Frank, Frank, Football, Furtado and rats and bins. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Frank Green is at it again...
Nelly Furtado is BACK and we are so here for it!
We're also here for the absolute raging success of the FIFA Women's World Cup - how bloody good!
Baby Frank is in his poo era...
Apparently we are in for a Rat Girl Summer...
And possibly the smoothest segue from rats to new green food scrap bins...
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Baby Crocs, Greasy sluts, RSA pours and Snags. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 05:44:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Would you catch the bus after a one night stand?
Frank's got baby Crocs and Brodie's ready to stage an intervention.
We discuss our RSA drink of choice and reminisce about the days of working in radio and cooking thousands of Sizzler sausages (pretty sure it's not the first time we've talked about it but my goodness it's a memory).
Plus we are OUTRAGED at Barcelona.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Aliens and sun bears, self waxing, kid carparks and virginity. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610020/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you're looking for in-depth analysis into UFO's you won't find it here.
Same with sun bears.
But Gracie can offer some self-waxing advice.
Caitlin can tell you how to celebrate your birthday all by yourself.
And Brodie can offer you some pearls of wisdom one week after the great yoni mapping of 2023...
Also, an amazing listener question which makes us discuss "losing your virginity" and how it really needs to shut up and just not be a societal expectation.</description></item><item><title>The great yoni mapping of 2023... | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brodie's yoni mapping has happened and we are here to debrief all about it - it was an incredible experience!
Plus we debrief all the tour goss, check in with Caitlin who's getting her health back, and Gracie's got a rolling Frank which is another challenge for our gorgeous Mum!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Skims, boundaries, theft, old love, 1000 Margs. Live from Auckland! | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Well, the last show in Auckland did not disappoint!
We've had an absolute blast on this tour, and hope everyone who's been listening has been enjoying the episodes - we best see ya'll at the next tour which we are already thinking about (after 300 hours sleep haha).
A busy show this week with a full Skims report, a chat about boundaries, someone stole something, and we debrief about the 1000 Margaritas we had the week before and the tea around that.</description></item><item><title>Escorts, Yoni mapping, Pet Day. The Wellington Show! | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wellington did NOT disappoint and nothing was off limits!
We discuss escorts, and how it might be a better idea than dating apps.
Someone's getting a Yoni map this week...
Gracie surprises us with a gift, and Caitlin lands a slick nursing joke (LOLOLOL).
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dick amnesia, a lost tooth, Nigella Pawson and a Gorilla (LIVE FROM Ōtautahi Christchurch) | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610024/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610024/</guid><description>Podcast Description We had an absolute blast on the first stop of the tour in beautiful Ōtautahi Christchurch.
Thank you so much to Novotel Christchurch Airport for having us - it was an amazing event and we appreciate your support.
She sure was a busy show, covering things like dick amnesia, some pretty hilarious animal stories (cats and gorillas), and a missing tooth.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode with Real Estate Agent Courtney Pero | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610025/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to this extra special bonus episode with Courtney Pero - a Real Estate Agent based in Ōtautahi Christchurch with Harcourts.
There’s always so much noise around the housing market, whether you’re buying or selling, thinking, freaking out, dreaming - it can get very overwhelming and a bit scary…
We’ve got some of your questions you’ve sent through so thank you lovely listeners.
This episode is brought to you by Courtney Pero.</description></item><item><title>Jason Momoa, Kombucha and cucumbers. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610026/</guid><description>Podcast Description She's a bit of a shorter episode this week but all our remaining minutes will be carried over to our FIRST LIVE SHOW WOOOOOOHOOOOOOOOO!!!
(Which ya'll will get next Monday and that will be the episode for the week FYI).
But don't worry, there's still time to talk about Jason Momoa.
And Kombucha.
And cucumbers.
And Frank graduating!!!!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dry white wine, Mancession, Mount Dads, beige flags. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610027/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 05:47:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610027/</guid><description>Podcast Description We're back and we realise that we are indeed of an age where we enjoy a DRY WHITE WINE (can only be said in the voice though).
Nevermind the recession, what about how many negative quarters in a row we've dealt with in regards to the man shortage (mancession - see what we did there).
Mount Dads - IYKYK
Beige flags.
Doggies in the bed.
Soup for life.</description></item><item><title>Dame Caitlin, blue vulvas, Frank Green and dog poo-gate. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610028/</guid><description>Podcast Description We learn all about blue vulvas today!
Brodie has another rant about Frank Green water bottles (I mean she hardly ever rants) AND a hot, steaming, fresh dog poo update.
Gracie is dicing with danger aka cutting Pumpkins - why are they so RUTHLESS to deal with?
Caitlin cried during The Little Mermaid and we fully support that but we CANNOT get around a tomato bene (you'll understand when you hear it right at the end).</description></item><item><title>The wing, white socks, bra hooks, race bibs and WOFs. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610029/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you suck on the chicken wing?
Are you down with the black tights and white socks trend that's back?
Do you hook your bra up properly?
Should you be able to use marathons to find love and is the race bib the answer?
Should you make sure your car is clean before getting a WOF?
SO MANY QUESTIONS!
We bloody love your support, and would love it even more if you like and subscribe the show wherever you listen to it (subscribe on Apple, follow on Spotify).</description></item><item><title>Basic bitches for the win, flirt school and fake emergencies. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610030/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610030/</guid><description>Podcast Description We've come to the conclusion that we are indeed basic bitches (yes, just today haha) and we actually really happy with it.
Brodie gives an update on Flirt School and while it was super fun and there was learnings...it's still a grim outlook out there folks.
We urge Caitlin to do some DM sliding.
Gracie is in a nude nail era and is also having a wild time on the Apple Ciders and we are here for it.</description></item><item><title>Herpes, Hickeys and Hard Eggs. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610031/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 05:08:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610031/</guid><description>Podcast Description We're pretty sure herpes, hickeys and hard eggs were talked about in the first five minutes but it'll give you an idea of the tone of the podcast today...
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Slutty takeaways, pub grime dudes and Masturbation May. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610032/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610032/</guid><description>Podcast Description We've got a new term to describe the various levels of takeaways and we think it'll stick.
It's Masturbation May in case you didn't know, but shit it's high maintenance.
Are you into dudes that have that "pub grime" look?
We have a dating app update, and some wise advice for one of our single sisters!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Met Gala f*ckery, a town called Dildo, and a couple of rebirths. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610033/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610033/</guid><description>Podcast Description You best believe we dive into every orifice of the Met Gala. We love it, we hate it, we love to love and hate it at the same time ok?!?!?!
Caitlin is having a much deserved holiday, but the other two have essentially had a rebirth!
Brodie gives a debrief on the Routeburn Classic.
Gracie had a gorgie night out.
And a dick-shaped iceberg discovered by a man from Dildo.</description></item><item><title>Captions, a death in Vegas and slick hair and berms. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610034/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gracie thinks the only thing AI might be good for is coming up with our punishing social media captions.
Brodie thinks she knows where her final resting place is.
Caitlin learns what a berm is.
Another quick Coachella debrief.
Gumboot tea, cauliflower and white cowboy boots.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Undies as pants, Barbie and an emotional dump. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610035/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 07:02:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Undies as pants for fashion? We possibly spent way too long on this.
Barbie the movie better have the sex scenes we created when we had Barbies or we're not watching...
There's also some emotional dumping in this episode...
And the trickiest listener question to date...
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Charisma, Our Penny, the Honky Donkey, and Mortgages! | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610036/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610036/</guid><description>Podcast Description She's absolutely chocka this week!
We learn where the rizz actually comes from.
Two rockstars feature on the podcast this week, Penny Lancaster (aka Rod Stewart's wife) and of course, the Honky Donkey at the Fairlie show...
Plus we catch up with Jenna from Mortgages with Jenna, to answer some very helpful questions about buying a house, getting a mortgage, basically all that overwhelming adulting stuff we all need to know about!</description></item><item><title>Adult eggs, vegan poos and cheating boyfriends. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610037/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Caitlin is 32 and still gets an Easter Egg delivered to her door at Easter.
There are hot cross buns that cost SIX DOLLARS.
We possibly will offend the entire vegan community this week...
We want to cancel toilet spray.
And how to deal with cheating boyfriends.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ugly pashes, pub pashes, shrugs and miso soup. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610038/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 09:32:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610038/</guid><description>Podcast Description There was an ugly pash this week and it got us reminiscing about pub pashes.
Why are shrugs creeping their way back in?
Is miso soup overrated, underrated or perfectly rated?
*note we had technical difficulties on this record, so apologies for the audio sounding different. XXX
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Frank's first episode! Crocs, fireballs, paper towels and Marlon Williams. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Frank is LIVE in the studio for his first podcast and he NAILED it!!
We break the news to Gracie that Crocs are dangerous.
Don't mix tequila and fireball shots.
Are paper towels an important part of your kitchen life? And do you wash your tea towels with your clothes?!
Very wholesome today as you can see! X
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tuesdays, roasting, footpaths and hasselback potatoes. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610040/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 07:17:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610040/</guid><description>Podcast Description We've decided Tuesday is the worst day of the week...hence why we normally record on a Wednesday! But anyway here we are.
We discuss the merits of a good roast (both types haha).
Footpath etiquette.
Josh Emett and his hasselback potatoes.
Riding in cars with boys.
Paying to get into clubs.
Flying fried rice.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>HARRY!!!!! And hearses, mom parks and 2nd earrings. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610041/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 08:06:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610041/</guid><description>Podcast Description The gang is all back together and IN THE SAME ROOM TOGETHER!!
You best believe there's a BIG Harry debrief.
Gracie got second ear piercings and we all want second ear piercings.
Brodie's back from off the grid and off the grid was good, and Caitlin's made a skin decision.
And, are there other uses for a hearse?!?!?!?!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mom chat with Meg | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:53:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Meg Mansell joins Caitlin and Gracie to talk of life as a new (ish) mum.
We talk relationships, sleeping separately, going back to work, nipples, expectations, in-laws, all the good stuff. It’s all there even though we only a short amount of time, we love Meg! B is back next week, see you then! xx
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Milk ducts, sourdough, boogers and shoey’s | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 08:25:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610043/</guid><description>Podcast Description B is off the grid for 2 weeks, so Gracie and Caitlin are fumbling their way through the agenda this week! Gracie shares more on the beautiful ups and downs of breastfeeding and newborns and brings a great yet, slightly disturbing game Caitlin has a hot tip on heatless curls and realises she knows nothing at all about Europe and geography And another amazing life update from another beautiful mama x</description></item><item><title>A poonami, front and top loaders, and ssssssshhhhhhhhhhh. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 07:09:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gracie arrives to the poddy fresh from dealing with a Frank poonami which makes Brodie reminisce about the times she poonami'd (SHE WAS A BABY TOO FYI).
Caitlin learns about the difference between a top and a front...
Does ssssshhhhhh offend you?
Plus, an AMAZING life update from one of our wonderful listeners. xxx
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Gracie's back! Plus Lazy Susan's and Apple Watches... | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610045/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 05:55:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610045/</guid><description>Podcast Description We have the most special catch up with Gracie, who shares such a beautiful, honest story about how Frank arrived in this world! Meanwhile, thanks to the inspiration from our amazing listeners - Caitlin is slowly being convinced to shoot her shot at the gym, and Brodie's poised and ready to go too (not sure who with though haha).
And we go hard against Apple Watches...
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Polyamory, manifesting dreams and gym dates. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610046/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 08:02:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Monogamy, polyamory, open relationships, a sly threesome when you're in a relationship. What do you guys think of it all?! We are fascinated by the different ways in which people operate.
Also, STFU if you have a problem with Sam Smith celebrating who they want to be.
Caitlin and Brodie realise they urge dreams on, but sometimes it gets out of hand.
And TALK TO THE BOY AT THE GYM!</description></item><item><title>Pillow partners, lion heads and peaking at high school. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610047/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 04:27:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are pillows the next best bed partner?
Lion-heads as fashion - give us strength.
Aire as a baby name - give us strength.
Did you "peak" at high school?
And what to do when all your life plans blow up in your face.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Saying no, eggs, the rizz and black boots. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610048/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 05:02:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610048/</guid><description>Podcast Description HAPPY NEW YEAR!!
It's just Caitlin and Brodie because our beautiful new Mum Gracie is at home with the most glorious wee boy Frank and they are doing so well, we are so happy for them and hoping our G is trying to get as much sleep as possible!
It's a real delightful catch up about all the bits and bobs that happened over the silly season.
That includes: the egg shortage, a one night stand, expired Christmas ham, black boots and festivals, and a broken flying fox.</description></item><item><title>See you on the other side (with a new baby)!!! | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610049/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 01:20:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can you believe the next time we record a podcast Gracie will have a wee baby boy! We are so excited and happy for Gracie and Ali, and know they are going to be the most wonderful parents!
We recap the year, all the good, the bad, and the bits in between!
And share some highlights and a couple of lowlights.
Thank you for your amazing support again this year, it has truly meant the world to us, we LOVE YOU!</description></item><item><title>Hey Siri, pedal pushers, plastic cheese and Uber Drivers... | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610050/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 06:53:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610050/</guid><description>Podcast Description A MONSTER OF AN EPISODE...
White Lotus, Love Island, Harry and Meghan.
Hair extensions and pedal pushers.
Milking boobies, plastic cheese and asparagus.
And, Uber Drivers.
And that doesn't even scratch the surface...
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Le Snaks, ultra marathons and compliments. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610051/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 05:01:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610051/</guid><description>Podcast Description The great Kepler Challenge debrief after Brodie completes her first ultra marathon!
We discuss all the great food we've lost this year.
Should we be giving more compliments/feeding the egos when we're on the dating apps?
Caitlin is contemplating spending New Year's Eve alone...
Gracie had a Catfish marathon on her birthday and we are absolutely here for it.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hard launches, Bridget Jones and fruit sticks. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610052/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 05:11:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gosh there's quite a bit of brain fry in this episode - we have no doubt you'll hear it - we blame the end of year f*ckery.
Are you a hard launch or soft launch type of person?
Do you hate when someone tells you you look like someone?
And what do you put on your fruit sticks?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Farts + Poos, refunds and more poos. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610053/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 19:42:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gosh there is a lot of poo chat this week - and we hear the first on air fart in the history of The Girls Uninterrupted!
Brodie provides her post-marathon report and unfortunately it wasn't a good pick up spot.
Caitlin fights the big fella and WINS.
Gracie's body is up to all sorts of things, and she's really missing her exercise.
And then we finish on poos...it's great!</description></item><item><title>Do not disturb, hash browns and a new pick up spot? | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610054/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 19:24:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610054/</guid><description>Podcast Description WOMEN'S SPORT, WOMEN'S SPORT, WOMEN'S SPORT!!!!!
Brodie's off to do the Queenstown Marathon and thinks it could be an opportunity for something else...
Caitlin and Gracie change Brodie's phone life for the better.
Gracie can't tie her shoelaces anymore.
Caitlin burnt her head.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Christchurch Live Show! | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610055/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 21:26:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610055/</guid><description>Podcast Description We had an absolute blast on a glorious Sunday afternoon in Christchurch!
Thanks to everyone who came along, we hope you had a good time, and hope everyone who wasn't there enjoys some pretty hilarious chats - including a surprise cameo from Jo Kane at the end...
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cake mix, Mariah, 3B Cream, young adult books. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610056/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 19:37:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Right so we're in November and we discuss whether we can start applying "f*ck it, it's Christmas" to everything...
Caitlin shares an alarming fact about where she listens to Mariah's Christmas song.
We're not impressed with Chrissy Teigen.
Gracie's 31 weeks pregnant, had her final hypnobirthing class and needs some chafing cream.
Brodie's working, running and tutu-ing.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ye, Ants, OOS, Beans, Snoop Dogg, and The Pink Pig. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610057/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 05:35:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Plenty on the minutes today starting with Ye's contract with Adidas being ripped up over his antisemitic comments.
Have you seen how terrifying ants are up close?
We'll potentially offend the Swifties today so here's your warning...
It takes a punishingly long time for Brodie to realise she was right all along with OOS.
And, a story about The Pink Pig that will go down in history!
See omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>The Auckland Live Show! | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610058/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 21:11:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Oh my goodness WHAT A NIGHT!! Thank you so much to everyone who came to the live show at Wynyard Pavilion - we had an absolute blast!
Hope everyone who couldn't make it enjoys this episode, we can tell you it's quite a different feeling saying all the stuff we say with faces looking back at you but we loved every minute!
Thanks to our tour Sponsors, Puma and CeraVe - we couldn't have done it without you!</description></item><item><title>Bad flatties, pottery classes, unsuccessful flirting. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610059/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 20:05:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610059/</guid><description>Podcast Description We share some absolute horror stories about old flatmates - everyone's got a shocker right?
Caitlin's off to pottery classes and we cannot wait to see the results.
Brodie flirted and wasn't successful but hey it was still a time.
Gracie's in her third trimester and about to move house so she's all bloody go!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Butter Boards, Fingering, Brats, Deep Hard n Funky | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610060/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 07:11:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Another mammoth episode because quite frankly it went so many places.
Has alcohol become not cool?
Are butter boards the new platter?
A lesson on fingering.
Cailtin's got to stop calling herself a Brat...
Remember Deep Hard n Funky?
And some advice for a young listener tempted to travel...
Plus HEAPS more!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Anne Hathaway, dance dance doof doof and Costco. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610061/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 06:11:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610061/</guid><description>Podcast Description The girls disagree on Anne Hathaway's double movie "glow ups".
They geek out and remind you how important it is to vote in the Local Government elections.
But don't worry, we get back into some dancey dancey doofy doofy (lol).
What you can buy at Costco and who out of us is keen to go.
We get some more fascinating learnings from Gracie's hypnobirthing classes.
And couples who watch porn together.</description></item><item><title>Hymns, Adam Levine, baby names and rib boobs. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610062/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 07:57:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610062/</guid><description>Podcast Description BUSY MEETING TONIGHT!!
We learn all about the "hymns" Caitlin used to sing.
We dissect the Adam Levine cheating scandal.
Baby names and pregnancy models.
Rib boobs are cool.
Handmaid's Tale arguments.
And, we learn about "Floppy Face, Floppy Fanny".
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Grey hair, Cruise Ships and ballet flats. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610063/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 20:14:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610063/</guid><description>Podcast Description We talk about whether you have to "embrace" grey hair or not...
Would you go on a Cruise?
Ballet flats are apparently making a comeback, and none of us are here for it.
Gracie reports back from Sydney, Caitlin is about to graduate and Brodie is a day away from moving house so she's all go!
And a really tricky listener question about career vs love...
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Age gaps, gumboots and kiss emojis. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610064/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 04:20:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610064/</guid><description>Podcast Description We dissect the Don't Worry Darling drama because it's just SO GOOD!
Age gaps: Do they matter? Are they any of our business? What's the problem?
Plus there's some career chat, board meeting chat, relationship break up chat and Gracie is exploring hypnobirthing!
Plus, flirting co-workers and kiss emojis...
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sleepovers, Taco emojis and The Bog | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610065/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 08:16:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can you remember sleepovers as a kid? They're part of growing up right?
Corn boy, taco emojis and Britney Spears.
Voting in local Govt is sexy and important.
Boring adult shit.
Mixed veggies.
The Bog.
xx
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Brought to you by double standards. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610066/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 07:53:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610066/</guid><description>Podcast Description From Andrew Tate, to the Prime Minister of Finland, to Tommy Lee&amp;rsquo;s unsolicited dick pick&amp;hellip;gosh the theme really is double standards.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Sexual Wellbeing Class. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610067/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 04:27:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last year we spoke to the amazingly wonderful Beatrice Thorne, General Manager and part of the founding team at Eve. It was the talk about our bodies we’d never had, and we learnt so much and it turns out so did you - it was such a popular episode.Well B&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Greek Gods, knowing what cloths to use + Christmas Cake (yuck). | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610068/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 06:24:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610068/</guid><description>Podcast Description The band is back together baby!!! The gals have a glorious catch up about Brodie&amp;rsquo;s amazing trip to Europe with her Mum. Caitlin had a birthday and it hit her like a tonne of bricks at 1am in the bathroom of a bar in Wellington&amp;hellip; Gracie&amp;rsquo;s feeling fab, an&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Being a villain, the phonetic alphabet and weather with Renee Wright | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610069/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 04:09:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610069/</guid><description>Podcast Description We chat to NZ’s favourite weather woman, Renee Wright, about her career, motherhood to four gorgeous tamariki and why she’s always ‘cast as the villain’ – also we talk about her passion for pillows!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Babies, nipples and Harry Styles with guest host Megan Papas | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610070/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 04:27:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brodie&amp;rsquo;s swanning around in Croatia which we are not at all jealous about, so joining us this week is special guest Megan Papas. Following our big announcement (ahhhh!!!) there&amp;rsquo;s a LOT of baby talk in this episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A glorious chat with guest host Sharyn Casey | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610071/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 21:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brodie and Gracie are away this week, but we recorded a beautiful episode with the wonderful Sharyn Casey - and we fell in love with her a bit more (for the record the love was strong already but she&amp;rsquo;ll do that to you).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>G-bangers, punishing space chat, smears and boxing. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610072/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 08:08:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610072/</guid><description>Podcast Description We have the wonderful Tegan Yorwarth as a guest host this week! She&amp;rsquo;s about to get in the boxing ring at Fight for Life and we couldn&amp;rsquo;t be more proud. Tegan mucks in on all the events from the week, which includes quite possibly the most punishing chat y&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Vabbing, Kate Bush, Anusol and Coke Zero. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610073/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 00:23:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610073/</guid><description>Podcast Description We have the wonderful Grace Palmer as a guest host this week! The second season of her hilariously brilliant show, Good Grief is on TVNZ+ right now. There are a wide variety of topics today - from vabbing (WTF) to Minions, embarrassing Chemist exchanges &amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why Roe v Wade being overturned hurts. EVERYWHERE. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610074/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 08:40:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610074/</guid><description>Podcast Description We get pretty personal about the Roe v Wade overturning and why it is so important to stand up and speak out - even if we don&amp;rsquo;t live in America. This is a hugely distressing and extremely backward moment in history. It&amp;rsquo;s ok to feel upset, it&amp;rsquo;s ok to feel&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The fizz, Thirty AF, Moustaches. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610075/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 20:54:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610075/</guid><description>Podcast Description We talk V, Coke Zero and Booze. What absolute f*ckery shambles is the new TVNZ show FBoy Island? Barbie and Ken are coming and we&amp;rsquo;re not sure whether it&amp;rsquo;s for adults or kids and will Gosling and Robbie nail it? Gracie and Ali are finally going on their &amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Celebrating the wins, balancing the hustle and dirty flatmates. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610076/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 21:16:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610076/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;re back for a glorious catch up after a week apart! Brodie&amp;rsquo;s figuring out what life looks like after dancing. Caitlin&amp;rsquo;s working a million jobs and loving every minute. Gracie&amp;rsquo;s donned the boxing gloves and has found a new passion! We talk about the sh&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The dancing queen and THAT kiss... | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610077/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 08:47:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Well, Dancing With The Stars is over and our gal got second! UNREAL! There&amp;rsquo;s a big debrief and we get the answers about Enrique&amp;hellip; We are taking a break next week, but we can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see you in fortnight! LOVE YOU XXX
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Proud Mary, travel and the Fairlie Play! | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610078/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 07:21:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brodie&amp;rsquo;s gearing up for the Dancing With The Stars GRAND FINAL! Gracie&amp;rsquo;s excited about visiting her Grandpa in the States soon&amp;hellip; Caitlin is hitting Fairlie this weekend to watch her dad in a play! And yes, we do talk about Kourtney&amp;rsquo;s wedding and the fas&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Abortions, celebrity trials, Julia Fox and hoop earrings. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610079/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 20:25:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610079/</guid><description>Podcast Description We discuss the scary reality that women in the U.S. are facing right now over abortion laws. Why is the internet siding with Johnny Depp and destroying Amber Heard? Julia Fox wears her underwear at the supermarket and we&amp;rsquo;re not mad about it. Hoop earring&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Keeping up with the Tok, Crocs and Sprite burps. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610080/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 08:57:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610080/</guid><description>Podcast Description She&amp;rsquo;s a busy wee episode with the Dancing with the Stars film crew with us tonight! Brodie&amp;rsquo;s not only learning to dance, she&amp;rsquo;s learning the TikTok thanks to superstar new bestie Jazz Thornton. Gracie yet again tries to sell the Crocs (which, by the way, &amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tinglets, sausages in bread and the Met Gala. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610081/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 07:34:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610081/</guid><description>Podcast Description The weekly Dancing debrief! A dissection of the Met Gala. Man buns, thumb rings and chain necklaces. Those sausages wrapped in bread outside Bunnings. And more of course! X
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Spare lingerie in your handbag: Yay or nay? | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610082/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 09:07:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610082/</guid><description>Podcast Description We kick off with a big Dancing with the Stars debrief! Caitlin got her scooter stolen outside the hospital, but there&amp;rsquo;s been a silver lining&amp;hellip; We have a good vent about Elon Musk. Gracie has some EPIC life advice. And do you put spare undies in your han&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Harry, flap accidents and Lynx Africa. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610083/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 10:52:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brodie is writing this blurb at 10.54pm and really should be in bed. So, as always, it&amp;rsquo;s a $1 mixture of randomness in which we hope you enjoy (ie that&amp;rsquo;s all my dancing brain can cope with at this time). Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to vote and watch Dancing with the St&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The hot guy at high school + what not to stick in your ears... | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610084/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 04:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brodie&amp;rsquo;s discovered Jack Harlow&amp;hellip; Remember the boys at high school with the satin boxers and low-rise pants? Got us thinking about our high school crushes! Our expert nurse Caitlin has some sound advice about what NOT to stick in your ears. Gracie tells&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dancing, sex scenes and road cones. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610085/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Caitlin and Gracie ask Brodie a million questions about being on Dancing with the Stars because EXCITING!!! We talk unsolicited dick pics and how unacceptable they are. Are there more road cones in New Zealand than people? Is New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve overrated, pe&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Eyebrows, pen-is pals and I’m fiiiiiiiine! | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610086/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 08:02:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610086/</guid><description>Podcast Description She&amp;rsquo;s an absolute monster of an episode because there&amp;rsquo;s so much to talk about! From the Oscars slap, to Harry Styles, to thin eyebrows, to pyjamas etiquette, to being friend-zoned, to borrowing wedding dresses, to intact boxes, to Caitlin crying. It&amp;rsquo;s AL&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Caitlin’s epiphany, Craigy D’s and fights. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610087/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 07:47:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Caitlin reveals where her nickname came from and it&amp;rsquo;s ridiculously brilliant. She also gives her expertise in sports and MAFS and we are here for it. Gracie and Brodie send a DM to the actual Craig David. If you know what a Craigy D is you&amp;rsquo;ll understand!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Brodie tried a new thing, adult Wiggles and the road code. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610088/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 07:35:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who bloody knew The Wiggles were doing adult shows? And what exactly does that mean? Turns out Caitlin is not only a healthcare professional but reckons she knows the road code like the back of her hand (lol). Brodie tried out a new thing&amp;hellip; Gracie&amp;rsquo;s got&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Foot fetishes, cassette tapes and Irish Moss Jubes. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610089/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 20:17:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610089/</guid><description>Podcast Description The nostalgia of taping the &amp;ldquo;Hot 9 at 9&amp;rdquo; radio show on your cassette tape&amp;hellip; What does your taste in lollies say about you? Brodie tries to over-pronounce Balenciaga and will possibly never live it down. Have you ever been with someone with a foot fetish&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Brodie joins the Army! | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610090/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 07:15:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610090/</guid><description>Podcast Description There&amp;rsquo;s a lot to discuss in this podcast (starting with the behaviour of those in Wellington), but we really sit down and have a good yarn about Brodie joining the army as a teenager, a real deep dive into the archives - including how she shat her pants &amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Gorgeous gorgeous girls, Uncut Gems and night shifts. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610091/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 06:19:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610091/</guid><description>Podcast Description A good little catch up as we navigate our way through the Omicron outbreak (hope you&amp;rsquo;re all doing ok!). Caitlin is starting night shifts so is in full blown nurse mode. She also had a spray tan and left half of it on the dentist&amp;rsquo;s chair&amp;hellip; Brodie is maki&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tinder sperm donors and outstanding ex revenge stories! | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610092/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 06:39:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Superbowl and Kanye are at the top of the list. Then, would you accept a sperm donor off Tinder? We have some outstanding ex revenge stories. Caitlin is getting ready for her first NURSING SHIFT!! Brodie is trying to traverse the Coast still whilst packi&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tinder disasters, horny emojis and PDA. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610093/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 06:36:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Off the back of the new Netflix doco, The Tinder Swindler, we discuss some experiences women here in New Zealand have had - gosh there are some real dicks out there! Do we all interpret emojis differently? Because apparently the Gen Zers are using one of&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Gracie’s in Vogue, Caitlin’s going on a hike-date, Brodie’s getting rained on. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610094/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 06:33:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610094/</guid><description>Podcast Description GRACIE IS IN BRITISH VOGUE AND WE ARE SO EXCITED (absolutely deserves caps lock haha)!! Caitlin thinks it&amp;rsquo;s a good idea to climb a very steep hill on her third date&amp;hellip; It looks as though Omicron AND now the weather gods have other ideas for Brodie in her&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Life in red, green M&amp;Ms and oh to be 20 again (unless you’re Caitlin who’s THRIVING). | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610095/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 06:53:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610095/</guid><description>Podcast Description A little hui and some thoughts and feelings on the changes made as we stare down the barrel of an Omicron outbreak. We try get through that without being toooooo depressing though and move on to the Green M&amp;amp;M scandal and then onto weird food combos. The&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Once you pop you can’t stop... | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610096/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 19:41:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610096/</guid><description>Podcast Description The girls get all deep (bahahaha) and discuss star signs - are you into them? Gracie and Brodie remember some interesting books they had at high school and no they weren&amp;rsquo;t your standard 1B5. Caitlin has had a bit on, so brace yourselves&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A bucket hat pash, sea lice and no one cares. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610097/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 06:56:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Heyyyyyyyyyyyy!!!! Happy New Year etc etc etc. 2022 is the year that, at the start of the episode we said &amp;ldquo;hey let’s not too much pressure on it and just see what happens&amp;rdquo;. Then at the end we said: &amp;ldquo;just go straight to the top&amp;rdquo;. And we stand by both. All&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>LIVE LAUGH LOVE UNTIL NEXT YEAR! | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 04:12:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610098/</guid><description>Podcast Description She&amp;rsquo;s a super long one so you can split it over the next couple of weeks haha! Just really a big debrief about what has happened this year for all of us, and what we&amp;rsquo;re thinking about for next year. Some great listener questions and thoughts too. Thank y&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Santa sacks, chin hairs and nudes. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610099/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 00:32:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Second-to-last episode of the year! Caitlin reveals she still gets a Santa Sack on Christmas Day&amp;hellip; Gracie is ready for freeeeeedoooommmmm! Brodie doesn&amp;rsquo;t know how to send nudes. Also: chin hairs, airfryers and the Sex and The City flop.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Gracie‘s 30, Brodie‘s thirsty, Caitlin‘s bored. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610100/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 05:48:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gracie&amp;rsquo;s still recovering from the weekend which we are absolutely here for - it&amp;rsquo;s not everyday you turn 30! Bit of pop culture squeezed in there (Love Island, Kardashians, Selling Sunset). Some sports bra chat. Brodie&amp;rsquo;s been on more adventures but none &amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We dive into a man‘s brain... | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610101/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610101/</guid><description>Podcast Description We have the wonderful Case Kenny with us this week - all the way from Chicago. Case is a successful podcaster, with New Mindset, Who Dis? He also has a very popular series of mindfulness journals so we thought it best to absolutely interrogate him. We ha&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The end of 2021 Survival Guide with Jacqui Maguire | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610102/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610102/</guid><description>Podcast Description We thought it would be the perfect time to do an extra special bonus episode with our wonderful friend of the show and superstar clinical psychologist Jacqui Maguire. In this episode: How to deal with Christmas and awkward family situations. Conversation&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Balls, bras, love bites and goon bags. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610103/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 06:09:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Every time we think we won&amp;rsquo;t go long and talk for ages&amp;hellip;we go long and talk for ages! Pete Davidson and THAT Kim K hickey&amp;hellip; Adele can do no wrong. All three gals have great famous people interviews to share as we delve into the archives! Turns out you &amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nurse Caitlin, Gracie‘s UberEats and shop rats. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610104/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 20:31:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Caitlin is dusty AF because she just finished her LAST exam before she becomes a nurse and that calls for celebration! You may hear her brain buffering from time to time&amp;hellip;ha! Gracie ordered quite possibly the weirdest thing on UberEats ever. We do a dee&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>I‘m just a teenage dirtbag baby. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610105/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 06:47:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610105/</guid><description>Podcast Description We dissect the week that was pets in exchange for trees on Instagram. Brodie unleashes her teenage bogan. Caitlin is RIDICULOUSLY close to becoming a nurse. Gracie has the best advice for an email signature. Plus all the bits and bobs in between!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>First crushes, Pete Davidson and Moisturiser | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610106/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 06:54:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610106/</guid><description>Podcast Description I tell you what, delving into the archives is the gift that keeps on giving. The girls try remember their very first crushes and no Brodie&amp;rsquo;s is NOT her cousin. Why do we always blame the chick when the guy is being the dick (quite literally, it&amp;rsquo;s over a &amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What‘s the right first question when you match on Bumble? | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610107/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 05:45:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you know how traffic lights work (not Covid ones, actual ones)? We delve into our Halloween archives&amp;hellip; We debate what on earth you should say as your first yarn when you match with someone. What happens when you love your boyfriend but are attracted &amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Julie Watson - understanding our LGBTTQIA+ community | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610108/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 06:23:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610108/</guid><description>Podcast Description We have an amazing guest to chat to this week - Julie Watson is a Rainbow Tick programme manager and has worked extensively in supporting and advocating in the LGBTTQIA+ area over the past two decades through the Human Rights Commission and more latterly&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We delve into the archives and it‘s a TIME! | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610109/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 05:41:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610109/</guid><description>Podcast Description We go a whole episode without talking about COVID (well, almost but we did bloody well)!!! Caitlin learns for the first time where Travis Barker comes from. And, we decide to bring in &amp;ldquo;delve into the archives&amp;rdquo; where we share tales from back in the day wh&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What is a ”that girl” and why are we old? | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610110/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 06:28:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tonight is a very busy show in which we believe we may contradict ourselves on more than one occasion. You can probably guess why. We talk about bodies, and then tell you not to worry about bodies but then talk some more about bodies and then tell you it&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Not all men...yeah we know. But we are angry because too many men do. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610111/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 05:51:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610111/</guid><description>Podcast Description We won&amp;rsquo;t lie&amp;hellip;the first part of this episode is pretty heavy and deals with sexual assault, violence and murder. Of women, by men. It is sad, we are angry, we are hurt, we need to keep talking and NOT stop. Yeah yeah yeah we know &amp;ldquo;not all men&amp;rdquo; rape and &amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is masculine and feminine energy a load of shite? | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610112/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 21:02:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610112/</guid><description>Podcast Description We look into masculine and feminine energy and whether it&amp;rsquo;s all a load of words made up to make you have think to be one or the other. Is there such a thing as harmless flirting? We think so. What pizza topping are you? Caitlin thinks Brodie&amp;rsquo;s a chicken/&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What‘s a spray skirt? | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610113/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 07:52:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Imagine eating a 50 cent mixture of lollies, some are glorious, some are sour AF, some get stuck in your teeth. Well yeah, this episode is the podcast version of that 50 cent mixture (ok so not super sour but you catch our drift haha). And yes, two out o&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>This is the talk about our bodies we NEVER got! | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610114/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 07:57:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our minds are absolutely blown after this! Honestly, this is that class at school we NEVER had. It&amp;rsquo;s proudly brought to you by Eve Wellness - the New Zealand health brand on a mission to end the stigma and misinformation surrounding cycles, hormones, men&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Strippers, Mullets and Alpha Chicks | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610115/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 10:03:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610115/</guid><description>Podcast Description You are in great hands tonight, between The Girls Uninterrupted and the wonderful Jules and Jodes from Good Bitch Podcast we have pretty much solved all of the problems! From sex acts on strippers to whether you think a mullet is sexy, we leave no stone &amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rooting neighbours, colouring-in books and wearing Crocs. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610116/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 06:47:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Another week in lockdown, meaning we have a bit of time on our hands for all the yarns. Lockdown life continues&amp;hellip;which includes eating, sometimes showering and watching all of the shows. We have a super tricky rooting neighbour dilemma. Caitlin&amp;rsquo;s about &amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Wear ya trackies, use the SP2, eat the bread. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610117/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 06:47:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610117/</guid><description>Podcast Description New Zealand is in its second week of our second major nationwide lockdown, so we&amp;rsquo;re just here to talk shit, have a laugh, a little cry, talk shit, etc etc. Love you all, stay safe, stay home, save lives! And don&amp;rsquo;t forget to: GET OUTSIDE AND SPREAD YOUR L&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Back in lockdown, talking about booze, and are you fried or steamed? | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610118/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 07:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610118/</guid><description>Podcast Description New Zealand is back in a Level 4 Lockdown with community transmission detected with the Delta strain. We are with you in these scary times! Brodie&amp;rsquo;s on TikTok after caving in (we knew that would happen). We discuss a really brave listener question about &amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Comfort undies are sexy, putting yourself out there is sexy, we‘re all sexy! | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610119/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 08:01:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gosh she&amp;rsquo;s a another full agenda! Climate Change, Olympic withdrawals and unpacking male and female behaviour on Love Island. Comfort undies are sexy! Putting yourself out there (we&amp;rsquo;re all inspired after last week) is sexy too! Looking after your health &amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The woman who went on a date a week every year til she found love (spoiler: 138 dates!). | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610120/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 07:24:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rebekah Campbell shares such a beautiful story about how she decided at a certain point in her life - amidst the success and bright lights of her career - that there was in fact something missing. She was determined to find love, so decided to go on one &amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The barren wasteland of single men. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610121/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 07:36:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Frothing about JLo and Ben. Not so frothing about the barren wasteland of single men. Some gorgeous relationship tips from our Gracie. And all the bits and bobs in between!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rochelle and Philly from R&amp;P Insurance! | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610122/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 20:31:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610122/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week is proudly brought to you by R&amp;amp;P Insurance - this is a Wāhine run brand run by 2 ex-corporate gals, Rochelle Carly and Philly McMeekan, who are just incredible women to speak to! They really do have a passion for people and insurance is the bi-&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Billionaires, the big move and getting your tits out. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610123/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 08:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610123/</guid><description>Podcast Description She&amp;rsquo;s a long one again&amp;hellip;look when we&amp;rsquo;re on a roll there&amp;rsquo;s no stopping us (and you tell us you love it so we do it haha)! A little rant about billionaires, and dick-swinging into space. Brodie has some big news. Gracie&amp;rsquo;s got the Love Island script memori&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>If last week was motivation, this week is not. It's winter, it's trashy TV, it's soup. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610124/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 08:12:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Look, we are deep in the bowels of winter, so it&amp;rsquo;s understandable if everyone is a bit MEH. We say that, because that&amp;rsquo;s exactly where we are, so if you&amp;rsquo;re in the zone for some sort of uplifting hour then I&amp;rsquo;m sorry we&amp;rsquo;re not that this week (lol). But, in &amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cassie Roma answers all your career questions and she is a GODDESS! | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610125/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 08:02:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610125/</guid><description>Podcast Description So many of you have been writing in recently with amazing career questions. And we all have points in our lives where we don&amp;rsquo;t know what we&amp;rsquo;re doing, don&amp;rsquo;t know what to do next, don&amp;rsquo;t know how to leave a job, and are worried about what other people and &amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Fearless Podcast - Melodie Robinson | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610126/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 19:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kia ora and welcome to The Fearless Podcast Series powered by Puma. It gives me great pleasure to introduce you to today’s guest, Melodie Robinson - sports journalist and presenter, and a World Cup winning Black Fern. Mel has played a big role in paving&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ear wax, broken knees and one-night stand etiquette. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610127/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 08:04:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610127/</guid><description>Podcast Description We bring you the new Covid slogan thanks to Jo Kane (aka Brodie&amp;rsquo;s Mum) which is: &amp;ldquo;be nice, be kind, and if you can&amp;rsquo;t, fuck off.&amp;rdquo; We discuss Laurel Hubbard&amp;rsquo;s selection in the women&amp;rsquo;s weightlifting team for New Zealand at the Tokyo Olympics. Gracie dabbles&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Fearless Podcast - Dame Susan Devoy | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610128/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kia ora and welcome to The Fearless Podcast Series powered by Puma. It gives me great pleasure to introduce you to today’s guest, Dame Susan Devoy - New Zealand’s greatest ever Squash player. The four-time World Open and eight-time British Open Champion&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is it rage season?? | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610129/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 09:02:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610129/</guid><description>Podcast Description There is a whole lot of raging happening in this week&amp;rsquo;s episode&amp;hellip; Some of it we&amp;rsquo;re blaming on the weather, some of it we&amp;rsquo;re blaming on the government, some of it we&amp;rsquo;re blaming on ourselves. So, if you&amp;rsquo;re feeling a bit ragey at the moment, don&amp;rsquo;t worry, &amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Fearless Podcast - Karin Burger, Sam Winders, Kimiora Poi | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610130/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 20:27:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kia ora and welcome to The Fearless Podcast Series powered by Puma. It gives me great pleasure to introduce you to today’s guests, three of our very talented netballers, Karin Burger - Silver Fern number 171, Sam Winders - Silver Fern number 165 and Kimi&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Girls Uninterrupted talk to SHIT YOU SHOULD CARE ABOUT! | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610131/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 05:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we have two amazing young women joining us on the show. Liv and Lucy are two of the three founders of SHIT YOU SHOULD CARE ABOUT. It&amp;rsquo;s amazing to think this Instagram page was born via a text message in a lecture hall at Victoria University in Wel&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Fearless Podcast - Katie Bowen and Rosie White | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610132/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kia ora and welcome to The Fearless Podcast Series powered by Puma. It gives me great pleasure to introduce you to today’s guests, two major players and stars of New Zealand Football, Katie Bowen and Rosie White. Katie is coming to us from Kansas City -&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bridesmaid proposals, owning your flaws and looking back at our fasshuuunnns. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610133/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 09:01:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Warning: Brodie f*%ks up the intro but decided to leave it in there. My my my have we got 17,000 topics crammed into today&amp;rsquo;s episode for you! Bridesmaid proposals: Yay or Nay? Naomi Osaka is a human being BEFORE tennis star and we need to remind ourselve&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Fearless Podcast - Louisa Wall | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610134/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kia ora and welcome to The Fearless Podcast Series powered by Puma. It gives me great pleasure to introduce you to today’s guest, former Silver Fern and Black Fern Louisa Wall - Ngāti Tūwharetoa, Ngāti Hineuru, Waikato and Ngāti Kuri. Louisa is a current&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A blood supermoon, threesomes/thruples and Pronouns. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610135/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 08:43:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gosh we talked for AGES tonight! First of all, thank you so very much for all your support this past year (since we took ownership of the podcast and re-launched). We have hit over 500,000 downloads so we are pretty bloody stoked, and just want to say we&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Fearless Podcast - Dame Noeline Taurua | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610136/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 20:33:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kia ora and welcome to The Fearless Podcast Series powered by Puma. It gives me great pleasure to introduce you to today’s guest, the Silver Ferns Coach Dame Noeline Taurua. An absolute legend of a player herself, Dame Noeline has been a phenomenal forc&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Caitlin ate chicken, Brodie ran a marathon and Gracie told us we are no longer cool. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610137/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 08:13:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lots to catch up on this week! Caitlin ate chicken and we told her that was ok. Brodie ran a marathon and it was hard but she is also ok. Gracie taught us about cheugy and we are absolutely not ok about that and will NOT be adding it to our vocabulary. P&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr Morgan Edwards | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610138/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 21:06:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610138/</guid><description>Podcast Description From looking after your vagina to the COVID vaccine, the wonderful Dr Morgan Edwards has a yarn about all of the health things!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Arseholes, Flannelette Sheets, Bill Gates is single. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610139/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 07:30:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lots in the minutes this week! Our typical punishing weather chat is in there, plus knowing what your arsehole looks like (actual). On a more serious note, we talk about feelings we have when we&amp;rsquo;re not sure whether we&amp;rsquo;ll have a family or not. Bill Gates&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Adult Tracksuits. He's probably not going to call. Oh yeah, and foreplay RULES. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610140/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 07:43:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610140/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is like one of those ones when you haven&amp;rsquo;t caught up in a while, you&amp;rsquo;ve all got a lot to say, and shit gets busy and exciting! From tracksuits to high waisted jeans to what you put in your burgers, to Zac Efron&amp;rsquo;s face, to taking control in t&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nice guy chats, "The Caitlin" has success, and a little talk about Imposter Syndrome. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610141/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 20:35:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Caitlin shares a yarn about the good guys! We hear a success story about trialing out &amp;ldquo;The Caitlin&amp;rdquo; hehe! Brodie discusses self-doubt and Imposter Syndrome. And, how do you get a yourself a squad? Have a great weekend everyone! X
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Inspired Unemployed | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610142/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:27:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we have a very special episode with two lads we know have put smiles on millions of people&amp;rsquo;s faces. Matt Ford and Jack Steele are two tradies from the south coast of New South Wales, Australia, who many will know as The Inspired Unemployed. They ar&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>This is a really great episode, but YOU WAIT TIL YOU HEAR WHO IS ON NEXT WEEK... | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610143/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 07:46:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610143/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are very stoked to hear about the new trans-Tasman travel bubble. We urge you to please please please keep on top of your cervical screening. We are furious about Bridgerton. We have our all important/helpful/useless advice. AND HOLY SHITBALLS NEXT WE&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Stuck boats, knowing your brought from your bought and finding the perfect kiss... | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610144/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 07:16:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610144/</guid><description>Podcast Description There&amp;rsquo;s actually about a million topics in this episode so strap yourselves in and get amongst and for the love of Elvis have a safe and happy Easter! xxx
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Gracie is back so WEDDING. Women's rights because WOMEN. And housing because ADULTS. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610145/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 07:10:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610145/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a jam-packed episode in which we go through every detail about Gracie&amp;rsquo;s stunning wedding! We also discuss the new housing changes the Government has just announced (very adulting, we know). And TRIGGER WARNING: We do go into a serious discussion &amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Olympic BMX Legend Sarah Walker | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610146/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kiwi BMX Racer Sarah Walker joins us for a special episode today, in celebration of Women’s Empowerment Month, a campaign brought to you by Me Today and Women’s Refuge. Sarah talks to us about the challenges of being a professional sportsperson - she&amp;rsquo;s s&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Gracie's Wedding, Harry + Meghan, Yoga and Gen Zers. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610147/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 19:45:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Busy show as we build up to Gracie&amp;rsquo;s wedding this weekend! We also discuss THAT interview - you know the one where Harry and Meghan lift the lid with Oprah on why they left the Royal Family. Brodie&amp;rsquo;s started yoga finally. Millennials v Gen Zers - apparen&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Today went really hard on career and life advice... | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610148/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 07:41:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Look, we know it&amp;rsquo;s a weird, confusing and somewhat unsettling time, so we are just trying to navigate through as much as you are! We want you to know it&amp;rsquo;s ok to feel a bit all over the place, and we hope that this episode makes you feel like we are right&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>That hot videographer, feeling frazzled and taking a stand. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610149/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 07:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lots to discuss this week, as Caitlin shares the all important lesson of remembering to turn your microphone off when talking about someone (aka: a hot videographer). We talk about the Covid Vaccine and why it&amp;rsquo;s so important. How to tackle uncomfortable &amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Covid, Carrots and Strip Clubs. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610150/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 07:30:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610150/</guid><description>Podcast Description We discuss the fact that Auckland, NZ is in the middle of a three day lockdown as we record this, but we also want to give you some things to smile about too. So there&amp;rsquo;s the results of Caitlin&amp;rsquo;s speed-dating escapades, Gracie&amp;rsquo;s super romantic first time,&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Blocked pipes, speed-dating and some useless tips on how to live your life. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610151/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 05:03:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, Brodie prepares Caitlin for her big night of speed-dating ahead of cringe Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day. We open up the floor for questions, in an attempt to give some lovely listeners a nice long episode so they can enjoy it on their long runs!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>0900 voices, what does shit game even mean and knowing your mussel from your oyster | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610152/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 19:22:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brodie teaches the girls about the phone sex age and also stitches her mother up with fake love news, Gracie is a rare bride who&amp;rsquo;s not fussed about people having their phones out on her wedding day and Caitlin doesn&amp;rsquo;t know her mussel from her oyster.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cleaning your fanny, some serious stuff, and what meal is your ideal man? | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610153/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 07:00:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610153/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brodie&amp;rsquo;s in her underpants, Caitlin&amp;rsquo;s complaining that Brodie won&amp;rsquo;t turn her aircon on as it&amp;rsquo;s 36 degrees in Christchurch, and Gracie has created an epic new game where you figure out what meal best represents the man you want. Just your standard Wednesd&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Make your money work for you in 2021 | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610154/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 20:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610154/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week&amp;rsquo;s episode is brought to you by Hatch, and we speak to its co-founder Kristen Lunman. Hatch is a Kiwi company wanting to give fellow Kiwis straightforward and affordable access to the US share markets. Kristen breaks down a lot of the stereotype&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>New Year, Same Us! | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610155/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2021 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gosh, where do we start. Gracie&amp;rsquo;s eating crab nuggets and Brodie got Subway delivered from 50m up the road. How&amp;rsquo;s your 2021 going? Also Bridgerton.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>See you in 2021! | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610156/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610156/</guid><description>Podcast Description 2020, did that just happen? It&amp;rsquo;s our last episode of the year and we just want to thank you all for coming along on this ride. Stay safe and don&amp;rsquo;t put up with creeps xx This episode is brought to you by Bondi Sands. Be confidently protected ever day with&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Creeps, Christmas parties and texts you don't want. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610157/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 00:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610157/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the second to the last show of the year, Brodie and Caitlin crawl through an episode, just like how we are all crawling to the end of the year. This episode is brought to you by Bondi Sands. Be confidently protected every day with suncare, the Bondi S&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nipples, New Year's Eve and Nigel No Mates | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610158/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 06:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610158/</guid><description>Podcast Description We discuss women&amp;rsquo;s boobs vs men&amp;rsquo;s boobs, Caitlin talks pre-party anxiety, Gracie&amp;rsquo;s getting her head around some massive life events welcoming her into 2021 - and how are you saying goodbye to 2020? One of us is dancing her arse off, the other is celebrat&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hammers under pillows and hungry fannies | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610159/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 20:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610159/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s December, so Christmas f**kery has begun, Caitlin&amp;rsquo;s overthinking again, Brodie&amp;rsquo;s got a hammer under her pillow, Gracie&amp;rsquo;s budgeting tip for Christmas and do you have a hungry fanny? This episode is brought to you by Bondi Sands. Be confidently protec&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Eve Palmer! | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610160/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 04:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610160/</guid><description>Podcast Description She&amp;rsquo;s talented, she&amp;rsquo;s funny and she&amp;rsquo;s bloody gorgeous inside and out. Eve Palmer is our guest host this week and we talk marathons, breakdowns and babies&amp;hellip; yes there&amp;rsquo;s a BIG announcement!!This episode is brought to you by Bondi Sands. Be confidently pro&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>New sex toys... with a side of wholesome | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610161/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 08:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610161/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Gracie thinks that this Christmas we should replace chocolate with sex toys in the advent calendar (R16). Plus the girls just have a really nice round up of where our lives are as we approach the end of a pretty whack year.This episode is broug&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Presidents, summer bods and tea bags. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610162/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 06:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610162/</guid><description>Podcast Description The girls discuss the US presidential elections, we point the middle finger at &amp;ldquo;summer bods&amp;rdquo; and how do you tea bag? This episode was proudly brought to you by EFFEN vodka. Available at all good liquor stores for those over 18. How EFFEN good.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tricky bosses, wedding drama and YAY to our diverse parliament! | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610163/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Wednesday! Today, the girls have a light discussion on American politics, there&amp;rsquo;s been a set back in the wedding plans and a listener question about tricky relationships with bosses. This episode was proudly brought to you by EFFEN vodka. Available&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Non-mum shaming, cheating and board games. Plus: sex toys, buttholes and bathtubs. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610164/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 06:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610164/</guid><description>Podcast Description The title says it all really.Love you byyeee
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trigger Warning: A Discussion Around Sexual Abuse | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610165/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 19:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610165/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today&amp;rsquo;s episode, the girls discuss sexual abuse after recent allegations that have been made against a group of Wellington musicians. We also talk nipples and Instagram double standards, and not feeling pressured this silly season. Where you can get h&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Voting, Marriage and Blow Jobs. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610166/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 05:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610166/</guid><description>Podcast Description A last minute reminder to exercise your right to vote! Who pays for weddings? And, Caitlin introduces us to “The Caitlin”.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Raw Sisters | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610167/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 23:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rosa and Margo Flanagan are two bright, bubbly sisters who, at just 24 and 22 are playing an awesome part in the plant-based food movement. They&amp;rsquo;re just about to release their second cookbook, All Eaters Welcome, which, having had a squizz at, is absolut&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Somatic Sexologist Morgan Penn | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610168/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sex.. and other things! Actually, it&amp;rsquo;s mainly just sex.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Great Period of 2020 | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610169/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 20:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610169/</guid><description>Podcast Description No moon cup or period undies were to save Brodie in the great period of 2020. Caitlin and Brodie tell Gracie about their wedding plans. Yes you read that right
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kim Crossman for Mental Health Awareness Week | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610170/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610170/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s Mental Health Awareness Week in New Zealand and we speak to the wonderful Kim Crossman about her journey with depression. Warning: we will be discussing issues around mental health including suicide. Need to talk? Free call or text 1737 any time for&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Caroline Holloway from The Cosmetic Clinic | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610171/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 08:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610171/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Caroline from The Cosmetic Clinic answers our 50 thousand questions on injectables and debunks the stigma around botox and fillers.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Politics... and the Kardashians. What a combo. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610172/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 10:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610172/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s late and not everything makes sense, but neither does the world right now. Somewhere in here we talk politics, the Kardashians and Caitlin dabbles in the art of mentoring. You&amp;rsquo;re in for a treat.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hilary Souter on Influencer Marketing | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610173/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 08:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610173/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week the Advertising Standards Authority released some hard and fast rules around influencer marketing. Social Media has become such a grey area and the ASA has set out the guidelines in black and white. We were joined by the chief executive of the &amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>There's a lot to talk about right now. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610174/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 08:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610174/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today is one of those days where we just have to talk about everything. We thank you for your questions, and thank you for listening. X
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hannah Barrett | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610175/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610175/</guid><description>Podcast Description The girls caught up with the absolutely delightful Hannah Barrett to talk about motherhood, being a wag, &amp;ldquo;wet ass pussys&amp;rdquo; and the cutest first date story.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sunday sessions, new passions and tonight is the night! | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610176/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 06:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610176/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;ve all been there - a Monday hangover to really make you feel alive. Brodie was kind enough to experience a top five to give you advice on how to deal. Gracie may&amp;rsquo;ve found a new passion and we are absolutely here for it. Caitlin has the biggest pimple&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The strength of the Sisterhood, new business ventures and for the love of Elvis, merge like a zip | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610177/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 10:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610177/</guid><description>Podcast Description The girls are still buzzing over the first leg of the podcast tour and how special it was to be around amazing women. Brodie talks about her new business venture + it wouldn’t be a podcast without random topics like the benefits of merging like a zip.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Phoebe Parson’s from Confessions of A Train Wreck | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610178/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 02:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610178/</guid><description>Podcast Description We chat to the wonderful Phoebe Parsons about turning 30, haemorrhoids and crop tops. But on a serious note, we also talk about mental health, anxiety and eating disorders.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Overpriced courgettes (in more ways then one) | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610179/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 08:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you seen the price of bloody courgettes? Anyway, onto much more important issues such as FWB&amp;rsquo;s, family holidays, productivity, anti&amp;ndash;abortionists and loving someone that doesn&amp;rsquo;t love you back.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Special guest host - PJ Harding! | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610180/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 05:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Melbourne lockdown, long distance relationships, living with OCD, Yoni Wands sexual empowerment and needing to poo after a ONS
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The future of influencer marketing | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610181/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610181/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the wake of the Advertising Standards Authority ruling against Simone Anderson, the girls discuss the future of influencer marketing and what needs to change. Then we talk smears, getting out of a Winter funk and the benefits of a squad outing!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What potato chip are you? | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610182/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 08:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610182/</guid><description>Podcast Description Potato chips, careers, abortions, dildos and Dr. Ashley Bloomfield. Strap yourself in, she’s hectic.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A big proposal, someone's horny and trance music. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610183/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 22:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610183/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s been a hot minute since the girls had a bloody good catch up, so you can imagine there was a bit on. Gracie&amp;rsquo;s planning her wedding, Caitlin feels old and Brodie is getting back on the horse, well trying to&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Stacey and Scotty Morrison - racism, history, learning, understanding, changing. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610184/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 01:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610184/</guid><description>Podcast Description The death of George Floyd has galvanised a movement all around the world - it has stepped up the fight for Black Lives Matter. We speak to Scotty and Stacey Morrison about this moment in history. But also, and importantly, what is going on in our own bac&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kiwi Model Maia Cotton | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610185/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 00:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610185/</guid><description>Podcast Description From Palmy all the way to New York, we talk to Kiwi model Maia Cotton about working in an industry where your success is based on your looks. She discusses the negative impacts this has had on her about how she has learnt to overcome them.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Spoiler Alert: NOTHING HAPPENS! | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610186/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 06:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610186/</guid><description>Podcast Description Life with a little bit more freedom, the great debate raging over Normal People and cheating husbands.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Look. Each to their own. | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610187/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 22:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610187/</guid><description>Podcast Description The girls chat about NZ being in level 2 of COVID19, reality TV shows, under boob and being a virgin in your 20&amp;rsquo;s.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Undies, legs and boys with Jess Quinn | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610188/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 05:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610188/</guid><description>Podcast Description We catch up with Jess Quinn on being in her undies, her refreshing take on body positivity that we all need to hear and having a pain in the arse of a leg.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Money money money with Hannah McQueen | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610189/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 05:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610189/</guid><description>Podcast Description The girls catch up with financial advisor Hannah McQueen from EnableMe NZ and answer your questions on saving, budgeting, homeownership and getting through these mad times
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Owning Your Lows, Burger Rings Jizz &amp; Beatboxing | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610190/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 04:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610190/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s Monday and we&amp;rsquo;ve lost the plot.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Woman in Business - Julia Matthews | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610191/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 06:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610191/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two Islands founder, Julia Matthews talks about starting her own business and shares some insight in to what has been the key to success for her. Seven months pregnant, Julia talks about becoming a mum for the first time. She also tells the girls about h&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Friday Drinks Round 2 | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610192/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 06:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610192/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dresses on, lippy on, chat is ON. Oh yeah, and chat includes butt chat!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Do you and be you, for you - with Hannah Romano | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610193/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 04:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610193/</guid><description>Podcast Description The girls speak to the wonderful Hannah Romano about how she is making a difference within the fitness industry and her no-bullshit approach to life. Hannah also talks openly about the devastation of losing a child and how she got through.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Friday Drinks | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610194/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 08:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610194/</guid><description>Podcast Description So the girls got dolled up, had some drinks and chatted to you like you are in our bubble x
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Virtual Hug With Clinical Psychologist - Jacqui Maguire | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610195/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 06:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610195/</guid><description>Podcast Description The girls put some of your questions and concerns to Clinical Psychologist Jacqui Maguire in this unusual time.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Easter Yarns | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610196/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 22:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610196/</guid><description>Podcast Description Easter is a time for chocolate and shit chats. Here at The Girls Uninterrupted we provide the shit chats. You&amp;rsquo;ll have to BYO choclate.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Steph Claire Smith and Laura Henshaw | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610197/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 23:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610197/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are joined by the incredible Keep It Cleaner founders to talk fitness, business, love, friendship, gratitude and so much more. Good god these two are wise!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How We Get By In Lockdown | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610198/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 06:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610198/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to The Girls Uninterrupted, formly Girls On Top. Brodie, Caitlin and Gracie are in week two of COVID-19 lockdown in New Zealand and are getting by with cooking, exercise and chatting up the annoymous man living upstairs.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Girls Uninterrupted - Trailer | The Girls Uninterrupted</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9150610199/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 01:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9150610199/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;re baaaaaaaack! The Girls Uninterrupted (formerly Girls on Top) have had a bit of a makeover but we&amp;rsquo;re ready to come and sit with you in your living room and have a glorious catch up like besties do!
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>