<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Crime story - CBC on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/crime-story-cbc/</link><description>Recent content in Crime story - CBC on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:10:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/crime-story-cbc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Alligator Candy: Every Parent’s Nightmare | Crime Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1776060012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1776060012/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1973, Jon Kushner set off on his bicycle with plans to pick up candy for his little brother, David. But when he didn’t return home, Jon’s parents panicked. A week later, he was discovered in a shallow grave. He was just 11 years old.
Jon’s little brother, David Kushner, is now a journalist who has written for publications like Rolling Stone, The New Yorker and Vanity Fair. In 2016, he turned the pen on himself and released Alligator Candy, a moving memoir and podcast, about his brother’s murder and how his family coped in the aftermath.</description></item><item><title>Devil in the Ditch: A Southern Murder Mystery | Crime Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1776060001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 00:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1776060001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Larrison Campbell had just started a new job in New York City when her father called with terrible news. Her beloved grandmother, Presh, had been murdered in their hometown of Greenville, Mississippi. The news inspired endless theories and suspicions. In her podcast, Devil in the Ditch, Campbell returns to Greenville to reopen the case and explore what happens when a murder goes unsolved.
For early access to Crime Story episodes and to listen ad-free, subscribe to CBC&amp;rsquo;s True Crime channel on our show page in Apple Podcasts.</description></item><item><title>Madness of Two: Aliens and the Apocalypse | Crime Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1776060002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 00:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1776060002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chad and Lori looked like the picture of newlywed happiness when they landed in Hawaii. But what they didn’t share was that they were fugitives, on the run from a spree of murders that included Lori’s own children. In this episode, we explore how a perfect soccer mom became a convicted murderer. It’s a tale of religious fanaticism, brainwashing and straight up greed – reported by journalist Sarah Treleavan.</description></item><item><title>Unabomber: Beyond the Myth | Crime Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1776060003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 00:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1776060003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ted Kaczynski terrorized the United States with his homemade bombs for nearly 20 years. Ever since his capture, Kaczynski’s story has been the subject of countless books and TV shows trying to unpack his unique psychology. Was the unabomber a madman or a misunderstood genius? In his podcast, Project Unabom, journalist Eric Benson revisits the story and dives deep into the unabomber’s own archives, to understand who he really was.</description></item><item><title>The Teacher’s Pet: Solving a cold case 40 years later | Crime Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1776060004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1776060004/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Lyn Dawson disappeared in 1982, many suspected her husband Chris Dawson had something to do with it. But for 40 years, the case went nowhere and Chris was free to live his life. All that changed when journalist Hedley Thomas entered the picture. Hedley unleashed a story of murder, sexual exploitation, failed criminal investigations, and later, a movement to put Chris behind bars. Hedley Thomas joins Crime Story to discuss Lyn’s case and his hugely influential podcast investigating it, The Teacher’s Pet.</description></item><item><title>The Girlfriends: Doctor. Pilot. Murderer? | Crime Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1776060005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 00:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1776060005/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Carole Fisher met Bob Bierenbaum in 1989, he seemed like a catch. He was a Jewish doctor who spoke five languages, a gourmand who loved skiing, and a New Yorker who could fly planes. He was every Jewish mother’s dream. But there was something off about Bob. He could fly into a sudden rage and be distant and controlling. Carole sensed he was hiding something. More than 30 years after Carole and Bob broke up, she uncovers his dark and sordid past in a podcast called The Girlfriends.</description></item><item><title>The Human Scale: Love and Death | Crime Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1776060006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 00:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1776060006/</guid><description>Podcast Description On December 1, 2016, police found the body of Dr. Elana Fric in a suitcase by the Humber River. Her husband, Dr. Mohammed Shamji, was arrested the next day. The murder and arrest made immediate headlines with Shamji as the focus, while Elana slipped into the background. But journalist Michael Lista promised to take a very different approach in reporting this story.
Watch this episode on CBC Podcasts&amp;rsquo; YouTube channel: www.</description></item><item><title>The Attack of Lenard Clark: Chicago Divided | Crime Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1776060007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 00:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1776060007/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1997, Lenard Clark was beaten into a coma by a gang of white teens simply for being Black in a white neighbourhood. One of Clark’s attackers was from a powerful Chicago family, with ties dating back to Al Capone. Yohance Lacour was a young writer at the time and was frustrated by the media’s coverage. 25 years later, he revisits the case in You Didn’t See Nothin, a podcast that’s part investigation, part memoir.</description></item><item><title>Chasing Cosby: The Rise &amp; Fall of America’s Dad | Crime Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1776060008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1776060008/</guid><description>Podcast Description For nearly 50 years, Bill Cosby charmed America. But behind the scenes, there were rumours of something sinister – that Cosby was drugging and assaulting women.
Nicole Weisensee Egan was the first reporter to dig into the claims against Cosby, when many journalists were afraid to do so. Her book and podcast, Chasing Cosby, is the definitive take on the rise and fall of Bill Cosby.
For early access to Crime Story episodes and to listen ad-free, subscribe to CBC&amp;rsquo;s True Crime channel on our show page in Apple Podcasts.</description></item><item><title>Bone Valley: ‘Why is Leo Schofield still in jail?’ | Crime Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1776060010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1776060010/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2018, author Gilbert King received a tip from a Florida judge that there was a man in prison serving a life sentence he didn’t deserve. King’s pursuit of that lead became Bone Valley—a remarkable podcast about cold blooded murder, the deeply flawed conviction of Leo Schofield and a relentless pursuit of the truth.
For early access to Crime Story episodes and to listen ad-free, subscribe to CBC&amp;rsquo;s True Crime channel on our show page in Apple Podcasts.</description></item><item><title>NXIVM: Inside The Celebrity Cult | Crime Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1776060009/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1776060009/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Josh Bloch ran into an old friend on Hornby Island, he had no idea what would come next. Sarah had just left a cult called NXIVM and was afraid for her safety. She had spent years under NXIVM’s control, and had been branded with the cult leader’s initials.
Josh brought Sarah’s story to Kathleen, and together they began to dig. What they found was a story of sexual abuse and master manipulation.</description></item><item><title>Introducing Crime Story | Crime Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1776060011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 00:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1776060011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Every week, Crime Story brings you an in-depth conversation with a storyteller who has lived and breathed a tale of true crime. Go inside some of the most riveting and complex crimes in recent memory. Crime Story drops Mondays, starting October 16.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>