<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Newscast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/newscast/</link><description>Recent content in Newscast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 20:21:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/newscast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Red Sea Rebel Attacks | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510302/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 20:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510302/</guid><description>Podcast Description Newscast brings you daily analysis of the latest political news stories from the BBC. Today, we look at BP’s decision to pause all Red Sea shipments after rebel attacks. The firm blamed the &amp;ldquo;deteriorating security situation&amp;rdquo; in the region as Iran-backed Houthis target ships they believe are bound for Israel. Adam speaks to Diplomatic correspondent James Landale and John Stawpert from the International Chamber of Shipping to find out what it means and how it could affect prices here.</description></item><item><title>The Michelle Mone interview: Reaction! | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510303/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 13:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510303/</guid><description>Podcast Description Newscast brings you daily analysis of the latest news stories from the BBC. In this episode, Laura and Paddy bring you the reaction to the interview with Baroness Mone and her husband, Doug Barrowman. They’re also joined by chief political correspondent, Henry Zeffman, as the government and Labour respond. Hear the extended interview with Michelle Mone and Doug Barrowman here: https://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/p0h02s78 This episode of Newscast was presented by Laura Kuenssberg and Paddy O’Connell.</description></item><item><title>The Michelle Mone and Doug Barrowman interview | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510304/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510304/</guid><description>Podcast Description Newscast brings you daily analysis of the latest news stories from the BBC. In this special episode, we bring you an extended interview with Baroness Mone and her husband, Doug Barrowman.
She admits that she stands to benefit from tens of millions of pounds of profit from PPE that was sold to the UK government during the pandemic by a company led by her husband.
The couple also accept that they lied to the press about their involvement with the firm.</description></item><item><title>Michelle Mone interview preview, Sunak and Starmer scorecards, and 2024 predictions | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510301/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 16:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510301/</guid><description>Podcast Description Newscast brings you daily analysis of the latest news stories from the BBC. Today, Laura and Paddy preview an interview with Baroness Mone, the Tory peer and entrepreneur at the center of a PPE scandal during the pandemic. Extended interview out tomorrow.
They also talk about the possible return of a devolved government return in Northern Ireland, and give their political predictions for 2024.
Today's Newscast was presented by Laura Kuenssberg and Paddy O’Connell.</description></item><item><title>Prince Harry: Hacked | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510001/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 18:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Newscast brings you daily analysis of the latest news stories from the BBC. Today, we look at the High Court ruling that Prince Harry was the victim of phone hacking by Mirror Group Newspapers. MGN issue a statement saying the group “apologises unreservedly”. What does this mean for the future of the Royal Family, and for the press in this country?
Adam is joined by media editor Katie Razzall, home affairs correspondent Tom Symonds, and royal commentator Peter Hunt.</description></item><item><title>Parliament: End of Term Report | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 21:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Newscast brings you daily analysis of the latest political news stories from the BBC. Today, we look at the big questions hanging over Westminster as MPs prepare to break for Christmas recess. What next for the Rwanda Bill? When might we see a General Election? and who’s favourite flavour of ice cream is vanilla?
Adam is joined by Conservative MP Dr Luke Evans, Labour MP + Shadow Culture Secretary Thangam Debbonaire and SNP Cabinet Office Spokesperson Kirsty Blackman</description></item><item><title>COP28: Fossil Fuels Down, Not Out | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 17:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Newscast brings you daily analysis of the latest political news stories from the BBC. Today, we look at the deal that’s been agreed at COP28.
Climate editor Justin Rowlatt goes through the detail, and Nigel Topping from the Climate Change Committee tells us what it means.
And Wales’ First Minister Mark Drakeford has announced he will be stepping down in March. Former Wales political editor and host of Walescast, Felicity Evans, explains why.</description></item><item><title>Sunak Survives Rwanda Vote (For Now) | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Newscast brings you daily analysis of the latest political news stories from the BBC. Today, we look at vote on the Rwanda Bill. After a charm offensive to his back bench MPs, the Prime Minister managed to shore up enough support for his Rwanda bill. Adam and Chris look at what happened today in the Commons and whether the real test is yet to come?
Meanwhile, climate talks run into the night at COP28 as countries try to salvage a deal to prevent it from being seen as a failure.</description></item><item><title>Is Rishi Sunak facing a Rebellion on Rwanda? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 20:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Newscast brings you daily analysis of the latest political news stories from the BBC. Today, we look at what’s happening with the plan to send asylum seekers to Rwanda. Conservative MPs met throughout the day to discuss the plan ahead of crunch vote for Rishi Sunak.
Adam is joined by Chris Mason and former No10 communications director Craig Oliver.
Meanwhile, the Prime Minister spent the day giving evidence to the Covid inquiry and defended the Eat Out to Help Out scheme.</description></item><item><title>Could This Be Rishi Sunak’s Worst Week EVER? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510006/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 13:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Newscast brings you daily analysis of the latest news stories from the BBC. Today, we look at the divisions within the Conservative Party. Laura’s been talking Robert Jenrick who resigned as immigration minister this week, as well as the levelling up secretary, Michael Gove.
Former No. 10 advisor and founder of the blog site Conservative Home Tim Montgomerie is in the Newscast studio reacting to what they had to say.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine in ‘mortal danger’ without aid: First Lady Zelenska with Laura in Kyiv | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510007/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 13:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Newscast brings you daily analysis of the latest news stories from the BBC. Today, we look at the war in Ukraine.
In an exclusive interview Ukraine’s First Lady Olena Zelenska warns of “mortal danger” if financial support to her country isn’t continued.
You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.com/newscastcommunityhere
Today's Newscast was presented by Laura Kuenssberg and Paddy O’Connell. It was made by Chris Flynn with Bella Saltiel.</description></item><item><title>What Next For Ofsted? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510008/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 18:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Newscast brings you daily analysis of the latest news stories from the BBC. Today, we look at what’s next for Ofsted. This follows an inquest into the death of head teacher Ruth Perry which ruled that Ofsted contributed to her death. The BBC’s education editor Branwen Jeffreys, professor of Sociology of Education at UCL Institute of Education, Alice Bradbury, and executive principal of Passmores cooperative, Vic Goddard, join Adam to discuss the future of the schools regulator.</description></item><item><title>Sunak defends Rwanda plan | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 21:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510009/</guid><description>Podcast Description The prime minister has defended his Rwanda bill at a press conference in which he described the plan as the “toughest immigration law ever”. But his own party is split over it.
It came the morning after the resignation of immigration minister Robert Jenrick, who said the new law wasn’t tough enough. And former Prime Minister Boris Johnson finishes his evidence at the Covid inquiry after being asked about partygate, Eat Out to Help Out and his time in hospital.</description></item><item><title>Boris Johnson at Covid Inquiry + SURPRISE Government Resignation | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 20:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today on Newscast, the former Prime Minister Boris Johnson gives evidence to the Covid inquiry in the first of a two-day questioning of his government’s handling of the pandemic.
Adam is joined by the BBC’s health reporter Jim Reed as well as Alex Thomas from the Institute for Government and The FT’s Lucy Fisher to unpack the key issues and what we’ve learnt from his evidence. And, the government has published emergency Rwanda legislation which makes clear that in UK law, Rwanda is a safe country for asylum seekers.</description></item><item><title>Rwanda Plan Takes Flight? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510011/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 20:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510011/</guid><description>Podcast Description The home secretary, James Cleverly has signed a new asylum treaty with the Rwandan government in an attempt to address the concerns of the Supreme Court.
Adam is joined by former home office advisor Claire Pearsall and the BBC’s West Africa correspondent Mayeni Jones to unpack what’s in the treaty and why it matters.
And what’s happening at COP28? The BBC’s climate editor Justin Rowlatt and former political strategist to the UNFCC Tom Rivett-Carnac explain what has been going on at the climate conference.</description></item><item><title>How much is too much legal migration? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 21:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510012/</guid><description>Podcast Description The home secretary, James Cleverly, has announced a five-point plan aimed at delivering the “biggest ever cut” in net migration to the UK. James looks at how different sectors might be impacted. We hear from Lord Bilimoria, Founder and Chairman of Cobra Beer, Crossbench Peer and Vice President of the CBI who thinks this is an “economically illiterate” plan. And Nadra Ahmed, Chair of the National Care Association, who insists this will only heighten staff shortages.</description></item><item><title>Keir Starmer’s Maggie Thatcher Splash | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510013/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510013/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Labour leader has said the former Tory leader effected "meaningful change” in the Sunday Telegraph. Paddy’s been speaking to him about why.
Also, as we head into the winter, Laura has been talking to the Health Secretary Victoria Atkins about whether the NHS is ready.
Today's Newscast was presented by Laura Kuenssberg, Paddy O’Connell and Henry Zeffman. It was made by Chris Flynn with Beth Ashmead Latham. The technical producer was Ricardo McCarthy.</description></item><item><title>What’s Boris Johnson going to say at the Covid inquiry? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510014/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 17:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former PM Boris Johnson will appear at the Covid inquiry next week, and journalists are being told what to expect. Laura and Paddy talk about his media management.
They also look back at a week in which Rishi Sunak cancelled a meeting with the Greek PM. We hear from Greece’s former finance minister Yanis Varoufakis on the issue at the heart of it - the Pantheon Sculptures.
And former Australian PM Julia Gillard is on from COP28 in Dubai to talk about what’s happening there, and her climate legacy in Australia.</description></item><item><title>Royal Ties | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 17:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Buckingham Palace says it's considering all options, after the King and Princess of Wales were identified as two members of the Royal Family who allegedly discussed the skin colour of Prince Harry and Meghan's son. The names appeared in a Dutch translation of a book which the author insists was an error. Adam speaks to BBC Royal Correspondent Jonny Diamond. And King Charles is currently is at a major climate gathering in Dubai, where he’s warned COP28 delegates that the world is far off track from meeting key climate targets.</description></item><item><title>Sadiq Khan on Alistair Darling, COP and Xmas Trees | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 21:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam chats to Labour Mayor of London Sadiq Khan about Alistair Darling, COP28, Ulez and the Trafalgar Square Christmas tree. And as Matt Hancock faces the Covid inquiry, Chris and former civil servant Jill Rutter give their analysis.
You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.com/newscastcommunityhere
Today's Newscast was presented by Adam Fleming. It was made by Jack Maclaren with Gemma Roper. The senior news editors are Jonathan Aspinwall and Sam Bonham.</description></item><item><title>COP28: A Guide to the Climate Change Conference | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 19:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510017/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 28th Climate Change Conference starts on Thursday in Dubai, and we’re giving you all the information you need to make sense of it.
To guide us through: - Nigel Topping, business champion at the Climate Change Committee
- Vanessa Nakate, climate activist and UNICEF Goodwill Ambassador
- Jordan Dunbar, host of BBC’s The Climate Question podcast
You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.com/newscastcommunityhere
Today&amp;rsquo;s Newscast was presented by Adam Fleming.</description></item><item><title>Is Rishi Sunak Losing his Elgin Marbles? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510018/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 21:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rishi Sunak cancelled a meeting with the Greek Prime Minister Kyriakos Mitsotakis at short notice after an argument over the Parthenon Sculptures aka the Elgin Marbles.
To unpack this disagreement Adam and Chris are joined by historian and comedian Natalie Haynes.
And an inquest into the death of Ruth Perry, a primary school headteacher who took her own life following an Ofsted inspection started today. Adam speaks to the BBC’s education editor Branwen Jeffreys.</description></item><item><title>Fair COP? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 19:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Documents obtained by the BBC show the UAE wanted to discuss new fossil fuel projects with a number of countries at COP28. The BBC’s climate editor and the journalist who got the scoop, Justin Rowlatt and Professor of Political Economy at University of Sheffield, Michael Jacobs joined Adam to discuss what this means for this week’s climate conference.
And a new pay offer has been made to consultants in England.</description></item><item><title>Migration: Labour Put A Number On It | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510020/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 13:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shadow cabinet minister Darren Jones has told Laura that his party would bring down net migration to ‘normal levels’ of ‘a couple of hundred thousand a year’, by the end of a Labour government first term.
And we hear from the families of newly released hostages in Israel, who Paddy’s been talking to.
You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.com/newscastcommunityhere
Today's Newscast was presented by Laura Kuenssberg and Paddy O’Connell.</description></item><item><title>Immigration: How high is too high? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510021/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 17:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510021/</guid><description>Podcast Description We try to answer some of the questions that politicians can’t. And Paddy goes to Stockton to find out what people in the constituency think of “s**tgate”. With thanks to Richard Drake at Drake The Bookshop in Stockton. You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.com/newscastcommunityhere.
Today's Newscast was presented by Laura Kuenssberg and Paddy O’Connell. It was made by Chris Flynn with Sam McLaren. The technical producer was Ricardo McCarthy.</description></item><item><title>Israel-Gaza: Hostages and detainees released | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 19:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510022/</guid><description>Podcast Description 13 Israelis, 10 Thais and one Filipino hostage have been released by Hamas and are back in Israel. 39 Palestinian have been freed by Israeli authorities.
The BBC’s chief international correspondent Lyse Doucet joins Adam in the studio to explain how these landmark releases played out.
And the special envoy on Covid-19 for the World Health Organisation, Dr David Nabarro swings by to analyse another eventful week in the Covid-19 inquiry.</description></item><item><title>How Much Will Energy Cost Next Year? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 22:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Energy bills are on the up and Money Saving Expert Martin Lewis is on the pod to chat to Adam and Chris about what you can do about it. He also shared his thoughts on the Autumn Statement
And as we find out that net migration - the difference between the number of people coming to live in the UK and those leaving - hit 745,000 last year, Adam speaks to Labour’s shadow home secretary Yvette Cooper.</description></item><item><title>Autumn Statement: Are Taxes Really Getting Cut? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 20:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510024/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Chancellor, Jeremy Hunt, announced ‘the biggest tax cut in British history’ for businesses and the ‘largest ever tax cut for workers’ in today’s Autumn Statement. But are these tax cuts all they seem? How come overall the tax burden will rise to the highest level since the Second World War? And did the Chancellor hint at a spring election?
Adam and Chris are joined by the BBC’s economics editor Faisal Islam and the chief executive of the CBI Rain Newton-Smith to talk this all through.</description></item><item><title>How Did the Police Handle the Nicola Bulley Case? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510025/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510025/</guid><description>Podcast Description A damning report into the Nicola Bulley case finds that the release of sensitive personal information was “avoidable and unnecessary”. On the release of personal information, Lancashire Police's Deputy Chief Constable Sacha Hatchett said: "We worked proactively with the Information Commissioner's Office immediately after the disclosure was made and they concluded that no action was required against the force.”
Following the disappearance which sparked a TikTok frenzy, what can we learn from the review?</description></item><item><title>Covid Inquiry: Diary of a CSA (Sir Patrick Vallance) | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510026/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510026/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s session at the Covid Inquiry, more of chief scientific adviser Sir Patrick Vallance’s diary was revealed. He described Boris Johnson as ‘weak and indecisive’ and being ‘clearly bamboozled’ by Covid science. Adam and Chris talk to health correspondent, Jim Reed, to understand what we can learn from the evidence.
And staff at OpenAI, the creator of ChatGPT, demanded the return of their former boss, Sam Altman, after he was unexpectedly fired.</description></item><item><title>Are Tax Cuts Coming? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510027/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 13:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510027/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Chancellor Jeremy Hunt is finalising spending plans ahead of Wednesday’s Autumn Statement.
Laura’s been speaking to him this morning, as well as his opposite number from Labour, Rachel Reeves.
And Paddy’s been hearing from people across the country who’ve told him what they would like to hear from the chancellor.
Economics editor Faisal Islam is in the studio to talk it all through.
You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.</description></item><item><title>Making an Autumn Statement: What could we hear from the chancellor next week? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510028/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 16:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510028/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Chancellor Jeremy Hunt is considering cutting inheritance and business taxes, the BBC has been told.
He will present new economic policies in the Autumn Statement on Wednesday.
Former Treasury minister, David Gauke, gives Laura and Paddy an inside look into how Autumn Statements are made.
And they unpack another busy week of Westminster politics.
You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.com/newscastcommunityhere
Today&amp;rsquo;s Newscast was presented by Laura Kuenssberg and Paddy O’Connell.</description></item><item><title>Israel-Gaza: Is The Aid Enough? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510029/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 17:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam is joined by chief international correspondent Lyse Doucet and international editor Jeremy Bowen to discuss the latest from the Israel-Gaza conflict. As Israel agrees to allow more fuel into Gaza, the IDF try to prove that Al-Shifa Hospital was a key Hamas command centre.
Why has Israel let in aid now? How could the US influence Netanyahu to call a ceasefire? And how is this conflict different to other recent wars?</description></item><item><title>A Week is a Long Time in Politics | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510030/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 22:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eight shadow ministers have resigned or were sacked from Labour’s frontbench after voting for an immediate ceasefire in the Israel-Gaza war. And new foreign secretary David Cameron makes his first visit to Ukraine.
Adam and Chris talk over the huge political stories of the week with Ava-Santina Evans, political correspondent at PoliticsJOE, and Patrick Maguire, columnist at The Times. You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.com/newscastcommunityhere</description></item><item><title>Rishi, Rwanda and Human Rights (Plus a Labour Rebellion) | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510031/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 20:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rishi Sunak says he will introduce emergency legislation to “confirm Rwanda is safe” but with pressure mounting from his party, how far will he actually go? Home and legal correspondent Dominic Casciani joins Adam and Chris.
And as UK inflation drops to its lowest rate in two years, the government says its pledge to halve inflation has been met early. Adam talks to economics correspondent, Dharshini David to find out more.</description></item><item><title>Rwanda Flights CANCELLED | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510032/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 14:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510032/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Supreme Court has ruled that the government’s Rwanda asylum plan is unlawful. But Rishi Sunak says the government are not giving up on the plan.
How did the Supreme Court reach this ruling? And what could Rishi Sunak do next?
Adam and Chris are joined by political correspondent Alex Forsyth and home and legal correspondent Dominic Casciani to talk it all through. You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.</description></item><item><title>Braverman's Revenge | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510033/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 20:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Suella Braverman launches a full-scale attack on her old boss Rishi Sunak, a day after he sacked her as home secretary.
In a blistering letter to the prime minister, she said he had repeatedly failed on key policies and broken pledges over immigration.
Adam and Chris are joined by former BBC home affairs correspondent Danny Shaw and former special advisor at the home office Salma Shah to discuss what it all means.</description></item><item><title>The David Cameron Interview | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510034/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 19:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510034/</guid><description>Podcast Description The new foreign secretary speaks. Chris talks it through with Adam, and they reflect on a day of changes in Rishi Sunak’s cabinet.
You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.com/newscastcommunityhere
Today&amp;rsquo;s Newscast was presented by Adam Fleming. It was made by Chris Flynn with Sam McLaren and Gemma Roper. The technical producer was Rohan Madison. The editors are Jonathan Aspinwall and Sam Bonham.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>David Cameron Returns | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510035/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 14:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510035/</guid><description>Podcast Description The former prime minister is in government, and Suella Braverman isn’t.
David Cameron is foreign secretary and James Cleverly has been moved to the Home Office after Rishi Sunak’s latest cabinet reshuffle. Cameron, who was prime minister from 2010 to 2016, isn’t a sitting MP but has now been appointed to the House of Lords.
Adam and Chris are joined by chief political correspondent Henry Zeffman and Cameron’s former deputy chief of staff Baroness Kate Fall to discuss his return.</description></item><item><title>London Protests: Braverman on the Brink? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510036/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 14:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510036/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s pressure on the home secretary after protest violence at the weekend and Laura’s been talking to defence secretary Grant Shapps about whether she could lose her job.
Laura and James are joined by chief political correspondent Henry Zeffman to talk all this through.
You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.com/newscastcommunityhere.
Today's Newscast was presented by Laura Kuenssberg and James Cook. It was made by Chris Flynn and Joe Wilkinson.</description></item><item><title>London Protests: What Happened? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510037/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 21:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Arrests in London as thousands attend pro-Palestinian march and counter-protest.
Home editor Mark Easton has been on the street and in the Metropolitan Police’s control room - in a secret underground location. He’s in the Newscast studio.
And Laura gives her take on whether Rishi Sunak is being made to look weak by Suella Braverman.
You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.com/newscastcommunityhere
Today's Newscast was presented by Laura Kuenssberg and James Cook.</description></item><item><title>The Protests and the Police | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510038/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 22:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510038/</guid><description>Podcast Description The police prepare for an unprecedented security operation ahead of a pro-Palestinian demonstration in London.
James talks to home and legal affairs correspondent Dominic Casciani and former Met Police Chief Superintendent, Dal Babu, about how to police a protest.
And Alex Forsyth gives us the latest updates on how members of the Cabinet have responded - or avoided responding - to Suella Braverman's comments.
You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.</description></item><item><title>Suella Braverman: Home Secretary Under the Hammer? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510039/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 19:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Suella Braverman is facing questions about her future. Adam and Chris talk with GB News’ Christopher Hope, Politico’s Rosa Prince, and the Daily Mirror’s John Stevens.
Today's Newscast was presented by Adam Fleming and Chris Mason. It was made by Chris Flynn with Miranda Slade. The technical producer was Ged Sudlow. The senior news editors are Jonathan Aspinwall and Sam Bonham.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Covid inquiry: Talking "chickenpox parties" | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 19:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ex-civil service chief apologises for suggestions made during the pandemic. To help analyse the latest at the Covid inquiry, Adam is joined by health correspondent Jim Reed and Emma Norris from the Institute for Government. And Adam talks to Professor Ed Hawkins, who's on the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change, about why this year is set to become the hottest year on record.
You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.</description></item><item><title>Three King’s Speech Takeaways | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510041/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510041/</guid><description>Podcast Description King Charles has set out the government’s agenda for the year. We look at what it could mean in practice.
Adam and Chris are joined by Danny Shaw to discuss plans to bring in tougher sentences on some serious crimes. There were also housing policy plans announced, making it harder for landlords to evict tenants and changes to the leasehold system England and Wales. Vicky Spratt helps make sense of what it means.</description></item><item><title>Marching Orders: Met Police Urges Demo Delay | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510042/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 21:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510042/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Metropolitan Police has urged the organisers of pro-Palestinian marches to call off their planned demonstration on Armistice Day. The home secretary, Suella Braverman, said there was a “risk of serious public disorder” if the marches went ahead.
To help understand the challenges and complexities of policing these events, Adam is joined by former Met detective superintendent Shabnam Chaudhri and the BBC’s home affairs correspondent, Dominic Casciani. Prime Minister Rishi Sunak has described allegations that a Conservative MP committed multiple rapes as "</description></item><item><title>Covid Inquiry Consequences | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510043/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 13:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Evidence at the Covid inquiry has shown there were huge tensions within Number 10 during the pandemic. But is what we're hearing damaging the reputation of the current government?
Laura’s been talking to the Deputy Prime Minister Oliver Dowden about it.
We also discuss the political and policing challenges of plans for a mass rally next Saturday on Armistice Day.
Laura and Paddy are joined by chief political correspondent Henry Zeffman to talk this all through.</description></item><item><title>Sunak’s 2024 plans and his ‘bromance’ with Musk | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510044/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 16:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510044/</guid><description>Podcast Description King Charles will outline the government's law-making plans in Parliament on Tuesday.
All the expected announcements, including plans to ban no fault evictions for renters, and to restrict the use of tents by homeless people.
Was Sunak's chat with Elon Musk the start of a new 'bromance'?
Plus Paddy and Laura's tribute to actor Matthew Perry and what Friends means to them.
You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.</description></item><item><title>In the room with Sunak and Musk | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510045/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 18:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510045/</guid><description>Podcast Description The prime minister has been speaking to tech billionaire Elon Musk, who said that at some point all jobs would be redundant because of artificial intelligence. Technology editor Zoe Kleinman was in the room, and is on Newscast.
Correspondent Daniel De Simone is also on, discussing the latest evidence he’s found in the murder case of Stephen Lawrence, which raises further questions about a 6th suspect in the case.</description></item><item><title>The Covid Inquiry Enquiries | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510046/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510046/</guid><description>Podcast Description The latest evidence to the Covid Inquiry included the revelation that the former health secretary Matt Hancock wanted to decide “who should live or die” in the event of the NHS becoming overwhelmed. That was the testimony given by Sir Simon Stevens, who led NHS England until 2021. His was followed by the country’s most senior health official, Sir Christopher Wormald, who said that the government was “at least a week late” in imposing restrictions on society at the beginning of the crisis.</description></item><item><title>Why Were Women 'Invisible' During Covid? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510047/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 20:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510047/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been another extraordinary day of testimony at the Covid Inquiry. Wednesday’s session began with Helen MacNamara, a top official at Downing Street during the height of the pandemic. She described a “macho” culture at No 10 in which women “became invisible overnight”.
She also said she’d struggle to pick “a single day” in which Covid restrictions were followed and recalled meetings at which people were “laughing at the Italians” in the early days of the crisis.</description></item><item><title>Covid Inquiry: Government Short Cummings? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510048/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 20:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Figures at the centre of the government decisions during the coronavirus pandemic give evidence to the UK Covid-19 inquiry. First up was Lee Cain, who was a senior aide to former Prime Minister Boris Johnson. Then it was Dominic Cummings, who was Mr Johnson’s chief adviser until he resigned in late 2020.
The inquiry heard the pandemic was the wrong crisis for Boris Johnson’s skillset, the government had “no plan” to help vulnerable people in lockdown and diary entries also read out suggest Mr Johnson believed old people should get the virus to protect others.</description></item><item><title>WhatsAppening at the Covid Inquiry? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510049/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 20:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510049/</guid><description>Podcast Description It was a day of explosive evidence and revealing WhatsApp messages at today’s session of the Covid inquiry. First up was former senior civil servant Martin Reynolds, who apologised “unreservedly” for organising BYOB lockdown parties. He also faced questions on why messages in a WhatsApp group of government officials were ‘set to disappear’.
He was then followed by another aide, Imran Shafi, who said he thought Boris Johnson had questioned why the economy was being destroyed "</description></item><item><title>UK Politics and the War in the Middle East | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510050/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 15:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Israeli forces continue moving troops into Gaza as bombing continues.
And different positions have emerged in UK politics on what should be done to help civilians in the region.
Political editor of Newsnight, Nick Watt helps us make sense of them, and Lyse Doucet, BBC chief international reporter, tells us how the politics of the conflict is playing out across the world.
You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.</description></item><item><title>Israel Ground Operation in Gaza | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510051/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 14:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Paddy O’Connell is joined by the BBC’s chief international correspondent Lyse Doucet and special correspondent Fergal Keane to discuss the next chapter in the Israel-Gaza conflict.
The Israeli military says that its forces entered Gaza after heavy bombardment throughout the night. You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.com/newscastcommunityhere.
Today's Newscast was hosted by Paddy O’Connell. It was made by Chris Flynn with Gemma Roper. The technical producer was Mike Regaard.</description></item><item><title>X, Rated: Elon Musk’s First Year | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510052/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 18:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510052/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a year since Elon Musk formally completed his acquisition of X, formerly known as Twitter. Since then the business has faced a number of challenges, including ongoing issues surrounding content moderation and a battle to make the platform profitable. To help us understand the business from all angles, Adam is joined by the BBC’s disinformation correspondent, Marianna Spring, and tech investor Ross Gerber. And, the BBC’s Leila Nathoo drops in to discuss tensions in the Labour Party after Sadiq Khan, Andy Burnham and Anas Sarwar all call for a ceasefire in Gaza.</description></item><item><title>AI: Nothing to 'Lose Sleep Over'? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510053/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510053/</guid><description>Podcast Description The prime minister has outlined the potential risks of artificial intelligence, arguing we must not “put our heads in the sand”. His comments come ahead of a two-day AI safety summit at Bletchley Park in Buckinghamshire next week. Professors Hannah Fry and Gina Neff join us in the studio to discuss the event as well as the risks and opportunities presented by AI. And, Bastille singer Dan Smith takes a seat next to Planet Earth III director Kiri Cashell for a conversation about how they made the music and television for the latest iteration of Sir David Attenborough’s iconic documentary series.</description></item><item><title>365 Days of PM Rishi Sunak: How's He Done? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510054/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam and Chris reflect on one year of Prime Minister Rishi Sunak as Sir Keir Starmer comes under pressure from his own MPs because of his position on the Israel-Gaza conflict. And there are plans to send an all-UK astronaut mission into space. BBC science correspondent Jonathan Amos and the first British astronaut Helen Sharman discuss whether the project is good news for space exploration. You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.</description></item><item><title>Israel-Gaza: High Stakes Diplomacy | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510055/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 19:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510055/</guid><description>Podcast Description After two Israeli hostages were released by Hamas last night, BBC diplomatic correspondent James Landale joins Katya Adler, who’s in Jerusalem, to discuss how diplomacy is impacting the Israel-Gaza conflict. And, Adam is joined by BBC football correspondent John Murray to discuss how UEFA’s calendar shakeup could cause a significant increase in carbon emissions.
You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.com/newscastcommunityhere
Today&amp;rsquo;s Newscast was presented by Adam Fleming.</description></item><item><title>Israel-Gaza: Policing UK Protests | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510056/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 19:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Several government ministers have called for tougher policing of protests after a row over the police’s handling of pro-Palestinian protests at the weekend. Adam and Chris discuss how the day unfolded after the prime minister committed a further £20 million in humanitarian aid for civilians in Gaza. And we’re joined in studio by Jonathan Wittenberg and Ibrahim Mogra, the rabbi and imam who are working together to unite their communities during the Israel-Gaza conflict.</description></item><item><title>Israel-Gaza: The West Bank Strike | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510057/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 14:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510057/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Israeli military says it was a targeted attack against Hamas.
Paddy and Victoria talk about the operation with chief international correspondent Lyse Doucet.
And chief political correspondent Henry Zeffman assesses the Conservatives’ electoral prospects after two by-election defeats.
You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.com/newscastcommunityhere.
Today's Newscast was presented by Paddy O’Connell and Victoria Derbyshire. It was made by Chris Flynn with Gemma Roper. The technical producer was Matthew Dean The senior news editors are Jonathan Aspinwall and Sam Bonham.</description></item><item><title>Sweary WhatsApps At The Covid Inquiry | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510058/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 12:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510058/</guid><description>Podcast Description WhatsApps seen by the UK’s Covid-19 Inquiry have given us an insight into the different opinions inside government during the pandemic.
Health reporter and host of The Covid Inquiry Podcast Jim Reed has been closely following every day of evidence. He’s in the studio with Dr. Catherine Haddon from the Institute for Government to look at what we’ve learned.
Marianna Spring is also in to help with tips on how to recognise disinformation online, as claim, counterclaim, and straight up lies swirl on social media.</description></item><item><title>By-Electioncast Live! | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510059/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 07:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510059/</guid><description>Podcast Description ​​Labour win two by-elections and we record one podcast on TV! Newscast was live early this morning to analyse and react to the results of the Tamworth and Mid Bedfordshire by-elections. ​​
​​Adam Fleming and Paddy O’Connell chat through Labour’s historic double by-election win with help from Chris Mason, Alex Forsyth, Henry Zeffman, Professor John Curtice, Jeremy Vine and Labour MP Peter Kyle.
​​
​​You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.</description></item><item><title>Israel-Gaza: Lyse Doucet and Jeremy Bowen | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510060/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 21:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vehicles carrying aid are waiting to be allowed into Gaza to bring in vital supplies.
International editor Jeremy Bowen and chief international correspondent Lyse Doucet join Chris from Israel to discuss.
The three of them also talk about Rishi Sunak’s visit to the country, and the different allegiances in the middle east.
You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.com/newscastcommunityhere
Today&amp;rsquo;s Newscast was presented by Chris Mason and Lyse Doucet.</description></item><item><title>Gaza Hospital Blast: The Information War | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510061/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 18:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hundreds of people are known to have died in a blast at a Gaza hospital on Tuesday. Hamas blames Israel for the attack, while Israel has insisted it is not to blame. BBC Verify’s Shayan Sardarizadeh joins Adam in the studio to discuss what we know so far.
And, on the day that US President Joe Biden flew to Israel in an attempt to calm tensions, we’re joined by former CIA director David Petraeus and US special correspondent Katty Kay to assess the bigger picture for the US as they attempt to deescalate the conflict.</description></item><item><title>Emergency episode: The Gaza Hospital Strike | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510062/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 22:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510062/</guid><description>Podcast Description A huge blast at a hospital in Gaza City is reported to have killed hundreds.
In this emergency episode recorded at 10pm tonight in Israel, host of The Conflict podcast, BBC International Correspondent Lyse Doucet, and her colleague Anna Foster, grapple with the breaking news and the claims and counter claims as protests break out across the region.
This episode was made by Clare Williamson and Joe Kent in London and Alex Lederman and Naomi Scherbel-Ball in Israel.</description></item><item><title>Is the UK Getting a Pay Rise? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510063/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 18:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wage growth has overtaken inflation for the first time in two years, in a sign that cost of living pressures may now be starting to ease. The Institute for Fiscal Studies has warned, however, that the UK remains stuck in a bind between high inflation and weak economic growth. Their director, Paul Johnson, joins Adam alongside the BBC’s chief economics correspondent, Dharshini David, to unpack the day’s economic headlines.</description></item><item><title>Israel-Gaza: Could the Conflict Spread? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510064/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 21:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam and Chris are joined by BBC world affairs editor John Simpson to discuss the potential implications of Israel’s expected ground invasion of Gaza. Rishi Sunak set out the UK government’s response to the situation in Parliament and announced an increase in humanitarian aid to Gaza by £10 million.
And Europe editor Katya Adler analyses the results of the Polish elections as exit polls suggest that the governing right-wing Law and Justice party won the most seats but will lose its majority in parliament.</description></item><item><title>Israel-Gaza: Attack by land, air and sea | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510065/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 13:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tanks and troops gather for an expected offensive into Gaza.
Paddy and Victoria discuss new details about the planned attack, and the British government’s position on the conflict.
Chris Mason and James Cook are at the SNP annual conference in Aberdeen. They explain the SNP’s new strategy for a second referendum on Scottish independence.
You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.com/newscastcommunityhere
Today's Newscast was hosted by Paddy O’Connell and Victoria Derbyshire.</description></item><item><title>Urban War Insights And The Hamas Tunnels | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510066/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 17:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Israel appears to be preparing for a ground invasion into Gaza. Paddy’s joined by Lyse Doucet as they get detail on what that could look like from defence correspondent Jonathan Beale.
They also discuss the underground network set up by Hamas in Gaza.
We also answer some of your questions, in this collaboration with The Conflict podcast.
You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.com/newscastcommunityhere
Today's Newscast was hosted by Paddy O’Connell and Lyse Doucet.</description></item><item><title>Israel-Gaza: One Million Told To Leave Home | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510067/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 20:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510067/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Israeli military has ordered around 1 million people in northern Gaza to move to the south within 24 hours.
BBC documentary and podcast maker, Josh Baker is on the podcast from Jerusalem, to help explain the difficulties that civilians will have following that order. He also talks about the aftermath of attacks on civilians by Hamas.
Yesterday, David Baddiel mentioned a group that helps maintain safety at synagogues and Jewish schools in the UK called the Community Security Trust, so we thought we’d invite them on to find out more.</description></item><item><title>David Baddiel on Israel and Antisemitism | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510068/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 20:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510068/</guid><description>Podcast Description As Israel’s siege of Gaza continues, the UN has warned that Gaza is in a ‘dire situation’. Joining us in the studio is the writer and comedian, David Baddiel, who talks about what the past week has been like for British Jews.
Following the end of their party conference, Pat McFadden, who’s in charge of Labour’s electoral strategy, also stops by to talk to us about the party’s game plan ahead of the next general election.</description></item><item><title>Starmer Bets on the House | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510069/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 20:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510069/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the Labour Party Conference draws to a close, Chris joins Adam to discuss his interview with Sir Keir Starmer, in which the Labour leader reiterated his pledge to build 1.5 million homes. And the chair of the British Palestinian Committee, Dr Aimee Shalan, speaks to Adam about the situation in Gaza after Israel cut off its access to electricity.
You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.</description></item><item><title>Labour Conference: Sir Glitter Starmer | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510070/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sir Keir Starmer sets out his plan for government at the Labour Party Conference. Adam is joined by Chris Mason to discuss the speech, where the Labour leader laid out promised a "decade of renewal under Labour”
Adam also chats to shadow health secretary Wes Streeting. And, Israel’s ambassador to the UK, Tzipi Hotovely speaks to Adam about the UK’s support for Israel and why she feels these attacks are comparable to the Holocaust.</description></item><item><title>Israel-Gaza: The Siege | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510071/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 18:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam is joined by chief international correspondent Lyse Doucet and world affairs editor John Simpson to discuss the events in Israel, as Benjamin Netanyahu warns the country will use “enormous force” against Hamas. And as the world reacts to the events, Lyse and John focus on how the conflict will affect other countries in the Middle East, such as Lebanon and Iran.
The essential background you need to understand the conflict can be found here: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Israel-Gaza: Fear For Hostages Taken By Hamas | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510072/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 14:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hundreds of people have been killed and kidnapped as fighting in Israel and Gaza continues.
The BBC’s security correspondent Frank Gardner is on to discuss what we know about the situation.
And after Sir Keir Starmer’s Sunday morning interview, Victoria and Paddy chat to chief political correspondent Henry Zeffman about Labour’s ideas for the NHS and housing.
You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.com/newscastcommunityhere
Today's Newscast was hosted by Paddy O’Connell and Victoria Derbyshire.</description></item><item><title>Attack on Israel from Gaza | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510073/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 17:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Paddy and Victoria catch up with international editor Jeremy Bowen as he heads to Israel to cover a major new crisis in the Middle East.
And, on the eve of Labour conference, Lord Mandelson talks through how Sir Keir Starmer should now redefine himself. You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.com/newscastcommunityhere
Today’s Newscast was presented by Paddy O'Connell and Victoria Derbyshire. It was made by Tom Smithard with Arsenii Sokolov.</description></item><item><title>By-Election: Labour Day in Scotland | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510074/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 17:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Starmer tells campaigners they "blew the doors off" in Friday's by-election.
Adam is joined by Scotland editor, James Cook, and political scientist, Professor Sir John Curtice, to analyse the results in Rutherglen and Hamilton West.
And, on its 10th birthday, the National Crime Agency’s director general, Graeme Biggar, is in the studio talking about illegal migration, organised crime, and fraud.
You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.</description></item><item><title>Rishi Sunak Puts Out Cigarettes | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510075/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 20:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510075/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the dust settles after Rishi Sunak’s conference speech, Adam and Chris focus on the fallout from the biggest talking points, including the prime minister’s plans to ban smoking for younger generations.
They’re joined by doctor and TV presenter Alexander "Dr Xand" van Tulleken to hear the medical profession’s reaction and whether it’s true that there’s no safe level of smoking.
And to help analyse the wider political context of the speech, we’re joined in the studio by former special adviser Anita Boateng and broadcaster and author Matt Chorley who give us their own reflections of being at party conferences.</description></item><item><title>Amol Rajan and Nick Robinson Introduce 'The Today Podcast' | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510076/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amol and Nick give Newscast a taste of their brand new podcast.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sunak ends Tory Conference (and HS2 to Manchester) | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510077/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 19:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510077/</guid><description>Podcast Description In his first Conservative conference speech as prime minister, Rishi Sunak confirms the Manchester leg of HS2 is to be scrapped. In its place, a range of new transport projects for the Midlands and the North are to be put forward. Aside from HS2, he also proposes raising the age that people can buy tobacco and cigarettes in England every year to create a "smoke-free generation.” Alongside the smoking changes, Sunak also wants to clamp down on vaping among children.</description></item><item><title>Is Rishi Sunak Being Overshadowed? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510078/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 20:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510078/</guid><description>Podcast Description After intense speculation on the future of HS2, the BBC understands the prime minister is to announce the scrapping of HS2 from West Midlands to Manchester in his closing conference speech on Wednesday. Chris joins Adam to reflect on his interview earlier in the day with Rishi Sunak. As the Conservative Party Conference draws to a close, Henry Zeffman, the BBC's chief political correspondent, sits down with Adam to assess another busy day for the party.</description></item><item><title>Tory Conference Derailed By HS2 | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510079/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 20:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510079/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the day of the chancellor’s speech, everyone’s talking about a train line.
West Midlands Tory mayor Andy Street has said Rishi Sunak would be "cancelling the future" if he "gives up" on the Manchester leg of HS2.
Adam and Chris are there for his impromptu press conference.
Conservative Party chairman Greg Hands joins to react to that, as well as what Jeremy Hunt and Liz Truss had to say today.</description></item><item><title>The Rishi Sunak Interview | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510080/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 13:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Analysis of Laura’s sit down with the PM.
Paddy’s presenting with her, and they’re joined by chief political correspondent Henry Zeffman.
They talk about refusals in the interview to commit to HS2 in full, as well as tax cuts before the next election, and how it all looks together with Sunak’s attempts to be seen as being on the front foot.
You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.</description></item><item><title>Will The Rishi Rebrand Work? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510081/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 17:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can the PM win over voters as the ‘change candidate’?
Laura and Paddy discuss.
And Newscasters have been getting in touch about 'State of Chaos’ - Laura’s show about the political turmoil in the May/Johnson/Truss years. She answers some of them, and talks about what putting the programme together was like.
You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.com/newscastcommunityhere
Today’s Newscast was presented by Laura Kuenssberg and Paddy O'Connell.</description></item><item><title>U K Economy? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510082/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 18:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510082/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Chancellor will be addressing the Conservative party conference on Monday to set out his economic vision - but what health is the UK economy in?
Faisal Islam and Dharshini David have been reporting on economic affairs around the UK and how consumers are coping. Joined by Rain Newton-Smith, chief executive of the Confederation of British Industry, they discuss all aspects of the economy from infrastructure, to energy, to robots.</description></item><item><title>Breaking GB News: Ofcom Investigates | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510083/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 20:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510083/</guid><description>Podcast Description The media regulator Ofcom has announced it will investigate the Dan Wootton Tonight show on GB News after a sexism row sparked 7,300 complaints. Adam and Chris sit down with GB News presenter Nana Akua to discuss the last 24 hours and the nature of impartiality rules.
Also, Asa Bennett, a former adviser to Liz Truss, joins us to discuss what it was like writing a conference speech for the former prime minister ahead of the Conservative Party Conference.</description></item><item><title>Breaking GB News: The Ava-Santina Interview | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510084/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 17:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510084/</guid><description>Podcast Description “It’s made me feel disgusting, it’s made me feel vile".
Political correspondent at PoliticsJoe Ava-Santina speaks about the comments made about her by GB News presenter Laurence Fox. He and Dan Wootton have both been suspended by the broadcaster.
And, the UK's largest untapped oil field has been approved by regulators. Adam speaks to the country manager for Equinor Alex Grant, one of the main stakeholders and Scotland Editor James Cook.</description></item><item><title>The Ed Davey Train: Lib Dem Conference | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510085/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 20:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sir Ed Davey launches an all-out attack on the Conservative government’s record on the NHS as he closes the Liberal Democrat party conference. Chris Mason gives his analysis and Adam quizzes Lib Dem MP Christine Jardine on the finer details of her party’s policies.
And does the 1951 Refugee Convention need updating? Suella Braverman thinks so. Adam is joined by the Labour Peer, Lord Dubs, to discuss the Home Secretary’s speech on migration.</description></item><item><title>Why Are The Police Putting Down Their Guns? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510086/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Soldiers were put on standby after hundreds of Metropolitan Police officers stepped back from firearms duties after an officer was charged with the murder of Chris Kaba last September. Home affairs correspondent Tom Symonds talks us through a dramatic day for the Met alongside Harriet Wistrich, the lawyer who represented the family of Jean Charles de Menezes after he was killed by police in 2005.
And what next for HS2?</description></item><item><title>Are Government Putting the Brakes on HS2? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510087/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 12:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510087/</guid><description>Podcast Description More politicians refuse to commit to plans for the rail link. Paddy is joined by Victoria Derbyshire who has been hosting Sunday with Laura Kuenssberg. Rachel Johnson, journalist and broadcaster, joins them in the studio fresh from sitting on Victoria’s panel and Henry Zeffman, BBC chief political correspondent, analyses the details of this morning’s interviews. Victoria’s been speaking to Grant Shapps, defence secretary and former transport secretary, about HS2.</description></item><item><title>What REALLY Happens at Party Conferences? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510088/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Paddy is joined by Salma Shah, former Conservative adviser, and Marie Le Conte, political journalist, to discuss party conference season which begins today.
What happens at a conference? Who are party conferences for? And is this all about ‘electioneering’?
They also discuss the latest policy announcements from the government, the Labour party and the Liberal Democrats. And Newscasters send in their thoughts on political slogans. You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.</description></item><item><title>​​Labournomics: Ask Reeves | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510089/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 16:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510089/</guid><description>Podcast Description ​​The shadow chancellor Rachel Reeves is in the studio. ​​
​​She promises to hand more power to the UK economic watchdog the Office for Budget Responsibility (OBR), discusses Sir Keir Starmer’s comments on common ground with the EU, and tells Adam where Labour is on HS2.
​​
​​You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.com/newscastcommunityhere.
​​
​​Today's Newscast was presented by Adam Fleming. It was made by Chris Flynn with Joe Wilkinson and Keiligh Baker.</description></item><item><title>The Murdoch Succession | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510090/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 21:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rupert Murdoch has stepped aside as chairman of Fox and News Corp. Adam and Chris are joined by former editor of The Sun, Kelvin MacKenzie, PoliticsJOE’s Ava Santina and former Boris Johnson adviser Cleo Watson to discuss what this means for the media landscape.
And COP26 President Sir Alok Sharma dials in from the UN Climate Action Summit in New York to give his thoughts on Rishi Sunak’s pivot on net zero plans.</description></item><item><title>Climate (Policy) Change | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510091/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 20:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Prime Minister Rishi Sunak pushes back the ban on the sale of new petrol and diesel cars in the UK from 2030 to 2035 and extends the transition from gas boilers to heat pumps.
Adam is joined by Chris Mason, Faisal Islam and the Labour Mayor of London, Sadiq Khan.
And the BBC’s Disinformation &amp;amp; Social Media Correspondent, Marianna Spring, pops by to chat about her documentary looking at how the TikTok algorithm can create frenzies.</description></item><item><title>Sunak Tightens His Green Belt | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510092/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 20:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rishi Sunak could weaken some of the government's key green commitments in a major policy shift.
Chris joins Adam from Westminster to discuss what the prime minister might do and what it means for net zero.
And a public inquiry has found detainees at Brook House migrant removal centre were subjected to degrading treatment and unnecessary pain. Callum Tulley, a former Brook House officer and whistleblower, now BBC journalist, gives us his reaction to the inquiry’s report.</description></item><item><title>The Investigation into Russell Brand | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510093/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510093/</guid><description>Podcast Description How did Channel 4’s Dispatches &amp;amp; The Sunday Times put the Russell Brand investigation together? Adam is joined by Louisa Compton, head of news and current affairs at Channel 4 and Alistair Jackson, investigations editor of Dispatches.
And Liz Truss is back on the political stage, urging the Prime Minister to cut taxes a year after her Downing Street exit. The BBC’s Chris Mason and Faisal Islam give us their take on her speech.</description></item><item><title>The Russell Brand Allegations | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510094/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 12:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Paddy’s been talking to Rosamund Urwin, the journalist who led The Sunday Times investigation into allegations against comedian Russell Brand.
And Laura’s been talking to the Foreign Secretary James Cleverly about it. He says the entertainment industry has questions to answer.
They discuss what those questions might be, and the work that’s gone into publishing the story.
Also in the studio is the Telegraph’s political editor Ben Riley-Smith, who’s been uncovering details of what was going on behind the scenes as recent prime ministers lost their jobs.</description></item><item><title>Inside Labour's Election Strategy | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510095/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510095/</guid><description>Podcast Description What’s Labour’s plan to win the next election?
Laura and Paddy discuss the opposition’s plan to attract votes, as they make immigration and crime their subjects of the moment.
They also talk about accusations against comedian and actor Russell Brand of rape, sexual assaults and emotional abuse in The Times and on Channel 4’s Dispatches, which he denies.
And a former Network Rail director in the North of England is on to talk about whether HS2 will make it as far as Manchester, and why it’s cost so much money.</description></item><item><title>XL Bully Dogs Banned | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510096/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 20:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marianna Spring sits in for Adam.
Rishi Sunak has pledged to ban American bully XL dogs, following a spate of attacks.
Marianna is joined by the BBC’s Navtej Johal, who’s been following the story all week and a has spoken to a young victim. Dog law specialist Trevor Cooper is also on.
And thousands of people are still missing in the city of Derna in north-east Libya, after two dams burst.</description></item><item><title>Crystal Keir: Labour's Small Boats Plan | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510097/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 19:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sir Keir Starmer seeks new deal with EU to stop smugglers.
Labour’s Emily Thornberry joins Adam and Chris to take us through what their plan is.
And, the government’s target to reduce the hospital waiting list in England is in doubt according to the prime minister. He was speaking to health editor Hugh Pym, who joins us, as does Saffron Cordery from NHS Providers. 00:00 Labour’s plan to stop small boat gangs
20:20 PM admits target to cut waiting times in doubt You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.</description></item><item><title>From Russia, With Kim Jong Un | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 19:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510098/</guid><description>Podcast Description BBC world affairs editor John Simpson and former spy chief Christopher Steele reveal what the Russian and North Korean leaders meeting means for the rest of the world.
And Political Thinking presenter Nick Robinson joins Adam to discuss his revealing interview with former Prime Minister Theresa May.
You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.com/newscastcommunityhere.
Today's Newscast was presented by Adam Fleming. It was made by George Dabby with Keiligh Baker, Josh Jenkins and Niamh Hughes.</description></item><item><title>Pension Tension: End of the Triple Lock? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510099/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510099/</guid><description>Podcast Description The state pension is likely to rise by 8.5% in April because of the ‘triple lock’. The policy means that the value increases in line with average earnings, inflation or 2.5% - whichever is highest. Adam and Chris are joined by our Economics Editor Faisal Islam and Jonathan Cribb from the Institute for Fiscal Studies to explore the ramifications.
Google has been in court for a trial brought by the US government.</description></item><item><title>End of the UK-China 'Golden Era'?: George Osborne Interview | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510100/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 21:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Questions continue following the arrest of a parliamentary researcher on suspicion of spying for China. The man, who has not been charged, has today insisted that he is ‘completely innocent’.
We are joined by George Osborne to discuss how the government should engage with Beijing. The former chancellor also gives his thoughts on Rishi Sunak and Keir Starmer’s prospects in the next general election.
Wilko will close all 400 of its shops after a rescue deal for the chain fell through.</description></item><item><title>A Spy in Parliament? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510101/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 12:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Researcher arrested amid claims he was spying for China. Chief political correspondent Henry Zeffman helps Laura and James Cook understand what information Westminster staffers get access to, as well as the UK government’s reaction to the news.
And, the case of escaped prisoner Daniel Khalife has put prisons at the top of the political agenda. Laura’s interviewed the justice secretary Alex Chalk. We reflect on his comments and on the question of how important prisons are to politicians and the electorate.</description></item><item><title>How the Police Caught Daniel Khalife | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510102/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 17:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510102/</guid><description>Podcast Description The ex-soldier was pulled off a bike by a plain clothes officer.
The BBC’s Dominic Casciani joins Laura in the studio and Chris, who’s dialling in from the G20 in India, to explain what techniques the police may have used to track down and capture the escaped prisoner, Daniel Khalife.
At least 1000 people have died following an earthquake in Morocco. Clara Bennett from Hampshire was on holiday in Marrakech with her family when the earthquake struck.</description></item><item><title>The Modi Bunch: India's G20 Ambitions | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510103/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510103/</guid><description>Podcast Description The world’s eyes are on Delhi as world leaders meet.
Chris Mason joins from India. Adam and Chris chat to the former head of the UK’s Foreign Office Sir Simon McDonald about India’s ambitions. And the government’s renewable power strategy has been dealt a blow after no new offshore wind project contracts were bought by developers at a recent auction. Emma Pinchbeck, CEO of Energy UK, the body that represents the energy industry, gives her view on what went wrong.</description></item><item><title>Re-New Horizons | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510104/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 19:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510104/</guid><description>Podcast Description The UK rejoins the EU's flagship scientific research scheme
What does it mean to the country? The UK’s top scientific advisor Dame Angela McLean is on, as well as Katya Adler, who tells us whether this could be a thaw in UK/EU relations.
And what does the case of the escaped Wandsworth prisoner tell us about the state of prisons? Former BBC home affairs correspondent Danny Shaw and former Head of the National Counter Terrorism Security Office Chris Phillips gives Adam the lowdown.</description></item><item><title>CrisisCast: Escaped prisoner, School Concrete and THAT kiss | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510105/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 19:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris and Adam speak about the escaped prisoner and the on-going issue of RAAC in schools. For more on the government’s handling of concrete, Adam is joined by hosts of the new BBC Sounds podcast When It Hits the Fan, crisis PR gurus David Yelland and Simon Lewis. They also chat about Spain’s World Cup Kiss with Spanish lawyer Miriam González Durántez. What does the story say about the country’s treatment of women?</description></item><item><title>Sewage Happens (Again) | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510106/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 19:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510106/</guid><description>Podcast Description A BBC investigation has revealed that three major water companies have been illegally spilling sewage on days when it’s not raining. Our correspondents Jonah Fisher and Emma Vardy bring us up to date.
Birmingham City Council has effectively declared bankruptcy. Alex Forsyth joins Adam to explain how their finances have got to this point.
You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.com/newscastcommunityhere
Today's Newscast was presented by Adam Fleming.</description></item><item><title>'F***ing good job' | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510107/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 20:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Politics is back in Westminster with an almighty bang.
A hot-mic moment lands the education secretary in hot water as Sir Keir Starmer shuffles his shadow cabinet. Adam and Chris dissect the day’s events.
Adam is also joined by former Labour foreign secretary, now chief executive of the International Rescue Committee, David Miliband to discuss Ukraine. You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.com/newscastcommunityhere
Today's Newscast was presented by Adam Fleming.</description></item><item><title>The Costs of Crumbly Concrete and THAT Piers Morgan Answer | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510108/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Day two of weekend Newscasts with Laura Kuenssberg and Paddy O’Connell. And brand new BBC political chief correspondent, Henry Zeffman, joins them from his sofa at home. Laura gives her take on her interview with the Chancellor, Jeremy Hunt, who says the government "won't take any risks" with children's safety following the crumbly concrete crisis. But how worried should the government be about the political heat?
And what did everyone make of Laura’s exchange with Piers Morgan?</description></item><item><title>Laura and Paddy's weekend Newscast is here! | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510109/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 16:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Talking crumbly concrete and Sunak’s in tray.
Welcome to the first ever weekend Newscast, with Laura Kuenssberg and Paddy O’Connell!
Today they hear from Kirstie Allsopp, from the TV show Location, Location, Location, about falling house prices. And they talk about the political impact of the concrete problem in schools. Also, a surprise guest pops into the studio for a very special Newscast outro. Btw, in case you've missed it, Laura and Paddy will be on Newscast on Saturday and Sundays, popping into the Newscast studio from their respective weekend TV and radio shows.</description></item><item><title>RAAC To School | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510110/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Potentially Dangerous RAAC Concrete found in schools just before the start of term.
Former teacher and a senior analyst for the Times Education Supplement, Gráinne Hallahan explains how widespread the problem is, and who’s picking up the bill. We also hear from a parent whose son’s school is affected.
And, Chris Giles from the Financial Times is on to talk about how a change to the way we measure growth could mean the UK’s economy could actually be doing better than we thought.</description></item><item><title>Mini Rishuffle | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510111/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 21:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ben Wallace resigns, Grant Shapps replaces him as defence secretary and Claire Coutinho takes over as energy secretary. Chris Mason and Laura Kuenssberg join Adam to chat about why Rishi Sunak has reassembled his top team and what else is in the Prime Minister’s in-tray for Parliament’s return. And filmmakers Matt Shea and Jamie Tahsin discuss how they investigated the influencer Andrew Tate for their new documentary ‘Andrew Tate: The Man Who Groomed The World?</description></item><item><title>Can You Force Criminals Into Court? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510112/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 20:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Offenders will be made to attend sentencing hearings under new laws.
Farah Naz, the aunt of Zara Aleena, who was killed in 2022, joins Adam to talk about her experience of the perpetrator not attending his sentencing. Former Old Bailey judge Wendy Joseph KC explains the difficulties of forcing criminals into the dock.
Foreign Secretary James Cleverly has said that the UK will not disengage with China as he travels to Beijing for talks.</description></item><item><title>Ground Control to Major Glitch | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510113/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 19:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510113/</guid><description>Podcast Description How did a technical issue lead to hundreds of cancelled flights?
An investigation has been launched over UK flight disruption that has left thousands of passengers stranded.
Former air traffic controller, Michele Robson and operating director at Liverpool John Lennon Airport, Paul Staples, join Sima Kotecha to help us understand the system that should keep planes taking off on time.
Newscasters Bex and Lydia also share their experience of cancelled flights.</description></item><item><title>Why are energy bills still so high? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510114/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 19:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Police forces in the UK have made welfare checks on every household that purchased poison from an online seller based in Canada. Over 200 people bought the poisonous substance from Kenneth Law, with 88 people subsequently dying, many of them young and still at university. James Beale and Will Roe, The Times journalists who tracked down Law, tell us how they posed as a potential buyer, eventually taking their findings to the Canadian authorities.</description></item><item><title>Educating Newscast | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510115/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 21:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510115/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s GCSE results day! Branwen Jeffreys is reporting on the picture across England, Wales and Northern Ireland, while headteachers Sir Anthony Seldon and Educating Yorkshire’s Jonny Mitchell tell Adam how their schools got on.
And documentary-maker Louis Theroux has made a speech about the future of TV in which he said the BBC has been ‘playing it safe’. Former creative director of BBC Alan Yentob and documentarian Molly Dineen discuss how documentaries are commissioned.</description></item><item><title>Prigozhin: Has Putin Struck Again? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510116/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 20:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510116/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boss of the Wagner mercenary group, Yevgeny Prigozhin, is presumed dead after a plane crash north of Moscow killed all on board.
Ukrainecast’s Vitaly Shevchenko and security correspondent, Frank Gardner, join Adam to go through what we know. Lou Osborn from the monitoring group All Eyes on Wagner also shares her expertise.
And, India has made history by landing a spacecraft near the south pole of the Moon for the first time.</description></item><item><title>Scotland’s Drug Problem | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510117/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 20:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Drugs deaths are falling in Scotland, but it continues to have the worst drug death rate in Europe. Scotland editor James Cook has been to Portugal, where they’ve decriminalised drugs for personal use. He’s on to talk about whether its working, and what the UK could learn, with Professor Fiona Measham, chair in criminology at the University of Liverpool.
And could we be on the verge of a national screening programme for prostate cancer?</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby Jailed For Life | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510118/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 17:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lucy Letby will spend the rest of her life in prison with no chance of parole. She refused to appear in court to hear her sentence or the statements of grief and loss from the families of the babies she murdered. Shaun Lintern, health editor at The Sunday Times, has spent years investigating the case and is in the studio.
And 5 Live commentator Vicki Sparks is back on, as well as former England player Karen Bardsley, talk us through what it was like commentating on the first World Cup final for England since 1966, and what’s next for the women’s game.</description></item><item><title>Gabby Logan on the Lionesses' World Cup chances | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510119/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 11:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510119/</guid><description>Podcast Description TV anchor and Newscaster Gabby Logan chats with Adam about who the Lionesses are up against, how Australia embraced the Beautiful Game, and her disappointment at Prince William’s no-show on Sunday. You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.com/newscastcommunityhere
Today's Newscast was hosted by Adam Fleming. It was made by Fiona Leach with Josh Jenkin. The technical producer was Emma Crowe. The editor is Jonathan Aspinwall.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial baby killer Lucy Letby | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510120/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 21:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nurse Lucy Letby has been found guilty of murdering seven babies and attempting to murder a further six. She deliberately injected babies in her care with air, force fed others milk and poisoned two with insulin. Her crimes make her the UK's most prolific child serial killer in modern times.
We hear from two journalists covering the case and the ten month long trial, the BBC’s Judith Mortiz and Caroline Cheetham, host of The Trial of Lucy Letby podcast.</description></item><item><title>Goodbye Parky | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510121/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 20:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510121/</guid><description>Podcast Description How did Michael Parkinson change British television? To mark his death at the age of 88, Adam assembles his own panel of legends for a chat on the imaginary sofas of the Newscast studio.
Parkinson producer Bea Ballard, former BBC One controller Lorraine Heggessey and presenter Dame Esther Rantzen lift the lid on behind-the-scenes moments and delve into the enduring power of Parky. We also catch up with the BBC’s education editor Branwen Jeffries at the end of a busy day taking questions from our Discord community on today’s A-Level, T-Level and BTEC results.</description></item><item><title>Three Lionesses on the Scoresheet | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510122/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 20:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510122/</guid><description>Podcast Description England reached the Women's World Cup final for the first time. The BBC's Vicki Sparks speaks to Adam from Sydney, straight after commentating on the match. And the BBC's Dominic Casciani talks us through DNA evidence and updates in Andrew Malkinson’s case after he had a wrongful conviction for rape overturned by the Court of Appeal last month. We also hear from Neal Keeling, chief reporter at the Manchester Evening News, who covered the original court case, who reflects on his reporting at the time of Andrew’s conviction.</description></item><item><title>The Newscast Security Briefing | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510123/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 19:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Three people have been arrested and are suspected of spying for Russia in the UK. It’s BBC correspondent Daniel De Simone’s exclusive, and he’s in the studio to give the background. And, information from 10,000 employees at the Police Service of Northern Ireland has been mistakenly released.
An ex PSNI officer is on to discuss why many are feeling unsafe as a result, as well as Jordan Dunbar, presenter of BBC podcast series Blood On The Dance Floor, which is about the killing of a Northern Irish police officer.</description></item><item><title>Wildfires in Hawaii | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510124/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 20:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510124/</guid><description>Podcast Description At least 96 people died in wildfires in Hawaii, making them the deadliest in the US in more than a century.
CBS reporter Jessica Kartalija is on the island of Maui and tells us about why the toll is so large, and the questions being asked in its aftermath.
What can be done to mitigate against wildfires and make towns and cities more resilient? We talk to Dr Kimiko Barrett, an adviser to the Biden administration on wildfires, and analyst at Headwaters Economics.</description></item><item><title>Some Strike It, Doc | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510125/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 18:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam’s joined by the BBC’s health reporter Jim Reed who lets him peek inside two junior doctors’ pay slips - a new trainee and an old hand. And we try to answer the question of whether they earn more or less than a barista. TV and theatreland’s James Graham talks England and penalties, from Southgate to Kane and the Lionesses. You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.</description></item><item><title>Hip-Hop Happy Birthday | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510126/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 21:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Broadcasting legend Trevor Nelson celebrates 50 years of hip-hop. He chats to Adam about the early days of hip-hop, his stand-out tracks and the impact the music has had on popular culture.
The BBC's Ben Chu and the FT’s Yuan Yang talk about the Chinese economy. What is going wrong and should the rest of the world be worried? 00:00 - Steps count
02:23 - Chinese economy 14:43 - Cost of living 16:16 - 50 years of hip-hop</description></item><item><title>Small Boats, Big Numbers | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510127/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 19:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Understanding the asylum system, and the benefits of 5000 steps.
Chief political correspondent Nick Eardley discusses the government’s latest immigration policy proposals and leading immigration barrister Colin Yeo explains how the legal system works for asylum seekers.
New research says that doing more than just 3967 steps a day can boost your health. Stats legend Sir David Speigelhalter explains what the numbers mean, and best-selling author of The Salt Path, Raynor Winn, tells Adam how walking has changed her life.</description></item><item><title>What the Hack? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510128/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 20:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Voters’ personal details stolen in cyber attack.
The Electoral Commission has revealed that they have been the subject of a ‘complex attack’ and hackers have accessed electoral registers. BBC cyber correspondent Joe Tidy and Mihaela Jembei from the Information Commissioner’s Office join Adam to discuss what we know so far, and who could be behind the breach.
Niger has closed its airspace as a military group continues their coup.</description></item><item><title>Disease X | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510129/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 20:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510129/</guid><description>Podcast Description How to stop the next pandemic
One of the UK&amp;rsquo;s most secretive research centres has been looking into Disease X. James Gallagher and Professor Dame Jenny Harries tell us more about how the centre hopes to safeguard the UK against the next pandemic.
The BBC&amp;rsquo;s Ellie Price explains what&amp;rsquo;s going on as the first asylum seekers board the Bibby Stockholm housing barge in Dorset.
After a tense penalty shootout, the Lionesses have made it to the quarter-finals!</description></item><item><title>Sea Change | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510130/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 19:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510130/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Edinburgh Fringe kicks off this week! Adam is checking out the vibe at the Festival with comedians John Robins and Rosie Holt.
Oceans reached their hottest ever recorded temperatures this week. BBC’s former climate analyst Roger Harrabin and Blue Planet cameraman Doug Allan join Adam to discuss the findings and share what they’ve seen when working around the world’s oceans. And… What do you call your TV remote?</description></item><item><title>All We Need Is Radio Rajar | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510131/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 21:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam gets out his hoofer-doofer (everyone else calls it a remote control) and starts flicking through the media landscape in search of answers for why no-one is watching or listening to the stuff they were just a few years ago.
Legendary disc jockeys Tony Blackburn and Shaun Keaveny give their take on the latest Rajar ratings which show a steep decline in listening to traditional networks like Radio 2 and Radio 4.</description></item><item><title>Argy Bargey | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510132/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 20:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510132/</guid><description>Podcast Description The row over the barge set to house hundreds of asylum seekers.
Adam is back in the studio and is joined by home affairs editor Mark Easton, as well as BBC Solent journalist Sophie Cridland to discuss when people might start to board the great big boat called Bibby Stockholm.
Rishi Sunak has said Nadine Dorries's constituents are not being properly represented. Alex Forsyth is on to talk about why, and why she’s not yet stood down like she said she would.</description></item><item><title>Boozenews | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510133/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 21:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alcohol tax up, house prices down, and food inflation slowing.
There’s loads of news about the changing price of various things, including alcohol, so The Newscast Arms is reopening.
At the bar with us is:
- Cost of living correspondent Coletta Smith, who explains how the government's alcohol tax changes will work.
- Boss of Iceland Richard Walker, who talks about how customers might experience slowing inflation.
- Property website Zoopla’s research and insights director Richard Donnell, who chats through why house prices are falling.</description></item><item><title>Oil Or Nothing? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510134/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 19:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rishi Sunak has defended granting 100 new North Sea oil and gas licences, and said the government will fund a carbon capture project in the north east of Scotland.
Scotland editor James Cook and climate analyst Sepi Golzari-Munro join Alex Forsyth to discuss what it could mean for the nation, and for the whole of the UK.
The BBC’s Good Morning Scotland presenter Martin Geissler’s interviewed the prime minster this morning.</description></item><item><title>Junk Food for Thought | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510135/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 19:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr Xand van Tulleken and Dr Dolly van Tulleken join Adam to chat about confusing portion sizes, ultra-processed foods and how the government could act to improve Britain’s diet. And BBC international editor Jeremy Bowen unpicks events in Israel after a tumultuous week which saw mass protests after a vote passed limiting the power of the country’s Supreme Court. You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.com/newscastcommunityhere</description></item><item><title>Energy Profits With Ed Miliband | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510136/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 20:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ed Miliband, shadow climate change secretary, joins Adam and Alex to talk about Labour’s position on windfall taxes and green energy.
And Justin Webb, host of Today and Americast, reflects on his emotional interview with Andy Malkinson, who was formally cleared on Wednesday after serving 17 years in prison after being wrongfully convicted of rape.
You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.com/newscastcommunityhere
Today's Newscast was presented by Adam Fleming.</description></item><item><title>Debunking Debanking | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510137/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 19:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are bank accounts being closed because of people's political views?
It’s a claim made by former UKIP leader Nigel Farage, who’s at the centre of the story that’s led to the resignation of NatWest CEO Dame Alison Rose.
Dame Alison admitted she had made a mistake in speaking to the BBC about Farage's relationship with the bank.
BBC global trade correspondent Dharshini David is on to talk though her tenure, and Today programme presenter Nick Robinson, who’s just interviewed Farage, also joins the conversation to put it into political context.</description></item><item><title>Global Warnings | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510138/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 19:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510138/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hottest June on record, and July heat near 'impossible' without climate change.
Four records have been broken so far this year relating to the world’s climate. To discuss each of them, and understand how they could be linked, Adam is joined by climate editor Justin Rowlatt, as well as climate scientist Ed Hawkins.
Tim Leunig, former economic adviser to the then-chancellor Rishi Sunak is also on to go through green solutions on the table and who should pay for them.</description></item><item><title>Greece's Wildfire Tragedy | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510139/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 18:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wildfires on several Greek islands have left many Brits worrying about how to get home, including BBC sports journalist Warren Muggleton, who was on holiday in Rhodes. He joins Adam and the BBC’s Azadeh Moshiri from Rhodes airport to discuss the impact of the fires on residents and tourists.
And Katya Adler is in Madrid unpacking Spain’s election results and reflecting on what they say about extreme politics in Europe.</description></item><item><title>By-electioncast | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510140/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 07:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Labour 1, Lib Dems 1, Conservatives 1. For this LIVE Newscast, Adam chats with some of our favourite BBC political correspondents and reporters, Alex Forsyth, Chris Mason, Nick Watt, Jeremy Vine, David Wallace Lockhart, Jenny Kumar and polling expert John Curtice to discuss the ins and outs of the overnight by-election results.
You can join our Newscast online community here: https://discord.gg/HKHAQAYKfK Today's Newscast was hosted by Adam Fleming. It was made by Alex Collins and Hayley Clarke.</description></item><item><title>AI: P45? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510141/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 19:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam is joined by BBC Click presenter Spencer Kelly and lawyer Tarun Tawakley to find out how the UK’s legislation on Artificial Intelligence in the employment sector stacks up, as well as how capable AI could be at replacing the human workforce.
And as the Women’s World Cup gets underway Down Under, Fox Sports commentator Jacqui Oatley reports on the first match of the tournament, the atmosphere in Sydney and how the Lionesses are looking.</description></item><item><title>Rate of the Nation | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510142/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 20:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510142/</guid><description>Podcast Description What the UK’s surprise inflation drop means for you…
PM presenter Evan Davis and Newsnight’s Ben Chu join Adam to chat about the slight drop in the UK’s inflation rate and what could be behind it, as well as all the different types of ‘flation’ we’ve heard about recently.
And Jean Lee, co-host of The Lazarus Heist podcast, discusses what we know so far about US soldier, Travis King, who is being held in North Korea after crossing the border during a tour of the Joint Security Area between North and South Korea.</description></item><item><title>McProblems | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510143/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 22:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fast food chain workers speak out over sexual abuse claims. Adam is joined by employment correspondent Zoe Conway and business reporter Noor Nanji who reveal how young people in particular are impacted. We hear from Christine, a former worker who tells us about her own experiences.
McDonald's said it would look into all reports of harassment, abuse or discrimination of any kind and that proven allegations would be met with "</description></item><item><title>Heat of the Moment | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510144/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 21:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510144/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why are temperatures soaring around the world?
Amol Rajan comes on Newscast to talk about his new job as host of University Challenge and gives us his thoughts on the BBC presenter scandal after a week of allegations in the media.
And the BBC’s Climate Editor, Justin Rowlatt, dials in from Spain to bring us the latest news from Europe’s heatwave. Eleni Myrivili, the United Nation’s Chief Heat Officer, joins him to discuss how societies must adapt to higher temperatures.</description></item><item><title>Hollywood Strikes Back | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510145/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 18:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Culture editor Katie Razzall joins Adam to explain why, for the first time since the 1960s, both the Screen Actors Guild and Writers Guild of America are on strike. They also speak to the actor Brian Cox.
There’s more movie news as ‘Barbenheimer’ fever takes over the red carpet. BBC Radio 1’s in-house film critic Ali Plumb is on hand to tell us what’s behind the hype.
And friends of the pod Robert Peston and Steph McGovern talk about their own new podcast ‘The Rest Is Money’.</description></item><item><title>Pay Attention | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510146/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rishi Sunak makes what he says is the final offer on pay rises for the public sector. But what’s on the table, and where’s the money coming from? Chris and Faisal join Adam to discuss the government’s offer and the response from the unions.
Also, Sofia Bettiza, BBC reporter in Rome, and Mike Berners-Lee, climate scientist, discuss the heatwaves engulfing southern Europe and parts of the US.
You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.</description></item><item><title>BBC Presenter Allegations: Huw Edwards Named | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510147/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 20:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510147/</guid><description>Podcast Description His wife has issued a statement on his behalf. Huw Edwards been named as the BBC presenter facing allegations over payments for sexually explicit images, in a statement issued on his behalf by his wife.
Media editor Katie Razzall and legal correspondent Dominic Casciani have been covering events since allegations were made in The Sun on Friday. They join Adam in the studio to talk about what’s in the statement.</description></item><item><title>BBC Presenter Allegations: New Claims | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510148/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510148/</guid><description>Podcast Description A young person has told BBC News they felt threatened by the presenter at the centre of a row over payment for sexually explicit photos. We go through the new details, and speak to Radio 4 presenter Sarah Montague, after she interviewed the man in charge of the BBC, director general Tim Davie. And Craig Oliver, former senior editor at BBC News, gives his verdict on how the corporation is covering itself.</description></item><item><title>BBC Presenter Allegations: The Lawyer's Letter | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510149/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 20:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510149/</guid><description>Podcast Description The lawyer for the young person disputes claims against BBC presenter, after a weekend of allegations, but The Sun stands by its story.
The BBC’s culture editor Katie Razzall and home and legal correspondent Dominic Casciani explain what we know, and what we still don’t know.
They explore the legal difficulties in covering this story, including why the BBC presenter can’t be named.
You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.</description></item><item><title>Just Stop Sport? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510150/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 20:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510150/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Newscast, Adam is joined by BBC cricket correspondent Jonathan Agnew and tennis commentator Katie Smith to talk about how the crowds reacted when Just Stop Oil stopped play at the Ashes and Wimbledon. And the managing director of Silverstone, hosting this weekend’s Formula 1, tells Adam that the British Grand Prix is pulling out the stops to prevent any attempts to invade the circuit. And drinks journalist Alice Lascelles from the Financial Times celebrates the this summer’s cocktail - the Hugo Spritz.</description></item><item><title>Angela Of The North | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510151/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510151/</guid><description>Podcast Description "I got death threats to my children"
Deputy Leader of the Labour Party, Angela Rayner, tells Newscast that she’s worried about her family’s safety.
Adam and Chris are joined by Angela Rayner to talk about her family's safety, her accent, snobbery, Mhairi Black, Taylor Swift and opera.
And there’s a new social media app in town called Threads. But can it dethrone Twitter as a go-to platform for journalists?</description></item><item><title>Alzheimer's: Am I At Risk? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510152/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 17:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Broadcaster Fiona Phillips reveals her diagnosis, and we’re joined by experts who help us understand the condition.
BBC medical editor Fergus Walsh, and professor of clinical neurology Paresh Malhotra explain how common it is, and the drugs that could help us cope with it in the future.
And Karen White, whose dad was diagnosed with the condition in 2017, tells us what it’s like to care for a person with it.</description></item><item><title>Dawn Of The Threads | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510153/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 20:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510153/</guid><description>Podcast Description Meta will launch a Twitter rival app on Thursday.
Adam is joined by Shiona McCallum, BBC tech reporter, and Vivian Schiller, the former head of news at Twitter, to talk about the effect they expect it to have on our online lives.
Chris Mason is also on with the latest as the police reopen an investigation into a &amp;lsquo;jingle and mingle&amp;rsquo; event at Conservative HQ while Covid restrictions were in place.</description></item><item><title>Jeremy Bowen on Israel's Military Operation | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510154/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 20:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510154/</guid><description>Podcast Description The BBC’s international editor Jeremy Bowen explains what’s behind what appears to be one of Israel’s biggest military operations in years in the occupied West Bank.
And Adam and Chris discuss how fuel retailers will be forced to publish live prices under a new scheme aimed at stopping them overcharging.
Plus - the prospect of Orkney Island Council considering an ‘Orkxit’, and what’s ‘new’ about the New Conservatives.</description></item><item><title>Paris is Burning | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510155/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 18:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam’s joined by Europe editor, Katya Adler, and Amina Kalache, a journalist from the Paris suburb of Nanterre where a 17 year old boy, Nahel M, was shot dead by a police officer while at the wheel of a car.
And Hugh Pym, the BBC’s health editor, tells Adam what’s in the Government’s long-awaited plan to plug the long-term gaps in NHS England’s staffing. You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.</description></item><item><title>Check Your Privileges Committee | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510156/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 20:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tory MPs are accused of interfering with the Partygate probe.
Adam and Chris are joined by shadow leader of the House of Commons Thangam Debbonaire to discuss what the latest report from the Privileges Committee could mean for freedom of speech. Plus, Conservative peer and former ministerial adviser Lord Finkelstein reveals how his parents’ experience of the Holocaust shaped his own world view. You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.</description></item><item><title>Thames They Are A-Changin' | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510157/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 20:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510157/</guid><description>Podcast Description Thames Water is in talks to secure extra funding as the government says it is ready to act in a worst case scenario if the company collapses. Adam is joined by Newsnight’s economics editor Ben Chu to explain why the company is in trouble, and how it could affect the public. And Chris Stark from the UK Climate Change Committee is in the studio to go through a new report by the body, which concludes that the UK is no longer a world leader.</description></item><item><title>Hancock's Three Hours | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510158/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 20:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510158/</guid><description>Podcast Description The ex-health secretary says pandemic planning was "completely wrong" in Covid inquiry evidence.
Health reporter Jim Reed, who spent three hours watching the testimony joins Adam, along with Emma Norris from the Institute for Government.
Also, a damning report into English and Welsh cricket says racism, sexism, classism and elitism are widespread in the game. West Indies cricket legend Michael Holding, and former professional cricketer now journalist, Isabelle Westbury, give their reaction.</description></item><item><title>Stephen Lawrence: The 6th Suspect | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510159/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 20:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510159/</guid><description>Podcast Description How the BBC uncovered a new suspect in the Stephen Lawrence murder.
Adam speaks to home affairs correspondent Daniel De Simone who has spent the last two years looking into the police investigation into the 1993 murder of Stephen Lawrence - the UK's most notorious racist killing. Daniel’s investigation has for the first time named a major suspect in the case.
We also hear from former BBC correspondent, Danny Shaw, who has reported on the story and the subsequent inquiry, investigations and trials over the last 30 years.</description></item><item><title>Ukrainecast: Is Russia on the verge of a coup? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510160/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 14:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510160/</guid><description>Podcast Description President Putin decries "betrayal" and "treason" after a dramatic challenge by the chief of the Wagner mercenary force, Yevgeny Prigozhin.
Russia editor Steve Rosenberg, security correspondent Frank Gardner and broadcaster Gabriel Gatehouse try to make sense of a moving and murky situation in Russia.
Today’s extra episode is presented by Victoria Derbyshire and Vitaliy Shevchenko.
The series producer is Tim Walklate. The senior news editor is Sam Bonham.</description></item><item><title>Titan Implosion: How Did It Happen? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510161/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 18:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510161/</guid><description>Podcast Description What could have caused the Titan disaster, and why has it attracted so much coverage? Science correspondent Jonathan Amos joins us to discuss.
Media and culture editor Katie Razzall and entertainment reporter Daniel Rosney are in Glastonbury for the start of the festival.
And there’s set to be another high pollen count weekend. Hay fever sufferer and diplomatic correspondent James Landale gets advice from GP Dr Sarah Jarvis.</description></item><item><title>Titan Sub: Five Dead | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510162/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 23:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510162/</guid><description>Podcast Description The US Coastguard has confirmed the “catastrophic implosion” of Titan submersible, and tributes have been paid to those on board who’ve died.
Adam talks to North America Correspondent Nomia Iqbal, who’s in Newfoundland where it set off from, as well as David Russell, who led the UK effort to rescue survivors from the sunken Russian submarine Kursk in the Barents Sea in 2000.
You can join our Newscast online community here: https://tinyurl.</description></item><item><title>Rate Rise: Martin Lewis on what it means | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510163/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 19:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510163/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Bank of England has raised interest rates to their highest level in nearly 15 years. Money expert Martin Lewis explains what it means for people with mortgages, renters and savers. He says increasing interest rates to tackle inflation is designed to hurt. Also, Education Secretary Gillian Keegan discusses what the high rate of inflation means for pay negotiations with teachers. Today's Newscast was presented by Adam Fleming. It was made by Clare Williamson.</description></item><item><title>The Missing Sub: A Sound of Hope | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510164/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510164/</guid><description>Podcast Description Noise from the ocean raises hopes of a rescue.
Adam is joined by BBC science correspondent Victoria Gill and Dr Joe MacInnis, who was among the first to dive down to the wreck of the Titanic and knows one of the five people on board well, to discuss the complex search to find the missing Titanic submersible.
Also, interest rates are expected to rise again after UK inflation remained much higher than expected for the fourth month in a row.</description></item><item><title>The Missing Titanic Sub | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510165/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 14:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rescue efforts are ongoing for the missing Titanic sub.
In this live Newscast, Adam is joined by three guests to help understand why a tourist submersible carrying five people went missing while diving to the wreck of the Titanic.
Simon Platts directed a BBC documentary episode about the Titanic sub last year. David Russell was a Royal Navy submariner in charge of the British response to the Kursk submarine disaster in 2000.</description></item><item><title>"Jingle and Mingle" | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510166/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 20:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510166/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tory aides were invited to a Covid party in December 2020. Adam and Chris are joined by Scotland editor James Cook to discuss that latest lockdown video, the future of Nicola Sturgeon and Sir Keir Starmer’s plans for North Sea Oil exploration.
Also, former Prime Minister David Cameron has appeared before the Covid Inquiry. Health reporter Jim Reed and Emma Norris from the Institute of Government discuss the coalition government’s approach to pandemic preparedness.</description></item><item><title>Rising to the Ashes | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510167/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 19:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510167/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s the first day of the Ashes - can Felix White from the Tailenders podcast on BBC Sounds convince Adam to embrace cricket?
A capsized fishing boat carrying migrants is feared to be one of Europe's worst migrant disasters. BBC reporter Sophia Bettiza and chief international correspondent Lyse Doucet discuss what’s happening in southern Greece. And Adam Kay, author of This Is Going to Hurt and a former junior doctor, chats about his new book - Undoctored - as well as this week’s junior doctor strikes in England.</description></item><item><title>The After Partygate Report | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510168/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 20:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Let's be blunt: it says he lied. Adam and Chris are joined by former Conservative advisor, Salma Shah, and the Guardian’s Political Editor, Pippa Crerar, to unpack the Partygate report and discuss what happens next.
Author and co-founder of the Women’s Equality Party, Catherine Mayer, whose partner Andy died at the beginning of the pandemic, returns to the podcast three years since she was last on.
Also, mathematician and Maths Appeal podcaster, Bobby Seagull, explains why Rishi Sunak has put up a load of ones and zeros on the door at Downing Street.</description></item><item><title>Privileged Information | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510169/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 13:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510169/</guid><description>Podcast Description What next for Boris Johnson after Privileges Committee says he deliberately misled the Commons?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Nottingham Vigil | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510170/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 18:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510170/</guid><description>Podcast Description "Look after each other”. BBC Midlands correspondent Navtej Johal talks to Adam about the tragic events in Nottingham, which have left three people dead. And Newsbeat reporter Charlotte Simpson reflects on the outpouring of grief from the student community at today’s vigil.
There was a tiny bit of good economic news today: the UK economy grew by 0.2%. But BBC Economics editor, Faisal Islam explains how inflation and interest rates continue to pose a clear and present danger.</description></item><item><title>Covid Inquiry: What could we learn? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510171/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 20:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510171/</guid><description>Podcast Description How will the three year inquiry into the pandemic unfold? Adam talks to More or Less presenter Tim Harford about how statistics influenced government decision making on the lockdown and vaccines. BBC Health Editor Hugh Pym was in the room for the first day of public hearings and tells us how families reacted at the beginning of the long-awaited proceedings. Adam also talks to Emma Norris, the Institute for Government’s expert on public inquiries to untangle what the inquiry hopes to achieve and what she took away from day one.</description></item><item><title>War Of The Words | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510172/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 21:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Boris Johnson accuses Rishi Sunak of “talking rubbish” as row erupts over honours. Chris Mason explains what it’s all about.
And there are more former leaders in the news… Europe editor Katya Adler reflects on the colourful political life of Silvio Berlusconi following his death at 86.
Scotland editor James Cook explains how the arrest of Nicola Sturgeon has been playing out politically.
Disinformation and social media correspondent Marianna Spring talks about her new podcast Marianna in Conspiracyland.</description></item><item><title>Boris Johnson Resigns | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510173/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 22:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510173/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ex-PM quits Parliament over Partygate report. Adam and Chris go through his dramatic resignation statement, and discuss the fallout to come, with the former PM’s former communications director, Will Walden.
Today's Newscast was presented by Adam Fleming. It was made by Chris Flynn. The senior news editor was Sam Bonham.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Johnson Does The Honours | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510174/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 19:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510174/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris Mason is back from the US to run us through who’s who on the resignation honours list, and discuss why former minister Nadine Dorries might have resigned with immediate effect as a Conservative MP.
BBC North America Editor Sarah Smith looks at the charges facing Donald Trump over the handling of classified documents.
And Private Eye Editor Ian Hislop tells us about this year’s winner of the Paul Foot Award for Investigative and Campaigning Journalism, David Conn.</description></item><item><title>Semiconducting Business | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510175/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 21:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510175/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rishi Sunak and Joe Biden take to the stage to announce a new economic partnership called the Atlantic Declaration. Chris Mason sends a message from Washington DC explaining what’s going on to Adam and today’s guest host Alex Forsyth, Presenter of ‘Any Questions?’ on Radio 4 and Political Correspondent for BBC News.
Andrew Neil, broadcaster and chair of The Spectator, is also on hand for his analysis of the deal, as well as Prince Harry’s court battle with Mirror Group Newspapers.</description></item><item><title>Prince Harry: Court of Opinions | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510176/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 20:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510176/</guid><description>Podcast Description Prince Harry is cross-examined for a second day in court. BBC media editor Katie Razzall and legal correspondent Dominic Casciani, outline the latest developments in his case against Mirror Group Newspapers. And Adam finds out how the story is going down across the world with New Zealand correspondent, Mei Heron.
Newscast’s Chris Mason is in Washington where he has been interviewing the Prime Minister, Rishi Sunak.
And with thousands fleeing southern Ukraine after a major dam burst, Ukrainecast’s Victoria Derbyshire, speaks to a Olga, a resident of Kherson whose city has been flooded.</description></item><item><title>The Man And The Mirror | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510177/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 20:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510177/</guid><description>Podcast Description A look inside the courtroom as Prince Harry gives evidence in phone hacking trial.
BBC media editor Katie Razzall and legal correspondent Dominic Casciani update Adam Fleming after watching Prince Harry’s first appearance in the witness box in the case against Mirror Group Newspapers.
Ukrainecast’s Vitaly Shevchenko analyses what might happen next after a major dam burst in Kherson, causing widespread flooding and evacuations.
And Adam catches up with Katya Adler, after we spotted her in the office.</description></item><item><title>Harry and the Chamber of Phone Hacking Secrets | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510178/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 20:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510178/</guid><description>Podcast Description Explaining Prince Harry’s court case against Mirror Group Newspapers
BBC media editor Katie Razzall and lawyer Mark Stephens talk Adam Fleming through the first day of the trial and discuss what Prince Harry will have to face when he takes the stand on Tuesday.
Chris Mason is back after parliamentary recess and he tells us what Rishi Sunak had to say about illegal migration when he was in Kent today.</description></item><item><title>Analysing the Phillip Schofield interview | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510179/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 19:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510179/</guid><description>Podcast Description What next after the BBC’s interview with the former This Morning presenter?
After Philip Schofield’s first interview since leaving ITV, Adam is joined by 5 Live's Nicky Campbell and Lorraine Heggessey, former controller of BBC One. They unpack what we learned and the potential impact on the TV industry. Union boss Mick Lynch comes in ahead of a weekend of disruption to answer questions from Newscasters.
Today’s Newscast was presented by Adam Fleming.</description></item><item><title>Phillip Schofield: The Interview | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510180/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 07:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here's the whole interview with the former This Morning presenter, with the BBC's Amol Rajan.
If you have been impacted suicide or any of the issues discussed in this podcast, please visit www.bbc.co.uk/actionline.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Still Haven't Found WhatsApp They're Looking For | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510181/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510181/</guid><description>Podcast Description The government will launch a legal challenge over the Covid inquiry’s demand for messages between Boris Johnson and his advisers during the pandemic. Adam speaks to one of the those advisers, Cleo Watson, who was the former prime minister’s deputy chief of staff, and is now the author of Whips.
Also, the BBC has interviewed controversial influencer Andrew Tate. We go through what he said, and the decision to interview him, with the BBC’s Marianna Spring and journalist Matt Shea who has made a documentary about Tate.</description></item><item><title>ITV To Review Schofield Affair | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510182/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510182/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lorraine Heggessey, former controller of BBC One and Head of Children's BBC talks to Adam about the future of Phillip Schofield and ITV, which has launched a review into its handling of a relationship between the presenter and his colleague.
We also talk about how governments are gearing up to regulate artificial intelligence with Joe Tidy, the BBC’s cyber correspondent. And Chris Mason has been pulled back from his holiday to discuss Boris Johnson’s WhatsApps.</description></item><item><title>Covid Enquiries | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510183/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 21:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510183/</guid><description>Podcast Description Number 10 deny a cover-up over Boris Johnson’s Covid Whatsapp messages. The Covid inquiry has demanded that the former PM hand over unredacted messages, diaries and notebooks by Thursday. Adam talks it all through with political correspondent Alex Forsyth and the Institute for Government’s Catherine Haddon, who also teaches ministers the do’s and don’ts of doing official business over WhatsApp.
Plus the BBC’s former China correspondent John Sudworth and producer Simon Maybin talk about their new Radio 4 series which explores Covid’s origin.</description></item><item><title>The One With Faisal and Rachel Reeves | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510184/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 19:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510184/</guid><description>Podcast Description The shadow chancellor’s American dream
Economics Editor Faisal Islam is in the hot seat. Labour’s Rachel Reeves has been in New York and Washington to talk about how one of the US administration’s flagship policies has inspired her own economic vision. America’s Inflation Reduction Act will boost the green economy and provide huge subsidies to consumers who buy American-made products. How might a similar scheme work in the UK?</description></item><item><title>Migration Nation | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510185/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 20:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510185/</guid><description>Podcast Description We chat to Shadow Home Secretary Yvette Cooper.
Adam is back from his holiday and is joined by Scotland Editor James Cook. They speak to the Shadow Home Secretary Yvette Cooper and Madeleine Sumption, director of the Migration Observatory at Oxford University. Chris Mason is also on a beach (!) in Great Yarmouth reporting on how migration numbers have gone down in parts of the country that voted for Brexit.</description></item><item><title>More or Less Inflation? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510186/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 19:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510186/</guid><description>Podcast Description Inflation has fallen, but will we really notice the difference?
Scotland editor James Cook steps in for Adam today. He talks to consumer champion Gemma Godfrey and Tim Harford, presenter of Radio 4’s More or Less, about today’s announcement that inflation has dropped below 10% for the first time since last August.
And it’s already been a very busy week in Westminster. Political editor Chris Mason talks through the latest developments.</description></item><item><title>Planet of the Vapes | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510187/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 20:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510187/</guid><description>Podcast Description How illegal vaping is threatening the health of school children.
BBC chief political correspondent Nick Eardley is hosting today's Newscast. He’s joined by health editor Hugh Pym and celebrity doctor Michael Mosley to talk through the problems around illegal vaping, both inside and outside the classroom.
Jim Gamble, who was heavily involved in the investigation into the disappearance of Madeleine McCann, dials in to discuss a possible development in the long-running case.</description></item><item><title>A Braverman Decision to Make | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510188/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 20:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510188/</guid><description>Podcast Description What will Rishi Sunak do with the home secretary?
Suella Braverman says she is "confident nothing untoward happened", but has refused to be drawn over whether she asked civil servants to arrange a one-to-one speed awareness course for her. Standing in for Adam today are Americast presenters Marianna Spring and Justin Webb, who are joined by Newsnight political editor Nick Watt and Sir Jonathan Jones, who was the government’s most senior lawyer, to take part in their very own ‘ministerial code awareness course’.</description></item><item><title>​​Dermot O’Leary &amp; Tina Daheley Do Newscast | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510189/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 18:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510189/</guid><description>Podcast Description Radio 2 duo get the latest on the G7 summit in Japan.
​​
​​Political correspondent Alex Forsyth and chief international correspondent Lyse Doucet are around to help, plus Chris Mason sends an audio postcard from Hiroshima. ​​
​​Plus media editor Katie Razzall reflects on a week of Harry and Meghan's New York paparazzi incident.
​​
​​Today’s Newscast was presented by Dermot O’Leary and Tina Daheley. It was made by Chris Flynn with Rufus Gray, Ben Carter, Joe Wallace and Madeleine Drury.</description></item><item><title>Sewage Happens | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510190/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 21:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510190/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lib Dem leader Ed Davey on sewage, social care, and election stunts.
Hot off the back of big local elections gains, the Liberal Democrat leader Ed Davey joins today’s Newscast hosts, BBC Presenter Tina Daheley and Scotland Editor James Cook. Chris Mason is in Japan with the Prime Minister for a G7 summit. And Dr Tamsin Edwards, a climate scientist at King’s College London, responds to news that global warming is set to break a key 1.</description></item><item><title>Stop! In the Name of Gove | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510191/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510191/</guid><description>Podcast Description Landlords could be banned from evicting tenants with no justification as part of a long-promised overhaul of the private rental sector in England.
Adam and Chris question Housing Secretary Michael Gove on the new law being tabled in Parliament on Wednesday, which would also give renters the legal right to request a pet in their home. And, he talks about reports of a rift in government over immigration plans, suggestions that the Brexit deal needs to be revised, and what those accents he did on BBC Breakfast last year were all about.</description></item><item><title>Farming Todaycast | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510192/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510192/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam opens Fleming's Farm and ploughs through trade deals, food security and labour shortages in the farming industry with BBC economics editor Faisal Islam and Anna Hill, presenter of Farming Today.
Love Island star and sheep farmer Will Young dials in to discuss what it's like working in the profession.
And, BBC gaming correspondent Steffan Powell is in the studio to explain Microsoft's Activision takeover, which was approved by the EU but vetoed by the UK.</description></item><item><title>God Save Loreen | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510193/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 21:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510193/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tory right-wingers are getting worried about the direction of Rishi Sunak’s government. Boris Johnson’s spin doctor at Number 10, Guto Harri, tells Adam and Chris why some still support the ex-PM and what it was like listening in to his calls with President Zelensky.
Radio 2’s Scott Mills spills the beans on how Eurovision went in Liverpool, plus MP Andrea Jenkyns sings us a special rendition of Sweden’s winning song.</description></item><item><title>Home Truths | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510194/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 18:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510194/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Newscast guide to housing. As the Bank of England issues warnings over the offer of no-deposit mortgages, we look at the state of the housing and rental market in the UK.
Housing correspondent for the i newspaper, Vicky Spratt, tells Adam what to expect from a major shakeup of renting rules.
Estate agent Megan Eighteen tells us how industry insiders are feeling.
And Newsnight economics editor Ben Chu explains the finances behind owning vs renting, and whether housing is actually a good long term investment.</description></item><item><title>TransPennine Eurovision Express | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510195/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 19:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510195/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam gets the train to Liverpool for Eurovision, as a rail service is nationalised.
Joining him at Lime Street station is Ben Clatworthy, transport correspondent for the Times, to discuss what the nationalisation of TransPennine Express means for passengers.
Also, with the Eurovision final imminent, the Eurovisioncast team drop in to give us a preview, and a brief on how the scoring works.
Today’s Newscast was presented by Adam Fleming.</description></item><item><title>Newsbeatcast | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510196/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 19:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510196/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s the BBC Radio 1 Newsbeat takeover with Pria Rai and Calum Leslie.
Chris Mason drops in to impart his advice on presenting Newscast, and to give an update on what’s been happening in parliament today.
Health correspondent James Gallagher talks through some of the big health stories, including calls for tighter regulation around aesthetic procedures like lip fillers. And two-time world boxing champion, Carl Frampton, opens up about mental health in sport and Northern Ireland, in his new documentary.</description></item><item><title>Coronation Beat | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510197/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 21:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510197/</guid><description>Podcast Description What do we know about the law behind the Coronation arrests?
Adam is joined by home editor Mark Easton and former chief constable of Northumbria Police Sue Sim to discuss what the arrest of six anti-monarchy protesters means for the police going forward.
Russia editor Steve Rosenberg is in Liverpool to be Newscast’s on the ground reporter as Eurovision gets under way.
And, investigative journalist Jamie Bartlett talks through his latest intriguing podcast.</description></item><item><title>Eurovisioncast Week Begins! | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510198/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510198/</guid><description>Podcast Description Live from Måns Zelmerlöw’s bed! Listen to Eurovisioncast everyday this week on BBC Sounds, for post show reviews, backstage insights, and big name interviews. Today's Eurovisioncast was hosted by Eurovision winner Måns Zelmerlöw, BBC Breakfast’s Nina Warhurst, BBC News Eurovision Reporter Daniel Rosney, and BBC Radio Merseyside's Ngunan Adamu. The podcast producer is Emma Forde. Sound design was by Nicky Edwards. The social media producer is Melanie Stewart-Smith. The podcast commissioning producer was Caroline McEvoy.</description></item><item><title>Coronationcast | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510199/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 20:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510199/</guid><description>Podcast Description Behind the scenes on this historic day. We go through the best bits, talking points and chat about what it was like behind the scenes as King Charles III and Queen Camilla are crowned at Westminster Abbey. Adam’s joined by the man who’s come to be Newscast’s voice of the "royal moment", Jim Naughtie, as well as royal correspondent Jonny Dymond.
5 Live’s Rachel Burden also joins us from the pub, and John Murray explains the difference between football and royal event commentary.</description></item><item><title>HRH, the PNS, and the WHO | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510200/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 18:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510200/</guid><description>Podcast Description We preview the King’s Coronation by looking at how it will compare with the past with the hosts of The Rest is History podcast Dominic Sandbrook and Tom Holland. The World Health Organisation (WHO) has declared that Covid-19 no longer represents a "global health emergency". Medical Editor for the BBC Fergus Walsh returns to the podcast to put the news into perspective.
And with most of England’s local election results in, deputy political editor Vicki Young helps us makes sense of what they mean for the country.</description></item><item><title>Live, Laugh, Local Elections | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510201/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 07:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510201/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is John Curtice on TV? Yes! And so is Newscast.
The results of England’s local elections have started coming in, so Newscast have woken up early (or stayed up all night) to talk about what it all means in a special live episode, broadcast on BBC iPlayer.
Adam is joined in the studio by Laura Kuenssberg and Chris Mason fresh from reporting on the results overnight. Professor Sir John Curtice tells us how he’s crunching the numbers, Alex Forsyth calls in from Salford and Vicki Young dials in from her breakfast table.</description></item><item><title>International Newscast | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510202/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 19:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510202/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s local election day in England and while people are voting broadcasters aren’t allowed to report details of campaigning or election issues… so we’re going global. By that we mean Turkey, Sudan, Moscow and the West Bank. The BBC’s Orla Guerin has interviewed Turkish opposition leader Kemal Kilicdaroglu ahead of presidential elections there, Lyse Doucet has been reporting on Sudan, and Jeremy Bowen has just got back from Jerusalem.</description></item><item><title>Scamscast | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510203/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 19:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510203/</guid><description>Podcast Description The government bans cold calls selling financial products. Adam takes a look at the announcement and the world of scams with Nick Stapleton from the BBC’s Scam Interceptors and cost of living correspondent Kevin Peachey. BBC deputy political editor Vicki Young looks ahead to Thursdays local elections in England.
And Lisa Takeuchi Cullen, from the Writers Guild of America, talks about the US shows going dark as writers step away from their keyboards for their first strike in 15 years.</description></item><item><title>NHStrike a Deal | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510204/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 20:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510204/</guid><description>Podcast Description More than a million NHS staff in England are to receive a 5% pay rise, after health unions backed a pay deal with the government. Adam and Chris are joined by health editor Hugh Pym, as well as Unison head of health Sara Gorton, who chairs the joint NHS union group.
And as the BBC launches an emergency pop-up radio service for Sudan, we hear from presenter of the first edition - Omar El Tayeb.</description></item><item><title>Richard Sharp Resignationcast | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510205/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 20:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510205/</guid><description>Podcast Description The BBC chairman Richard Sharp has resigned after a report found he broke transparency rules over his dealings with Boris Johnson ahead of his appointment. Adam is joined by culture and media editor, Katie Razzall, and whitehall editor at the Sunday Times, Gabriel Pogrund, who uncovered the story that prompted the report.
And we look at the present and future of artificial intelligence with AI expert Nina Schick, and Will Jackson creator of human-like robot AMECA.</description></item><item><title>Newscarpool Karaoke | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510206/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 21:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510206/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam pays homage to James Corden’s final carpool karaoke. Labour’s Shadow Foreign Secretary, David Lammy, joins him in the passenger seat and gives his take on the government’s response to the crisis in Sudan.
And, with local elections in England and Northern Ireland happening next week, Adam and Chris are joined by Professor Sir John Curtice to find out what the opinion polls suggest.
Today’s Newscast was presented by Adam Fleming and Chris Mason.</description></item><item><title>Bobbies and Jobbies | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510207/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 19:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510207/</guid><description>Podcast Description Has the government honoured its manifesto pledge and successfully recruited 20,000 police officers since 2019? Crime, justice and police commentator Danny Shaw joins Adam and Chris to fact check those claims. Also under the microscope is the government’s new target to reduce sewage overflows by 2050.
6-Music’s resident news hound Matt Everitt also drops by for a summary of all the music-related stories, including Ed Sheeran’s plagiarism court battle with the family of Marvin Gaye.</description></item><item><title>Escape from Khartoum | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510208/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 20:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510208/</guid><description>Podcast Description After the first evacuation planes carrying British nationals arrive in Cyprus, Adam hears one Newscaster’s first-hand account of fleeing war-torn Sudan, and speaks to Larry Madowo, CNN’s international correspondent, from Nairobi.
And the BBC’s media editor Katie Razzall is in the studio to tell us about three major court cases that Prince Harry has made against tabloid newspapers.
Today’s Newscast was presented by Adam Fleming. It was made by Tim Walklate with George Dabby, Cat Farnsworth and Miranda Slade.</description></item><item><title>CoroNation | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510209/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 20:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510209/</guid><description>Podcast Description How popular is the monarchy under King Charles? Adam is joined by BBC royal correspondent Nicholas Witchell and Radio 5 Live’s Nicky Campbell to talk through new polling into the public mood ahead of the King's coronation.
And political editor Chris Mason and former head of the Foreign Office, Sir Simon Fraser, discuss the government’s options, with thousands of British citizens trapped in Sudan. Today’s Newscast was presented by Adam Fleming.</description></item><item><title>Raab Resignationcast | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510210/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 18:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510210/</guid><description>Podcast Description Deputy Prime Minister Dominic Raab has resigned from the government after a report upheld bullying allegations against him. Adam is joined by Sima Kotecha, Newsnight’s UK Editor, Deputy Political Editor Vicki Young, and Lord Gavin Barwell, Theresa May’s former chief of staff.
Today’s Newscast was presented by Adam Fleming. It was made by Chris Flynn with Rufus Gray and Cordelia Hemming. The technical producer was Michael Regaard. The senior news editor was Sam Bonham.</description></item><item><title>Raabullying Probe Delay | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510211/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 20:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510211/</guid><description>Podcast Description Westminster waits for report into Dominic Raab’s behaviour
The Prime Minister Rishi Sunak is considering the much anticipated report into alleged bullying by the Justice Secretary and Deputy Prime Minister, Dominic Raab. Adam and Chris talk about what to expect and are joined by Sir Alex Allan, who was the government’s independent adviser on ministerial interests from 2011-2020.
Adam catches up with Lauren Mahon and Steve Bland from the You, Me and the Big C podcast.</description></item><item><title>The Most Expensive Thing Since Sliced Bread | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510212/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 20:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510212/</guid><description>Podcast Description With inflation still high, when will food prices start to fall?
Adam talks to business editor Simon Jack to make sense of today’s numbers and why things like bread and cereal cost so much. Also, the BBC’s Sarah Smith and Jeremy Barr from the Washington Post discuss Fox News’ settlement over a defamation case with the voting machine company, Dominion, for $787.5m.
And Sophie Raworth explains what it’s like doing ultra marathons, after one recent runner had her medal taken away for driving some of the route.</description></item><item><title>More SNProblems | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510213/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 20:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510213/</guid><description>Podcast Description The SNP treasurer Colin Beattie who was arrested by police investigating the party's finances has been released without charge pending further investigation.
To untangle what this all means for the party and its new leader, Adam is joined by Scotland editor, James Cook, and chief political correspondent, Nick Eardley.
Also, after two major sport events are disrupted by protesters, former captain of the Wales women’s football team, Laura McAllister, and sociology professor, Dr Graeme Hayes, assess how effective protests can be in the sporting arena.</description></item><item><title>Rishinometry | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510214/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 20:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510214/</guid><description>Podcast Description Prime Minister Rishi Sunak is being investigated by Parliament's standards watchdog over a possible failure to declare an interest. Adam is joined by Chris to examine what it could mean.
Also, as the Prime Minister sets up a review to tackle what he calls an “anti-maths mindset” in England, Countdown co-presenter Rachel Riley is in the studio to assess whether his plans add up.
And BBC World Service presenter James Copnall gives us the latest on the violence which has rocked Sudan’s capital Khartoum.</description></item><item><title>Leaky Friday | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510215/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 19:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510215/</guid><description>Podcast Description Everything you need to know about how confidential US intelligence was leaked, and who’s accused of being behind them.
Adam is joined by security correspondent Gordon Corera, journalist for the BBC’s newly created forensic hub, Shayan Sardarizadeh, and North America correspondent Anthony Zurcher.
We also have the latest on the current junior doctors strike.
And, author and comedian David Baddiel speaks to Adam about why he doesn’t believe in a god and his theories as to why some do.</description></item><item><title>Mooscast | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510216/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 19:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510216/</guid><description>Podcast Description President Joe Biden explores his family roots on his tour of Ireland and addresses parliament in Dublin. Ireland correspondent Emma Vardy and Economic correspondent Faisal Islam chat through the significance of the visit.
After North Korea’s latest missile test sparked alarm in Japan, Jean Lee, former Associated Press bureau chief in Pyongyang and host of the BBC’s Lazarus Heist podcast, gives her take on what message the leader Kim Jong Un is trying to send.</description></item><item><title>A Musk Listen | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510217/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 21:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510217/</guid><description>Podcast Description Elon Musk speaks to the BBC about Twitter, tackling hate speech and not posting after 3am.
Adam is joined by the BBC’s technology reporter, James Clayton, and culture and media editor, Katie Razzall, to dissect the hour long interview. And with the news that 248 phones are stolen in London a day, Adam speaks with consumer champion and watchdog presenter, Matt Allwright, to discuss why the police don’t investigate these crimes and what people can do to protect their devices.</description></item><item><title>Biden in Belfast | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510218/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 21:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510218/</guid><description>Podcast Description President Biden visits Belfast to mark anniversary of the Good Friday Agreement
Adam and Chris discuss what&amp;rsquo;s on the agenda during Biden&amp;rsquo;s trip, whether his meeting with Sunak is a &amp;ldquo;bilat&amp;rdquo; or just a coffee, and what it all means for the Special Relationship.
They also speak with Mark Lucas, who used to make party political broadcasts for New Labour, about Keir Starmer&amp;rsquo;s new ads which attack Rishi Sunak and his wife.</description></item><item><title>He Said Xi Said | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510219/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 20:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510219/</guid><description>Podcast Description As French leader Emmanuel Macron meets his Chinese counterpart Xi Jinping in Beijing, chief international correspondent Lyse Doucet and diplomatic correspondent James Landale join Adam to talk about China’s growing presence as a mediator in world conflicts.
Sainsbury's has defended its new minced beef packaging after some shoppers complained it turned the meat to mush. Carbon-footprint expert Professor Mike Berners-Lee explains whether the low-plastic packaging could help in the climate crisis.</description></item><item><title>SNPolice Investigation | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510220/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510220/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former SNP boss - and husband of Nicola Sturgeon, the former Scottish first minister - Peter Murrell has been released without charge, pending further investigation into party finances. Scotland Editor James Cook explains the background to his arrest and what this means for the party.
Jeff Leigh-Jones, who escaped a modern day cult, joins Catrin Nye, the BBC Journalist whose new documentary uncovered how the organisation operated.
Today’s Newscast was presented Adam Fleming.</description></item><item><title>Living With Parkinson's | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510221/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 20:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510221/</guid><description>Podcast Description What’s it like to have the condition?
Former BBC North America editor Mark Mardell joins Sima Kotecha and Marianna Spring to talk about living with Parkinson’s disease. Sima’s dad Suresh, who also has the condition, joins too.
Mark is also on hand to explain the significance of Donald Trump’s historic court hearing in New York as he becomes the first former US president to face criminal charges.
Today’s Newscast was presented by Marianna Spring and Sima Kotecha.</description></item><item><title>A Striking Comeback | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510222/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 21:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510222/</guid><description>Podcast Description More teacher strikes are planned... But are there others coming too? Alan Jones, industrial correspondent for PA, joins Marianna Spring and Sima Kotecha (who are sitting in for Adam) for a strike action audit.
After a pro-war blogger was killed in a blast at a St Petersburg cafe, the BBC’s Will Vernon is in Moscow to help make sense of what’s happening in Russia.
Also, Sima’s mum and Marianna’s dad celebrate 50 years since the first mobile phone call.</description></item><item><title>Arresting Developments | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510223/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 16:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510223/</guid><description>Podcast Description The BBC's disinformation and social media correspondent Marianna Spring joins Adam to talk about how the world is reacting to Donald Trump's indictment online, as well as how US voters are experiencing the news on their feeds.
The UK government says it has struck the &amp;ldquo;biggest trade deal since Brexit&amp;rdquo;, but how big are the benefits for the economy? The BBC&amp;rsquo;s trade and economics correspondent Dharshini David gives her analysis.</description></item><item><title>Slipping through the Net Zero? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510224/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510224/</guid><description>Podcast Description Government launches its new UK climate plan, but does it go far enough? Adam and Chris are joined by Labour’s Liz Kendall, the shadow minister for health and social care, and Emma Pinchbeck, boss of Energy UK, the energy industry’s trade association.
And the government’s former health tsar and co-founder of Leon Restaurants, Henry Dimbleby, outlines the impact he thinks obesity is having on the NHS.
Today’s Newscast was presented by Adam Fleming and Chris Mason and was made by Cordelia Hemming with Rufus Gray.</description></item><item><title>Government Barges In | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510225/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 19:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510225/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ministers are exploring using ferries to house migrants. Adam and Chris delve into plans announced today that would see illegal immigrants housed at RAF bases - as well as suggestions they could be moved onto barges - and ask why some Conservative MPs aren’t happy.
Twitter boss Elon Musk calls for a pause to the development of Artificial Intelligence, saying it poses a threat to humanity. Adam chats with the BBC’s technology editor, Zoe Kleinman, and techy, Ivana Bartoletti, about whether we’re ready for the new tech.</description></item><item><title>Female Journalists Talk About Their Online Trolls | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510226/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 18:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510226/</guid><description>Podcast Description The BBC's Laura Kuenssberg, Sima Kotecha and Marianna Spring in conversation. In a special edition of Newscast, some of the women who regularly report on this podcast reveal the online abuse they get as female journalists. Laura, Sima and Marianna discuss the shocking messages they've been sent, how they deal with them, and whether speaking out about trolls makes any difference. Also, Dr Julie Posetti, from the International Centre for Journalists, explains what can be done to tackle this issue.</description></item><item><title>Succession In Scotland | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510227/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 20:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510227/</guid><description>Podcast Description Humza Yousaf has been elected to follow Nicola Sturgeon as the next SNP leader and will soon become Scotland’s first minister. BBC Scotland editor James Cook, BBC special correspondent James Naughtie, and Newsnight presenter Kirsty Wark talk about what it means for the future of Scotland and the rest of the UK.
Israel’s Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu has delayed controversial plans to reform the judicial system after mass protests.</description></item><item><title>Aggrieve La France | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510228/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 20:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510228/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam is joined from Paris by Catherine Norris-Trent, senior correspondent for France 24, to explain what’s behind some of the worst days of violence since demonstrations began in January.
Plus, Alastair Campbell, Tony Blair’s former press secretary, and the BBC’s security correspondent Gordon Corera, reflect on Iraq’s legacy in the week of the 20th anniversary of the war. Today’s Newscast was made by Chris Flynn with Madeleine Drury, Miranda Slade, and Cordelia Hemming.</description></item><item><title>A TikToking off in Parliament | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510229/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 21:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510229/</guid><description>Podcast Description The social media app has been banned from all parliamentary phones. Adam and Chris are joined by the former conservative leader, Sir Iain Duncan Smith, who explains why he thinks TikTok should be banned on ministers' personal phones. He also gives his reaction to Boris Johnson's evidence to MPs on Partygate.
Tony Schumacher, Screen Writer for the Bafta nominated TV police drama ‘The Responder’, shares how the series was inspired by his own experiences as a police officer.</description></item><item><title>Partygate: The Afterparty | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510230/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 19:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510230/</guid><description>Podcast Description The BBC's Adam Fleming, Chris Mason and Vicki Young are joined by Will Walden, Boris Johnson's former Director of Communications, to dissect the key moments of Boris Johnson’s grilling by MPs over the Partygate scandal. They also discuss the day’s other big Westminster stories.
Today’s Newscast was presented by Adam Fleming and Chris Mason. It was made by Sam Bonham with Cordelia Hemming and Cat Farnsworth.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Johnson Defence | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510231/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510231/</guid><description>Podcast Description What can we expect from Boris Johnson’s Partygate grilling on Wednesday?
Adam is joined by Chris Mason and the Guardian’s Pippa Crerar to look ahead to the former prime minister’s much-anticipated appearance before the Commons Privileges Committee.
And Baroness Casey is in the studio to go over the details of her damning report which says that the Metropolitan Police force is "institutionally racist, misogynist and homophobic". Today’s Newscast was presented by Adam Fleming and made by Tim Walklate with Cordelia Hemming, Chris Flynn and Cat Farnsworth.</description></item><item><title>The DUP, IPCC, RMT and Xi | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510232/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 20:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510232/</guid><description>Podcast Description A legion of experts join Adam to make sense of a busy news day. Chris Mason outlines the DUP’s decision to vote against the government’s Brexit plans and the move by RMT members at Network Rail to accept a pay deal.
World affairs editor John Simpson dials in with leading Russia expert Angela Stent to chew over Chinese President Xi Jinping’s visit to Moscow to meet Vladimir Putin.</description></item><item><title>Challenge Peston | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510233/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 18:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510233/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a week that’s featured the PM’s visit to the US, a Budget and a potential resolution to the NHS pay dispute, Adam is joined by ITV’s Robert Peston to unpack a busy few days in politics.
Legendary 90s TV show Challenge Anneka is back - the programme’s eponymous host tells us what to expect.
And the BBC’s James Gallagher and CBBC’s Dr Xand Van Tulleken discuss the latest advice from a new study into peanut allergies.</description></item><item><title>Striking a Deal? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510234/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 22:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510234/</guid><description>Podcast Description A 5% pay rise has been offered to NHS staff in England, including ambulance workers and nurses. Is it enough to stop the strikes? Adam and Chris get reaction from Shadow Chancellor, Rachel Reeves, who also gives her take on this week’s budget.
Sara Gorton, Head of Health at Unison, has been negotiating with government on the NHS strike. She explains why they’re recommending their members back the deal.</description></item><item><title>The Hunt for Growth | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510235/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 21:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510235/</guid><description>Podcast Description What does the Spring Budget mean for the economy, and for you?
Adam and Chris dissect Jeremy Hunt’s Budget with Claer Barrett, Financial Times columnist and host of the FT’s Money Clinic Podcast, and former Conservative chancellor Ken Clarke.
Today’s episode was presented by Adam Fleming and made by Tim Walklate with Adam Chowdhury and Madeleine Drury. The technical producers were Mike Regaard and Andrew Mills. The senior news editor is Sam Bonham.</description></item><item><title>Budget Newscast | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510236/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 20:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510236/</guid><description>Podcast Description Evan Davis on how tomorrow’s budget could affect your pension pot, energy bills, and childcare costs.
And, BBC Scotland’s Kaye Adams joins Scotland editor James Cook to profile the people who could be Scotland’s next first minister.
Today’s Newscast was presented by Adam Fleming and made by Chris Flynn with Adam Chowdhury, Cordelia Hemming and Miranda Slade. The technical producer was Emma Crowe. The senior news editor was Sam Bonham.</description></item><item><title>Newscast Everywhere All At Once | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510237/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 21:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510237/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lineker's BBC return, the junior doctors strike and the big winner at the Oscars.
In a jam-packed edition of Newscast, Adam is joined by the BBC’s Katie Razzall from LA, who unpacks the latest in the row over impartiality and gives her take on the film that won big at the Oscars.
Chris Mason is in San Diego following Rishi Sunak on his visit to finalise a defence agreement with US President Joe Biden.</description></item><item><title>Lineker Benched | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510238/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 20:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510238/</guid><description>Podcast Description After Gary Lineker is pulled from presenting Match of the Day over comments he made criticising the government's new asylum policy, media editor Katie Razzall tells Adam what it means for the broadcaster.
Chris gives political reaction, fresh from his trip to Paris where there were meetings between the prime minister and President Macron.
And broadcaster Andrew Neil tells us why he thinks the BBC’s got it right.</description></item><item><title>Sex Education | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510239/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510239/</guid><description>Podcast Description Education Secretary Gillian Keegan is questioned on what’s being done to try to avoid planned teacher strikes and whether she thinks we’re getting sex education right in the UK.
Chris and Adam also explain why Rishi Sunak is heading to France to talk about the government's small boats policy, before hearing alternatives to it from Green Party MP Caroline Lucas.
Today's episode was presented by Adam Fleming and Chris Mason and was made by Chris Flynn with Daniel Wittenberg.</description></item><item><title>BBC Tackles Gary Lineker | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510240/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 20:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510240/</guid><description>Podcast Description What should the BBC do about the Match of the Day host, after criticism of his tweets on the government's asylum policy?
Former director of BBC News, Richard Sambrook, reveals how he would handle the comments, from an impartiality point of view, and media editor, Katie Razzall, discusses what the future could look like for the Match of the Day presenter.
Also, Adam speaks to Nasa's Dr Nicola Fox about her meteoric rise to become the first woman as its head of science.</description></item><item><title>Ticket to Merseyside | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510241/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 20:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510241/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tickets to the Eurovision Song Contest in Liverpool this May sold out in 90 minutes after huge demand. Find out if Adam managed to get his hands on one.
Also, Chris Mason and the BBC's Dominic Casciani try to make sense of new legislation to try to stop people crossing the Channel on small boats.
And Tom Bateman joins us from Jerusalem to explain why hundreds of thousands of people have been protesting against judicial reforms in Israel.</description></item><item><title>Elon Musk Have His Say | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510242/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 21:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510242/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can Twitter protect its users from trolling? The BBC’s disinformation &amp;amp; social media correspondent, Marianna Spring, is in the studio to tell us about her Panorama investigation into the platform and her Twitter exchange with Elon Musk..
Also, Adam and Chris are joined by the former head of the Home Civil Service, Lord Kerslake, to discuss the controversy surrounding Sue Gray’s potential new role, the government’s migrant plans, and why Blackberry messaging was safer than Whatsapps.</description></item><item><title>Partygate People | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510243/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510243/</guid><description>Podcast Description MPs from the privileges committee have said Boris Johnson may have misled Parliament multiple times over Partygate - but the former PM insists he will be vindicated by their report.
Meanwhile, Tory MPs say they’re angry that Sue Gray, who lead the Partygate probe, has been offered a job by the Labour party. Alex Forsyth explains why these two stories matter.
Nicola Adams, two-time Olympic boxing champion and backer of the ‘This Girl Can’ campaign, joins Adam and the BBC’s Natalie Pirks to examine why millions of women are turned off sport.</description></item><item><title>Isabel Oakeshott Has Entered The Chat | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510244/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 22:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510244/</guid><description>Podcast Description Behind the scenes on the Covid WhatsApp leak… Chris Mason speaks to Isabel Oakeshott, the journalist who leaked messages that Matt Hancock sent during Covid. The Former Health Secretary has called it a betrayal.
We're also joined by the BBC's Judith Moritz to discuss the findings and failings of MI5, after an inquiry into the Manchester Arena bombing in 2017 finally concludes.
And, as families across the UK celebrate World Book Day, the author Michael Rosen jumps in the studio to share his thoughts on altering language in books and his first-hand experience of Covid.</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus Newscast: Hancock’s Whatsapps | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510245/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 21:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510245/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former Health Secretary Matt Hancock disputes claim he rejected care home Covid advice.
Adam is joined by Chris and BBC media editor Katie Razzall to discuss Matt Hancock’s Whatsapp messages at the height of the pandemic, which were leaked to the Daily Telegraph.
Also, Justin Webb from Americast and the BBC’s Victoria Gill examine FBI Director Christopher Wray’s comments that Covid-19 most likely originated in a Chinese government-controlled lab.</description></item><item><title>The Gathering Stormont | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510246/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 21:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510246/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can Rishi Sunak sell his deal to Northern Ireland’s political parties?
Adam is joined by Mark Carruthers, BBC Northern Ireland’s politics presenter, to trace the Prime Minister’s trip across the region. Meanwhile in Westminster, Chris has the latest on Rishi Sunak’s meeting with the 1922 Committee of Tory backbenchers. Plus, The Independent’s flight-free travel editor Helen Coffey explains how the aviation industry’s climate ambitions have had their wings clipped in a new report.</description></item><item><title>Brexitcast: Win-Windsor? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510247/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 22:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510247/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s a new trade deal for Northern Ireland with the EU. It’s goodbye Northern Ireland Protocol, and hello Windsor Framework – but it’s unclear whether the Democratic Unionist Party will back the agreement and bring back the power-sharing government.
PM Rishi Sunak and EU chief Ursula von der Leyen were all warm smiles in Windsor when they pitched their plan to use “green lanes” and “red lanes” to cut customs checks and allow Northern Ireland a say in new EU rules.</description></item><item><title>Brexitcast: Another done deal? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510248/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 23:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510248/</guid><description>Podcast Description Downing Street says they are having "final talks" with the EU on a new Brexit deal for Northern Ireland. Adam, Chris and Katya get together for a Sunday night Brexitcast! Today's episode was presented by Adam Fleming. The technical producer was Holly Palmer. The senior news editor was Sam Bonham.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ukrainecast: 12 months on | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510249/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 20:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510249/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ukrainians gather for a special broadcast at the BBC Radio Theatre, hosted by Ukrainecast and Newsnight. They share their fears for families at home, feelings of guilt about escaping to safety and the need for justice. Host Victoria Derbyshire, BBC Monitoring’s Russia editor Vitaly Shevchenko and Newsnight’s diplomatic editor Mark Urban reflect on the past year and discuss what the next 12 months could bring. This episode was made by Ben Carter, Fiona Leach, Natasha Fernandes, Luke Radcliff, Arsenii Sokolov and Clare Williamson.</description></item><item><title>Five Missions Impossible? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510250/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 22:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510250/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Labour leader sets out his big plan. Shadow Health Secretary, Wes Streeting, says it’s part of a ten year vision!
And Tom Tugendhat, Conservative minister for security, says the government is already training Ukrainian pilots to fly British fighter jets, as Ukraine prepares to mark one year since the Russian invasion.
Today's episode was presented by Adam Fleming and Victoria Derbyshire and was made by Cordelia Hemming with Pearse Lynch and Danny Wittenberg.</description></item><item><title>Salad Barred | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510251/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 20:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510251/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why is there a shortage of fruit and vegetables in the UK?
After Tesco became the latest supermarket to introduce limits on sales of certain fruit and vegetables due to shortages of fresh produce, Adam is joined by the BBC’s Faisal Islam and Farming Today’s Anna Hill to discuss what this all means for our shopping trolleys.
We hear from JOsh Baker, host of The Shamima Begum Story, Series 2 of the investigative podcast I’m Not a Monster, after her bid to regain UK citizenship was rejected.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine War: From Our Own Correspondents | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510252/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510252/</guid><description>Podcast Description The BBC’s foreign reporters assemble and discuss the war. Adam is joined by Lyse Doucet and Jeremy Bowen in Kyiv, John Simpson in Lviv, Sarah Smith in Warsaw and Steve Rosenberg in Moscow, following two high-stakes speeches from Presidents Putin and Biden.
Clive Myrie also "dials up" from Kharkiv to give us the latest from the east of the country.
Today's episode was presented by Adam Fleming and was made by Tim Walklate with Danny Wittenberg, Pearse Lynch and Maddie Drury.</description></item><item><title>Nicola Bulley: "We Can Let You Rest Now" | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510253/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 21:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510253/</guid><description>Podcast Description A body found in a Lancashire river on Sunday was that of missing mother-of-two Nicola Bulley, police have said, before reading a family statement which criticised media intrusion.
Adam speaks to the BBC’s Judith Moritz, who is in St Michael's on Wyre, as well as a former detective superintendent - Julie Mackay.
And we discuss the heavily criticised changes to Roald Dahl’s books with culture editor Katy Razzall and children’s author Philip Ardagh.</description></item><item><title>Sturgeon’s Succession, with Brian Cox | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510254/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 21:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510254/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nikki Fox and Emma Tracey, who are standing in for Adam, speak to actor and SNP member Brian Cox about Nicola Sturgeon’s departure, and who he would like to see in charge of the party.
And as Rishi Sunak travels to Belfast to discuss the Northern Ireland Protocol, they get the latest on developments from Ireland correspondent Chris Page.
More NHS strikes have been announced for March. Baron Victor Adebowale, Chair of the NHS Confederation, talks about how they could be resolved.</description></item><item><title>Plenty More Fish in the SNP | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510255/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 20:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510255/</guid><description>Podcast Description Scotland is looking for a new first minister. As the race to replace Nicola Sturgeon starts to take shape, Newsnight’s Kirsty Wark, “fresh” off the sleeper train from Edinburgh, and Scottish Labour leader, Anas Sarwar, share their views on what’s next for Scottish politics and independence.
The family of missing Nicola Bulley say speculation about her private life needs to stop. A policing expert, and a press officer who worked on the Madeleine McCann case, explain why Lancashire Police revealed details about her personal struggles.</description></item><item><title>Resignationcast: Nicola Sturgeon | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510256/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510256/</guid><description>Podcast Description Scotland’s first minister says she will resign.
Chris Mason (who was on a train en route to Edinburgh) gives his instant reaction to the decision... And we get more analysis about Sturgeon's resignation speech, her legacy and the future of Scottish and UK politics with the BBC’s Alex Forsyth (in Westminster), Scotland editor James Cook (in Edinburgh) and special correspondent Jim Naughtie (in the studio with Adam in London).</description></item><item><title>Council Culture | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510257/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 21:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510257/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why are so many councils in England raising taxes? Adam and the BBC’s Alex Forsyth are joined by Conservative councillor David Shelvey and Labour councillor Bev Craig to look at the pressures on local councils.
And Bake Off judge, Prue Leith, and her son, Conservative MP Danny Kruger, debate assisted dying ahead of a documentary they've made together.
Today's episode was presented by Adam Fleming and was made by Tim Walklate with Cordelia Hemming, Chris Flynn and Miranda Slade.</description></item><item><title>Born in the UFO | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510258/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 21:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510258/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why is the White House shooting down flying objects? Adam is joined by the BBC’s security correspondent, Gordon Corera, and North America correspondent, Sarah Smith, to discuss the mystery that’s gripping America. After a weekend of showbiz news Radio 1 DJ, Jack Saunders, gives his take on the performances and pageantry at the Brits and the Super Bowl.
And one week on from the earthquakes that hit Turkey and Syria, we get an update from Lyse Doucet who is in Turkey.</description></item><item><title>The Struggle For Aid In Syria | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510259/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 20:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510259/</guid><description>Podcast Description The first aid deliveries has started to arrive in Syria after Monday’s deadly earthquakes.
Adam speaks to Syrian director, Waad Al-Kateab, who directed of the award winning documentary ‘For Sama’, and her husband Hamza Al-Kateab, a doctor and human rights activist, who say much more support is needed.
The UK has narrowly avoided a recession according to new statistics. Paul Johnson, director at the Institute for Fiscal Studies explains what that actually means for people’s daily lives.</description></item><item><title>The Earthquake Response | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510260/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 22:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510260/</guid><description>Podcast Description How are search and rescue teams saving people in Turkey and Syria?
The BBC's Anna Foster describes how the relief effort is playing out on the ground in one of the cities hardest hit by the earthquakes.
Baroness Amos, Labour member of the House of Lords, and former UN Under-Secretary-General for Humanitarian Affairs and Emergency Relief Coordinator, gives a bit of perspective on the situation in Turkey and Syria.</description></item><item><title>Zelensky's Flying Visit | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510261/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 21:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510261/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ukraine’s President makes a surprise visit to the UK.
We get reaction from one of the people who shared the stage with President Zelensky at Westminster Hall, Sir Lindsay Hoyle, the House of Commons speaker. Chris and security correspondent Frank Gardner are also on hand to chew over what this means in foreign policy terms.
And we discuss the latest on missing 45-year-old mother-of-two Nicola Bulley with Marianna Spring, disinformation and social media correspondent, and BBC reporter Nick Garnett.</description></item><item><title>“The Earthquake Orphan” | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510262/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 21:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510262/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rescuers are desperately searching for survivors under the rubble of buildings in southern Turkey and northern Syria after two huge earthquakes on Monday. Adam and the BBC’s Lyse Doucet discuss some of the stories of hope and loss in the aftermath of the quake. They speak to one man from Manchester who’s helping to get aid out to the affected areas.
Also, we get the latest on the mini-reshuffle with Chris and Alex Forsyth, host of the BBC’s Any Questions.</description></item><item><title>Major Earthquakes Hit Turkey and Syria | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510263/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 21:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510263/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rescue operations are under way across much of southern Turkey and northern Syria after huge earthquakes have left thousands dead.
Kaled Jarkas joins us from Gaziantep, the Turkish epicentre of the tremors, as well as BBC international editor Jeremy Bowen, who gives the overview from London.
And Spectator political editor Katy Balls speaks to Adam and Chris, after getting the first interview with Liz Truss since her resignation as PM.</description></item><item><title>Tinker, Tailor, Soldier, Balloon | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510264/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 20:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510264/</guid><description>Podcast Description The US Secretary of State Antony Blinken has postponed his trip to China after an alleged Chinese spy balloon flew across the state of Montana.
Adam speaks to BBC security correspondent Gordon Corera as well as Aaron Flint, host of the Montana Talks breakfast radio show.
And as disgraced pop star Gary Glitter is freed from prison, we hear from BBC correspondent Sarah Campbell who covered his trial in 2015, and barrister Kirsty Brimelow KC who explains why he's served half his 16-year jail term inside.</description></item><item><title>Declaring an Interest Rate | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510265/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 22:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510265/</guid><description>Podcast Description Greater Manchester Mayor, Andy Burnham, talks strikes, devolution and Beyoncé. And former MP, and serial cabinet minister, Justine Greening, is in the studio to talk about solutions to government's levelling-up policy, Raab bullying allegations, and whether the Conservatives have any chance at the next election. Today's episode was presented by Adam Fleming and Chris Mason and was made by Chris Flynn with George Crafer. The assistant editor was Sam Bonham.</description></item><item><title>Hard Day’s Strike | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510266/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 21:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510266/</guid><description>Podcast Description On what’s thought to be the biggest single day of industrial action for a decade, we talk to Len McCluskey, the former leader of Britain’s biggest union, Unite.
He tells Adam what he thinks Sir Keir Starmer should be doing differently in response, and how he’d be trying to use ‘leverage’ in negotiations. Adam also speaks to Americast presenter Sarah Smith about the funeral of Tyre Nichols, who died in Memphis last week after a beating by police.</description></item><item><title>'Walkout Wednesday': A Guide | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510267/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 22:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510267/</guid><description>Podcast Description Everything you need to know ahead of Wednesday’s strikes with the help of Alan Jones, PA’s Industrial Correspondent.
Stephanie Flanders, Head of Bloomberg News Economics, is also on to join the dots between the walkouts and the state of the UK‘s finances, as we learn that the UK economy is expected to shrink in 2023.
Also on the podcast, Liverpool officially becomes the Eurovision host city… which also means the launch of Eurovisioncast!</description></item><item><title>Brexitcast: Breakfast with Barnier | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510268/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 22:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510268/</guid><description>Podcast Description Three years since the UK left the EU, talks are still going on over trading arrangements. Why are they happening and what has changed since Brexit?
Adam is back in Brussels to mark the anniversary – and we’ve got the whole Brexitcast gang together! There will of course be cake, as well as analysis and memories from the BBC’s Europe editor Katya Adler, and political editors past and present, Laura Kuenssberg and Chris Mason.</description></item><item><title>EEEEconomics | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510269/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 19:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510269/</guid><description>Podcast Description Newsnight's economics editor Ben Chu discusses Chancellor Jeremy Hunt's strategy, and what all those Es stand for.
Chris Packham also joins from Ken Hill Farm in Norfolk, where he's been filming a special Winterwatch in which he interviews Sir David Attenborough. And Josh Widdicombe tells Adam what it was like reporting for local papers across the UK with his friend Nish Kumar for a new TV show.
Today's episode was presented by Adam Fleming and made by Chris Flynn with Miranda Slade and Amy Elizabeth.</description></item><item><title>TaxTok | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510270/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 22:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510270/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a HMRC boss says there are “no penalties for innocent errors”, Adam and Chris talk through the latest with Nadhim Zahawi’s tax affairs.
They’re joined by shadow foreign secretary David Lammy, who sets out Labour’s view on the UK’s relationship with Europe.
And Dame Arlene Foster, former first minister of Northern Ireland, talks about breaking the Brexit stalemate in Northern Ireland, and the state of the the Good Friday Agreement.</description></item><item><title>Tanksgiving | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510271/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 21:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510271/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is the West’s supply of tanks to Ukraine a game-changer?
Adam is joined by Ukrainecast’s Vitaly Shevchenko and BBC Europe editor Katya Adler to discuss whether the delivery of battle tanks from Washington and Berlin to Kyiv will make any kind of difference in the war against Russia.
And we perform a check-up on the health service with Chris Hopson, chief strategy officer for NHS England.
Today’s episode was presented by Adam Fleming and made by Tim Walklate with Rufus Gray, Daniel Wittenberg and Chris Flynn.</description></item><item><title>Together in Electric Schemes | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510272/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 21:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510272/</guid><description>Podcast Description A million people have signed up to a scheme with the National Grid which rewards them with discounts if they reduce how much energy they use.
Adam finds out how one customer has already saved £35 after signing up to the scheme and Newsnight’s economics editor Ben Chu explains how it works and why it was introduced.
The BBC’s Home Affairs correspondent, June Kelly looks at the future of the probation service, after a report highlighted a catalogue of failings that left a serial offender free to murder Zara Aleena.</description></item><item><title>Huw'scast | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510273/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 21:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510273/</guid><description>Podcast Description Newsreader Huw Edwards is in the Newscast studio to discuss addressing the nation following the Queen's death, the annual BBC Young Reporter Competition and why podcasts maybe aren't his thing. Also, Adam and Chris are joined by tax expert Rebecca Benneyworth to crunch the numbers on Conservative party chairman Nadhim Zahawi's tax headache. Today's episode was presented by Adam Fleming and was made by Tim Walklate with George Dabby, Madeleine Drury, Annabel Dry, and Daniel Wittenberg.</description></item><item><title>Fasten Your Seatbelts For Greg James and Roisin Hastie | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510274/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 19:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510274/</guid><description>Podcast Description The BBC Radio 1 Breakfast duo takeover Newscast. They chat to Laura Kuenssberg about strikes, Sunak’s seatbelt, and unpopular opinions.
The BBC’s chief international correspondent, Lyse Doucet, speaks from Kabul after interviewing Amina Mohammed, who's leading the United Nations visit to Afghanistan.
And Newscast adopts "Animal News" from Radio 1 , with reports of a giant toads, shouting dolphins, and busy beavers.
Today’s episode was presented by Greg James and Roisin Hastie and was made by Chris Flynn with Daniel Wittenberg, Adam Chowdhury, Cordelia Hemming, and Rufus Gray.</description></item><item><title>The Gender Say Gap | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510275/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 23:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510275/</guid><description>Podcast Description With Conservative Business Secretary Grant Shapps, Labour's Bridget Phillipson and the SNP's Mhairi Black. Three of the country’s leading politicians are on the podcast talking through some of the biggest political issues right now, including the UK government blocking a Scottish bill for the first time ever.
This episode of Newscast was presented by Chris Mason and James Cook and was made by Chris Flynn with Danny Wittenberg. The senior news editor was Sam Bonham.</description></item><item><title>Economy Class | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510276/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 23:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510276/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why is UK inflation dropping... while some food prices are still rising? Newsnight's Sima Kotecha is in the hotseat for today’s episode, and she’s joined by the BBC’s Evan Davis and Claer Barrett from the FT, to chew over the latest economic trends. Also, after the head of the food watchdog suggested that it’s unwise to bring cake into the office, The Great British Bake Off winner and Today programme host, Martha Kearney, tells us whether she’ll be taking on that advice.</description></item><item><title>Ken Brucecast | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510277/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 22:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510277/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the Radio 2 legend announces he’s hanging up his BBC boots, Adam challenges Chris Mason to Newscast’s version of ‘Popmaster’.
Chris discusses the ongoing row over Scotland's gender reforms.
And, with China facing an historic population decline, the BBC’s Jeremy and Cindy Yu from the Spectator join Adam to analyse what this could mean for the world's most populous nation. Today’s episode was presented by Adam Fleming and made by Tim Walklate with Josh Jenkins, George Dabby, and Rufus Gray.</description></item><item><title>School's Out (for Teachers) | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510278/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510278/</guid><description>Podcast Description What could the teachers' strikes in England and Wales mean for parents?
Adam is joined by Mary Bousted from the National Education Union and the BBC’s Branwen Jeffreys to discuss the upcoming industrial action.
Also, former police watchdog Zoë Billingham joins the BBC’s Helena Wilkinson to explore police reform after an officer pleaded guilty to 49 offences, including dozens of rapes.
Today’s episode was presented by Adam Fleming and made by Tim Walklate with Chris Flynn, George Dabby, Miranda Slade and Rufus Gray The technical producer was Mike Regaard.</description></item><item><title>The James Norton Show | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510279/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 19:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510279/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Valley star James Norton talks about the success of the show, helping Ukrainian friends caught up in the war, and how a health breakthrough could improve his life. Plus, the government’s net zero strategy is put under the spotlight by Chris Stark, Chief Executive of the UK's Climate Change Committee and Sophie Eastaugh from the BBC’s The Climate Question podcast.
This episode of Newscast was presented by Adam Fleming and was made by Chris Flynn with Ivana Davidovic, Miranda Slade, Cecelia Armstrong and Madeleine Drury.</description></item><item><title>Gender Politics | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510280/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 22:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510280/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Culture Secretary Michelle Donelan tells Adam and Chris that she’s disappointed with Scotland’s Gender Recognition Bill. She also says she’s "not ruling out" the idea of sending social media bosses to prison if they fail to protect children from damaging content online.
The head of the TUC Paul Nowak says the unions still have public support as we face more strikes. Plus, stick around for a taste of his musical talent.</description></item><item><title>The Influence of Andrew Tate | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510281/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 22:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510281/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who is the self-proclaimed misogynist and why are people worried about his influence over young boys’ behaviour?
Adam talks to the BBC’s Marianna Spring and Michael Conroy, founder of Men at Work, about the controversial British-American influencer who is in custody in Romania.
And Josh Baker from the new podcast, The Shamima Begum Story, tells us about his interviews with Shamima Begum.
Today’s episode was presented by Adam Fleming and made by Tim Walklate with Madeleine Drury, Chris Flynn, Verity Wilde and Cecelia Armstrong.</description></item><item><title>Blue Lights Out | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510282/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 22:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510282/</guid><description>Podcast Description Talking strikes, pay negotiations and GPs with Labour’s Wes Streeting.
Adam and Chris sit down with the shadow health secretary to discuss what Labour would be doing differently if they were in government.
Plus, Tim Harford from More or Less brings his spreadsheet for some NHS number crunching.
Today’s episode was presented by Adam Fleming and made by Tim Walklate with Madeleine Drury, Danny Wittenberg and Ivana Davidovic. The technical producer was Michael Regaard.</description></item><item><title>Prince Harry: Spare On Air | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510283/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 21:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510283/</guid><description>Podcast Description What did we learn from Prince Harry’s round of interviews?
Before shoppers queue up to buy his new book, BBC royal correspondent Jonny Dymond, and culture editor Katy Razzall join Adam to discuss the Duke’s relationship with his brother, allegations about the Queen Consort, and his facial hair.
Also, 5 Live’s Nicky Campbell and Radio 4’s Alex Renton discuss their experiences of child abuse.
Today’s episode was presented by Adam Fleming and made by Tim Walklate with Verity Wilde, Chris Flynn, Madeline Drury, Danny Wittenberg, and Miranda Slade.</description></item><item><title>New Year, New Covid Sub-Variant | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510284/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510284/</guid><description>Podcast Description How worried should we be about the spread of coronavirus abroad?
Restrictions are about to ease in China and there’s a new strain of Coronavirus in the USA. James Gallagher, presenter of Radio 4’s Inside Health and Kerry Allen, the BBC’s China media analyst put Covid back on the agenda. How to Fail podcast presenter Elizabeth Day also joins Adam to talk about New Year’s resolutions, and Radio 4’s Just One Thing host Dr Michael Mosley shares his top tips for sticking with them.</description></item><item><title>Prince Harry: Royality Check | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510285/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 21:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510285/</guid><description>Podcast Description Duke of Sussex accuses his brother William of physically attacking him. Royal Correspondent Jonny Dymond reveals details of a stream of sensational claims and accusations from Prince Harry's new memoir, Spare.
And Lord Mandelson, Labour’s election campaign director under Tony Blair, joins Adam and Chris to give his assessment of Sir Keir Starmer’s speech today, and of the state of the party as a whole.
Today’s episode was presented by Adam Fleming and made by Tim Walklate with Chris Flynn, Josh Jenkins and Adam Chowdhury.</description></item><item><title>The Rish List: Sunak’s New Year’s Resolutions | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510286/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 22:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510286/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Prime Minister sets out plans in his first major speech of 2023. Former speech writer to David Cameron and Theresa May, Jessica Cunniffe, joins Adam and Chris to go through Rishi Sunak’s first speech of the year, in which he set out his five pledges for the public to judge him on.
And with train services disrupted again this week due to ongoing strikes, the boss of Network Rail, Andrew Haines, tells us how close he thinks he is to a deal with the unions.</description></item><item><title>NHS Under Pressure | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510287/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 22:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510287/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the government admits the NHS is facing an “unprecedented challenge”, A&amp;amp;E consultant Dr Maya Naravi tells us that in 25 years of working in emergency medicine, this is “the worst I have ever seen it”. BBC health editor Hugh Pym joins us to explain what’s behind the problems and what’s being done to try to relieve them.
And amid widespread walkouts, Alan Jones, the PA’s industrial correspondent, talks us through what disruption we should expect as a result of strike action this year.</description></item><item><title>Best of Castfest | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510288/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 11:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510288/</guid><description>Podcast Description Reliving the first live Castfest from the BBC Radio Theatre. On 18th October 2022, Newscast and all of our sister podcasts came together in front of a studio audience to mark 100 years of the BBC.
For the first time, and for our final episode of this year, here are some highlights from the event, which was hosted by Adam and Ukrainecast’s Victoria Derbyshire. As you’ll hear, it came at a key time in 2022: in the run-up to the US mid-term elections, at a potential turning point in the war in Ukraine, and shortly before the demise of Liz Truss.</description></item><item><title>The Newscast Christmas Leftovers | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510289/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 16:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510289/</guid><description>Podcast Description Never before heard conversations with Richard Osman, Hans Zimmer, and Hugh Bonneville. In this special edition of Newscast, we bring you the interviews that had to be left in storage when major news events took over.
Adam talks to gameshow host and Thursday Murder Club author Richard Osman about how he writes the books, and why he chose detectives in their 70s as his main characters.
We hear from the man who wrote the music for some of the biggest films ever, Hans Zimmer.</description></item><item><title>2022: The Newscast Review | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510290/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510290/</guid><description>Podcast Description After 12 months that saw war in Ukraine, three prime ministers in Number 10, the end of the second Elizabethan era and the Lionesses bringing football home, Radio 4 asked us to look back at some of the most memorable stories. And, of course, we thought we’d share that with you too.
Adam and Chris are joined by Lyse Doucet, the BBC’s chief international correspondent, Newsnight’s economics editor Ben Chu and our technology editor Zoe Kleinman to look back on the events that shaped 2022.</description></item><item><title>The Newscast Christmas Party 2022 with Greg James, Zoe Ball and Joe Lycett | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510291/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510291/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam is joined by the UK's biggest breakfast show presenters: Radio 2’s Zoe Ball and Radio 1’s Greg James.
Joe Lycett also joins to look back at the biggest broadcasting moments of 2022 including Sam Ryder's Eurovision triumph, the Lionesses' Euro 2022 win and the coverage of the Queen's death.
And Grammy winning vocal group The King's Singers have a very special rendition of The Twelve Days of Christmas, made with the help of you Newscasters.</description></item><item><title>Driving Home For Christmas? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510292/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 18:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510292/</guid><description>Podcast Description As further strike action hits air, road, and rail over Christmas, we discuss the implications with the the country’s most recognised travel journalist Simon Calder, and Radio 2’s travel reporter Bobbie Pryor. Michelin-starred chef Tom Kerridge talks about how business is going as food prices rise, and gives his best Christmas recipes on a budget.
And Scotland makes history in passing a bill that makes it easier to change your legal gender.</description></item><item><title>Call In a Strike | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510293/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 20:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510293/</guid><description>Podcast Description As thousands of ambulance workers across England and Wales strike, we discuss how it’s impacting people at a local level. BBC Radio Sheffield’s Toby Foster, BBC Radio Cornwall’s Julie Skentelbery, and BBC Radio Kent’s Anna Cookson join Adam to discuss how listeners have reacted to the industrial action. Also, it’s been a busy week for former US president Donald Trump. Americast host Justin Webb fills us in on the news from across the pond.</description></item><item><title>The Ambulance Strike | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510294/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 21:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510294/</guid><description>Podcast Description Health bosses have warned they cannot guarantee patient safety during strikes by thousands of ambulance workers in England and Wales on Wednesday. Adam is joined by Unison boss Christina McAnea and BBC health reporter Jim Reed to explore how the industrial action could impact the NHS.
And the BBC’s Fergus Walsh celebrates some of the latest medical innovations, including a trial of a personalised cancer vaccine and how a baby's life was 'probably saved' by umbilical stem cells.</description></item><item><title>Rwanda Ruling | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510295/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 21:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510295/</guid><description>Podcast Description Where does Monday's High Court ruling leave the Rwanda migrant plan? The UK High Court has found that the government's plan to send some asylum seekers to Rwanda is lawful. Adam is joined by the BBC’s Dominic Casciani and Nick Eardley to discuss the political, legal and practical ramifications of the decision. Former White House adviser, and soon-to-be Chancellor of Durham University, Fiona Hill, talks about fears of nuclear war, the upcoming winter in Ukraine and how high fees may have kept her away from university.</description></item><item><title>Support v Disruption: Striking a Balance? | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510296/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 21:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510296/</guid><description>Podcast Description Does the public support the strikes? We speak to two Broadcasters who chat to the general public for a living. 5 Live Breakfast’s Nicky Campbell and presenter of Radio 4’s Any Questions, Alex Forsyth, are on to help us try to figure out what the mood of the country is. Marina Glasgow, the chief conciliator at the Advisory, Conciliation and Arbitration Service - also known as ACAS - explains her role in finding a resolution to the disputes.</description></item><item><title>Three Wise Political Editors | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510297/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 21:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510297/</guid><description>Podcast Description ITV’s Robert Peston and Sky’s Beth Rigby join Chris and Adam to look back on a tumultuous year in politics, recapping the biggest political moments of 2022 - as well as what happened behind the scenes.
Nurses in England, Wales and Northern Ireland are on strike in the first of two days of industrial action this month. Sunday Times health editor Shaun Lintern explains what impact the strikes are having on the NHS.</description></item><item><title>The Iceland Boss: Frozen Food For Thought | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510298/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 21:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510298/</guid><description>Podcast Description The UK rate of inflation is down, but will it continue to fall? Adam speaks to Richard Walker, the managing director of Iceland Foods, about the price of food this Christmas… as well as his ambitions to be prime minister.
Who is Sam Bankman-Fried, the man behind the failed cryptocurrency exchange FTX? Adam is joined by the BBC’s cyber reporter Joe Tidy and Jamie Bartlett, presenter of the BBC Sounds podcast series The Missing Cryptoqueen.</description></item><item><title>Leaping to Nuclear Fusion Conclusions | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510299/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 21:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510299/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is today’s scientific breakthrough the “holy grail” of clean energy?
Adam is joined by the BBC’s science editor, Becky Morelle, who explains what nuclear fusion is, and why today’s news is a big deal.
Chris Mason talks us through Rishi Sunak’s immigration plans. And business editor, Simon Jack, joins Newscaster Chana Horn to discuss what impact the current strike action is having in her business and the wider economy.</description></item><item><title>Weather (Or Not) To Travel | Newscast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3903510300/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 21:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3903510300/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bad weather adds to a week of significant strike disruption. Chris tells Adam why there’s no hope of the strikes being called off, despite talks, and crisis management expert Rob Doran explains what the government might be doing to soften the blow caused by the industrial action.
And after Adam’s successful performance on Celebrity Mastermind at the weekend, presenter Clive Myrie gives his take on why he triumphed.</description></item></channel></rss>