<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Kim Hill Collection on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/kim-hill-collection/</link><description>Recent content in Kim Hill Collection on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/kim-hill-collection/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2007: Germaine Greer | Kim Hill Collection</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2375760009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2375760009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Australian feminist author Dr Germaine Greer became &amp;ldquo;the high priestess of feminism&amp;rdquo; with her 1972 book ‘The Female Eunuch’. Throughout the 50 years since then, she hasn&amp;rsquo;t been far from the headlines. Kim Hill spoke with her in 2007 about her life and career.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>2017: Hugh McCarroll | Kim Hill Collection</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2375760010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2375760010/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2017, long-time inventor and astronomy enthusiast Hugh McCarroll was named one of 15 finalists in a global competition designed by NASA. The idea was to crowdsource ideas for how to collect human waste away from the body, hands-free, for fully suited astronauts for up to a six-day period. The Space Poop Challenge elicited almost 8,000 entries. Although Hamilton-based Hugh didn&amp;rsquo;t win first prize, he was &amp;ldquo;over the moon&amp;rdquo; to make the final 15.</description></item><item><title>2020: Jane Fonda | Kim Hill Collection</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2375760008/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2375760008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor, producer, activist and former fitness guru, Jane Fonda reflects on her relationship with climate change activism in her 2020 book: ‘What Can I Do? My Path from Climate Despair to Action’. She speaks with Kim Hill about her life on the front line as an activist, campaigning for over 50 years, tackling the climate crisis as her latest cause.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>2009: JJ Joseph and Celia Lashlie | Kim Hill Collection</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2375760001/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2375760001/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2006, JJ Joseph was convicted of a violent assault on his wife, but against the odds he was able to turn his life around. He tells his story in the 2008 book, &amp;lsquo;Fighting for My Life&amp;rsquo;, with a forward written by social justice advocate Celia Lashlie. They both join Kim to talk about the book and how real progress on violence will only happen when men speak out against it.</description></item><item><title>2017: Scott Brown | Kim Hill Collection</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2375760002/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2375760002/</guid><description>Podcast Description The US Ambassador to New Zealand and Samoa under the Trump administration in 2017, Scott Brown spoke with Kim Hill about his diplomatic role, as well many aspects of his political career, and some of Trump&amp;rsquo;s more polarising decisions.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>2008: Sister Loyola Galvin | Kim Hill Collection</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2375760003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2375760003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sister Loyola Galvin was known as the gardening nun. She organised a community garden at the Home of Compassion in Island Bay, Wellington. In 2008, at 86, she was named NZ Gardener of the Year by The Economist magazine.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>2017: David Sedaris | Kim Hill Collection</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2375760004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2375760004/</guid><description>Podcast Description American writer David Sedaris is famous for his self-deprecating and highly personal essay collections which manage to combine funny and sad in equal measure. Sedaris joins Kim Hill in 2017 to discuss his book ‘Theft by Finding’, which is a compendium of his diary from 1977 to 2022.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>2006: Sam Neill and John Clarke | Kim Hill Collection</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2375760005/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2375760005/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2006, Kim Hill spoke with two &amp;ldquo;quintessential Kiwi blokes&amp;rdquo; actor Sam Neill and comedian John Clarke about their friendship and their collaboration on two TV films based on Shane Maloney&amp;rsquo;s novels ‘Stiff’ and ‘The Brush Off’.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>2016: Burt Reynolds | Kim Hill Collection</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2375760006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 10:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2375760006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Burt Reynolds was Hollywood&amp;rsquo;s biggest box-office star from 1978 to 1982, following his starring role in Smokey and the Bandit. He had money, mansions, and wives, but that money went in various ways including bad investments and bad marriages. Kim spoke with Reynolds in 2016 when he was 79, discussing his life, career, and autobiography ‘But Enough About Me’.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kim Hill on Interviewing | Kim Hill Collection</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2375760007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2375760007/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this introduction interview, Kim Hill talks with Emile Donovan about the collection and good interviewing.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>