<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>32 Thoughts: The Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/32-thoughts-the-podcast/</link><description>Recent content in 32 Thoughts: The Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 13:20:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/32-thoughts-the-podcast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Goaltending Roller Coaster | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520349/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 13:20:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520349/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this edition of 32 Thoughts: The Podcast Jeff and Elliotte dive into the red hot goalie trade market as a number of teams are looking to solidify between the pipes before the Christmas trade freeze. The guys talk about Jordan Kyrou and the St. Louis Blues who are feeling the new coach bump. Plus, there&amp;rsquo;s an NHL-Olympic meeting happening soon to talk about Milano Cortina 2026. Will the arena be ready in time?</description></item><item><title>Craig Berube Hit His Expiry Date | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520001/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 13:18:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte talk about the St. Louis Blues letting go of Head Coach Craig Berube and the reception that Jordan Kyrou received from Blues fans on Thursday. They dove into Roberto Luongo&amp;rsquo;s Ring of Honour night in Vancouver and his storied time with the Canucks. They also talked about the Minnesota Wild and Chris O&amp;rsquo;Hearn parting ways and pieced together the information they have so far. The guys touch on the new Skills Competition format for the 2024 NHL All Star Weekend, and they play with the idea of Sydney Crosby winning MVP this season.</description></item><item><title>Marek Was Right About the Flyers | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 13:21:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte take a look back at a violent weekend across the NHL as they key in on some nasty hits. They talk about how they expect the NHL to react and what they would do in this situation. The guys review some of the headlines from Saturday including the futures of Ethan Bear and Andrei Kuzmenko. Jeff and Elliotte talk about the unravelling Carolina Hurricanes and the surprising Philadelphia Flyers.</description></item><item><title>Sorting Through the Trade Market for Defencemen | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520003/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss Patrick Kane&amp;rsquo;s Red Wings debut before sorting through the trade market for defencemen. They dive into Calgary&amp;rsquo;s decisions when it comes to goaltending and highlight the resurgent Edmonton Oilers. Can the Oilers keep this up long enough to get back in the playoff race?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Leafs Wanted Both Zadorov and Tanev | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss what they believe will be on the table at this week&amp;rsquo;s NHL BOG meetings in Seattle. Elliotte highlights the Toronto Maple Leafs interest in both Nikita Zadorov and Chris Tanev before Zadorov was traded to Vancouver. The guys also talk about the Oilers commitment to goaltender Jack Campbell and they dive into the extension for Sam Montembeault in Montreal.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Perry's Statement, Kane's Decision and Trade Buzz | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520005/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte react to the statement released by Corey Perry regarding the incident that led to his contract termination. They also dive into the Nikita Zadorov trade that sees the coveted defensemen land in Vancouver. They also lay out the latest details regarding Patrick Kane&amp;rsquo;s decision to sign with Detroit andJeff and Elliotte discuss the vibe around the Toronto Maple Leafs and what moves could be on the horizon.</description></item><item><title>Where are the Patrick Kane Winds Blowing? | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the latest news regarding free agent forward Patrick Kane&amp;rsquo;s future as the Detroit Red Wings emerge as the new favourite to sign him. They also talk about what happened with the NHL&amp;rsquo;s handling of players who support causes such as Pride or Native American Heritage and what the NHL is worried about big picture. Jeff and Elliotte close out the podcast by talking about pro wrestler and friend of the show, CM Punk.</description></item><item><title>This Season Has Been Drama Filled | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520007/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte examine the latest surrounding the Edmonton Oilers and how the team is inclined to weather the storm. They also dive into the Columbus Blue Jackets and highlight their biggest takeaways following their win over Chicago. Elliotte provides an update on Patrick Kane&amp;rsquo;s future and the fellas get conspiratorial when discussing the Winter Classic jersey leaks.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Does Something Need to Give in Columbus? | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Patrik Laine has been healthy scratched in Columbus by Pascal Vincent. Jeff and Elliotte debate whether this was the right decision to make or if it could&amp;rsquo;ve been handled differently. They also discuss the potential impact of this down season from Columbus on star prospect Adam Fantilli. The guys also provide some updates on the World Cup of Hockey and this season&amp;rsquo;s All Star Game in Toronto and Jeff tells an amazing story that will knock your socks off in this edition of the Montana&amp;rsquo;s Thought Line.</description></item><item><title>All Eyes are on Sweden | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520009/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte key in on the 2023 NHL Global Series in Sweden as the Senators and Red Wings drop the puck. They discuss the importance of international best-on-best hockey for a country like Sweden and when we might see those tournaments return. Jeff and Elliotte also talk about the struggling New York Islanders who have lost 7 straight and Elliotte provides an update on Elias Pettersson&amp;rsquo;s future with the Canucks as well as Patrick Kane&amp;rsquo;s future in the league.</description></item><item><title>The Ground Shifted Under Woodcroft | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte expand on the Edmonton Oilers relieving Jay Woodcroft of his head coaching duties and replacing him with Kris Knoblauch and Paul Coffey. Next, they discuss the latest in the Nikita Zadorov trade request reports, touch on the future of Samuel Montembeault in Montreal, and talk about Bo Horvat&amp;rsquo;s return to Vancouver this week to play his old club. They wrap the podcast by touching on this year&amp;rsquo;s Hall of Fame class.</description></item><item><title>McDavid and the Oilers Continue to Stumble | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520011/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520011/</guid><description>Podcast Description The rough road continues for the Edmonton Oilers as they fall to the rebuilding San Jose Sharks on Thursday night. Where can this Oilers team possibly go from here? Jeff and Elliotte also add to the latest in Vancouver where former Canucks President Trevor Linden revealed details of disagreements that took place between himself and then GM Jim Benning. They also discuss the latest in Calgary where Jonathan Huberdeau was sat for an entire period.</description></item><item><title>Where Is It Hottest in Canada? | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Things are tense in Edmonton, Ottawa, and Toronto. Jeff and Elliotte take the temperature of these three Canadian hockey markets. Can Edmonton correct its goaltending? Will Ottawa fire its head coach under fan pressure? Why aren&amp;rsquo;t the new guys finding success in Toronto? They also touch on the Sharks abysmal season that&amp;rsquo;s seen them lose back-to-back games where they&amp;rsquo;ve allowed 10 goals.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Michael Andlauer Doesn't Hold Back | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520013/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Following Michael Andlauer&amp;rsquo;s very open press conference on Wednesday reflecting on the punishment&amp;rsquo;s levied on his hockey club, Jeff and Elliotte give their thoughts on what was said by the Sens owner. They speak on the latest regarding neck protection in the NHL, which players are choosing to embrace the change, and finish up talking about NHL veterans in Paul Stastny and Nicklas Backstrom after both made big announcements this week.</description></item><item><title>"What Is Anyone Going to Do?" | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte recap an eventful Heritage Classic matchup between the Edmonton Oilers and Calgary Flames. Next, they dive into Joe Thornton&amp;rsquo;s retirement announcement while also touching on the fallout of the Shane Pinto suspension in Ottawa. They also take time to discuss the tragedy out of the UK where Adam Johnson passed away from an accidental skate cut during an EIHL game.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Details of the Pinto Suspension | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 12:07:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte dive into the Shane Pinto suspension and unveil some more details regarding the timeline and where the league and PA might go from here when it comes to educating players about their gambling rules. They recap a bizarre Thursday night across the league and add to the report that the NHL is moving towards decentralizing its Entry Draft.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Shane Pinto Suspended | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 15:45:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte react and add to the news that Shane Pinto has been suspended for breaking the NHL’s gambling rules. Elliotte dives into what he’s been told and reveals how the NHL came to this conclusion.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trouble in Northern Alberta | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss everything concerning the Edmonton Oilers as they hurtle towards the Heritage Classic against the Calgary Flames. Elliotte adds to his river cruise interview with Canucks forward Elias Pettersson and the guys talk about the Maple Leafs&amp;rsquo; resolve in a big comeback over the weekend.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Decentralizing the NHL Draft | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520018/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff Marek and Elliotte Friedman continue to discuss the NHL&amp;rsquo;s exploration into possibly decentralizing its annual Entry Draft. They also talk about the economics of the league and how the dip in attendance has impacted franchises.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lots to Talk About | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 12:35:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte provide the latest developments on pride tape&amp;rsquo;s use in the NHL. They go around the league and look at the top headlines from Conor Garland in Vancouver to Devon Toews extension with the Avalanche. As always, they also answer your questions in the Montana&amp;rsquo;s Thought Line.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Pursuit of Hockey Happiness Begins | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520020/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Regular season hockey is back! Jeff and Elliotte take a look at the biggest storylines thus far in this very young season. They key in on the attention Connor Bedard has received, the Canucks blowing out the Stanley Cup favourite Oilers, and they talk about the Leafs&amp;rsquo; changing their goal song and the reception it received.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>32 Snapshots | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 15:59:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff Marek and Elliotte Friedman touch on every National Hockey League franchise on the eve of the NHL&amp;rsquo;s regular season. They discuss what they believe will come of each team this upcoming year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>NHL Expansion Is on the Horizon | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff Marek and Elliotte Friedman discuss what they&amp;rsquo;ve learned about Pat &amp;ldquo;Yzerman Light&amp;rdquo; Verbeek this summer, touch on NHL Expansion seemingly on the horizon, and how the NHLPA wants to leverage that.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Worst Kept Secret in Hockey | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520023/</guid><description>Podcast Description This podcast is dedicated to Flames Assistant General Manager Chris Snow who passed away from ALS complications on September 30th 2023. You can donate to the Calgary Flames Foundation to directly fund ALS research and new treatments at the most progressive institutes across Canada at nhl.com/flames/fans/snowystrong.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Putting the C in Calgary | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520024/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520024/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is dedicated to the Snow family of Calgary. To donate funds to help ALS research and to find new treatments go to https://www.nhl.com/flames/fans/snowystrong
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Andlauer Officially Owns the Senators | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte react to Michael Andlauer officially becoming the owner of the Ottawa Senators. They dive into some NHL young stars in the spotlight this week and react to Evgeny Kuznetsov speaking out against his former coach. The guys also interview LA Kings President Luc Robitaille and Edmonton Oilers CEO Jeff Jackson.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Turmoil in Tampa | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520026/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte get into the turmoil that has arisen in Tampa Bay between Steven Stamkos and GM Julien BriseBois. They break down the Tanner Pearson trade to Montreal and expand on what William Nylander&amp;rsquo;s possible move to center could mean for his future with the Leafs.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Babcock Resigns | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520027/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte break down Mike Babcock resigning as head coach of the Blue Jackets, Bedard’s rookie camp, the Senators sale, and sit down with Anders Lee and Seth Jarvis.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Babcock Decision Coming? | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520028/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 14:51:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the Mike Babcock situation and PTOs, chat with Bedard, Crosby, Draisaitl and Jack Hughes, and say goodbye to a member of their podcast team to wrap the episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Blue Jacket Blowup | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520029/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 18:09:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte break down the Mike Babcock player meeting situation in Columbus, chat with Johnny Gaudreau and Billy, discuss the Thomas Tatar contract and catch up with Troy Terry.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The PTO Song | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520030/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 15:12:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the the current state of the NHL, the latest on the ownership of the Senators, and they catch up with Filip Gustavsson and Lucas Raymond.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Colonel Sanderson | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520031/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 13:52:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the latest around the Jets and Connor Hellebuyck, the Senators locking in Jake Sanderson, Rasmus Dahlin rumours, and they catch up with Alexander Barkov, Pierre Engvall, Tim Stutzle and JJ Peterka.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>European Voices | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520032/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 06:56:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Elliotte discusses some of the latest news off the top and then the guys sit down with an array of NHL players from the European Media Tour in Stockholm.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jaywalking In Stockholm | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520033/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 14:38:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte are in Stockholm for the NHL European Media Tour! They catch up with William Nylander and Rasmus Andersson, and get to the news of the summer — Auston Matthews signs a 4-year extension!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dallas Green | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520034/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte welcome back award-winning musician Dallas Green to the podcast to discuss his feature with Ryan O&amp;rsquo;Reilly at Massey Hall, opening for Rage Against the Machine, his latest record, touring with Alexisonfire, and much more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>That's A Wrap | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520035/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 23:18:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520035/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the season finale, Jeff and Elliotte go through all 32 teams discussing their free agency moves, what they will be looking to do ahead of next season, and things to keep an eye on throughout the off-season.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Goodbye Draft, Hello Free Agency | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520036/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 15:46:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte look ahead to free agency, discuss the PWHPA x PHF situation, and then Elliotte is joined by Jason Bukala to recap some of the biggest storylines from the NHL Draft.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Draft Day | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520037/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 12:56:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte sit down with Predators GM Barry Trotz at Bridgestone Arena to talk about the early days in Nashville and the guys go over the latest news as we gear up for the NHL Draft.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Draft Week | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520038/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 14:16:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520038/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re in Nashville! Jeff and Elliotte kick off the podcast by discussing the latest news around the league and then preview the NHL Draft with Sam Cosentino and Jason Bukala.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Up In Flames | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520039/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 15:09:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vegas Golden Knights owner, Bill Foley, joins the podcast! Jeff and Elliotte also recap the NHL Board of Governors meeting in New York, the latest on the Flames, and wonder what we&amp;rsquo;ll see from the Flyers next week.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Duck Surprise? | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 16:07:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte are joined by former NHL general manager Chuck Fletcher as he joins Sportsnet for the NHL Draft in Nashville and they go around the league with some of the latest news.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OEL UFA | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520041/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 15:12:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss Vancouver buying out Oliver Ekman-Larsson, the Stanley Cup parade in Vegas, the latest on Connor Brown and Jonathan Toews, and they take your questions.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Barba$hev | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520042/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 13:51:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the payday Ivan Barbashev is expected to see this summer, the latest on the Leafs and Auston Matthews, Pierre-Luc Dubois generating west coast interest, and lots of intrigue around Matvei Michkov.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Knights Hit The Jackpot | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 14:28:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the Vegas Golden Knights winning the Stanley Cup, Michael Andlauer purchasing the Ottawa Senators, and the Rangers hiring Peter Laviolette.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cup Is In The House | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520044/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 15:15:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte recap a crazy finish to Game 4 in Florida, discuss the prolonged Ottawa sale process, Kyle Dubas signs a benchmark contract in Pittsburgh, teams who are eyeing Pierre-Luc Dubois, and they take your questions.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We’ve Got A Series | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520045/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 15:54:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte chat with Brandon Montour and Mark Stone, recap game 3 of the Stanley Cup Final, break down the Damon Severson sign and trade, and give the latest on Alex DeBrincat &amp;amp; Pierre-Luc Dubois.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trade Season Starts Early | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520046/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 16:32:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte get into the three-team trade between the Kings-Blue Jackets-Flyers, wonder what Philly will do with Carter Hart and catch up with Bruce Cassidy and Paul Maurice in Las Vegas.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Media Day | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520047/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 17:21:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte are in Las Vegas! They chat with Matthew Tkachuk and Alex Pietrangelo, hear from both coaches on where the Cup will be won, and the Blue Jackets hire Mike Babcock as their next head coach.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>“We’re here. We’re ready to go.” | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520048/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 12:27:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte are joined by Ryan Smith, owner of the Utah Jazz and Real Salt Lake, to talk about his interest in owning an NHL franchise.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Waiting Game | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520049/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 12:15:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte provide more details on the Kyle Dubas situation, the latest on the GM search in Toronto, discuss what&amp;rsquo;s next for the Dallas Stars, coaching hires in Washington &amp;amp; Nashville, and Tom Dundon comments on the future of his team.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Apsveicam! | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520050/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 15:37:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the Kyle Dubas and Pittsburgh situations, chat with NHL Senior EVP of Media and International Strategy, David Proper about the Global Series &amp;amp; Australia, and give Latvia credit after their bronze medal performance at the IIHF World Championship.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Stayin’ Alive | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520051/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 15:15:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte recap Stars-Golden Knights Game 4, credit Florida, wonder about Carolina&amp;rsquo;s off-season, discuss the Kyle Dubas agent situation, and Jeff gets his rule change!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Burning Bright | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520052/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 15:52:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the Flames restructuring their front office and hiring Craig Conroy as GM, the Kyle Dubas statement, Ottawa sale and they take a very interesting voicemail.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Penguin Kyle? | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520053/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 13:18:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte continue to discuss the Kyle Dubas situation, possible GM candidates in Toronto, Calgary closing in on their next GM and they break down both conference finals.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Shanahan Shocker | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520054/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 21:53:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the Leafs not bringing back Kyle Dubas, recap the 4OT thriller between Florida-Carolina, chat with Paul Stastny, go around the league with some of the latest coaching/GM updates, and talk salary cap plus Clayton Keller.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Coyote Ugly | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520055/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 13:35:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the decision to reject the proposed Tempe Arena Project, recap Oilers &amp;amp; Leafs season-end pressers, provide coaching/GM updates, and are joined by Daniel Hilferty, Chairman &amp;amp; Chief Executive Officer of Comcast Spectacor.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>No Canada | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520056/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 15:24:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte wonder what the off-season will look like for the Oilers and Leafs, give credit to the Panthers and Golden Knights, discuss the Ottawa sale, and the coaching situation in New Jersey and Columbus.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>1 Game | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520057/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 15:37:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte get into the Alex Pietrangelo suspension, the Hurricanes eliminating the Devils, wonder what&amp;rsquo;s next for New Jersey, discuss the sale of the Senators, a new hire in Philadelphia and some talking around the Islanders.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>11:59 For Toronto | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520058/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 15:30:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the Leafs-Panthers series, Edmonton&amp;rsquo;s 5-on-5 play, Carolina coming out to play, the search for a coach in the Big Apple (Babcock?), Landeskog out for all of next season, Draft Lottery and Chicago&amp;rsquo;s rebuild.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Panther Meat | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520059/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 15:10:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte break down Toronto’s Game 3 performance, give credit to Seattle and New Jersey, continue to marvel at Leon Draisaitl, provide some news from around the league and chat Draft Lottery.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How About Bob? | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520060/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 15:38:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte recap Game 2 Panthers-Maple Leafs and Kraken-Stars, discuss Oilers-Golden Knights and Devils-Canes, talk about the Norris Trophy finalists, Snoop Dogg, and remember the late Petr Klima.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kraken 5, Pavelski 4 | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520061/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 15:28:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte talk Panthers-Leafs as well as Kraken-Stars (Pavelski), preview Edmonton-Las Vegas &amp;amp; New Jersey-Carolina, talk about the schedule and look at the off-season for the Rangers, Bruins &amp;amp; Flames.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Wow! | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520062/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 15:25:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte wrap up what might have been one of the craziest weekends in hockey &amp;ndash; Kyle Dubas and the Leafs, Patrice Bergeron, Kraken advance, embellishment, Jets, Ottawa sale and much more!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bowness Blast | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520063/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 14:47:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the post-game press conference from Rick Bowness, go through several of the series, and provide an update on Calgary&amp;rsquo;s GM search and Anaheim&amp;rsquo;s coaching search.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jordan Martinook | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520064/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte sit down with Jordan Martinook to talk about his Gordie Howe hat trick, Mr. Svechnikov, Canada&amp;rsquo;s best band, coming up with ideas for the Storm Surge, and riding the bus with Brent Burns (and his backpack).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Puck Face | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520065/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 14:24:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss each series starting with the Kings-Oilers, debate the Foligno-Faksa hit as well as the Makar-McCann, tip their hat to MacKenzie Weegar (arena deal in Calgary), and some news out of Anaheim.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jack To The Rescue | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520066/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 15:51:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte break down each series from the weekend, discuss Émilie Castonguay choosing to stay with the Canucks and take an interested listener question.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mark Stoned | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520067/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 15:47:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte go through each of the first-round series as things begin to ramp up through two games, talk about Mark Stone&amp;rsquo;s return, the Ryan O&amp;rsquo;Reilly feature and the officiating.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What Now Toronto? | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520068/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 15:37:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520068/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;re back three days a week for the playoffs! Jeff and Elliotte recap game 1 of each of the series, wonder what&amp;rsquo;s next for the Flames as they look for a new GM and new names enter the fold in the search for a president in Philadelphia.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Playoff Time! | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520069/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 17:40:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte preview every first-round series in the Stanley Cup Playoffs, provide more details on some of the changes around the league and do an off-season wrap on the teams that were eliminated.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Black Friday | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520070/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 16:56:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the front office changes in Pittsburgh, the Ducks firing their head coach, what some of the eliminated teams might do this off-season and the send-off for Jonathan Toews in Chicago.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rod Brind’Amour | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520071/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 18:34:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Elliotte sat down with Rod Brind’Amour in Ottawa to talk about his son Skyler winning the Frozen Four, the culture around the Hurricanes, his relationship with Tom Dundon, the 2006 Stanley Cup and officiating in the NHL.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Five More Days | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520072/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 14:35:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte break down a crazy weekend of hockey, discuss some college signings as well as Bo Horvat &amp;amp; Chris Wideman&amp;rsquo;s post-game comments, and Elliotte sits down with Noel Acciari of the Toronto Maple Leafs.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Coffee, Grunge &amp; Playoff Hockey | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520073/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 15:43:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte give credit to the Seattle Kraken for an impressive second season, discuss the wild card race in the East &amp;amp; West, detail the situation with the Chicago Wolves and wonder how healthy the Bolts will be going into the playoffs.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Wyatt Johnston | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520074/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 16:19:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff Marek sits down with rookie standout Wyatt Johnston at the American Airlines Center in Dallas to talk about his 20-goal season, living with Joe Pavelski and Marc Savard&amp;rsquo;s tape job.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>It’s Just A Flesh Wound | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520075/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 15:09:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte tip their hat to Brayden Schenn on his eventful weekend and Kris Letang on his 1000th game, NHL going to Australia, the marketing plan put forth by Ryan Reynolds, and the Jets &amp;amp; Flames making things interesting.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dinner Date | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520076/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss Gary Bettman&amp;rsquo;s dinner with Ryan Smith (Utah Jazz &amp;amp; Real Salt Lake owner), the media conference held by Marty Walsh, Scott Howson vs some AHL teams, and a fun game in Ottawa.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Max Domi | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520077/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 12:41:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520077/</guid><description>Podcast Description While in Dallas, Max Domi joined Jeff to talk about his new club, the situation with his teeth, being a pass-first player, finding the right stick, growing up around great hockey players, and playing under Pete DeBoer.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tin Foil Hats | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520078/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 14:50:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte put their tin foil hats on when talking about the Maple Leafs, wonder what the future is for the Jets core, discuss why we&amp;rsquo;re seeing more physical play this late into the season, and they take your questions!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cheech | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520079/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 15:37:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the comments made by Connor McDavid about the WBC, the 10-year NHL x Fanatics deal, John Garrett leaving the Canucks broadcast, and Jason Robertson joins the podcast.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Our Lone Star Itinerary | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520080/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 13:56:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte are in Dallas chatting about the Stars, fighting in hockey/after clean hits, the sale of the Senators, Martin St. Louis sitting Jonathan Drouin and James Reimer refusing to wear the Sharks Pride-themed jersey.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jay Woodcroft | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520081/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte chat with Oilers head coach Jay Woodcroft about video sessions with Connor McDavid, his time with Mike Babcock in Detroit, coaching 3-on-3, and the perfect length of a video session.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>FTRH | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520082/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 13:16:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte (in Florida) discuss the Daniel Brière press conference, a weekend of opposites for the Senators and Jets, what to expect at this week&amp;rsquo;s GM Meetings and they answer your questions.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Flyer Friday | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520083/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 15:57:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the changes in Philadelphia, the latest on the sale of the Ottawa Senators, upcoming GM meetings, and some exciting games down the stretch including Vegas-Tampa &amp;amp; Edmonton-Boston.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Here’s What Didn’t Happen | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520084/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the trades that didn&amp;rsquo;t go down and topics for the upcoming GM meetings, wonder where the Flyers go from here, and tip their hat to Jakob Chychrun on his debut with the Senators.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Thank God It's Over | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520085/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 13:27:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte wrap up a wild trade deadline week by discussing the Flyers, talks between Pittsburgh and Vancouver, the state of the Coyotes, Ottawa making a playoff push and Boston coming out on top.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bill Guerin | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520086/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 16:18:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte are joined by Minnesota Wild GM, Bill Guerin, for a lengthy chat about the trade deadline, the upcoming GM Meetings, how he manages his cap as well as his relationship with his owner, and how he&amp;rsquo;s not afraid of change.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deadline Sunday | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520087/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 15:05:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte preview all 32 teams wants/needs as we near the trade deadline and discuss what was a crazy Sunday in hockey with the Predators changing things up and the Devils trading for Timo Meier.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Eastern Octagon | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520088/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 14:24:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte continue to work the Patrick Kane situation, discuss the Boston-Washington trade and focus on the Keystone State as trade rumours begin to really heat up.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jake Allen | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520089/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 14:08:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Montreal goaltender Jake Allen joins Jeff and Elliotte for an in-depth chat about goalie gear, analyzing a play before a shot, he builds us the perfect goalie and tells us what it&amp;rsquo;s like playing with Carey Price.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Big Daddy Kane | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520090/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 14:22:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte talk Patrick Kane, the big trade between the Maple Leafs-Blues-Wild, latest on Timo Meier and Jakob Chychrun, they break down some of the buyers and sellers and explain why Joonas Korpisalo might be a good trade chip.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Here's What We Know | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520091/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 14:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte talk about trade talk around Tyler Bertuzzi, what the Blues and Golden Knights might be doing, the Oilers seem to be open for business, Chicago has some decisions to make and the guys remember two great men of the game.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mark Giordano | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520092/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 15:31:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mark Giordano joins Jeff and Elliotte from the Maple Leafs practice facility inside the NHL Alumni office to talk about his hockey journey, being a leader on the team and what it means to him as he approaches the all-time blocked shots record.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Drama In The Desert | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520093/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the Coyotes tweets about Jakob Chychrun, whether or not Erik Karlsson could be headed to Edmonton, take some listener questions, and much more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tarasenk-Go | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520094/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the Vladimir Tarasenko trade, present some suitors for Timo Meier including the Devils and Maple Leafs, talk about Bo Horvat playing the Canucks and they close the book on All-Star.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Juuse Saros | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520095/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520095/</guid><description>Podcast Description While in Florida, Jeff and Elliotte chatted with Preds All-Star goaltender, Juuse Saros, about his season, returning from injury, his draft year, being an undersized goalie and his tattoos.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Islanders Owe Us A Massage | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520096/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 15:47:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the Bo Horvat extension, chat with Elias Pettersson on the beach in Florida and present a few ways in which to improve the All-Star Game.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Beach Side At All-Star | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520097/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 15:53:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte are in Florida for the All-Star Game. They chat with Leon Draisaitl about his biggest feat, Nazem Kadri on his first few months in Calgary and Steve Mayer takes us for a walk on the beach.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>After The Horn: Arber Xhekaj | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 14:09:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Elliotte sits down with Arber Xhekaj to talk about his unlikely road to the NHL and then he chats with his parents, Simona and Jack, about their unbelievable journey to Canada. This was a Sportsnet &amp;ldquo;After The Horn&amp;rdquo; feature.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Don’t Debug The EBUG | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520099/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 13:59:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the altercation between Troy Stecher and Trevor Zegras, the upcoming NHLPA meet, finding a solution to the EBUG, the financially fit Bruins and they take your questions!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nobody Tanks | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520100/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 14:57:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss a massive sports broadcasting story that could impact the NHL, Gary Bettman&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;nobody tanks&amp;rsquo; comment and what&amp;rsquo;s the latest as we approach the trade deadline.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Connor Hellebuyck | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520101/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Winnipeg Jets goaltender Connor Hellebuyck sits down with Jeff and Elliotte to talk about his new children&amp;rsquo;s book, the evolution of goalie gear, players that annoy him and fishing with Dustin Byfuglien.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Goodbye, Gabby | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520102/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 15:09:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte dissect the hour-long Vancouver Canucks press conference announcing Rick Tocchet as the team&amp;rsquo;s new head coach, wonder what&amp;rsquo;s happening with Timo Meier &amp;amp; Vladislav Gavrikov and chat about the red-hot Oilers.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bo Goes? (Owen Sound) | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520103/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 15:29:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss some of the latest news from around the league before taking you to Heartwood Hall in Owen Sound, ON for their LIVE SHOW!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nigel Dawes | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520104/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Elliotte sat down with hockey journeyman, Nigel Dawes, in Germany to talk about his career in the NHL, playing on the best World Junior team ever assembled and why chose to play overseas in his 20s.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Remembering Gino | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520105/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 14:13:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte remember Gino Odjick, talk Canucks, Seattle&amp;rsquo;s record-setting road trip, Boston signs Pavel Zacha, Chicago&amp;rsquo;s plan this season and they take your questions!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tick Tocc | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520106/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 16:56:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte do a deep dive into the Vancouver Canucks, talk about the red-hot Kraken and K&amp;rsquo;Andre Miller’s heroics, the ceremony for P.K. Subban in Montreal and the amazing goal by Nela Lopusanova.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ryan McDonagh | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520107/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 15:40:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte sit down with Ryan McDonagh to talk about his love of fantasy football, the art of blocking a shot, the emotions of going from the Stanley Cup Final to being moved and why Nashville was the right fit.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What’s Up With … | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520108/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 14:51:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte talk Patrick Kane, Ivan Provorov, All-Star Skills Competitions, Oilers defence, crazy junior hockey trades and their upcoming live show in Owen Sound, Ontario!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jordan Eberle | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520109/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 14:40:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Elliotte sits down with Seattle Kraken winger Jordan Eberle to talk World Juniors and Connor Bedard, plays part of a song he wrote about the Islanders and attempts to strum a few notes on the guitar.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Phil Bourque | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520110/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte are joined for a lengthy conversation with 2-time Stanley Cup Champion and current Pittsburgh Penguins analyst, Phil Bourque, ahead of the Winter Classic in Boston.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>From The Green Monster | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520111/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 15:37:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte chat about the Winter Classic from atop Green Monster in Boston, tour Fenway Park with Steve Mayer and the latest news from around the league.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Fined For Flying | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520112/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 15:27:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte talk fines for Toronto, the culture in Philadephia, the red-hot Kings, David Pastrňák and the Bruins, Sam Ganger plays his 1000th game and Winter Classic at Fenway Park.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Marián Hossa | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520113/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 16:02:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520113/</guid><description>Podcast Description 3-time Stanley Cup Champion and Hockey Hall of Famer, Marián Hossa, joins Jeff and Elliotte to talk about his new book “My Journey from Trencín to the Hall of Fame”.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The 3rd Annual Holiday Party | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520114/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 22:15:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte invite you to the 3rd Annual 32 Thoughts Holiday Party featuring Rick Ball, Blake Murphy, Emily Kaplan, Justin Bourne, Jack Michaels, Liam McHugh and many more guests.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nigel Kirwan | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520115/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520115/</guid><description>Podcast Description He is the longest-serving employee of the Tampa Bay Lightning and his career path to becoming the Bolts video coach is one of the more unique stories around the NHL.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Untouchable | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520116/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 15:26:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte talk about the untouchable player on the Canucks, the latest on the Flyers &amp;amp; Predators, debate if Connor McDavid was offside and discuss potential changes to the 2023-24 schedule.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Oettinger Understood The Assignment | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520117/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 16:41:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss Jack Oettinger&amp;rsquo;s motivation versus Washington, the latest on the salary cap, Ryan Reynold is still interested in the Senators and David Perron plays in his 1000th game.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Todd McLellan | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520118/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 16:04:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520118/</guid><description>Podcast Description L.A. Kings head coach Todd McLellan sits down with Jeff and Elliotte for a lengthy chat about his career, coaching, and the evolution of the game.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Who's Taking Tolvanen? | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520119/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 15:44:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte (in Florida) discuss why the Predators placed Eeli Tolvanen on waivers, the latest on Jesse Puljujärvi, Darryl Sutter, and what&amp;rsquo;s on the agenda at the Board of Governors meetings.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tage Five | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520120/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 14:36:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss Zdeno Chara&amp;rsquo;s comment regarding the 2011 Vancouver Canucks, if Tage Thompson should have gone for the record and Kelly Hrudey tells us about Wayne Gretzky&amp;rsquo;s slap shot.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bryan Trottier | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520121/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 17:17:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hall of Famer, Stanley Cup Champion and author, Bryan Trottier joins Jeff and Elliotte to talk about his new book, All Roads Home, and about his journey in hockey.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Imminent And Under The Bus | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520122/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 15:58:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss Erik Karlsson and Brock Boeser, Jacob Trouba and the New York Rangers, the 2024 All-Star Game, Jordan Binnington, and they define the word “Imminent”.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Pheeeeeee-Nom | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520123/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 17:29:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte talk Connor Bedard, Cal Petersen and the LA Kings, 1,000 points for Steven Stamkos, Roberto Luongo being honoured in Vancouver and a look back at the month of November.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mask On, Mask Off | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520124/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the Connor Hellebuyck mask situation, Jakob Chychrun and the Sabres, goal post pegs, what the Oilers are in need of right now and the latest out of Vancouver.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The King | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520125/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 14:32:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520125/</guid><description>Podcast Description The guys discuss Elliotte&amp;rsquo;s latest blog where he talks Patric Hörnqvist, Jesper Bratt &amp;amp; Ryan Reaves and they pay tribute to the late Börje Salming.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Craig Anderson | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520126/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 17:22:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Elliotte sits down with Sabres goaltender Craig Anderson to talk about his love of cars, how he handles stress, playing summer hockey, hardest shooters to read and if he&amp;rsquo;ll be back next season.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Doing The Wright Thing | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520127/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 15:06:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss Shane Wright, potential trade talks between Vancouver-Ottawa, the sale of the Senators, Evgeni Malkin &amp;amp; Alex Goligoski play in their 1000th game, and we take your questions!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Out Of Gas, But Not Ideas | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520128/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 16:41:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte talk Erik Karlsson trade rumours, Andrew Brunette and the Vancouver Canucks, the Capitals looking for answers, and the Devils &amp;amp; Bruins continue to roll.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kelly McCrimmon | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520129/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Golden Knights GM Kelly McCrimmon tells Jeff and Elliotte how he approaches the salary cap, the narrative around the club, offer sheets, trading for Jack Eichel and his memories of North Battleford, SK.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Canada vs. USA. Do It, You Cowards! | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520130/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 15:07:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Elliotte gives us his World Cup of Hockey concept, Jeff tells us about an offside project he&amp;rsquo;s looking to pursue and they discuss the emotional tribute to Börje Salming this weekend in Toronto.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>“Re-sign Lindy!” | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520131/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 17:02:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss Jack Eichel’s follow-up performance in Buffalo, the red-hot Devils, Börje Salming&amp;rsquo;s return to Toronto, Hall of Fame weekend, and they address the Mitchell Miller situation.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Patrice Bergeron | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520132/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Elliotte chats with Boston Bruins captain Patrice Bergeron about his leadership style, future plans, memories from the 2011 and 2013 Stanley Cup Playoffs and his relationship with Brad Marchand.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Too Much Bieksa | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520133/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 15:27:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss Kevin Bieksa&amp;rsquo;s retirement in Vancouver, wonder if the Bruins can be stopped, Ottawa being for sale, Mike Rupp&amp;rsquo;s comments on the Auston Matthews altercation, and tip their hat to the Devils.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Duck, Duck, Lose | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520134/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 14:12:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520134/</guid><description>Podcast Description The guys discuss Toronto&amp;rsquo;s dreadful west coast swing, the latest arena news from Arizona, Shane Wright&amp;rsquo;s future, the Battle of Alberta, Islanders and Devils finding their groove and your questions!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Goals, One Assist And No Licks | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520135/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 16:55:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brad Marchand is back, Vancouver finally wins a game, Connor McDavid goes off (again), Arizona debuts their temporary arena, Ilya Sorokin is good and the 32 Thoughts Blog will look different.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Alligators, Fenway Park &amp; Around The Clock Hockey | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520136/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520136/</guid><description>Podcast Description NHL Chief Content Officer, Steve Mayer, joins Jeff and Elliotte to talk big ideas for big events, Winter Classic at Fenway Park, alligators at the All-Star game, working with P.K. Subban and the World Cup of Hockey.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Everything But The Waffles | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520137/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 15:45:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte talk about the struggling Vancouver Canucks, present a new location that&amp;rsquo;s on the NHLs radar, take a few of your questions and tell you which surprise team is here to stay.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Everything's Coming Up Robertson | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520138/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 15:10:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520138/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte wonder what&amp;rsquo;s going on with the Vancouver Canucks, discuss the drama in Toronto, give credit to the Sabres and the Devils, and they chat with Jason Robertson of the Dallas Stars.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>It’s Red Hot Behind The Bench | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520139/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 13:19:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss coaches who might be in the hot seat, wonder what’s going on in Ottawa, chat Toronto goaltending, tip their hat to the Redwood Line in Detroit and take your questions.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Great Start! | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520140/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 18:28:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte give some of their early takeaways from the season and discuss the Travis Sanheim &amp;amp; Mattias Samuelsson extensions.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Previewing The Western Conference | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520141/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 16:39:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte preview the Western Conference with the help of a few players including Roman Josi, Miro Heiskanen, Timo Meier and Clayton Keller.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Your Eastern Conference Preview | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520142/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 21:20:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte run through the waiver wire and then preview the entire Eastern Conference with the help of a few players including Zach Werenski, Sebastian Aho, Cam Atkinson and Andrei Vasilevskiy.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Last Stop: Hamilton | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520143/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 17:33:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the signing of Jason Robertson and Mathew Barzal, the Flyers sending Cam York to the AHL, the Flames extending MacKenzie Weegar and the guys chat with former NHLer, Steve Staios.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The In-Season Cup | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520144/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 17:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520144/</guid><description>Podcast Description The In-Season Cup is back! Jeff and Elliotte are joined by Olympic gold medalist &amp;amp; PWHPA member, Erin Ambrose and rinkside host for Sportsnet &amp;amp; Hockey Night in Canada, Kyle Bukauskas to pick their teams for the 2022-23 NHL season.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The New-Look Senators | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520145/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 16:40:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte travelled to Ottawa to chat with a few of the Senators including Brady Tkachuk and Claude Giroux along with GM Pierre Dorion and head coach D.J. Smith.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sunday In The Patch | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520146/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 18:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss a couple of defencemen that are off the market, Mark Stone, the Dale Hawerchuk statue at True North Square, goaltenders on the move and the latest on Jason Robertson.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trippin' Out In Trenton | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520147/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 14:10:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte chat about the new contract for Rasmus Sandin, hitting in pre-season, the salary cap, Florida extending Spencer Knight, and they discuss some news around the Vancouver Canucks.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Exaggeration Season | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520148/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 15:36:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte provide a few pre-season thoughts, touch on Mike Grier&amp;rsquo;s comments regarding his team&amp;rsquo;s participation in the global series game in Prague, and are joined by Allain Roy, the founder of RSG Hockey and the new President of NRX Hockey.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>London Calling | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520149/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 15:51:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Live from London, Ontario! Jeff and Elliotte kick off their 32 Tour hosted by Boston Pizza in London and record the podcast in front of an audience.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Twelve Carat Rib Injury | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520150/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 15:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte chat with Connor McDavid, Quinn Hughes, Jack Hughes and Jonathan Huberdeau but kick things off by talking toughness and discussing players who are currently unsigned.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Star Sighting In Vegas | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520151/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 23:52:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte chat with Sidney Crosby, Nathan MacKinnon, Mathew Barzal and Mark Scheifele in Las Vegas at the Player Media Tour.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>32 Podcast Tour | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520152/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 19:45:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte are in Sin City for the Player Media Tour and they have some big news. They are hitting the road for a podcast tour starting September 22nd to October 6th hosted by Boston Pizza. Get your tickets at www.32tour.com
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The European Pack | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520153/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520153/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte catch up with Nino Niederreiter, Kevin Fiala, Hampus Lindholm, Nico Hischier and Victor Olofsson while in Europe for the Player Media Tour.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tim $tützle | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520154/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 19:43:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the Tim Stützle contract, some other news from around the league, and chat with Moritz Seider and Jakub Vrana of the Detriot Red Wings.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Back To Work | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520155/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 16:26:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520155/</guid><description>Podcast Description With hockey season around the corner, Jeff and Elliotte dive into some news from around the league including contract extensions for J. T. Miller &amp;amp; Tage Thompson. Plus, they catch up with Pierre-Édouard Bellemare and Victor Hedman.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>High Expectations | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520156/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 14:17:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte are joined by Calgary goaltender Jacob Markström and Senators forward Tim Stützle to talk about their expectations going into the 2022-23 season and how their off-season unfolded.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Greetings From Paris | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520157/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 11:18:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520157/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte are in Paris for the European Player Media Tour and they recap the latest news from around the league, chat with Leon Draisaitl and catch up with deputy Commissioner Bill Daly.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Summer Surprise | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520158/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 20:13:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520158/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte are back with a surprise drop with a few updates on some of the latest moves that are yet to drop (or have dropped *Klingberg) and they discuss the blockbuster trade of the summer.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Schools Out For The Summer | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520159/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 18:51:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte cover the Johnny Gaudreau story from all angles, touch on several teams and players that made moves this week and thank YOU for a fantastic season.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Secure The Bag | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520160/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 14:03:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520160/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the latest around the goalie market, some names (there are lots!) to keep an eye on this week and a couple of interesting stories to follow.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Merci Montréal | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520161/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 22:55:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520161/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte recap day 1 of the NHL Draft from Montreal and then Elliotte provides a few notes from day 2.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rumours Rumours Everywhere | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520162/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 13:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520162/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte go over a lot in a short amount of time including Mike Grier in San Jose as their next GM, Alex DeBrincat potentially on the move, Marc-André Fleury and the goalie situation in Toronto, and who will go first overall at the NHL Draft.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Latest ... | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520163/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 14:53:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte give you the latest from around the league as players and coaches are on the move. Plus, they take your emails and calls!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Year Of The Avalanche | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520164/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 13:50:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520164/</guid><description>Podcast Description Congratulations to Colorado! Jeff and Elliotte discuss some of the post-final on-ice interviews, Cale Makar winning the Conn Smythe Trophy, and wonder what rosters will look like next season for the Bolts and Avs.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Game Of The Year | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520165/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 13:50:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte break down Andrei Vasilevskiy&amp;rsquo;s impressive performance in game 5, discuss Barry Trotz and his decision not to coach this season, wonder where the Jets go from here, and Luke Richardson in Chicago as the new head coach.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Thumbs Up For Kadri | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520166/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 13:59:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520166/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte recap an exciting game 4 and discuss the OT winner by Nazem Kadri, wonder what the Jets will do with Pierre-Luc Dubois &amp;amp; Blake Wheeler, talk about Paul Maurice + Panthers, and present their awards ballot.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bolts, Brady &amp; Bukauskas | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520167/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 13:30:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte recap the response from Tampa Bay in game 3, discuss Ethan Bear’s future in Carolina and Vancouver landing Andrei Kuzmenko, and they give their thoughts on the Hockey Canada investigation.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Total Domination | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520168/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 13:34:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte recap game 2 of the Stanley Cup final, discuss the future of Connor Brown in Ottawa, the Sharks GM search and potential candidates, and the latest on several coaching searches around the league.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rocky Mountain High | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520169/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 15:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte recap game 1 of the Stanley Cup final, address the Gary Bettman and Bill Daly press conference, give you the latest on the coaching carousel, and Peter MacTavish parts ways with the Senators.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Next Stop, Stanley Cup! | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520170/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 11:34:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte preview the Stanley Cup final, tip their hat to Steven Stamkos, wonder what the Rangers will do this off-season, chat Oilers and Sharks, coaches to keep an eye on, and Board of Governors meetings.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sifter, Snifter &amp; You Got Tampa’d | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520171/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 13:37:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520171/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte recap game 5 between the Rangers-Bolts, provide an update on several coaching searches around the league, and Jeff tells us a few good stories about Mikhail Sergachev.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lightning Strikes | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520172/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 15:55:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte recap Bolts-Rangers (game 4), wonder what the Oilers will do this off-season, discuss the Bruce Cassidy firing in Boston and David Pastrňák&amp;rsquo;s future with the team, and Montreal hires Marie-Philip Poulin.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Oil Spill | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520173/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 14:27:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520173/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte dive deep into the Oilers-Avalanche series, recap Lightning-Rangers, discuss Chicago&amp;rsquo;s off-season approach, marvel at Patrice Bergeron, and talk about the WEAKSIDESTRONG challenge.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Combine And Cale | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520174/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 14:16:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520174/</guid><description>Podcast Description The guys recap both conference finals, discuss the Jack Adams Award and Jeff provides a detailed update from the NHL Scouting Combine in Buffalo.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Good Call, Right? | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520175/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 14:04:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520175/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte recap the craziness that was game 1 Edmonton-Colorado, preview the Eastern Conference final, wonder what Carolina might do this off-season and touch on the end-of-season press conference in St. Louis.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Little Too Much Excitement | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520176/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 14:55:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520176/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte preview the Western Conference final, discuss some of the decisions the Flames and Blues have to make this off-season and they tip their hat to Jason Spezza who calls it a career after 19 NHL seasons.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kicking Back | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520177/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 12:09:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520177/</guid><description>Podcast Description The carcasts are back! Jeff and Elliotte discuss the finale of a wild Battle of Alberta, the Hurricanes continuing their home winning streak, and the Blues beating the Avalanche to stay alive. In non-playoff news, the coaching carousel begins to spin in Philly, and Rick Westhead reports on the awful allegations surrounding Hockey Canada.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Sweep And Some Tension | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520178/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 11:57:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520178/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte are still in the studio to discuss the latest action in the NHL playoffs, including Calgary&amp;rsquo;s loss in Edmonton and the Rangers rallying to tie their series, plus they react to the Lightning&amp;rsquo;s sweep of the Panthers and set up the next game of Colorado vs St Louis.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>It’s A Gusher! | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520179/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 14:50:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Due to a power outage in Stouffville, Jeff and Elliotte are in-studio to break down the latest news from around the league including the Bryan Rust &amp;amp; Mark Giordano extensions, and they recap all the playoff action from the weekend.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Blood, Sweat &amp; Stitches: The Tampa Bay Story | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520180/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 14:27:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte talk about the drive they see in the Lightning, the Blues&amp;rsquo; power play, what to expect in the Battle of Alberta this weekend, and a conversation about coaching styles.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Can Colorado Be Stopped? | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520181/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 15:02:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte recap the first two games from the second round, touch on a few end-of-season press conferences, and discuss the latest on Barry Trotz as he begins to interview with teams.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kyle’s Summer Of Kawhi | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520182/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 15:36:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520182/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte recap the two OT thrillers from Sunday night, preview the four matchups we’ll see in the next round, and look ahead to the off-season for the teams that were eliminated.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cancel Your Plans This Weekend | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520183/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 10:19:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520183/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte recap an exciting night of hockey, get you set for some game 7s on Saturday and wonder what the Wild might do this off-season as they were eliminated from the playoff by the St. Louis Blues.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Do You Sleep After That | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520184/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 15:25:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520184/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte recap the impressive comeback from the Maple Leafs, the excellent finish in Edmonton, wonder if the Rangers can get it together versus the Penguins, and chat about the Draft Lottery.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Islanders Shocker | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520185/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 16:29:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520185/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the Islanders firing Barry Trotz, what&amp;rsquo;s happening with a pair of All-Star defensemen in San Jose, and they recap each series from the Stanley Cup Playoffs.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Old Brown Shoe | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520186/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 14:10:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520186/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the play of Connor Ingram, Kelly McCrimmon returning as the GM of the Golden Knights, interest in Travis Green and John Chayka, and the New Jersey Devils season-end press conference.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>First Playoff Carcast | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520187/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 13:36:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520187/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff (at home) and Elliotte (driving home) discuss the season-end press conference in Vancouver as well as Winnipeg, and they touch on each of the playoff series for a few minutes.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Weekend Wrap + Playoff Preview | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520188/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520188/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte preview the Eastern and Western Conference matchups and they discuss some of the biggest stories from the weekend.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Leaving Las Vegas &amp; Craig Conroy | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520189/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 15:55:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520189/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the Vegas Golden Knights and if they can rebound after their rollercoaster season, if we&amp;rsquo;ll see roster changes in Vancouver this summer, and they chat with Calgary Flames assistant GM, Craig Conroy.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Guy! Guy! Guy! | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520190/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 15:59:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520190/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte remember the great Guy Lafleur, tip their hat to Ryan Getzlaf after a wonderful career, discuss the situation with Robin Lehner, and wonder what&amp;rsquo;s in store for San Jose, Winnipeg, Columbus and the Islanders this off-season.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Agent To The Stars | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520191/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520191/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gerry Johannson represents some of the biggest names in hockey. He joined Jeff and Elliotte to talk about Carey Price&amp;rsquo;s future, Ryan Getzlaf’s retirement and possible role in management, working with Luke Prokop last summer on his announcement, and how he got into the industry and when he got his break.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Martin St. Louis | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520192/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 13:13:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520192/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte chat with Martin St. Louis about getting back into professional hockey, what he&amp;rsquo;s learned over the first two months as head coach of the Montreal Canadiens, how he feels about people doubting his skills, and the impressive run of games by Cole Caufield.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Loss Of A Legend | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520193/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 17:54:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520193/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte reminisce about the late Mike Bossy and why Friday night in Montreal will be special, what Anaheim might do this off-season as they were knocked out of playoff contention, and they take your questions.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Pushing For The Playoffs | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520194/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 16:25:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520194/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte look at some potential first-round match-ups, discuss the San Jose GM search, wonder what Detroit will do this off-season as they were eliminated from playoff contention and talk Hart Trophy candidates.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Auston, Texas | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520195/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 14:40:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520195/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte (from his car) recap a historic night for Auston Matthews in Dallas, look ahead to the off-season for a pair of teams that have been eliminated from the playoffs, and discuss the future of the NHLPA with Donald Fehr at the helm.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Willing Combatants | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520196/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 16:19:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520196/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the on-ice situation from Friday night in Arizona, Keith Yandle’s iron man streak coming to an end, and where the New Jersey Devils go from here after being eliminated from the playoffs.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bruuuuuuuuuuuuce! | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520197/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 16:31:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520197/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte kick things off with a conversation about Bruce Boudreau and his future with the Canucks, remember the late Eugene Melnyk, and look ahead to the off-season for the four teams that have been eliminated from the playoffs
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Johnny Oduya On Travel, Coaching &amp; ATUNYA | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520198/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 03:47:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520198/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte are joined by 2-time Stanley Cup champion Johnny Oduya to talk about his travels to Kenya and Thailand, creating his training apparel brand Atunya and he shares a few funny stories from his days in the NHL.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Back To The Future | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520199/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 15:00:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520199/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss why there are talks of a weekday afternoon game next season, they dig into the LTIR conversation, Claude Giroux and the Senators, and the return of Evgenii Dadonov to Vegas.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Dadonov Dilemma | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520200/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 17:26:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520200/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte break down the Evgenii Dadonov situation and provide some of their main takeaways from the trade deadline.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>32 Deadlines | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520201/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 19:44:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520201/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte give a thought on all 32 teams and what they are looking to do as the trade deadline approaches.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Don’t Underestimate Tanner Jeannot | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520202/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 15:34:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520202/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tanner Jeannot joins Jeff and Elliotte to talk about his journey to the NHL from small-town Saskatchewan, the obstacles he overcame along the way, playing on a line with Colton Sissons and Yakov Trenin, playing under John Hynes, what made Tim Hunter the coach for him in Moose Jaw, the support he’s received from his community in Oxbow, and he talks about his workout routine and what he excels at most.</description></item><item><title>Meltdown in Steel Town | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520203/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 15:34:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520203/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte recap the Heritage Classic in Hamilton, discuss Toronto&amp;rsquo;s goaltending issues, potential moves on the horizon, some big news from the PWHPA, and they celebrate their 300th episode with their family.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Whistles Away | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520204/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 16:50:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520204/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte (in his car) recap a week that saw some questionable calls around the league, discuss the goaltending situation in Toronto and the play of the red hot Coyotes, Jack Eichel’s return to Buffalo, and the latest from Philadelphia.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Hot Stove Is Heating Up | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520205/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 17:46:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520205/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte give credit to Jason Robertson and Nick Schmaltz, touch on players of interest as we near the trade deadline, and discuss the comments made by Angela James regarding the state of women’s hockey.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>61 on 32 | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520206/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 17:57:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520206/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rick Nash joins the podcast to talk about his jersey retirement in Columbus and shares some of his favourite stories from his career. The guys also discuss the unstoppable Rangers, Jon Cooper getting ejected versus the Penguins and Jeff apologizes for a puck-ing mistake he made on the Monday podcast.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Meet Juraj Slafkovsky | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520207/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 14:40:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520207/</guid><description>Podcast Description Juraj Slafkovsky is 17 years old, and he was voted the 2022 men&amp;rsquo;s Olympic hockey MVP. He joined Jeff and Elliotte to talk about his Olympic journey, winning bronze for Slovakia, finding his scoring touch, his favourite team/player, and if he takes any stock in NHL Draft rankings.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>IIHF Rules On Russia | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520208/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 22:13:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520208/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the decision by the IIHF as it relates to Russian and Belarusian athletes and the 2023 World Juniors, the meeting in Arizona with the Coyotes and the NHLPA, and the wild Saturday night in Detriot.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Forsberg, Jets, Hawks &amp; Leafs | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520209/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 16:01:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520209/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss how a pair of North American players in the KHL are handling the conflict in Ukraine and what sporting events we might see cancelled in Russia, they continue to marvel at Zdeno Chára, wonder what Nashville will do with Filip Forsberg, and how Jake Muzzin going on LTIR will impact the Maple Leafs.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Leafs Get A Lyub Job | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520210/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 15:42:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520210/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the trade between the Maple Leafs and Coyotes, discuss Montreal&amp;rsquo;s mini win streak and their interest in Marie-Philip Poulin, and they break down the latest from Chicago&amp;rsquo;s GM search.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Carcast From The Rink | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520211/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 09:05:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520211/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte (while in his car) recap the heavyweight tilt between the Penguins and Maple Leafs, discuss the Claude Giroux press conference and where he might land, and wonder what Vancouver might be looking to do with some of their stars.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Alex Pietrangelo on Jack Eichel’s Return and Life After Hockey | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520212/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 15:55:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520212/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte are joined by Stanley Cup Champion, Alex Pietrangelo, to talk about his All-Star game experience, the return of Jack Eichel, his friendship with Jay Bouwmeester, and the importance of preparing for life after hockey.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Toffoli Traded &amp; Eichel Returns | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520213/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 21:39:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520213/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the Tyler Toffoli trade to Calgary, Sidney Crosby&amp;rsquo;s pursuit of 500 goals, the Oilers under Jay Woodcroft, the return of Jack Eichel this week, and Rosie DiManno’s opinion piece in the Toronto Star.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What A Week! | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520214/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 17:08:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520214/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte kick things off with an apology before getting into some rapid-fire thoughts from Elliotte’s latest blog, discuss the changes in Edmonton and Montreal, Vancouver hiring Cammi Granato, and the arena situation in Arizona.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>News Breaks &amp; Vegas Recap | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520215/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 15:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520215/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte recap All-Star Weekend in Las Vegas, discuss the Gary Bettman and Bill Daly press conference, and news breaks during the recording session that Chicago had fired their AHL athletic trainer for sexual harassment
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Succession | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520216/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 16:33:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520216/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the comments made by Rocky Wirtz at the Chicago Blackhawks town hall, Pat Verbeek&amp;rsquo;s first move as the new general manager of the Anaheim Ducks, and Elliotte tells us about his conversations with David Poile, Bill Guerin, and Rob Blake.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Shutting Down The Las Vegas Strip | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520217/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 20:59:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520217/</guid><description>Podcast Description Steve Mayer is the Chief Content Officer at the NHL. He joins Jeff and Elliotte to discuss All-Star Weekend in Las Vegas, how they are using the Bellagio Fountain and why they are shutting down the strip, and what it will take to get backwards skating into the skills competition.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Price Speaks and Is ‘The Michigan’ Boring | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520218/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 16:26:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520218/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the Carey Price press conference, wonder what&amp;rsquo;s next for the Canadiens and the Canucks, provide an update on Anaheim&amp;rsquo;s GM search, tell us why they love jersey retirement ceremonies, and debate if the &amp;lsquo;The Michigan&amp;rsquo; is now boring.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Edmonton’s Gamble, Arizona’s Downsize | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520219/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 18:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520219/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte explain how Evander Kane became an Oiler, discuss the arena situation in Arizona as well as the press conference in Philadelphia, and provide an update on the GM search in Chicago and Anaheim.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Meet the new Executive Director of the PHF Players’ Association | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520220/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 06:51:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520220/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex Sinatra is a Texas-barred attorney who is the new executive director of the PHFPA. She tells Jeff and Elliotte why she took the job and how her career path guided her to hockey. She also talks about some of her early priorities, challenges, potential partnerships and what&amp;rsquo;s important to the players.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Hard Look Back, And Then A Look Ahead | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520221/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 16:04:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520221/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss a pair of incidents that took place in the AHL and the ECHL, and they express their frustration as racist behaviour continues to be seen and heard in the game of hockey.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Barkov Breaks The Oilers &amp; Ryan Getzlaf Joins The Podcast | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520222/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 16:05:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520222/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte chat with Ducks captain Ryan Getzlaf, discuss the Oilers struggles after a 6-0 loss to the Panthers, Sheldon Keefe’s post-game comments, provide more updates on Vancouver’s GM search, marvel at Victor Hedman’s dominance, a few thoughts on Brad Marchand, and a few more teams are added to the Jakob Chychrun trade list.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Could Be A Newsy Week | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520223/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 16:17:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520223/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte wonder what the Oilers will do next as they fall to the Senators, discuss Montreal&amp;rsquo;s GM search and give some background on player agent Kent Hughes (who is in the running for the job), and explain why Florida is the real deal this season.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Like An Old Married Couple | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520224/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 15:50:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520224/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the Evander Kane situation and how the Canadian Border Services Agency is involved, the Ken Holland press conference, Bobby Clarke’s comments on Ron Hextall, the Panthers and Kodak Black, and All-Star snubs.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Devan Dubnyk on the Olympics, Burning Rubber &amp; Goalie Fights | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520225/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 18:19:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520225/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte chat with Devan Dubnyk about his desire to play on Canada’s Olympic team, getting back in game shape, the smell of burning rubber, the hardest shot he ever faced, almost fighting Jordan Binnington, and his favourite goalie growing up.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Wild Weekend Of Surprises | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520226/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 15:58:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520226/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the situation between Evander Kane and the San Jose Sharks, Rob Blake’s contract extension and the Kings hiring Marc Bergevin as a senior advisor to the GM, continued trade talks around Jakob Chychrun, the John Klingberg negotiation, and more updates out of Edmonton.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Elliotte’s DMs Are Open | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520227/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 16:45:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520227/</guid><description>Podcast Description Could the Winnipeg Jets be playing their homes games in Saskatoon? Jeff and Elliotte discuss the results of the season ticket holder survey sent out by the team and the logistics required to execute such a move. They also touch on the return of Tuukka Rask, how Edmonton could save their season, and why Sidney Crosby is still fantastic.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What To Watch For In 2022 | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520228/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 16:08:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520228/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a bit of a break, Jeff and Elliotte kick things off by explaining what the league might do with the schedule going forward, tell you some stories that they&amp;rsquo;ll be keeping an eye on in 2022, and take a few of your questions as well as a voicemail from the Thought Line.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mark Messier on Winning (and Losing), Costumes &amp; Commercials | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520229/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520229/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte are joined by six-time Stanley Cup champion Mark Messier to talk about his new book. No One Wins Alone. The guys ask Mark about his younger days hanging out with the Portland Buckaroos, if he had a certain way of winning, the type of player he’d be in today&amp;rsquo;s game, why Halloween parties were so important to him, and they talk about some of his more memorable commercials.</description></item><item><title>2nd Annual 32 Thoughts Holiday Party | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520230/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 18:43:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520230/</guid><description>Podcast Description As say goodbye to 2021, Jeff and Elliotte invite some of their favourite people from around Sportsnet to their second annual 32 Thoughts holiday party. Sit back, grab a drink and enjoy some holiday fun with the crew.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Some Other Things to Talk About | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520231/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 14:44:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520231/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte break down what was a difficult weekend around the league as more teams were shut down, talk Alex Tuch and his much-expected debut for the Sabres as well as Robin Lehner&amp;rsquo;s return to Long Island, tell us what team isn’t interested in Jakob Chychrun, and discuss potential front-office candidates in Vancouver.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Emergency Podcast! Paul Maurice and the Jets | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520232/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 23:14:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520232/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte break down Paul Maurice’s resignation and Dave Lowry being named interim head coach. They also discuss why a number of teams are shut down until Christmas and how much money Montreal lost by not allowing fans in the arena.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Everyone’s Favourite Discussion | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520233/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 14:27:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520233/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss COVID-19 protocols around the sports world, the impact the virus is having on the league, trade talks around Jakob Chychrun, Vancouver finding their stride as they begin to make hires, Pittsburgh’s surprising run, why this might be the weirdest NHL season, and they take a real interest question from the thought line.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Olympic-Sized Headache | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520234/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 16:26:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520234/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss some of the main takeaways from the NHL Board of Governors meeting in Florida which included the Olympics, the search for a general manager in Vancouver, what&amp;rsquo;s happening with the Bruins, how the Oilers are looking to improve their roster and they take some of your questions.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hunka Hunka Burning Glove | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520235/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 17:59:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520235/</guid><description>Podcast Description Elvis Merzlikins joins the podcast! But before that, Jeff and Elliotte discuss the Jason Spezza suspension, player safety, changes in Philadelphia, and the Zegras to Milano goal.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Time Has Come For The Canucks | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520236/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 08:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520236/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Vancouver Canucks fired their head coach and general manager on Sunday. Jeff and Elliotte discuss the changes in western Canada, the timing of them, the hiring of Bruce Boudreau and the impact he may have on the players, and why it was time to move on from Jim Benning.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Houston, We Have a Problem | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520237/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 16:28:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520237/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the report that the Arizona Coyotes could be for sale, they dissect the situation in Ottawa, discuss the Rob Brind&amp;rsquo;Amour fine and answer a few listener emails.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Manic Monday Montreal | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520238/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 14:49:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520238/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss the changes in Montreal, the struggling Flyers, Ottawa placing Matt Murray on waivers, Evander Kane finds new representation as he is put on waivers by the Sharks, concerns over the All-Star Game, and Brendan Lemieux biting Brady Tkachuk.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Canucks, Islanders and Stuff(ing) | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520239/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 17:50:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520239/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte wonder if we’ll see changes in Vancouver, how the Islanders are managing their roster around COVID protocol, how the All-Star game might look a bit different this season to limit the exposure to COVID-19 leading into the Olympics, why the Avalanche gave Jared Bednar a two-year extension, hot starts for Alexander Ovechkin and Nazem Kadri, and they answer some of your emails and voicemails.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>There's A Lot Going On | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520240/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 14:38:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520240/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte cover off a lot of stories including another tough loss for the Canucks, if there’s something going between Kevin Fiala and the Wild, they provide an update on the Omaha Lancers situation, discuss interest by the Fenway Sports Group in purchasing the Pittsburgh Penguins, and Islanders open their new arena but are hit by heavy COVID-19 protocol.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Canucks on the Clock | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520241/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 22:55:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520241/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vancouver is having a hard time finding its groove. Jeff and Elliotte discuss the struggling Canucks, what might be going wrong, possible changes, and how the market is reacting to the slow start. The guys also touch on Montreal, the Islanders coming home last place in the Metro, feedback from the Mike Forde interview, protecting the stars and how it might increase attendance, the situation with the Omaha Lancers, and they take some emails and your voicemails.</description></item><item><title>Reorganizing Your Organization | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520242/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 21:20:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520242/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte are joined by Mike Forde, Executive Chairman at Sportsology — a company that advises sports franchises on talent management and the creation of high-performance cultures. They discuss his scope of work in world sport (particularly in hockey, soccer and basketball), understanding the needs of an ownership group, their process in finding inefficiencies within an organizational structure, and some of the challenges that come with managing expectations in multilingual environments.</description></item><item><title>32 Goalie Thoughts - Part 2 | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520243/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520243/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kevin Woodley of In Goal Magazine &amp;amp; NHL.com is back to talk …. goalies! Jeff and Kevin discuss active goalie pads (1;30), goaltenders taking their training off the ice using virtual reality (8:00), pad design (17:00), the reverse-VH (20:30) and they take a voicemail question about the Boston Bruins goaltending situation (22:30).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>32 Goalie Thoughts – Part 1 | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520244/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 17:14:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520244/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you like goalies, this episode is for you! Jeff is joined by “The Goalie Whisperer” from In Goal Magazine, Kevin Woodley. They cover off a lot from between the pipes like how goaltenders have had to adapt to new shooting styles (44:00) to the rise of elite Russian goaltenders (11:15) over the last few years.
The guys also discuss different goaltending styles around the league and highlight some amazing performances so far this season — Igor Shesterkin (19:30), Andrei Vasilevskiy (7:30), Thatcher Demko (26:00), Robin Lehner (32:00), Jack Campbell (35:00) and Craig Anderson (40:00).</description></item><item><title>Weekend Update | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520245/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 17:25:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520245/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chicago fires head coach Jeremy Colliton and assistant coaches Tomas Mitell and Sheldon Brookbank. Jeff and Elliotte discuss the promotion of Rockford head coach Derek King (2:10), the level of freedom interim GM Kyle Davidson has within the organization, and if this is a lost season for the Blackhawks. They also touch on Jack Eichel’s arrival in Las Vegas (17:00), Ottawa recalling Erik Brannstrom from Belleville (17:45), the Maple Leafs finding their groove (25:00), St.</description></item><item><title>The Eich-stravaganza | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520246/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2021 15:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520246/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Buffalo Sabres have traded Jack Eichel! Elliotte tells us about his exclusive sit-down with the newest member of the Vegas Golden Knights (00:01) and when he plans to make his return to play. The guys then break down the Jack Eichel saga from every perspective including Eichel’s (8:45), Terry and Kim Pegula (15:00), Kevyn Adams (19:00), Pat Brisson (23:45), Vegas Golden Knights (27:30), Calgary Flames (32:00), Carolina Hurricanes (38:30) and the NHL (43:30).</description></item><item><title>Should They Do It Again? | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520247/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 12:48:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520247/</guid><description>Podcast Description The League has spoken. The NHLPA is speaking. Kevin Cheveldayoff will speak soon. Jeff and Elliotte discuss the press conference held by commissioner Gary Bettman and deputy commissioner Bill Daly on Monday and provide some details around the executive board meeting held by the NHLPA.
Music Outro: Michael Wilford – Rattle My Bones (ft. Sail Cassady)
Listen to the full track by Michael Wilford here
This podcast is produced and mixed by Amil Delic, and hosted by Jeff Marek and Elliotte Friedman.</description></item><item><title>Where Are We Going? | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520248/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520248/</guid><description>Podcast Description That’s the question. Jeff and Elliotte take an in-depth look at the Kyle Beach story and where it might be headed following the findings from the Chicago Blackhawks internal investigation. They address the news of Kevin Cheveldayoff not facing discipline (5:00), Joel Quenneville resigning (11:00), Donald Fehr and the NHLPA (15:45), players from the 2010 Blackhawks roster (20:40), Gary Bettman and the NHL (27:50), and where Chicago as a club goes from here (44:00).</description></item><item><title>A Brief Statement | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520249/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520249/</guid><description>Podcast Description Transcript</description></item><item><title>Early Season Panic | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520250/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 16:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520250/</guid><description>Podcast Description A pair of Orginal Six teams are really struggling out of the gates. Jeff and Elliotte discuss why the Leafs (00:01) aren’t playing to their potential, if changes are needed in Chicago (23:00) and list off some coaching candidates that are currently on the market (27:00).
They also talk about the Red Wings and their rookies (39:00), provide more news regarding Jack Eichel (42:00), the price for Vitali Kravtsov (47:00), interest in Barrett Hayton (48:00), Seattle’s home opener (50:00) and they take some of your questions (54:00).</description></item><item><title>“It’s Not Revenge?” | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520251/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 15:10:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520251/</guid><description>Podcast Description And the Carolina Hurricanes continue to haunt the Montreal Canadiens. Jeff and Elliotte recap Jesperi Kotkaniemi’s return to the Bell Centre (00:01), chuckle at what they saw post-game on social media and discuss Montreal’s early struggles.
They also chat about Brady Tkachuk’s return to the Senators (17:00), the goaltending situation in Calgary (20:00), Winnipeg getting it done shorthanded (23:00), Quinn Hughes continues to impress (27:00), the early season challenges (on and off the ice) in Chicago (29:00), the youthful Blues (41:30) and the winner by Vladimir Tarasenko (37:00), what we might see with the Rangers and Vitaly Kravtsov (51:00), and much more</description></item><item><title>ZEE-RO CHANCE! (stay till the end of the podcast) | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520252/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 15:07:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520252/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte debut their new segment on Hockey Night in Canada! They talk about the experience (00:01) and some of the topics from the segment including extension talks for John Klingberg (4:30), more Eichel updates (14:30), shortened rosters (42:00) and the new standards for officials (50:00).
They also touch on Colorado being in on almost every big-name player (23:00), Montreal losing some of their identity (10:45 &amp;amp; 28:45), injuries in Vegas (25:45), the Jack Hughes goal and celebration (36:30) and they answer some of your emails (57:30).</description></item><item><title>And Then There Were None. Everyone is Signed! | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520253/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 14:45:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520253/</guid><description>Podcast Description The season is underway and the 32 Thoughts podcast is back for its fifth season! Jeff and Elliotte give their thoughts on the first few days of action (37:00), break down the Nick Suzuki contract (10:15) along with Ryan Pulock’s deal with the Islanders (31:20), Senators signing Brady Tkachuk (00:01), chat about Alexander Ovechkin’s season opener (23:30), the Bruins and Charlie McAvoy (13:30) and the Predators signing Mattias Ekholm to a 4-year contract (27:30).</description></item><item><title>Western Conference Preview | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520254/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520254/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte preview the NHL’s Western Conference by division in alphabetical order. Pacific Division
Anaheim (1:20), Calgary (2:50), Oilers (4:50), Los Angles (7:35), San Jose (10:10), Seattle (13:25), Vancouver (15:15) and Vegas (17:50)
Central Division
Arizona (20:45), Chicago (24:10), Colorado (26:20), Dallas (27:30), Minnesota (29:10), Nashville (32:00), St. Louis (35:50) and Winnipeg (39:00)
Music Outro: The Magnolia – Stormy Weather
Listen to more tracks from The Magnolia here</description></item><item><title>Eastern Conference Preview | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520255/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 21:57:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520255/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte preview the NHL’s Eastern Conference by division in alphabetical order. Metropolitan Division
Carolina (3:30), Columbus (4:45), New Jersey (8:15), New York Islanders (12:10), New York Rangers (12:50), Philadelphia (20:20), Pittsburg (25:40) and Washington (28:20)
Atlantic Division
Boston (31:10), Buffalo (34:00), Detroit (39:00), Florida (42:10), Montreal (45:50). Ottawa (51:00), Tampa Bay (54:50) and Toronto (56:50)
Music Outro: Delicate Steve – Peaches
Listen to more tracks from Delicate Steve here</description></item><item><title>Seth Jones, Anders Lee &amp; Tim Stützle | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520256/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 16:15:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520256/</guid><description>Podcast Description Seth Jones of the Chicago Blackhawks joins Jeff and Elliotte (7:00) to talk about his eventful off-season, playing with his brother this season, knowing your worth, the new additions to the Blackhawks and what went down in Columbus last season.
The guys then chat with Anders Lee (19:00) about his love of dogs and Gordie Howe, resigning with the Islanders, his announcement tweet, playing without Jordan Eberle this season, his relationship with Lou Lamoriello and his recovery.</description></item><item><title>The In-Season Stanley Cup | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520257/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 13:17:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520257/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte have talked about doing the in-season Stanley Cup challenge for a couple of seasons but never had the time to coordinate it. But this season, they found the time and some friends to do it with!
The guys are joined by David Amber and Caroline Cameron of Sportsnet in the first annual 32 Thoughts In-Season Stanley Cup challenge. The rules are simple. In the snake draft, each player drafts 8 NHL teams.</description></item><item><title>Robin Lehner Speaks Out | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520258/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 13:14:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520258/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the weekend Robin Lehner went to Twitter to address the Jack Eichel situation, how the Sabres handled his ankle injury, teams giving “benzodiazepines to employees when they travel and Ambien”, and the treatment of players in Philadelphia by Alan Vigneault. Jeff and Elliotte address Lehner’s tweets (00:01) and discuss how teams, the league and the NHLPA might handle the comments.
They also touch on Elias Pettersson and Quinn Hughes (23:30) resigning with the Canucks, Travis Hamonic deciding to play this season (31:00), and 31 Thoughts: The Ripoff by Isabella Cadotte.</description></item><item><title>Darnell Nurse, Matthew Tkachuk &amp; Andrew Mangiapane | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520259/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520259/</guid><description>Podcast Description Darnell Nurse (10:00) chats with Jeff and Elliotte about his new contract with the Oilers and the negotiation process, playing and living with Connor McDavid, and a book that helped him manage his emotions throughout the season.
Matthew Tkachuk (21:30) joins the podcast to talk about the struggles his team had last season, managing emotions throughout the year, being coached by Darryl Sutter, playing without Mark Giordano, and his talks with his younger brother Brady about his contract negotiation with Ottawa.</description></item><item><title>A Proposal for the NHL’s Eichel Problem | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520260/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 17:47:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520260/</guid><description>Podcast Description The news pods are back! Jeff and Elliotte kick off this episode by previewing the upcoming “All or Nothing: Toronto Maple Leafs” docuseries on Amazon Prime (00:01) as they had the opportunity to screen it before its release on October 1st.
They then discuss the ongoing Jack Eichel situation in Buffalo and wonder if the NHL should get involved (19:00), provide some updates on the contract negotiations between Vancouver and their high profiled RFAs (28:10), what’s happening with Travis Hamonic (30:45), Seattle plays its first game in franchise history (32:00), Brady Tkachuk and the Senators continue talks (36:00), questions in New Jersey as they deal with an unvaccinated player on their roster (38:00), the Blues lock up their GM and make a trade with the Sens (45:00), Arizona hires John Ferguson Jr.</description></item><item><title>Nathan MacKinnon, Drew Doughty &amp; Steven Stamkos | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520261/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 21:34:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520261/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nathan Mackinnon (15:00) addresses the Nikita Zadorov comments from the summer, the importance of Gabriel Landeskog to the Avalanche, the process in Colorado, how he overcomes the feeling of being hesitant on the ice, and he tells the guys about an interesting line he played against this summer (that we could potentially see at the Olympics).
Drew Doughty (30:00) tells Jeff and Elliotte how it feels to be gunning for the Stanley Cup playoffs this season, his determination to make the Olympic team, what he would like to do post-career, the excitement to finally have fans back in arenas, and he clears the air around a certain story from the 2010 Olympics.</description></item><item><title>Auston Matthews, Mitch Marner, Tyler Toffoli &amp; Nick Suzuki | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520262/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520262/</guid><description>Podcast Description Auston Matthews (11:20) talks about his eventful off-season, how he’s feeling after his wrist surgery, what he’s excited about most this season, and he reflects on last season.
Mitch Marner (24:30) discusses how he plans on blocking out the noise, staying in touch with Auston Matthews throughout the summer, what he was best known for off the ice while with the London Knights, and potentially representing his country at the Olympics.</description></item><item><title>Bill Daly, Marc-André Fleury &amp; Jack Hughes | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520263/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 17:13:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520263/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bill Daly joins Jeff and Elliotte (10:00) to talk about arena capacity, salary cap, Olympics, COVID-19 protocol, Evander Kane, the Chicago Blackhawks investigation, data-tracking pucks, gambling, and the Arizona Coyotes.
Marc Andre-Fleury joins the podcast (26:45) to talk about his trade to Chicago, how this could potentially be his last season, most memorable moments from his time in Vegas, and how goaltending has changed since he joined the league.</description></item><item><title>Pierre-Luc Dubois, Mark Scheifele &amp; Jason Dickinson | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520264/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 23:25:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520264/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pierre-Luc Dubois chats with Jeff and Elliotte (7:20) about his skate-filled summer, focusing on his physical and mental health, watching different players around the league, and why he likes playing with Russian players.
Mark Scheifele joins the podcast (27:00) to chat about his skates with Ryan O’Reilly and Adam Oates in Lucan, Ontario, how he spent his summer, the aftermath following the hit on Jake Evans, keeping an eye on the Olympics, and his favourite Olympic hockey memory.</description></item><item><title>What’s In A Name? From the NWHL to the PHF | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520265/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 13:24:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520265/</guid><description>Podcast Description The National Women’s Hockey League (NWHL) is rebranding to become the Premier Hockey Federation (PHF). Tyler Tumminia, the commissioner of the PHF, joins Jeff and Elliotte to talk about the rebrand, why they made the change, conversations with other leagues, why they took “women” out of the league name, how does a rebrand of a league work behind the scenes, why they went with “federation”, ongoing talks with the NHL, and if they hope to attract more players by rebranding the league.</description></item><item><title>Kot-CANE-emi | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520266/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 15:59:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520266/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jesperi Kotkaniemi is a member of the Caroline Hurricanes. Jeff and Elliotte break down what went wrong between Kotkaniemi and Montreal Canadiens (00:01), why it’s challenging to find a quality centre in the NHL (Christian Dvorak traded to the Canadiens), what Carolina expects from Kotkaniemi, and if teams will view offer sheets differently going forward.
They also discuss other possible offer sheet candidates like Brady Tkachuk (26:30), provide an update on a pair of contract negotiations — Elias Pettersson and Quinn Hughes (28:00) as well as Kirill Kaprizov (28:30), and the guys wrap up the podcast by saying a few words about the late Jimmy Hayes (34:00).</description></item><item><title>Summer Offer Sheet Special | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520267/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:13:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520267/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Caroline Hurricanes strike back — two years later! On Saturday, the Canes tendered an offer sheet to restricted free agent Jesperi Kotkaniemi for one-year, $6.1-million. Jeff and Elliotte break down some of the details and possible thinking behind the offer sheet (1:30), discuss how Carolina decided to present the announcement publicly, contract extension talks between Kotkaniemi and the Canadiens, and the reaction out of Montreal.
They also touch on the Jack Eichel situation (18:30), why he chose to change his representation and the big meeting that took place a few weeks back in Buffalo.</description></item><item><title>Braiden Epp: Ready For The Fight | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520268/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520268/</guid><description>Podcast Description Earlier this year, the former captain of the Prince George Spruce Kings turned referee was diagnosed with multiple sclerosis. When 24-year-old Braiden Epp received the news, he quickly got involved in helping to find a cure for the disease.
Braiden joins Jeff and Elliotte to talk about some of the challenges he has faced since being diagnosed, why it was important to him and his peers to begin raising funds, getting back on the ice, memories from his junior hockey days, sharing the ice with Mathew Barzal, what he enjoys most about refereeing and the guys give Braiden a couple of in-game calls that a referee is forced to make but drive fans crazy.</description></item><item><title>Here’s 32 Thoughts | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520269/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 04:52:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520269/</guid><description>Podcast Description What a season! Jeff and Elliotte provide their thoughts on all 32 teams and what we might see from some GMs in the coming days/weeks. They also touch on the Evander Kane gambling allegations (00:00) and provide some context to the situation.
Pacific: Ducks (6:00), Flames (9:00), Oilers (10:30), Kings (16:30), Sharks (19:10), Kraken (21:00), Canucks (23:00), Vegas (27:00)
Central: Coyotes (33:45), Blackhawks (36:20), Avalanche (39:00), Stars (43:00), Wild (46:15), Predators (48:15), Blues (49:20), Jets (52:20)</description></item><item><title>Why Eichel Wants a Disc Replacement | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520270/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 06:10:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520270/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Chad Prusmack is a neurosurgeon based in Colorado who has provided Jack Eichel with a recommendation to correct a herniated disc in his neck by proceeding with artificial disc replacement surgery. Jeff and Elliotte chat with Dr. Prusmack about the procedure, the recovery and the risk associated with the surgery, and why this surgery would be more beneficial long-term rather than an anterior cervical discectomy with fusion (ACDF).</description></item><item><title>The Good and Bad of Draft Weekend | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520271/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 16:00:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520271/</guid><description>Podcast Description It was almost a perfect week for the NHL. Jeff and Elliotte kick off the podcast (00:00) discussing how the first round of the draft ended, how surprised they were by Montreal picking Logan Mailloux, if this can be avoided in the future, and how Chicago decided to make their first-round selection.
They also chat about the Seth Jones trade to Chicago (12:00), the rebuild in Columbus (20:50), a busy week for the Flyers (22:40), Buffalo trading Sam Reinhart (28:00), the latest on Jack Eichel (29:45), Vancouver trading for Oliver Ekman-Larsson and Conor Garland (34:00), Colorado gets one deal done but still have another with Gabriel Landeskog (43:00), where might we see Dougie Hamilton next season (49:30) and things to watch for this week (52:30).</description></item><item><title>Quick Expansion Chat | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520272/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 06:06:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520272/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Seattle Kraken has chosen their roster. Jeff and Elliotte talk about the day leading up to the expansion draft, why the Kraken didn’t pick up Carey Price (4:00), if Mark Giordano will be on the 2021-22 Seattle Kraken roster, and some thoughts on the overall team.
They also discuss Adam Larrson’s time in Edmonton (15:20), the high demand for Jamie Oleksiak, the Taylor Hall contract, and much more.</description></item><item><title>The Price is Right? | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520273/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 13:37:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520273/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Seattle Kraken are going to have some fun this week. Jeff and Elliotte open up the podcast with a deep dive into what they have been hearing out of Montreal (00:00), Seattle’s potential interest in Carey Price, and the risks associated with picking up the Vezina winning goaltender.
They also discuss the situation in Colorado between the Avalanche and Gabriel Landeskog (15:00), the Rangers signing Barclay Goodrow (20:00), what they are hearing around Jack Eichel (22:50) and Jaden Schwartz (24:30), if Yanni Gourde is more than just a third line centre (28:30), what a contract for Zach Hyman might look like (32:00), much more.</description></item><item><title>This is Luke Prokop’s podcast | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520274/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 17:05:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520274/</guid><description>Podcast Description Luke Prokop, Calgary Hitmen defencemen and Nashville Predators prospect.
Hi everyone. While the past year and a half has been crazy, it has also given me the chance to find my true self. I am no longer scared to hide who I am.
Today I am proud to publicly tell everyone that I am gay.
It has been quite the journey to get to this point in my life, but I could not be happier with my decision to come out.</description></item><item><title>Avalanche Prevention | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520275/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 07:10:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520275/</guid><description>Podcast Description The New Jersey Devils have acquired Ryan Graves from the Colorado Avalanche for Mikhail Maltsev and a second-round pick. Jeff and Elliotte break down the deal (00:00), what this means for Colorado and how New Jersey might approach their off-season with over $30 million in cap space (3:00).
They also discuss the Gabriel Landeskog contract negotiation (6:00), Zach Hyman (15:00), the goaltending situation in Toronto (20:00), some news out of Vancouver (18:00), and what Montreal might do with Shea Weber (27:00).</description></item><item><title>Listen before everything changes! | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520276/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 19:31:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520276/</guid><description>Podcast Description We lead the podcast off with some breaking news! The Minnesota Wild buy out the remaining four years of Zach Parise and Ryan Suter (00:00), the Canadiens agree to a three-year extension with head coach Dominique Ducharme (10:00), and Pekka Rinne calls it a career (11:00).
Duncan Keith is officially an Edmonton Oiler. Jeff and Elliotte discuss the trade between the Oilers and Blackhawks in detail (15:00), explain why (from their perspective) Ken Holland felt like it was the right move, and what the acquisition of Caleb Jones means for Chicago (32:00).</description></item><item><title>Lightning Strikes Twice | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520277/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 16:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520277/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Tampa Bay Lightning are the 2020-21 Stanley Cup champions. Jeff and Elliotte discuss (00:00) the Conn Smythe winning performance of Andrei Vasilevskiy, the entertaining post-game press conference from Nikita Kucherov, the play of the Tampa defense, and why the team was more motivated than ever before.
The guys also touch on what the Stanley Cup loss might mean for the Canadiens (23:30), the Carey Price and Shea Weber post-game press conference, finding that game breaker in the off-season, and if the club will resign Phillip Danault,</description></item><item><title>Back to Florida | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520278/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 08:23:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520278/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Montreal Canadiens find a way to extend the series. Jeff and Elliotte recap an exciting game 4 in Montreal (2:00), discuss the impact of Shea Weber throughout the game, wonder if there were more than 3500 fans in attendance at the Bell Centre and go over the lineup changes made by both coaches. They also break down the latest from Buffalo with Jack Eichel (20:30) and the hiring Sam Ventura (21:30) as the new VP of Hockey Strategy and Research, try to explain the hold up on the potential Duncan Keith trade (25:45) and they say a few words about the late Matiss Kivlenieks.</description></item><item><title>Devin Buffalo: Inspiring Indigenous Youth | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520279/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 16:13:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520279/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte are joined by former professional goaltender and the owner of Waniska Athletics, Devin Buffalo. Devin tells the guys about his path to Dartmouth College, playing junior hockey in Flin Flon, why it’s important to him to inspire the Indigenous youth of today, who he looked up to growing up, how visualization helped him get to where he is today, and he shares some of his experiences as an Indigenous goaltender.</description></item><item><title>Guelph Jammies | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520280/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 14:12:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520280/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Lightning continue to power through the Canadiens. Jeff and Elliotte recap game 3 of the Stanley Cup final (00:00), discuss the impact of Tyler Johnson and the impressive play of (injured) Nikita Kucherov, and explain how Conn Smythe voting works. Plus, they try to figure out where to get some Guelph Gryphons pajamas.
They also chat about the 8-year contract extension for Joel Eriksson Ek (24:15), L.A. Kings trading picks to acquire Viktor Arvidsson (27:30), what this trade means for Los Angeles (30:00), the ongoing talks around Duncan Keith (32:15), and Elliotte tells us about his first in-arena experience in well over a year (35:30).</description></item><item><title>Two Mistakes | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520281/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 14:12:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520281/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Canadiens outshoot the Lightning but don’t end up on top. Jeff and Elliotte break down game 2 (00:00), the play of the goaltenders, and how each goal had an interesting path to the back of the net.
They also discuss the upcoming hire of Andre Tourigny as the new head coach in Arizona (16:20), where we might see Duncan Keith next season (21:00), what to expect from Don Granato in Buffalo (23:50), a new 8-year contract for Ryan Nugent-Hopkins (25:50) and the guys get into some trophy talk to wrap up the podcast (33:00).</description></item><item><title>Patiocast | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520282/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 12:29:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520282/</guid><description>Podcast Description Elliotte is on a patio and the Stanley Cup final is underway! The guys recap game 1 (00:00) and detail how the Lightning attacked the Canadiens. They also discuss the state of the union address by Gary Bettman and Bill Daly highlighting the sexual assault allegations within the Blackhawks organization in 2010 (9:00) and where the league stands with the Olympics (12:45), the search for a coach in Arizona (17:00), Wayne Simmonds and the Leafs (19:00), if Mark Giordano could be an Oiler next season (22:30), where the Canucks are at with Quinn Hughes and Elias Petersson, and much more.</description></item><item><title>The Chicago Blackhawks and the Stanley Cup Final | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520283/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 06:40:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520283/</guid><description>Podcast Description A former Chicago Blackhawks player is suing the organization alleging sexual assault during the 2009-10 season. Jeff and Elliotte give their thoughts on the situation (00:00) and try to provide more details from what they have gathered.
They also preview the Stanley Cup final between the Canadiens and the Lightning (6:30), wonder how the Islanders will approach their off-season (19:30), discuss a couple of the coaching vacancies, and much more.</description></item><item><title>Olé, Olé, Olé, Olé!!!! | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520284/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 10:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520284/</guid><description>Podcast Description Saint-Jean-Baptiste Day, held annually on June 24, is the feast day of St John the Baptist… but today it was also the Montreal Canadiens day to break the fast and feast on the Golden Knights! Jeff and Elliotte discuss Montreal’s big win tonight (1:00) and also speculate about what this could mean for Vegas making moves for next year (12:15). A quick look ahead at what we can expect in Game 7 between the Islanders and Lightning (15:30).</description></item><item><title>Endangered Zebras | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520285/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 02:40:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520285/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a hotly contested Stanley Cup Playoffs series, officiating has taken centre stage as Jeff and Elliotte tackle controversial calls – or lack of calls – and tackle the question of what more can be done (6:24). But first, a surprise announcement and celebration spurs talk of hockey-inspired baby names (0:13).
The guys then discuss what makes Robin Lehner a standout on and off the ice (20:02), the possibility of an Oliver Ekman-Larsson trade (26:38), some potential coaching moves throughout the NHL (28:57), the process behind various NHL Awards selections (34:53), and finally Jeff and Elliotte answer your #Ask31 questions (38:00).</description></item><item><title>Coming Next Season: The 32 Thoughts Arm Wrestling Challenge | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520286/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 17:39:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520286/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subconjunctival hemorrhage occurs when a blood vessel breaks just underneath the surface of your eye. David Amber kicks off the podcast by telling Jeff and Elliotte the story of how a blood vessel broke in one of his eyes during his university days. The guys then chat about Carolina signing Rod Brind’Amour to a three-year deal (18:00) the same day he wins the Jack Adams Award, Tampa playing the villain role the last few seasons (12:20), the search for a coach in Seattle (23:45), Jack Eichel and Sam Reinhart possibly on the move (26:30), teams to watch as we approach the Entry &amp;amp; Expansion Drafts (29:30), and how Elliotte evaluates the Jim Gregory General Manager of the Year Award (32:00).</description></item><item><title>Islanders Mix Playoff Intensity With Identity | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520287/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 13:04:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520287/</guid><description>Podcast Description The third round of the Stanley Cup playoffs is underway! Jeff and Elliotte recap the Islanders-Lightning match-up (9:00) and the Canadiens-Golden Knights series (0:10) to kick off the podcast. They also discuss players who have been given permission to talk to other teams like Dougie Hamilton (19:30), the New York Rangers hiring Gerard Gallant as their new head coach (26:16), and which teams are keeping an eye on Jack Eichel (29:30).</description></item><item><title>The Final Four | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520288/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 16:51:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520288/</guid><description>Podcast Description The stage is set as Montreal, Tampa Bay, Las Vegas, and the New York Islanders battle it out for the Stanley Cup. Jeff and Elliotte recap the Golden Knights-Avalanche series (00:10), credit Peter DeBoer for the confidence he had in his team after going down two games, and wonder if he gets enough credit for what he’s done in his coaching career.
They also breifly look at the off-season for the Avalanche (15:30), what the Bruins planning on doing with Tuukka Rask, Taylor Hall and David Krejci (24:10), why Rod Brind’Amour hasn’t signed with the Hurricanes (19:00), and talk about some of the new faces behind the bench in Columbus (28:40), Calgary (33:10) and Vancouver (31:10).</description></item><item><title>Scott O’Neil: CEO of the New Jersey Devils &amp; Philadelphia 76ers | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520289/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 16:39:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520289/</guid><description>Podcast Description Scott O’Neil has held a number of executive positions in North American sports. He joins Jeff and Elliotte to talk about his new book “Be Where Your Feet Are”, finding stillness in your life, preparing for success as well as failure, the process with the 76ers, how his team is building out initiatives that better reflect their community, and he shares a Lou Lamoriello story from his early days with the NBA.</description></item><item><title>Snake Eyes for the Avalanche | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520290/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 11:22:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520290/</guid><description>Podcast Description Quick carcast to start the week! Jeff and Elliotte recap a pair of divisional match-ups (Avalanche-Golden Knights 2:30 &amp;amp; Jets-Habs 7:30) to kick off the podcast, discuss the gold medal victory by Gerard Gallant and Team Canada at the world hockey championship (19:00), the return of Stanley Cup playoff games on both sides of the border for the semifinals as Canadian federal government grants travel exemptions (26:00), the unstoppable Tampa Bay power play and chat about some exciting news from the OHL draft.</description></item><item><title>Scheifele Suspension | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520291/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 08:26:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520291/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mark Scheifele has been suspended four games for his hit on Jake Evans in game 1 of the Canadiens-Jets series. Jeff and Elliotte break down the wide variety of opinions (00:01) they’ve heard the last 24-hours from around the hockey world regarding the hit, what was said in the phone hearing, and if some players don’t understand how much the game changes during the Stanley Cup playoffs.
The guys also discuss officiating in the playoffs (19:00), recap all four divisional series (24:00), question if the conversation between Jack Eichel and the Sabres has changed now that Buffalo holds the first overall pick in the upcoming draft (35:45) and they finish the podcast off with a very open conversation about the situation in Toronto (47:40).</description></item><item><title>So You Think You’re Stressed … Here’s Steve Dangle! | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520292/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 09:49:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520292/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Montreal Canadiens force a game 7 against the Toronto Maple Leafs. Jeff and Elliotte discuss (25:00) the excitement around the game, fans in the stands in Montreal, and which team has the most to lose. Plus, they are joined by Steve Dangle (42:00) to talk about his frustrations, who he thinks is underperforming, and his watch events during every Leafs-Habs game on Sportsnet’s YouTube channel. They also touch on possible outcomes following the match penalty that was handed out to Ryan Reaves on Sunday night (00:01), the high flying scoring machine that is the Colorado Avalanche (2:20), Seth Jones deciding to test free agency (10:00) and PWHPA Secret Dream Gap Tour (1:02:00).</description></item><item><title>31 Lies | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520293/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 15:24:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520293/</guid><description>Podcast Description Back by popular demand, it’s the carcast with Jeff riding shotgun! The guys break down game 5 Leafs-Habs and what we could expect as the series heads back to Montreal where we’ll see fans in the stands (3:00). They also wonder if Pittsburgh (10:20) and Florida (24:30) will make any changes this off-season (10:20), preview game 7 Vegas-Minnesota, propose a few landing spots for Jim Rutherford as he finds himself an agent (32:00), discuss the shocking result in the Oilers-Jets series (36:00) and look ahead to Canes-Bolts next round (54:30).</description></item><item><title>A Stunning Sunday | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520294/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520294/</guid><description>Podcast Description A pair of recent Stanley Cup winners have been eliminated from the playoffs. Jeff and Elliotte break down what went wrong for Washington (6:40) and St. Louis (16:31) and list off some of their top priorities as they go into the off-season. They also discuss the return of Nikolaj Ehlers (0:00) and the Jets going up 3-0 in their series against the Oilers, the killer instinct of the Avalanche (24:00), Hall and the Bruins advancing (15:00), and Nazem Kadri appealing his 8-game suspension (28:15).</description></item><item><title>Post-Game Carcast | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520295/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 13:25:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520295/</guid><description>Podcast Description A late night of hockey means Elliotte joins us from the road. The guys discuss the scary incident that sent John Tavares to the hospital, the events that followed, and the type of response we might see from Toronto in game 2 on Saturday night. They also chat about the return of John Davidson to Columbus (18:20), Johnny Gaudreau’s comments at his end-of-season press conference (29:05), a heroic performance by Ryan Lomberg (14:00), and updates from Vancouver (21:50)</description></item><item><title>Paul Stastny and Six More, Please | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520296/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 16:52:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520296/</guid><description>Podcast Description Paul Stastny recently played his 1000th career NHL game. He joins Jeff and Elliotte to talk about (37:30) the milestone, his Hall of Fame father, the evolution of Nikolaj Ehlers, being coached by Paul Maurice, and how to slow down Connor McDavid and Leon Draisaitl.
The guys also recap the first couple days of the Stanley Cup playoffs (00:00), why Zach Parise was a healthy scratch (19:30), Colby Armstrong’s interview with Sidney Crosby (29:10), the performance by Craig Anderson and the Caps (32:25), the situation in Vancouver (59:30) and the unbelievable start to the Florida-Tampa series (01:00).</description></item><item><title>Sam the Florida Man | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520297/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520297/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Bennett has 15 points in 10 games with the Florida Panthers. He joins Jeff and Elliotte on the podcast (37:00) to talk about the trade that sent him to Florida, when he felt like his role was diminishing with the Flames, why he’s playing so well with the Panthers, the worldly skills of Alexander Barkov, how he prepares for the playoffs and what it’s like to play for Joel Quenneville.</description></item><item><title>Shane Wright: U18 World Champ | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520298/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 12:46:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520298/</guid><description>Podcast Description After winning a gold medal at the U18 World Championships with Team Canada, Shane Wright joins Jeff and Elliotte on the podcast to talk about his experience at the tournament, battling through a few minor illnesses during the tourney and what it means to represent Canada. They also chat about his favourite NHL team, players that impress him, and what he’d like to work on in the off-season.</description></item><item><title>The Muller Report | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520299/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 15:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520299/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirk Muller played in the NHL for 19 seasons and has been behind the bench since 2011. He joins Jeff and Elliotte on the podcast (42:00) to talk about Montreal’s impressive play in the bubble last season, how to find success as a player in a market like Montreal, his thoughts on Nick Suzuki and Jesperi Kotkaniemi, coaches that had an impact on his career, memories of Rendez-vous ’87, and his interest in finding a coaching job in the NHL.</description></item><item><title>Backes to the Future | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520300/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 16:44:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520300/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Backes has played for 3 teams (St. Louis, Boston and Anaheim) during his 15-year NHL career. He joined Jeff and Elliotte on the podcast (52:30) to talk about the celebration that took place on Wednesday night in St. Louis, what it was like to learn from veterans like Bill Guerin, Dallas Drake, Doug Weight and Keith Tkachuk when he joined the league, his rookie dinner, fighting Team Canada players ahead of the 2010 Olympics, being a buffer between the players and Ken Hitchcock, his work with dogs in the St.</description></item><item><title>Bob Hartley: A KHL Champion | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520301/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 15:27:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520301/</guid><description>Podcast Description He has won a championship in the NHL, AHL, NLA, QMJHL, and now the KHL. Avangard Omsk head coach, Bob Hartley, joins Jeff and Elliotte to talk about winning the Gagarin Cup, how Ilya Kovalchuk has changed since their days together in Atlanta, memories from his time with the Thrashers, if Kovalchuk wants to return to the NHL, coaches that he looked up to over the years, and he gives the guys a scouting report on Blue Jackets 21st overall draft pick, Yegor Chinakhov</description></item><item><title>The Brind’Amour Flex | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520302/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 14:28:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520302/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rod Brind’Amour is stepping up for his staff in Carolina. Jeff and Elliotte break down (00:10) the contract talks between Canes brass and their head coach, Brind’Amour’s request to see his staff taken care of before he signs his contract and what the market might look like if Brind’Amour was available.
They also discuss the Seattle Kraken now that they are officially the 32nd team in the NHL (14:00), teams not in the playoffs that caught the guys by surprise ….</description></item><item><title>Nashville’s Roman Empire | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520303/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 16:31:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520303/</guid><description>Podcast Description Roman Josi of the Nashville Predators joins the podcast for episode #200! He chats with Jeff and Elliotte (53:00) about the conversations amongst his teammates leading up to the trade deadline, what it’s like playing in front of Pekka Rinne, how meditation has helped him on and off the ice, and what he took away from each of his coaches in Nashville.
They then talk about Ryan Miller’s retirement (10:30), the AHL deciding not to hold playoffs except for the Pacific division (18:50), U.</description></item><item><title>A First-Class Gesture | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520304/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 16:21:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520304/</guid><description>Podcast Description Players from the Toronto Maple Leafs recently extended a helping hand to their AHL teammates. Jeff and Elliotte discuss Jason Spezza’s leadership in wanting to financially help his Marlies teammates and if we could see him in a managerial role in Toronto a few years from now.
They also chat about the playoff race in the Scotia North Division between Calgary, Montreal and Vancouver, the pressure on Montreal to make the playoffs, what Marc Bergevin might be feeling at this moment, and much more.</description></item><item><title>If You Give Us The Runway | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520305/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 18:40:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520305/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Vancouver Canucks played their first game in almost a month. Jeff and Elliotte discuss (00:00) what the victory against the Maple Leafs might mean for the team, the leadership of Bo Horvat, what was said in the locker room during the 2nd intermission, and the impressive play of Braden Holtby.
Debra Berman, National Stylist at Rogers Communications (Sportsnet &amp;amp; Hockey Night in Canada), joins the podcast (21:20) to talk about how Jeff and Elliotte’s fashion sense has evolved (thanks to her) over the last few years, which broadcasters weren’t willing to change their style, her approach when fitting on-air talent with a wardrobe that makes them feel good, and the important role hair, makeup &amp;amp; wardrobe play in the overall look and feel of a show.</description></item><item><title>Trade Deadline Wrap Up | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520306/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 15:39:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520306/</guid><description>Podcast Description The NHL Trade Deadline ended with a splash. Jeff and Elliotte discuss the trade between the Red Wings and Capitals (00:00), how it was structured, and why certain players (and picks) were in the mix. They also recap — Taylor Hall to Boston (17:30), the Pens picking up Jeff Carter (28:30), all the action from the Maple Leafs (30:40), the talks between Montreal and Tony DeAngelo, the additions in Florida (42:30), the situation in Vancouver, trade talks around Ryan Getzlaf (50:20) and much more.</description></item><item><title>Almost There | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520307/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 14:37:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520307/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Vancouver Canucks have re-signed Tanner Pearson. Jeff and Elliotte discuss why contract talks suddenly picked up (2:20), where things stand with Quinn Hughes and Elias Pettersson, why the Canucks might have to play out the regular season even if it means playing into the playoffs, and the general mood around the club as players and coaches deal with COVID-19.
They also chat about the Florida-Chicago trade (12:50), the cost of a first-round draft pick (14:30), possible suitors for Taylor Hall (19:00), what the Maple Leafs are possibly thinking as the deadline approaches (24:45), and they take some of your #Ask31 questions.</description></item><item><title>Who is Buying, Selling, or Staying ft. Chris Johnston | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520308/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 15:19:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520308/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Vancouver Canucks have 16 players and 3 coaches on the NHLs COVID-19 protocol list. Jeff and Elliotte provide an update on the situation in the Lower Mainland (00:01) and discuss possible outcomes from this including the potential of a playoff bubble and how it might affect the North Division for the remainder of the season.
Chris Johnston of Sportsnet joins the guys (10:40) to help preview the upcoming trade deadline.</description></item><item><title>Philadelphia Cheesed | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520309/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 15:20:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520309/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Flyers have some serious decisions to make over the coming months. Jeff and Elliotte discuss the situation in Philadelphia as the team goes through a difficult stretch (00:02), who might be available for the expansion draft, why Shayne Gostisbehere was waived, and how they might approach the trade deadline.
They also chat about the recent game postponement between Vancouver-Calgary due to COVID-19 protocol (19:20), the signing of Thatcher Demko (21:30), what Vancouver plans on doing (27:30) with their unsigned players (and coaches), goaltending in Toronto (26:00), what is happening in Nashville (30:00), teams to watch as we approach the deadline (Carolina 35:20 &amp;amp; Florida 38:20), Spencer Knight signing with the Panthers (40:10), a memorable post-game presser from Erik Karlsson (49:30), some of your #Ask31 questions (56:30) and much more.</description></item><item><title>Peeling Back the Layers | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520310/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 15:34:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520310/</guid><description>Podcast Description Veteran referee Tim Peel “no longer will be working NHL games now or in the future” according to the NHL after his hot mic incident. Jeff and Elliotte discuss how quickly the league made their decision (00:00), if the punishment was too harsh, the impact the incident could have on the league’s business model as it related to gambling, the relationship between players and officials, and what a perfect game for calls looks like to the guys.</description></item><item><title>The State of Women’s Hockey | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520311/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520311/</guid><description>Podcast Description The National Women’s Hockey League is set to return to play this weekend in Massachusetts to give out the Isobel Cup to one of the four remaining teams. Marisa Ingemi of NBC Sports and Sportsnet joins the podcast to talk about the leagues return to play, the relationship between the NWHL and PWHPA, the NHLs potential future involvement in women’s hockey, the impact Dani Rylan Kearney had on the NWHL, the job Tyler Tumminia has done since joining the league, and she gives us a bit of a preview to what we’re going to see this weekend in Boston.</description></item><item><title>News &amp; Notes plus Anton Forsberg’s Amazing Odyssey | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520312/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 12:59:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520312/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff joined the Hockey Night in Canada crew for his first in-arena game in over 14 months. He tells Elliotte about his experience in Montreal (00:00) and what surprised him most about being back in an NHL rink. They also break down what they’ve heard from around the league including teams to keep an eye on as we approach the trade deadline (15:10), a potential fit for Conor Garland (16:00), what Canadian club might be interested in Mattias Ekholm (23:50), if Ryan Ellis is a piece Nashville would be willing to move (10:30), some literal puck talk (55:00), Elliotte picks a mystery player to replace Anders Lee (32:15), they address the Jonathan Quick to Toronto rumours (31:00) and much more.</description></item><item><title>“Crossroads” With Kaleb Dahlgren | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520313/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 15:59:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520313/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Buffalo Sabres have parted ways with head coach Ralph Krueger. Jeff and Elliotte discuss why the team made the move (00:01), question if Zoom media availabilities add to the negativity around the club, which players are untouchable going into the trade deadline, and if the new coaching staff can help Rasmus Dahlin get out of his slump.
They also chat about the lack of goaltending in Ottawa (32:00), explain why Jimmy Vesey wasn’t available for the Canucks on Wednesday night (26:00), debate if coaches are needed on the bench (after watching the Rangers beat up on the Flyers) and take some of your #Ask31 (1:09:00) questions.</description></item><item><title>Join Elliotte On His Drive Home | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520314/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520314/</guid><description>Podcast Description Following the Maple Leafs-Senators game on Sunday night, Elliotte called Jeff on his way home from the studio to talk some hockey. Here’s their conversation.
Some of the topics that were discussed — Joey Daccord’s memorable night in Ottawa (00:00), the struggles in Toronto (7:30), why Nashville will be the team to watch as the trade deadline approaches (12:00), the recent “rebuild” comment by Erik Karlsson (15:00), new life in Calgary under Darryl Sutter (17:45), the red-hot Islanders (19:40), a theory on the secondary rights deal south of the board (30:20) and much more.</description></item><item><title>ESPN And The Future Of The NHL | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520315/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 15:04:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520315/</guid><description>Podcast Description The NHL has found its (back-to-the-future) broadcast partner in the United States. Jeff and Elliotte discuss why ESPN was the league’s top choice (13:10), what it means for NHL finances and what it’s like when a broadcaster loses its rights. They also break down the Bill Daly and Gary Bettman virtual media conference (2:00), offer an update on the NHL Draft and Lottery (9:40), wonder which teams are sellers and buyers going into the trade deadline (27:10) and much more.</description></item><item><title>Tom Wilson And A New Era For Women’s Hockey | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520316/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 17:08:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520316/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Wilson is suspended seven games for his hit on Brandon Carlo. Jeff and Elliotte break down the decision (00:00) and wonder if the number of games would have been different if Wilson wasn’t involved. They then chat about Jim Benning’s Canucks press conference (13:00), the continued struggles in Buffalo (18:00) and answer some #Ask31 questions (25:00).
The guys are also joined by NWHL interim commissioner Tyler Tumminia (36:30) who announces the league’s return, what went wrong in Lake Placid, what types of skills she’s leaned on to get through this difficult period, her openness to working with the PWHPA, what she envisions for the game, growing up around baseball and the types of business conversations she has with her husband, Pittsburgh Pirates GM Ben Cherington.</description></item><item><title>Remembering Walter | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520317/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 14:55:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520317/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte remember Canada’s hockey dad, Walter Gretzky, who passed away late Thursday night at the age of 82.
They also touch on Calgary’s coaching change with Darryl Sutter taking charge (12:00), Trent Frederic’s sneaky toughness (29:30), the hiring of Sean Burke in Montreal (21:00), Jarmo Kekalainen’s confidence in John Tortorella (36:00), the Leafs’ sweep of the Oilers (37:10) and much more.
Then, Minnesota captain Jared Spurgeon joins the podcast (44:00) to talk about the addition of Kirill Kaprizov, the team’s hot run this season, getting the ‘C’, signing a new contract in the off-season, the Wild’s retro jersey and his junior days in Spokane.</description></item><item><title>Sam Gagner: Taking Over the Marlboros with John Tavares | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520318/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 17:24:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520318/</guid><description>Podcast Description Detroit Red Wings forward Sam Gagner joins Jeff and Elliotte. They discuss why he and fellow Marlboros alumnus John Tavares wanted to get involved in minor hockey, where he was when Elliotte broke the news on Hockey Night in Canada, if he was surprised by the hockey community’s reaction, the types of changes he’d like to implement within the organization and some of the challenges that await them.</description></item><item><title>Best Game Ever Last Week | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520319/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 19:51:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520319/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you didn’t stay up late on Saturday night, you missed an exciting game in San Jose. Jeff and Elliotte discuss the back-and-forth contest between the Blues and Sharks (00:10), Jordan Binnnington’s tantrum and the current state of the St. Louis Blues. They also take your #Ask31 questions throughout the podcast (12:50), talk Nathan MacKinnon (14:20), the new look Wild (16:30), signature moves (22:00), Columbus’s difficult stretch (25:00), NBA (NHL?</description></item><item><title>The NHL Draft: What’s Best For The Game | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520320/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 15:45:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520320/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Canadiens have parted way with head coach Claude Julien and assistant Kirk Muller. Jeff and Elliotte discuss the changes in Montreal (00:00) and what we know about interim head coach Dominique Ducharme. The guys also chat about the 2021 NHL Draft (19:30) and if the date should be moved, an interesting moment from the Kings-Blues game (26:00), the situation in Buffalo (36:25) with Jeff Skinner (28:00) and much more.</description></item><item><title>It’s Good That You Hate Canada. Plus: Turtleneck Tales. | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520321/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 17:14:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520321/</guid><description>Podcast Description The turtleneck stole the show! Jeff opens the podcast asking Elliotte about his Hockey Night in Canada fashion choice (00:00), the inspiration behind it and the reaction on social media. They also talk hockey — the pair of games in Lake Tahoe (23:00), Sidney Crosby and Travis Zajac playing in their 1000th games (30:30), the L.A.’s impressive run (36:45), Calgary’s tough stretch (41:20), who’s available in Nashville (40:00) and why everyone south of the border hates the North Division (14:40).</description></item><item><title>What’s Going On Off The Ice In Arizona? | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520322/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 14:26:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520322/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte discuss Katie Strang’s investigation into the Arizona Coyotes’ alleged business practices and internal workings (00:00) and what they have been hearing. They also touch on Connor McDavid hitting 500 points (18:00), Elliotte’s mystery player (31:20), potential moves in Nashville (35:00), Florida’s strong start (37:00), another PWHPA partnership (42:00) and much more. Then Blake Bolden joins the guys (45:00) to talk about her role as an AHL scout with the L.</description></item><item><title>Tavares And Gagner: NHL Players And Minor Hockey Owners | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520323/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 14:17:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520323/</guid><description>Podcast Description John Tavares and Sam Gagner will operate the Toronto Marlboros minor-hockey club. Jeff and Elliotte explain why the pair were interested in the team (00:00), how it will work and why this is good for the Greater Toronto Hockey League. They also discuss the surprising Chicago Blackhawks (19:00), the struggling Predators (23:30), Francesco Aquilini’s tweet supporting his GM and coach (28:40), Brian Burke’s send off on Hockey Night in Canada (32:00) and much more.</description></item><item><title>We Texted WWE Superstar Edge… And Here We Are | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520324/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520324/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Royal Rumble champion, Adam Copeland a.k.a. Edge, joins Jeff and Elliotte to chat about his Toronto Maple Leafs fandom, his memorabilia collection, Sidney Crosby’s golden goal in 2010, falling in love with wrestling, returning from rehab and much more.
Music Outro: The Zolas – I Feel The Transition
Find more music by The Zolas here
This podcast is produced and sound designed by Amil Delic, and hosted by Jeff Marek and Elliotte Friedman.</description></item><item><title>Bye Bye, Burkie | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520325/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520325/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brian Burke is joining the Pittsburgh Penguins as their President of Hockey Operations. But before he goes, he joins Jeff and Elliotte to chat about why he decided to get back into an executive position, how the deal came together, what he likes about the organization, the message from ownership and much more. This podcast is produced and sound designed by Amil Delic, and hosted by Jeff Marek and Elliotte Friedman.</description></item><item><title>When You Mess Up, Fess Up And Dress Up | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520326/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 21:24:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520326/</guid><description>Podcast Description An offside controversy clouded Carolina’s win over the Blue Jackets Sunday. Jeff and Elliotte break down the situation (00:00), where the league went wrong and discuss if a rule change is needed. They also examine the struggling Canucks (20:30 &amp;amp; 38:00), McDavid and Draisaitl’s ice time (33:00), the injury to Wayne Simmonds (34:00), the talks around Sam Bennett (29:40), Florida’s first regulation loss of the season (35:30) and much more.</description></item><item><title>Our COVID Reality | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520327/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520327/</guid><description>Podcast Description The NHL is reacting quickly to its COVID-19 outbreak. Jeff and Elliotte discuss (00:00) how the virus is impacting teams, protocols being implemented to prevent further spread and what the league might do with so many games to make up. They also check in on Pittsburgh’s GM search (20:00) and talk about Tony DeAngelo’s time in New York (24:20), the Rangers hosting a PWHPA game (26:00), the NWHL suspending its season (28:00), Paul Maurice defending his captain (30:45), the struggling Canucks (37:50) and much more.</description></item><item><title>Kevin Bieksa On The Road And Tony DeAngelo On Waivers | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520328/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520328/</guid><description>Podcast Description This podcast took two hours to record as the news continued to trickle in. Jeff and Elliotte on what they were hearing throughout Sunday (00:30) as the New York Rangers placed Tony DeAngelo on waivers. They also discuss trade requests from Sam Bennett (10:30) and Victor Mete (13:45), the search for a GM in Pittsburgh (15:45), Lee Stempniak’s new role in Arizona (18:20), and much more. Plus, Kevin Bieksa joins the podcast (25:45) from… Toledo?</description></item><item><title>Two Shockers: Jim Rutherford And Tim &amp; Sid | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520329/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520329/</guid><description>Podcast Description After 20 years of entertaining listeners and viewers, Tim &amp;amp; Sid is changing — Sid is moving on. Jeff and Elliotte are joined by Tim Micallef and Sid Seixeiro (19:00) to talk about their long-time friendship and work together. Dating back to their days as interns at Headline Sports, then cutting their chops at TheScore with Elliotte, and on to Sportsnet 590 The FAN and Sportsnet TV, it’s been a special partnership.</description></item><item><title>Jarmo Kekalainen on the Dubois-Laine Deal | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520330/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 01:58:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520330/</guid><description>Podcast Description Columbus Blue Jackets GM Jarmo Kekalainen joins Jeff and Elliotte (11:50) to discuss how and when the trade with the Winnipeg Jets came together, why Jack Roslovic was an important piece, the possible misconception about Columbus as an organization and community, and how the club tried to move up in the 2016 draft to select Patrik Laine. The guys also talk about Vancouver’s struggles (51:00), Brent Burns’ silky mitts (54:00), youthful flair in New Jersey (57:45), ideas around the draft (1:07:10), the NHL suspending John Chayka (1:00:30) and much more.</description></item><item><title>What Now For Pierre-Luc Dubois? | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520331/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520331/</guid><description>Podcast Description Correction: The voice at the start of the podcast is Jody Shelley not John Forslund. Our apologies.
Pierre-Luc Dubois played five shifts for a total of 3:55 during Columbus’s overtime loss to Tampa Bay Thursday night. Following the game, Jeff and Elliotte take a stab at figuring out the complex situation (00:00) between the Blue Jackets and Dubois.
Then they discuss the details around Washington’s six-figure fine for violating COVID-19 protocols (13:00), the league’s plans if a team can’t finish the season and how cancelling games could impact players’ pensions.</description></item><item><title>Keith Yandle Scored While We Were Recording | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520332/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 16:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520332/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hockey is back and so is the drama. Jeff and Elliotte discuss the situation in Florida between Keith Yandle and the Panthers (00:00), if Pierre-Luc Dubois will be a Blue Jacket by season’s end (16:30), Jakub Voracek’s post-game comments on Friday (27:30), the impressive Minnesota Wild (49:30) and much more.
Music Outro: Ten Kills the Pack – Body
You can find more music from Ten Kills the Pack here</description></item><item><title>31 Season Previews | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520333/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 15:33:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520333/</guid><description>Podcast Description The NHL season starts today and Jeff and Elliotte preview it with a thought on each team, a couple things they’ll be keeping their eyes on, Stanley Cup predictions and much more. East Division (00:00) Central Division (27:00) West Division (53:30) North Division (1:14:30)
Music Outro: Scenic Route to Alaska – Call Your Friends
We also featured “Polarized” by Scenic Route to Alaska during our last segment
You can find their latest “Time for Yourself” here</description></item><item><title>The NHL Adapts On The Fly, Plus Jordan Subban: Hockey Player And Amplifying Entrepreneur | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520334/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 21:30:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520334/</guid><description>Podcast Description Some NHL training camps aren’t off to a good start thanks to COVID — the Stars are dealing with an outbreak in their organization and the Blue Jackets have cancelled practice “out of an abundance of caution and in accordance with NHL Covid-19 protocols.” Jeff and Elliotte discuss how the league will handle the positive cases, if we’ll see a bubble scenario again and what other teams are thinking.</description></item><item><title>Reporting to Training Camp | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520335/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 02:34:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520335/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte kick off 2021 with a conversation about how some organizations accept losing, what it takes to create a winning culture and how, sometimes, you have to lose to win.
They also discuss what the North Division could mean for the NHL from a revenue standpoint, expectations for a pair of Canadian teams, Pierre-Luc Dubois signing an extension, Zdeno Chara finding a new home and much more.</description></item><item><title>Welcome To Our Holiday Party | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520336/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520336/</guid><description>Podcast Description As 2020 comes to a close (thank goodness), Jeff and Elliotte host their first 31 Thoughts holiday party with friends from the Sportsnet hockey department. David Amber on his 15-year-old skates, an update on hunting season from Louie DeBrusk, Tara Slone reminisces about a sauna experience in Thunder Bay, Christine Simpson shares a story about her brother Craig, Caroline Cameron plays us a song, Kelly Hrudey talks about his caroling days, Anthony Stewart explains why his sister’s lasagna is better than your lasagna, Ryan Leslie tells us about a memorable flight home from L.</description></item><item><title>Let’s Make A Deal : The NHL And (Our Interview Guest) Anthony Duclair | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520337/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520337/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mark your calendars! The NHL season begins January 13 with a 56-game regular season that concludes May 8. Jeff and Elliotte discuss all the details, including unlimited goalies at training camp, possible locations for teams and more.
The guys also chat with newly signed Florida Panther Anthony Duclair about why he chose not to have an agent, what he took away from the experience and why Florida was the right fit before he reminisces about his days with the Quebec Remparts under Patrick Roy.</description></item><item><title>Tyler Seguin: All Business | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520338/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 14:11:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520338/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tyler Seguin has had a busy off-season rehabbing a torn labrum in Dallas. But while on the couch, he’s found time to build out his lifestyle brand, NINE ONE and do a photo shoot for his new favourite fragrance. Seguin joins the guys to discuss why he’s decided to focus on off-ice business interests, how his rehab is progressing, share a few stories from the Edmonton bubble and more.</description></item><item><title>The NHL Inches Closer To A Return | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520339/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 16:46:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520339/</guid><description>Podcast Description The league and the NHLPA are getting their pucks in a row for a return. Jeff and Elliotte discuss the long-term effects of the CBA, possible target dates, division realignment and ads on helmets.
They are also joined by newly hired Florida Panthers goaltending consultant François Allaire, who talks about his role, how it came about, the biggest changes between the pipes in the past decade, working with Patrick Roy and J-S Giguère, and the perfect height (if there is one) for a goaltender.</description></item><item><title>Rick Vaive: On Hockey And Life | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520340/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 18:16:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520340/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Catch 22: My Battles, in Hockey and in Life” is a new book by Rick Vaive with Scott Morrison.
Rick joins Jeff and Elliotte to talk about his new book, the Birmingham Bulls, playing with Bill Derlago, being the first Leaf to score 50 goals, Harold Ballard as an owner, coaches he enjoyed playing for, Börje Salming off the ice, and much more.
Music Outro: Hiroshi Sato – Say Goodbye</description></item><item><title>What We Could See During The 2021 Season That We’ve Never Seen Before | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520341/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 22:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520341/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte offer some updates on the NHL’s return, where the owners stand at the moment, salary deferrals and possible tweaks to the 2021 season like taxi squads, ads on jerseys, expanded playoffs and a shortened training camp/pre-season. RIP Fred Sasakamoose
This podcast is produced and sound designed by Amil Delic, and hosted by Jeff Marek and Elliotte Friedman. Audio Credits: New York Islanders
The views and opinions expressed in this podcast are those of the hosts and guests and do not necessarily reflect the position of Rogers Media Inc.</description></item><item><title>Mark Guy: From The Hockey Industry To The Auto Industry | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520342/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 02:35:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520342/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mark Guy has been an NHL agent with Newport Sports Management for more than 20 years. He’s represented big names like Steven Stamkos, Alex Pieterangelo, Bo Horvat, Travis Konecny, Tom Wilson, and the Subban and Strome brothers. But now he’s getting out.
Mark joins Jeff and Elliotte to talk about why he decided to leave the business, who he’ll miss working with, the biggest changes he’s seen in the industry and some of his more memorable negotiations.</description></item><item><title>Quick Check In | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520343/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 22:12:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520343/</guid><description>Podcast Description Talks around the 2021 NHL season are heating up. Jeff and Elliotte break down what they’ve heard regarding start and end dates, fans in the stands, sponsorship and the negotiation between the league and its players.
This episode is dedicated to the late Erin Paul. Our condolences to her family and friends.
This podcast is produced and sound designed by Amil Delic, and hosted by Jeff Marek and Elliotte Friedman.</description></item><item><title>Stan Bowman: A Change In Approach, Not A Change In Direction | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520344/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 16:13:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520344/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Chicago Blackhawks GM joins Jeff and Elliotte for a wide-ranging discussion. They talk about being transparent with the fanbase, building from within rather than through free agency, playing youth over veterans, how management approached the Jonathan Toews comments, the challenges he faces as a GM during the pandemic and much more.
Letter to their fans: https://www.sportsnet.ca/nhl/article/blackhawks-publish-letter-fans-confirming-team-rebuilding/
Music Outro: Sam Roberts Band – I Like the Way You Talk About the Future</description></item><item><title>Adam Oates: Get The Toys Off The Ice | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520345/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 18:01:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520345/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Hockey Hall of Famer and skills coach joins Jeff and Elliotte to talk about the types of drills that frustrate him and what coaches should focus on when designing practices before offering some creative pointers. They also discuss coaching during the pandemic, some of the challenges around travel and the approach he has when working with professionals versus youth players. Music Outro: Satellite &amp;amp; the Harpoonist – Ballet in a Phone Booth</description></item><item><title>Jamie Bozzo: Managing Players’ Careers | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520346/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520346/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sports Professional Management Inc. represents some big names in hockey, including William Nylander, Johnny Gaudreau, Torey Krug and Brandon Saad, and has a total value of active contracts that exceeds $222 million.
Jamie Bozzo handles client relationships for SPM, dealing with players and their families on all kinds of specialized scenarios. She joins Jeff and Elliotte for a wide-ranging discussion about prepping clients for free agency, working with players and organizations around trades, financial advice and much more, including detailing the work put in on Nylander’s down-to-the-wire extension with the Maple Leafs in late 2018.</description></item><item><title>There Was Alcohol Involved | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520347/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 18:31:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520347/</guid><description>Podcast Description After the longest NHL season ever, a few drinks are deserved all around as Jeff and Elliotte run down the past week in the NHL. Vegas landed the biggest free-agency fish in Alex Pietrangelo (00:01), to the displeasure of some Golden Knights players and their agents. The Canucks added Nate Schmidt (28:30), but only after they lost some key contributors. Taylor Hall bet on himself in Buffalo (19:00), Torey Krug took his talents to St.</description></item><item><title>Emptying Out The Notebook | 32 Thoughts: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5986520348/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 15:36:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5986520348/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff and Elliotte look at all 31 teams and discuss what their goals should be for the off-season (Atlantic – 34:15; Metropolitan – 47:30; Central – 1:05:30; Pacific – 1:17:45). But before doing that, they kick things off with a Word Association built specifically to challenge Elliotte, discuss Tampa’s tough road to the Stanley Cup (21:00) and how a flat cap will impact player salaries next season (31:00).</description></item></channel></rss>