<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Modern Love on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/modern-love/</link><description>Recent content in Modern Love on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/modern-love/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>I Married My Subway Crush | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Zoe Fishman couldn’t stop thinking about the man she called her “subway crush.” For years, she saw Ronen on the train and admired him from afar.
When they finally connected, it turned out Ronen felt the same, and they began a blissful life together. But when their story took a devastating turn, Zoe had to grapple with longing for Ronen at a distance again.
For the final episode of our season, we hear about the joy and loss that showed up in Zoe’s life, and the remarkable way she learned to live with both of them.</description></item><item><title>Author Read: I Married My Subway Crush | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 09:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Zoe Fishman reads her Modern Love essay, “The Subway Crush Who Crushed Me.&amp;quot;
To hear our conversation with Zoe, listen to the episode: “I Married My Subway Crush.”
Zoe Fishman is the author of several novels, most recently “The Fun Widow’s Book Tour.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Author Read: Our 34-Year Age Gap Didn’t Matter, Until It Did | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010003/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sonja Falck reads her Modern Love essay, “Our 34-Year Age Gap Was Showing.&amp;quot;
To hear our conversation with Sonja, listen to the episode: “Our 34-Year Age Gap Didn’t Matter, Until It Did.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Our 34-Year Age Gap Didn’t Matter, Until It Did | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sonja Falck was immediately attracted to Colin, the professor who was renting her a room. He was intellectual and lively, with bright eyes that drew her in. It was only after they were already dating that Sonja found out Colin’s age: He was 34 years older than her.
Their age gap didn’t give them pause. Sonja and Colin got married, had kids and built a fulfilling life together. But when Colin reached his 80s, and Sonja was in her mid-40s, Sonja realized she was craving a level of physical intimacy that Colin could no longer provide.</description></item><item><title>Author Read: Two Boys on Bikes, Falling in Love | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010005/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eric Darnell Pritchard reads their Modern Love essay, “Two Boys on Bicycles, Falling in Love.&amp;quot;
To hear our conversation with Eric, listen to the episode: “Two Boys on Bicycles, Falling in Love.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Boys on Bikes, Falling in Love | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eleven-year-old Eric Darnell Pritchard was a solitary kid. They preferred reading romance novels to playing sports, and watching soap operas to hanging out with the neighborhood kids. Although they were obsessed with love, they felt too different to find a romantic connection of their own.
Then, a cute boy moved in across the street. To Eric’s surprise, they both “like liked” each other. But when Eric told the wrong person about their new boyfriend, things quickly spun out of control.</description></item><item><title>Author Read: He Cared About Me, So I Broke Up With Him | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010007/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jessica Slice reads her Modern Love essay, “He Cared About Me, So I Broke Up With Him.&amp;quot;
To hear our conversation with Jessica, listen to the episode: “He Cared About Me, So I Broke Up With Him.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>He Cared About Me, So I Broke Up With Him | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010008/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Jessica Slice started dating a man named David, there was a lot to like about him. They could nerd out about books and board games, he was thoughtful and kind.
But Jessica had a problem. The more caring David was, the more she recoiled. &amp;ldquo;He’s the greatest!&amp;rdquo; She texted her sister. &amp;ldquo;But I doubt I’ll go out with him again.&amp;rdquo; This wasn’t the first time she&amp;rsquo;d felt like fleeing from affection, but something about David made Jessica hesitate.</description></item><item><title>Did I Fail as a Parent? | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rick Reiss was scared for his teenage son, Gabriel. Gabe was struggling with depression and mood swings, and no amount of therapy or medication seemed to work.
But when Gabe became violent, Rick wasn’t just scared for his son; he was scared of his son. Rick and his wife felt as if they had to do something drastic. So they made the decision to send Gabe to a wilderness therapy program.</description></item><item><title>Author Read: My Sweaty Revenge | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010010/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Christi Clancy reads her Modern Love essay, “Revenge of the Friend.&amp;quot;
To hear our conversation with Christi, listen to the episode: “My Sweaty Revenge.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>My Sweaty Revenge | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Christi Clancy had been avoiding her best friend’s ex-husband. He’d unexpectedly left her friend for another woman. After supporting her friend through the pain and heartbreak, Christi couldn’t help but resent the ex-husband for all the damage he’d done.
So when the man walked into Christi’s spin class, she saw an opportunity to exact revenge in the best way she knew how: on a spin bike.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>I Wrote This Essay, but Then Changed My Mind | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Heather Sellers wrote her Modern Love essay in 2013, about reconnecting with her elderly, estranged father. Although their relationship was painful, Heather made sure that her last words to her father were “I love you.” And at the time, that felt like closure.
Now, 10 years later, Heather tells our host, Anna Martin, that she would write a completely different essay today. She sees her father, and herself, in a new light — and realizes that “forgiveness” isn’t as simple a concept as she once believed.</description></item><item><title>Author Read: What Does It Mean to Be a Kept Woman? | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010013/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Deanna Fei reads her Modern Love essay, “To Keep but Not Be Kept.&amp;quot;
To hear our conversation with Deanna, listen to the episode: “What Does It Mean to Be a Kept Woman?”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What Does It Mean to Be a Kept Woman? | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Deanna Fei did not need a man. She was in her 20s, living in Shanghai on a Fulbright scholarship, writing her first novel: a book about fiercely independent Chinese women, very much like Deanna herself.
Growing up as a first-generation Chinese American, Deanna resented the way some men, specifically white men, looked down on her. She refused to be anyone’s fetish. By the time she arrived in Shanghai, she had sworn off dating white men all together.</description></item><item><title>Author Read: Don’t Hide in the Bathroom Stall | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Susan Gelles reads her Modern Love essay, “Single, and Surrounded by a Wall of Men.&amp;quot;
To hear our conversation with Susan, listen to the episode: “Don&amp;rsquo;t Hide in the Bathroom Stall.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Don’t Hide in the Bathroom Stall | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Susan Gelles was a lawyer in her 30s who was too busy to find love. But after finally admitting that she was lonely, Susan did something that went against all her best instincts. She started attending singles mixers.
On this episode, Susan shares her disastrous mismatches, awkward flirtations and the story of how she almost missed her chance to meet the love of her life.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Author Read: Have You Ever Kept a Secret From Your Wife? | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010017/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Khalid Abdulqaadir reads his Modern Love essay, “The Polygraph Test That Saved My Marriage.&amp;quot;
To hear our conversation with Khalid, listen to the episode: “Have You Ever Kept a Secret From Your Wife?”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Have You Ever Kept a Secret From Your Wife? | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Khalid Abdulqaadir’s life was full of secrets. He started keeping them when he was a teenager, after his father was accused of an unimaginable crime. He didn’t want to explain his family history every time he started a new relationship. So his secrets followed him, even as he got married.
Many years later, Khalid was interviewing for a job in the U.S. government, and he was required to take a polygraph test.</description></item><item><title>I Needed David Schwimmer’s Help | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Samantha Joseph’s childhood was scattered with golden trips to California to visit her Aunt Gail. Aunt Gail was the cool aunt. She worked in Hollywood and befriended actors like Robin Williams, Mayim Bialik and the cast of “Friends.” And yet she was still relatable (she’d get on the floor and play like a kid).
One day, those trips to California stopped: Aunt Gail no longer wanted to see Samantha’s family.</description></item><item><title>Essay Read: I Had To Stop Asking Why | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 19:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Samantha Joseph reads her Modern Love essay, “I Had to Stop Asking Why.” You can listen to Anna’s interview with Samantha in the “Modern Love” podcast feed - the episode is called “I Needed David Schwimmer’s Help:.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Essay Read: How I Lost the Fiancé But Won the Honeymoon | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nell Stephens reads her Modern Love essay, “How I Lost the Financé but Won the Honeymoon.” You can listen to Anna’s interview with Nell in the “Modern Love” podcast feed.
You can also read Nell’s essay on the New York Times website here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How I Lost the Fiancé But Won the Honeymoon | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bored and in love, Nell Stevens found a hobby combing the internet and entering her name into online contests. But, when she actually wins a prize — a luxury honeymoon in India — her world falls apart: The man she thought she was going to marry breaks up with her.
She decides to go on the trip anyway.
On today’s show, the host Anna Martin talks with Nell about her fiancé-less honeymoon — and what she had discovered about herself by the time she returned home.</description></item><item><title>My Invisible Husband | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010023/</guid><description>Podcast Description The last time David visited his ailing grandmother, he hid his wedding ring in his pocket. He’d never told her about his identity as a gay, married man. Fearful David’s grandmother would disown him, his family never told her about David’s loving marriage with his husband, Constantino. It was an untruth David lived with until the day she died.
Today, David shares how that untruth left a gaping hole in his relationship with his grandmother — and the power of telling the truth in his eulogy.</description></item><item><title>The Day My Family Changed Forever | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Imagine you are on vacation. Your favorite shirt is waiting for you in your suitcase. You go to put it on, only to realize it’s not there. You forgot it, and there’s nothing you can do now.
That’s an experience that played out time and again for Natalie Muñoz, who split her childhood and adolescence between her parents’ houses after their divorce. Now that she’s turning 18, she tells us how she’s finding a balance that works better for her.</description></item><item><title>The Gift of Holiday Men | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kema Christian-Coates’s childhood was filled with “holiday men,” absentee fathers — including her own — who returned each year around Christmas only to disappear again. Her father’s absence left a hole in her life and the fear that she, like her mother and grandmother, would never find a man she could rely on.
Today, we hear Kema’s story on realizing the power of her mother and grandmother’s presence in her life and on finding a lasting partnership.</description></item><item><title>Sex on the Run? No, We Parked. | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Having sex in a car is usually a last resort, born from the trappings of youth. For Susan Silas, it was a midlife necessity.
While working as a production accountant on a sitcom, Susan met a teamster. Despite having little in common — he was former military; she had been an antiwar protester — they hit it off. But, without a private place to go to, they found themselves having sex in the back seat of the teamster’s car.</description></item><item><title>What I Got Wrong About My Parents’ Marriage | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010027/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010027/</guid><description>Podcast Description As one of the only Indian girls in her tiny Canadian mountain town, Natasha Singh stood out — and she was unafraid of being different. At 13, she shaved her head. By 17, she had run away for good. A few years later she came out to her mother.
Natasha’s worldview was worlds apart from her very traditional immigrant parents. Her mother always wore a sari — never pants — and Natasha longed for the power and control her father wielded in the family.</description></item><item><title>For a 30-Year-Old Virgin, It’s Now or Never | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Clare Almand was born with congenital heart disease, so her life was never what she would call “normal.” By the time she was 30, she’d had 10 open-heart surgeries and her health was rapidly declining. Clare thought she was dying.
With death looming, she was running out of time to do something she’d never done, something she felt like everyone else had already checked off their list. Clare felt she was running out of time to lose her virginity.</description></item><item><title>The Marriage Proposal That Wasn’t | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010029/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bob Morris could tell that something was changing with his elderly father: His car was clean, his manners had improved and he had a shine in his eyes. He had a new “lady friend.” Her name was Arlene.
Arlene loved Bob’s father, but she also set clear boundaries with him. She didn’t want to care for him when he got sick and — despite what Bob’s father led Bob to believe — she didn’t want to marry him.</description></item><item><title>We Dated for Three Years. He Forgot It All. | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010030/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 14:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam and Tyler’s relationship was built on a philosophy of joy. Together, they climbed trees, ate cream puffs in bed, and danced in a field with their friends. But, after three years together, Sam was no longer in love, and they broke up.
A few months later, Sam was in a terrible accident. He had amnesia. He knew Tyler was important to him, but not why. He’d forgotten their entire relationship — and he didn’t remember their breakup.</description></item><item><title>He Ghosted. I'm Grateful. | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010031/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Denny Agassi moved to New York City with a mission: She was looking to have great sex.
Her first summer in the city, Denny downloaded the dating app Grindr. She filtered for trans friendly men looking for sex or short flings — and it worked.
Then, one day, she got a message from a man named Jack. He was poised, curious and caring. What she thought could only be something casual — a Grindr relationship — turned into something serious and meaningful.</description></item><item><title>Dating Advice From Jay Shetty | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010032/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 19:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010032/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Jay Shetty graduated from college, he was prepared for two different paths in life: to work in finance, or become a Hindu monk.
After three years at an ashram, Jay returned home to London hoping to share his learning with the world. He had to relearn how to make small talk — and how to flirt. He had his eye on someone special: a down-to-earth woman named Radhi.</description></item><item><title>The Healing Power of Love (Island) | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010033/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010033/</guid><description>Podcast Description 12 hopeful singles, thrown into a villa in Spain, hooking up, breaking up and making up. When Sophie Mackintosh was experiencing one of the darkest periods of her life, the reality TV show became her obsession. There was something about it that was deeply validating — and kept her coming back.
Today: Sophie’s reflections on &amp;ldquo;Love Island.&amp;rdquo; Plus, Lindsey Underwood, a Styles editor at The New York Times, gives us the lowdown on the show (she’s a superfan).</description></item><item><title>How a $100 Bet Saved Our Relationship | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010034/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mark Jason Williams and his mom often butted heads on two issues: She was uncomfortable when he brought up anything about being gay, and he was tired of her incessantly talking about how he survived childhood cancer.
By the age of 40, Mark had reached his wit’s end. He stopped pleading for her to change and instead proposed a $100 bet. But the real change in their relationship came when Mark broke his end of the bargain.</description></item><item><title>Stop Looking for the Perfect Partner | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010035/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010035/</guid><description>Podcast Description “The only three men I had ever imagined a future with all told me that something was missing,” Oz Johnson wrote in her Modern Love essay. When Oz was 23, her boyfriend said she met 99 percent of his criteria, but she was missing 1 percent. Over a decade later, another man broke up with her via email. Their love was almost perfect, he said, but not enough to last.</description></item><item><title>I Imagine Him Here | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010036/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felice Neal was in the checkout line at Whole Foods when she dropped her sweet potato. A handsome customer behind her said, “I think this is yours.” Felice was smitten.
Felice believes this meet-cute was fate — and it opened her up to new ways of looking for love in a city full of millions of strangers.
Then, Jessica Strange shares her story about losing her husband, and selling the house they had lived in with their children.</description></item><item><title>Dominate Me, but Not Like That | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010037/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010037/</guid><description>Podcast Description When it came to dating, Aly Tadros was used to hiding the messy parts of her life. “Why even bother? As soon as a guy finds out about my baggage, he bolts,” she wrote in her Modern Love essay.
That is, until Dan from OkCupid came along. His dating profile read: “I’m a feminist. I respect women while simultaneously enjoy dominating them.” That was the start of Aly’s journey into B.</description></item><item><title>Questions I Can’t Ask My Father | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010038/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010038/</guid><description>Podcast Description In her early 20s, Annabelle Allen longed to know what her dad had been like when he was her age. How did he spend his Saturdays? What was his first impression of her mom? When did he feel lonely? But Annabelle’s dad was diagnosed with Alzheimer’s disease at age 62, and ever since, memories of his past had started slipping away.
Recently, Annabelle was cleaning up her parents’ storage bin when she made an incredible discovery: more than a dozen of her dad’s old journals.</description></item><item><title>The Tricky Geometry of a Throuple | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010039/</guid><description>Podcast Description For years, Evan Sterrett’s relationship with his boyfriend had become “reruns of the same drama.” Evan wanted space; his boyfriend wanted commitment. But one summer, their relationship received a guest star — a third partner who resuscitated their joie de vivre.
Today, we hear Evan’s story about navigating the complex geometry of throuplehood. Then, we meet Samatra and April Doyle. They don’t live together and don’t co-parent, but they are married and intend to be together forever.</description></item><item><title>I Promised God It Was the Last Time | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Growing up in an ultra-Orthodox Hasidic community, Sara Glass was used to following strict rules — including what to wear, when to get married and whom to love. “I had strong feelings that I really should be with a woman and not with a man,” she told our host, Anna Martin. “But I wanted to do what God said was right.”
Sara married her first husband at age 19.</description></item><item><title>Your Weirdest Dates | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010041/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010041/</guid><description>Podcast Description What’s the most unusual place you’ve ever been on a date? We asked Modern Love listeners and the responses did not disappoint. Rummaging through landfills, listening to cases in night court … the stories get weird. Plus, there’s one that our host, Anna Martin, considers the most bizarre of all (hint: dead bodies).
For our last episode of 2022, we start with Dev Aujla’s essay about how he wound up traveling on a cargo ship across the Atlantic Ocean with a woman who, weeks earlier, had broken up with him at the advice of her astrologer.</description></item><item><title>A Bond Thicker Than Blood | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brandon Kyle Goodman never knew his father, but he did know his Uncle Ronnie. Uncle Ronnie was Brandon’s godfather, originally his mom’s college bestie — and essentially, her sibling. Uncle Ronnie owned a hair salon, used words like “fabulous” and “honey” and was “the only person who never questioned my effeminate nature,” Brandon said. But when Brandon became an adult, their relationship changed.
Today, Brandon reads his essay about the enduring bond with Uncle Ronnie.</description></item><item><title>No More Hiding | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010043/</guid><description>Podcast Description An A-student, a striving employee and a loyal friend, Terri Cheney is the sort of person who seems to have it all together. But, beneath her glowing facade, she faced the highs and lows of bipolar disorder. She kept her mental illness separated from her personal and professional lives, but she could not conceal this part of herself when it came to dating.
After Terri’s essay, we peek into another story: the romance of Dave and Janelle Funchess.</description></item><item><title>Encore: When Two Open Marriages Collide | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010044/</guid><description>Podcast Description What are the boundaries of an open marriage? What happens to them when your wife’s boyfriend has an accident that puts him in a coma? And what do you tell the kids?
Today, we’re revisiting Wayne Scott’s story about his open marriage — and a motorcycle accident that tested its boundaries. Then, we hear from Wayne and his wife, Elizabeth Thielman, about the dynamics of their “creative arrangement” and how their relationship has evolved in the years since.</description></item><item><title>Falling for Your Sperm Donor | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010045/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rex and Katharine met on a trip in South Dakota. She wanted a baby; he did not. Could he be a sperm donor? No problem. The agreement was simple. They would both get what they wanted: Katharine would raise her baby in California, and Rex would continue his life as a builder and tinker in Michigan.
Then, they fell in love.
After hearing Katharine’s story, Anna Martin, our host, talks with Rex about changing his mind, unlearning generational lessons and raising a son who is comfortable asking his dad questions.</description></item><item><title>What to Do With the Time We Get | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010046/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ari Diaconis knew a bright future lay ahead of him. He was a gifted athlete with a well-paying job at a Wall Street law firm, and a partner, Dunia, with whom he shared a deep connection. But a neurological illness shifted his vision for the path ahead and shined a spotlight on the present — snuggles in bed and time spent in their apartment — a life raft from the city downstairs.</description></item><item><title>The Internet Still Thinks I'm Pregnant | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010047/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amy Pittman was thrilled about her first pregnancy. She immediately downloaded a pregnancy app, and she was charmed when it showed her baby had grown from the size of a lavender bud to the size of a chocolate chip. When she miscarried, she deleted the app and the chocolate chip avatar, but the internet never caught on. Seven months later, Amy received a sample of baby formula. Although she had deleted the pregnancy app, the baby formula company didn’t know — and thought she was a new mom.</description></item><item><title>Not the Daughter She Wanted | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010048/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Her whole life, Putsata Reang (Put, for short) was accustomed to exceeding her parents expectations. She excelled in her career, paid for her parents to go on trips together and maintained a tight connection to her siblings and community.
Yet a fundamental part of Put – her identity as bisexual – was enough to crack the foundations of their relationship. When Put’s mother did not attend her wedding to the woman of her dreams, she feared she would never close the distance between them.</description></item><item><title>Encore: A Lifetime of Good Loving | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010049/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we’re revisiting the story of Bette Ann Moskowitz, who lost her husband of 56 years on the eve of the coronavirus pandemic. When Bette first met her husband, she was taken by his “smoldering looks and banked fires.” He was from Brooklyn; she was from the Bronx. They had little in common and their “prospects were not good,” as Bette put it, but they got married anyway.</description></item><item><title>When the Music Stopped | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010050/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Growing up in Brooklyn, Sonia Pérez recalled how her father would drink beer, sit on the sofa and lose himself in records from Puerto Rico, where he grew up. One day, he stopped listening. Sonia and her siblings wondered why.
On the other side of the world, in Ireland, Grainne Armstrong recalls the moment she experienced her daughter’s love for the first time, set to a soundtrack of opera and birdsong.</description></item><item><title>How to Learn My Love Language | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010051/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010051/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Ross Showalter turned 18 and began dating hearing men, he found himself communicating with them on their terms: using spoken language. Years of speech lessons and lip-reading practice forced Ross, who is Deaf, to conform to a society that favors sound. All of these men made the same promise: to learn sign language, only to never follow through. Then, on a spring day in the midst of the pandemic, Ross met Will.</description></item><item><title>One Last Haircut | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010052/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010052/</guid><description>Podcast Description They were standing in a Walmart parking lot when William’s wife turned to him and asked, “Are you gay?” Those three words catalyzed the end of their marriage, and the end of a 22-year partnership filled with many joys and rituals, including the haircuts William’s wife gave him. But those words were also an opportunity for growth — and a chance for William to heal.
In this episode, William Dameron shares his story of coming out to his wife and daughters.</description></item><item><title>How to Feel Yourself | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010053/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010053/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Everyone deserves an orgasm” is a fair way to word Diana de Vegh’s attitude toward life. Diana is a firm believer in the pursuit of pleasure — of all sorts — for all people. In the first episode of our new season of Modern Love, we hear Diana’s story about seeking help at a sleek sex shop in downtown Manhattan. Why should a legally blind 83-year-old woman have to struggle so much just to get a sex toy?</description></item><item><title>Could I Forgive Him One Last Time? | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010054/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010054/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Victoria Rosner was seven months pregnant, her husband filed for divorce. He “decided that he couldn’t be married anymore, not to me, he said, and probably not to anyone,” Victoria wrote in her Modern Love essay.
A couple of years later, while they were living many miles apart, he reached out to her with a request. He had been diagnosed with a cancer that had metastasized to his bones, and he wanted to spend the time he had left with Judah, their young son.</description></item><item><title>How to Find the One | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010055/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010055/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Meher Ahmad first saw the movie “Bend It Like Beckham” as a young girl, she was transfixed. Watching the main character, an Indian woman who looked like her, kiss her white soccer coach, she saw a vision of her own romantic future. While she felt pressure from her family and her culture to be with a Pakistani boy, the movie opened up her lanes of attraction — from white boys to, eventually, “anything but brown men.</description></item><item><title>The Shame Game | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010056/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010056/</guid><description>Podcast Description The year was 2006, and Damon Young had just met a woman on MySpace. Their back-and-forth was witty, flirty and easy. They went on a first date at Barnes &amp;amp; Noble, where they browsed books and continued to vibe.
Things were going great, Damon thought. That is, until she called off their second date. Damon was confused, but he had a hunch about what fueled her sudden disinterest: his teeth.</description></item><item><title>A Mother's Secret | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010057/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ayad Akhtar’s parents met in Pakistan in the early ’60s, when they were both medical students and “ridiculously attractive” — or so their friends say. Despite having a love marriage (against the wishes of their parents), theirs was rocky from the start.
“By the time I was 4, I already knew my father had ‘other women,’ as my mother used to call them,” Ayad wrote in his Modern Love essay.</description></item><item><title>‘Do It, I Dare You.’ | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010058/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010058/</guid><description>Podcast Description In his early 20s, Kevin Renn moved to New York City with dreams of making it as a playwright. When money got tight, he decided to fall back on a familiar option: babysitting.
“The question, though, wasn’t whether I would be a good nanny, but if anyone would let me — as a Black man who is over six feet tall,” Kevin said in his Modern Love essay.</description></item><item><title>Left to Be Found | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010059/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yvonne Liu knew from a young age that she was adopted, but she didn’t know the details. All she knew was that she had been left by her birth mother in a busy stairwell in Hong Kong. It wasn’t until she was 30, on the night before a critical surgery, that she was given a handwritten note in Chinese that transformed her understanding of where she had come from.</description></item><item><title>Only With Distance | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010060/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nora Johnson had been making weekly visits to older man after he suffered a mild stroke. But he wasn’t just any older man. “We had the worst marriage in the history of human relations,&amp;quot; Nora wrote in her 2014 Modern Love essay. “Dysfunctional doesn’t even begin to describe it.”
During her visits, the memories would coming pouring back: the fights, the vacations, the plunging bank account. But Nora’s ex-husband had forgotten all that.</description></item><item><title>A Younger Man | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010061/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Heather von Rohr had moved to Los Angeles with aspirations: to make it as a screenwriter and to fall in love, marry and have a child. In need of a day job, she took an entry-level position at the research library of a prestigious film academy.
At the library, she met Nick — who was 13 years younger than she was and in no position to support a family.</description></item><item><title>Marriage Classes at Guantánamo | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010062/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mansoor Adayfi was only 19 when he arrived at the prison camp at the Guantánamo Bay Naval Base in Cuba. Growing up in a tiny village in the mountains of Yemen, “I didn’t know much about the world,” he said. “Now my world was Guantánamo.”
For a period during his 14 years there, he and his fellow detainees organized informal classes for one another. There was a cooking class, taught by a former chef.</description></item><item><title>Season Premiere: One Man's Trash | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010063/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010063/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Mike Rucker and his partner, John, moved in together, they purchased a sofa they affectionately named Miss Bee. “I didn’t just feel grown up buying this sofa, I felt sophisticated,” Mike wrote in his Modern Love essay. Miss Bee had low arms, wooden legs with brass wheels and a white denim slipcover. Miss Bee was not only a provider of comfort, but also the anchor of Mike and John’s home life.</description></item><item><title>First Love Mixtape, Side B | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010064/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010064/</guid><description>Podcast Description What’s the song that taught you about love as a teen? When we asked this question at the start of the season, your anthems came pouring in. We heard from present-day teens, and we heard from listeners who have been with their partners for over 50 years. There were stories of Nat King Cole and One Direction, adrenaline rushes and loneliness, and many lessons in matters of the heart.</description></item><item><title>A Couple Walks Into City Hall | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010065/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010065/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s 2022, the year of matrimania. Roughly 2.5 million weddings are expected (a bump not seen since 1984), and other trends are wildly taking off — ceremonies for pets, weddings on weekdays, a revival of epic poofy dresses. While the business of nuptials is evolving, we revisit Pauline Miller’s essay from 2017 about one tried-and-true approach: tying the knot at City Hall (a decision fueled by Pauline’s desperate need for health care).</description></item><item><title>Right Swipes, Big City | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010066/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alexandra Capellini has been on the dating apps for about four years. Dating is already a fraught process, but to top it off, Alexandra has to decide if, when and how she should explain that she wears a prosthetic leg. Today, we listen to Alexandra’s essay about navigating the apps — and realizing that it’s not her responsibility to “make other guys more comfortable with meeting me.” Then, our host, Anna Martin, calls up Alexandra.</description></item><item><title>Confessions of a Late Bloomer | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010067/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Garrett Schlichte was exactly twice the age of his sister. When he was 28 and his sister was 14, she would dish to him on the phone about her teenage love life. But the feelings she was experiencing — like electric attraction and aching jealousy — were unfamiliar to Garrett. When he was a queer, closeted teenager, Garrett turned to romantic comedies to grasp the emotions of a real-life relationship.</description></item><item><title>A Mother’s Wild, Extravagant Love | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010068/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Genevieve Kingston has carried a cardboard box with her throughout her life, filled with gifts for major milestones — childhood birthdays, her first period, graduation.
The gifts are from her mother, who died of cancer just before Ms. Kingston’s 12th birthday. In her final days, she prepared postcards for the future and filled the box with her love.
In today’s episode, we listen to Ms. Kingston’s essay about opening the packages in the box, and her reflections on what was lost — and what was found.</description></item><item><title>Beyond Girlfriend-Boyfriend | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010069/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Three months into the pandemic, Haili Blassingame was crafting an email to her boyfriend of five years, Malcolm, with the subject line “My Terms.” She wanted to break up. Haili had met Malcolm in college. At first she was “giddy about the cute guy with the deep voice who looked like Obama,” she wrote in her Modern Love essay. But as they started dating, she found that their identities were intertwining and people were treating them differently just because they called themselves girlfriend and boyfriend.</description></item><item><title>When You Think You Know Your Parents | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010070/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ariel Sabar was visiting his parents in his childhood home in California, when he awoke one morning to high-pitched giggles coming from his parents’ room. He opened the door to a Norman Rockwell-type image: his father, 70, riding his stationary bike in his pajamas; and his 6-year-old son perched on its frame, cheerleading for his grandfather.
Ariel was stunned: “As a boy, I’d seen this house as a battlefield, a place where children and parents less often joshed than jousted,” he wrote in his 2009 Modern Love essay.</description></item><item><title>Married to a Deal Breaker | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010071/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010071/</guid><description>Podcast Description What are your dating non-negotiables? For Hyla Sabesin Finn, it was smoking — or so she thought. Hyla met Larry in college. She was 17; he was a 21-year-old law student, puffing away outside the library. Hyla had been “indoctrinated by parents whose cocktail parties were littered with ‘no smoking’ signs back when smokers still mingled freely in society,” she wrote in her 2005 Modern Love essay. In spite of this, she was smitten.</description></item><item><title>The ‘Ham Sandwich’ Effect | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010072/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Before Andrew Limbong went off to college, his mother cautioned him about the dire consequences he would face if he hugged a girl. Andrew grew up in a strict Christian household, and his parents are Indonesian immigrants, so they never spoke about sex at home. When Andrew was 20, he met his first girlfriend, Sam. He felt his cultural and parental influences putting “pressure on my blood vessels, not allowing the blood to go where I oh so desperately wanted it to,” he wrote in his Modern Love essay in 2011.</description></item><item><title>First Love Mixtape | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010073/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010073/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re back for a whole new season of stories. In today’s premiere, we introduce our new host, Anna Martin, who has a question for listeners: What’s the one song that taught you about love when you were a teenager? We listen to “What Lou Reed Taught Me About Love,” an essay about a young woman’s summer romance with a floppy-haired “rocker kid” and the records they would spin. Then, we hear from Times staff members about the songs they were obsessed with in their youth, and the memories — funny, empowering, nostalgic — that they carry with them.</description></item><item><title>Loving Across Borders | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010074/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010074/</guid><description>Podcast Description At age 11, Julissa Arce came to the United States from Mexico on a visa that expired three years later. For more than a decade, she lived as an undocumented immigrant, fearful of revealing her secret to anyone. “Every phone call or email I got from human resources would make my blood run cold,” she wrote in her Modern Love essay. And when it came to love, she would lie to nearly every man she dated, fearing the threat of exposure and deportation.</description></item><item><title>The Upside of Our Parents' Divorce | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010075/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010075/</guid><description>Podcast Description What’s the secret to sibling success? Apparently, an ugly divorce. At least, that’s how it went down for Ellen Umansky and her two brothers. Ellen’s parents separated when she was 9. “They loved us deeply, but there were battles to be won — emotional, reputational, financial,” Ellen wrote in her Modern Love essay.
As Ellen and her brothers were flung into a new reality of parental feuds and convoluted calendar arrangements, her brothers became her “one constant and comfort.</description></item><item><title>When His Shorts Are Just Too Tight | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010076/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Transcript</description></item><item><title>When Two Open Marriages Collide | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010077/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010077/</guid><description>Podcast Description What are the boundaries of an open marriage? And what are the boundaries of an open marriage when your wife’s boyfriend has an accident that puts him in a coma? Do you introduce yourself to the hospital workers as the patient’s girlfriend’s husband?
Wayne Scott and his wife, Elizabeth, have a “creative arrangement,” as Wayne puts it in his Modern Love essay. They share the children, the cats and the mortgage, but they have permission to see other people romantically.</description></item><item><title>The Right to Fail at Marriage | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010078/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010078/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2004, the comedian Cameron Esposito sat on the steps of Boston City Hall and watched as some of the first legally married same-sex couples in the United States emerged victoriously as newlyweds. Thirteen years, three boyfriends and 10 girlfriends later, Cameron was ready to marry the woman she assumed she would be with forever. “I expected to perfectly navigate marriage like some sort of lesbian phoenix that never stops rising,” Cameron wrote in her 2019 Modern Love essay.</description></item><item><title>Was It Me or Our Astrology? | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010079/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010079/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Love life not working out? Health problems? Everything going wrong?” Amisha Patel used to be skeptical of astrological services that offered claims about the future. Her parents, who immigrated to the U.S. from India, would make annual trips back to Gujarat. When they returned to their New Jersey home, they would share predictions from Hindu astrologers about the fates of their children. “I found my parents’ belief in fate unnerving and un-American,” Amisha wrote in her Modern Love essay.</description></item><item><title>Trapped in a Romance Scam | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010080/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last spring, Michael McAllister’s inbox started filling up with messages from heartbroken women. “I thought you were the man,” one wrote. “Embarrassing, but I kinda became obsessed with ‘you,’” another said. Michael discovered that his photos were being used to catfish women on dating apps — from Germany to Brazil to Chicago.
Today’s story explores a global dating scam (that’s still going on, by the way) and the pandemic-fueled loneliness of digital life.</description></item><item><title>Meet Cute at Zero Years Old | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010081/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kadine Christie’s birth story is one that has been told to her time and again. She was born in the mountain town of Spalding, Jamaica, in the presence of two women: her mother, Lorna, and a stranger, Lurline, who was going into labor in the same open ward. This is a story that feels like fiction, but is far from it. It has high stakes, unexpected connections and a surprising ending.</description></item><item><title>She Left Me There | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010082/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kacey Vu Shap had no desire to return to the Vietnamese orphanage of his youth. As a child, whenever he told people he was adopted, he would say that he came “premade” — that he spontaneously appeared one day at the Baltimore airport, greeted by a new family bearing flowers and kisses. “It was easier to sanitize my story by speaking only of my life as Kacey, who was loved and wanted, than to tell people of my life as Vu, who was abandoned and undesired,” Kacey wrote in his Modern Love essay.</description></item><item><title>Why Do People Get Married? | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010083/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to our season premiere. Seven years into a serious relationship, Jake Maynard got a text from his mother: “Gramma Gert: 3, Jake: 0.” This was her way of telling him that his grandmother, in her 80s, was getting married for the third time, while Jake remained unmarried and childless in his late 20s. His family found this strange. Stranger still, at least in Jake’s view, was his grandmother’s choice of partner.</description></item><item><title>The Return of the Modern Love Podcast | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010084/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010084/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Modern Love podcast will be back for a new season on May 12, with new episodes on Wednesdays. We hope you’ll join us!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What the Silence Said | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010085/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 21:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010085/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Laura and her husband divorced after two decades of marriage, their “little Colorado mountain town” could barely tell. It was quiet compared to the dramatic natural disasters that were afflicting the area — like flooding and wildfires. There were no raised voices, no feelings of fury.
So why did they split? In the lead-up to their divorce, Laura had a revelation about what good love — the kind that will “survive life” — is supposed to sound like.</description></item><item><title>‘Desire Is Never the Mistake’ | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010086/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 21:00:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010086/</guid><description>Podcast Description This holiday season, it’s OK to want more. Paula grew up in foster care, and year after year she would find herself “clobbered by desire” when the holidays rolled around. She longed for a mother and father to rescue her and “make everything better”; she wished for the hip-huggers and games she saw on TV.
When she was 21, she met a man named Jeff who ruptured this annual cycle of desire.</description></item><item><title>With the Help of Strangers | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010087/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 21:00:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010087/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode contains descriptions of domestic violence.
In 2013, Courtney Queeney published an essay about surviving domestic violence and the legal proceedings that followed. She described going to a courthouse every two weeks to renew her emergency protection order against her ex. It was during this period that she found “scattered bright spots” — things to laugh about when everything seemed unfunny. She found comfort in the woman who shared her court schedule; her lawyer, whom she revered; and the judge who made her crack up.</description></item><item><title>A Lifetime of Good Loving | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010088/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 21:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010088/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Bette met her husband, he was leaning against a wall at a party. He had, as she put it, “smoldering looks and banked fires.” He was from Brooklyn; she was from the Bronx. She assumed his silent “bad boy” vibe meant “dangerous love and dramatic heartbreak.”
They got married, and she realized that she’d misread his quiet demeanor: “His eyes were simply beautiful, and his silence wasn’t fierce; he just didn’t have anything to say at the moment.</description></item><item><title>Confronting Race on the First Date | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010089/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 21:00:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrew and Sarah met on a dating app. Their first date was just supposed to be coffee, but it lasted nine glorious hours. They talked nonstop across four San Francisco neighborhoods.
But by 2 a.m., Sarah had an admission to make. She told Andrew, who is Asian-American, that his “race might be an issue.” Andrew was shocked. The kicker? Sarah is also Asian-American.
Today, we hear both sides of this story — and find out where Sarah and Andrew are now.</description></item><item><title>No More Secrets | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010090/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sarah and Liz met on a blind date in New York City. Sarah ordered a club soda with a splash of cranberry juice. Liz ordered wine — twice.
A few weeks into dating, while taking a walk together through Chelsea Market, a feeling crystallized for Liz: “I knew in the way seasons change that I would love her before this one ended.”
In order to make this work, Liz knew she could no longer hide from Sarah that she had an unhealthy relationship with alcohol.</description></item><item><title>Dusty-Danger Dog | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010091/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 21:00:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Feeling election stress? Today&amp;rsquo;s stories about a man and his dog may help.
Timothy Braun was on a run through the Texas heat. When he stopped at a local animal shelter for a drink of water, he was taken by a dog who stared at him with pointy ears and mismatched eyes — one brown, one blue. He had no intention of adopting a dog, but “out of curiosity, or God knows what” he looked into the dog’s folder.</description></item><item><title>Devoted but Doomed | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010092/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 20:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010092/</guid><description>Podcast Description In college, Malcolm Conner penned a rambling email intended for his crush. “You have cow eyes,” he wrote. “I know that sounds like a bad thing but have you ever looked into a cow’s eyes? They are so deep and brown and beautiful.”
What he hadn’t disclosed — to his crush or to anyone at school — was that he was transgender and had transitioned at age 15. But he knew he had to tell this “charismatic acquaintance,” for what they had was flirtatious and unstoppable; it was, as Malcolm put it, physics.</description></item><item><title>When Getting Old Never Happens | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010093/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 20:01:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010093/</guid><description>Podcast Description They disagreed on a lot of things: She was a “bleeding-heart liberal”; he was a “conservative libertarian.” He “came from good Irish Catholic stock”; she called herself a “hopeful agnostic.”
When the firefighter chased her down the street to ask her out, she pinned him as “a bald, white, middle-aged New York City cliché.”
On their first date, no topic was off-limits. Not racism, not abortion, not substance abuse.</description></item><item><title>Season Premiere: Driveway Elegies | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010094/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 20:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010094/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode contains strong language.
On the first episode of the new Modern Love podcast, we hear from two women who examine their lives through the contents of their homes — the car in the driveway, the stained teacups, the razor and shaving cream by the sink. Though easy to ignore, these everyday objects often tell a larger story.
Featured stories:“Bye Bye ‘Family’ Minivan,&amp;quot; Kyrie Robinson“Tracking the Demise of My Marriage on Google Maps,” Maggie Smith</description></item><item><title>Welcome to the New Modern Love | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010095/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 20:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Love is going to sound a little different this season. Tune into the first episode on Oct. 14, with new episodes every Wednesday.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Confronting Race, Religion and Her Heart | With Zawe Ashton | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010096/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 19:55:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010096/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s essay, Lilian Oben writes about how essential it is to be seen in relationships — to be able to take up space, without being asked to change who we are. Her essay is read by Zawe Ashton (&amp;ldquo;Betrayal&amp;rdquo;).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why Can’t Men Say ‘I Love You’ to Each Other? | With Ncuti Gatwa | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010097/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 20:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you tell your friends you love them? And do you say it like that, using those words? Is it easy for you to say? Is it fraught? Ricardo Jaramillo takes those questions on in this week’s essay. It’s read by Ncuti Gatwa, who stars in “Sex Education” on Netflix.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Race Wasn't An Issue To Him, Which Was An Issue To Me With Lorraine Toussaint | Encore | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 19:25:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lorraine Toussaint (&amp;ldquo;The Glorias&amp;rdquo;) reads an essay by Kim McLarin. Then, we catch up with Kim to hear how she is doing in this moment.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Researching Jenna, Discovering Myself | With Hasan Minhaj | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010099/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 19:41:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hasan Minhaj (&amp;ldquo;Patriot Act with Hasan Minhaj&amp;rdquo;) reads Brian Goedde&amp;rsquo;s essay about a man investigating his own breakup.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Language Of Love With Saoirse Ronan | Encore | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010100/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 19:23:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Saoirse Ronan (&amp;ldquo;Little Women&amp;rdquo;) reads an essay about how a language barrier impacts the relationship between a young woman and an Iraqi doctor. This is an encore presentation.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How ‘Lolita’ Freed Me From My Own Humbert | With Jameela Jamil | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010101/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 19:07:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010101/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;Lolita,&amp;rdquo; Vladimir Nabokov’s novel about a man’s sexual obsession with a young girl, is famously controversial. But when Bindu Bansinath started to read it, it unexpectedly became a kind of road map for her, showing her a way out of the situation she was in. Jameela Jamil (&amp;ldquo;I Weigh&amp;rdquo;) reads her piece.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Alone In A Pandemic | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010102/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 23:31:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Living alone can be liberating, maddening, joyful &amp;hellip; lonely. It also might feel very different today than it did several months ago. This episode features stories from people who live alone, telling us how they are doing right now.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>To Fall In Love With Anyone, Do This | Encore | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010103/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 19:05:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010103/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you&amp;rsquo;re running out of things to do at home — or if you just need a break from stress and worry — we have a suggestion. Listen to this week&amp;rsquo;s episode featuring Gillian Jacobs and Mandy Len Catron, and then try the 36 questions that (may) lead to love. You can find the 36 questions here: https://nyti.ms/2SFbICi
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Years Ago, My Sister Vanished. I See Her Whenever I Want. | With Daisy Edgar-Jones | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010104/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 20:13:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Daisy Edgar-Jones (Hulu&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Normal People&amp;rdquo;) reads Kyleigh Leddy&amp;rsquo;s essay, about the online presence people leave behind.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sometimes It's Not You, Or The Math | With Laura Prepon | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010105/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 19:05:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010105/</guid><description>Podcast Description What if all the conventional wisdom about why you are single is wrong? Laura Prepon (&amp;ldquo;You And I, As Mothers&amp;rdquo;) reads Sara Eckel&amp;rsquo;s essay.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Your Stories of Love During The Pandemic: Part II | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010106/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 20:25:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010106/</guid><description>Podcast Description We hear more of your stories about how the COVID-19 outbreak has changed your relationships with one another.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Modern Love Presents: Sugar Calling | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010107/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 20:18:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Modern Love presents an excerpt of the first episode of “Sugar Calling.&amp;quot; Hear Cheryl Strayed in conversation with the author George Saunders, her old friend and mentor from graduate school.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Somewhere Inside, a Path to Empathy | With Daniel Radcliffe | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010108/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 19:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010108/</guid><description>Podcast Description When you’re in a new relationship, you’re always trying to present your best self. But anyone who’s been in a relationship for awhile knows that you can’t keep the act up forever. David Finch writes about that in his essay, which is read by Daniel Radcliffe. Daniel stars in the upcoming &amp;ldquo;Unbreakable Kimmy Schmidt&amp;rdquo; interactive special on Netflix.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Your Stories of Love During The Pandemic | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010109/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 19:31:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Listeners share stories of how their relationships have changed during the coronavirus outbreak.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Bibliophiles Flirt | With Uzo Aduba | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010110/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 17:29:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010110/</guid><description>Podcast Description There&amp;rsquo;s something wonderful about sharing your favorite books with the person you&amp;rsquo;re falling in love with. And Karla Derus was a longtime book lover, dating a man who was also a big reader. But Karla also had a secret. Emmy-winning actress Uzo Aduba (&amp;ldquo;Mrs. America&amp;rdquo;) reads Karla&amp;rsquo;s essay.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>When Your Greatest Romance Is A Friendship | Encore | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010111/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 17:43:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ali Fazal (&amp;ldquo;Victoria and Abul&amp;rdquo;) tells the story of an unlikely friendship between a man and his elderly neighbor. This is an encore presentation.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Modern Love Presents: Shipwrecked | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010112/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 15:48:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Could you use a little extra comfort and love from afar right now? We thought so. We&amp;rsquo;re sharing an episode of another WBUR podcast, &amp;ldquo;Endless Thread.&amp;rdquo; This is a story about processing grief, and where we turn when the people closest to us don&amp;rsquo;t seem to know what to do or say to help us move forward. If you enjoy this episode, subscribe to &amp;ldquo;Endless Thread&amp;rdquo; wherever you get your podcasts.</description></item><item><title>Recognizing What They Had, 20 Years Too Late | With Gugu Mbatha-Raw | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010113/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 18:53:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gugu Mbatha-Raw (&amp;ldquo;The Morning Show,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Misbehaviour&amp;rdquo;) reads an essay about a friendship between two people who meet in a pub in Notting Hill.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Kindness, And Xanax, Of Strangers | With Lesley Manville | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010114/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 18:32:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lesley Manville (&amp;ldquo;Ordinary Love&amp;rdquo;) reads an essay by Sally Hoskins about finding an unexpected support group in a hospital waiting room.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>I Saw A Playhouse, My Daughter Saw A Jail | With Brian Cox | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010115/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 19:41:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brian Cox (HBO&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Succession&amp;rdquo;) reads an essay about a father grappling with how to protect his child, but also let her live her life.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Just For Tonight, Pretend You Don't Know Me | With Nick Kroll | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010116/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 19:53:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010116/</guid><description>Podcast Description What if you had to pretend your partner was a stranger for a day? Would you fall in love again? Nick Kroll (&amp;ldquo;Olympic Dreams&amp;rdquo;) reads Tim Kreider&amp;rsquo;s essay.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tiny Love Stories For Valentine's Day | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010117/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 18:19:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010117/</guid><description>Podcast Description This Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day, we&amp;rsquo;re bringing you an episode made up of Tiny Love Stories — stories told in no more than 100 words.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>When Cupid Is A Prying Journalist | With Susan Kelechi Watson | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010118/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 20:43:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Susan Kelechi Watson (NBC&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;This Is Us,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;A Beautiful Day In The Neighborhood&amp;rdquo;) reads Deborah Copaken&amp;rsquo;s essay about how a lost love leads to an unexpected connection years later.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dedicated To Two Women | With Terry Crews | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010119/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 16:59:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Terry Crews (&amp;ldquo;Brooklyn Nine-Nine&amp;rdquo;) reads an essay by Brendan Halpin, about trying to find love again after loss.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Role I Was Born To Play | With Tan France | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010120/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 20:23:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tan France (&amp;ldquo;Queer Eye,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Next in Fashion&amp;rdquo;) reads an essay by Evan James, about a man finding his role within his family.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>My Secret Left Me Unable To Help | With Jessalyn Gilsig | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010121/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 20:59:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Love is about trust. But have you ever been tempted to breach that trust? To read someone&amp;rsquo;s diary, check their text messages, or read their emails? Jessalyn Gilsig reads an essay by Joyce Maynard about facing that temptation.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Take Me As I Am, Whoever I Am With Rebecca Hall | Encore | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010122/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 19:43:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rebecca Hall who stars in the upcoming movie &amp;ldquo;The Night House,&amp;rdquo; reads a story about dating &amp;ndash; while manic. This is an encore presentation.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Need To Find Me? Ask My Ham Man. | With Jenny Slate | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010123/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 20:53:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jenny Slate (&amp;ldquo;Stage Fright,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Little Weirds&amp;rdquo;) reads an essay by Catherine Down about the family you find when living far from home.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>An Interlude Of Clarity With Judd Apatow | Encore | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010124/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 18:31:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Director Judd Apatow reads an essay about a date that goes very wrong. This is an encore presentation.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Race Grows Sweeter With Mary Chapin Carpenter | Encore | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010125/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 15:59:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Singer-songwriter Mary Chapin Carpenter reads a story by Eve Pell, about finding new love later in life. This is an encore presentation.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nursing A Wound With Jake Gyllenhaal | Encore | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010126/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 19:17:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jake Gyllenhaal (&amp;ldquo;Stronger&amp;rdquo;) tells the story of a man recovering from heartbreak in a pediatrics wing.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Are You My Husband? | With Renée Elise Goldsberry | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010127/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 20:55:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Renée Elise Goldsberry (&amp;ldquo;Waves&amp;rdquo;) reads an essay about a woman and her husband navigating the aftermath of his traumatic brain injury.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Never Tell Our Business To Strangers | With Ruth Wilson | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010128/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 21:35:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010128/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;Never tell our business to strangers.&amp;rdquo; That&amp;rsquo;s what Jennifer Mascia was told growing up. But it wasn&amp;rsquo;t until she was an adult that she learned the reason why. Ruth Wilson (HBO&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;His Dark Materials&amp;rdquo;) reads Jennifer&amp;rsquo;s essay about discovering a dark family secret.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Who's Allowed To Hold Hands? | With Alicia Keys | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010129/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 19:55:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010129/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;I’ve noticed that there is a strange hierarchy of handholding that dictates who gets to express physical affection without repercussions,&amp;rdquo; Nicole Dennis-Benn writes in this week&amp;rsquo;s Modern Love story. It&amp;rsquo;s read by 15-time Grammy Award winning artist Alicia Keys, whose new single is called &amp;ldquo;Show Me Love.&amp;rdquo;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sharing A Cab, And My Toes With Greta Gerwig | Encore | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010130/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 18:29:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Greta Gerwig (&amp;ldquo;Little Women&amp;rdquo;) reads Julia Anne Miller&amp;rsquo;s essay, about sharing an unusual cab ride in New York City. This is an encore presentation.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Modern Love Presents: Kind World | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010131/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 22:38:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010131/</guid><description>Podcast Description We want to introduce you to another podcast we think you might love, called Kind World. It features stories of life-changing acts of kindness. And this week&amp;rsquo;s story features a story from the US/ Mexico border.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Waiting For The Wall To Crumble | With Kelly McCreary | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010132/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 20:37:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kelly McCreary (&amp;ldquo;Grey&amp;rsquo;s Anatomy&amp;rdquo;) reads an essay about a chance meeting on a bus that leads to a decades-long relationship.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Triangle's Sharpest Point | With Zawe Ashton | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010133/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 21:37:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010133/</guid><description>Podcast Description We make decisions every day that shape our lives in small ways. But it&amp;rsquo;s rare to face a real crossroads — a choice between living one life, and living another that&amp;rsquo;s entirely different. Zawe Ashton (&amp;ldquo;Betrayal&amp;rdquo;) reads an essay by Ingrid Maitland, who writes about making a choice like that.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We'll Meet Again In Five Years | With Regina King | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010134/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 18:37:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Regina King (HBO&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Watchmen&amp;rdquo;) reads an essay by a woman who thinks she&amp;rsquo;s met the right person for her — several years too early.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Words With (I Wish We Were More Than) Friends | With Ben Platt | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010135/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 19:55:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010135/</guid><description>Podcast Description When he was working in Nevada, Justin Race met a woman he thought was perfect for him. The only problem? They had only ever talked to each other through Words With Friends. Justin&amp;rsquo;s essay is read by Tony-winning actor Ben Platt, who stars in the new show &amp;ldquo;The Politician&amp;rdquo; on Netflix.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>He's Going Back To His Former Wife. Sort Of. | With Marisa Tomei | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010136/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 19:59:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marisa Tomei (&amp;ldquo;The Rose Tattoo&amp;rdquo;) reads an essay by Judith Newman about a woman fulfilling her husband&amp;rsquo;s unusual dying wish.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rallying To Keep The Game Alive | Live At CitySpace | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010137/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 19:31:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010137/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2013, Ann Leary wrote an essay about a rough patch in her marriage. We turned it into an episode of the Modern Love Podcast. And now, Ann&amp;rsquo;s story been adapted for television. In this episode, we revisit actress Connie Nielsen&amp;rsquo;s performance of Ann&amp;rsquo;s essay. Then, we&amp;rsquo;ll hear a live conversation between Ann, Modern Love editor Daniel Jones, and podcast producer Caitlin O&amp;rsquo;Keefe. They talk about what happened next for Ann and her husband, and what it was like for Ann to have her essay adapted for the Modern Love television show.</description></item><item><title>How 30 Blocks Became 30 Years | With Peter Sarsgaard | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010138/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 19:55:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010138/</guid><description>Podcast Description Peter Sarsgaard (&amp;ldquo;The Sound of Silence&amp;rdquo;) reads an essay about the relationship between a man with spinal muscular atrophy and his wife of more than 30 years.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>First I Met My Children, Then My Girlfriend. They’re Related. | With Kal Penn | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010139/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 19:37:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010139/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Aaron Long donated sperm twenty-five years ago, he didn&amp;rsquo;t realize that one day he would discover that he had ten biological children. But that&amp;rsquo;s what happened when he signed up for 23andMe. Kal Penn stars in the NBC comedy &amp;ldquo;Sunnyside&amp;rdquo;. He reads Aaron&amp;rsquo;s essay.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Screens Between Us With Issa Rae | Encore | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010140/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 17:53:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Issa Rae reads an essay about the intimacy and distance synonymous with online dating.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Tallest Man I Ever Loved | With Andrew Rannells | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010141/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 19:35:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrew Rannells has been nominated for two Tony Awards. He starred in HBO&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Girls.&amp;rdquo; But before any of that, he was just like a lot of 20-somethings — trying to make his career happen, and dreaming about his perfect boyfriend.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Seeing The World Through My Wife's Eyes With David Oyelowo | Encore | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010142/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 19:41:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010142/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t Let Go&amp;rdquo; star David Oyelowo reads an essay about a blind man navigating his marriage. This is an encore presentation.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>My Platonic Romance On The Psych Ward | With Miriam Shor | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010143/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 19:17:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010143/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week&amp;rsquo;s essay is about a deep, enduring friendship that starts in an unlikely place. Jeannie Vanasco writes about her relationship with a woman named Anita in her essay, &amp;ldquo;My Platonic Romance on the Psych Ward.&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s read by actress and director Miriam Shor, who stars in TV Land’s “Younger&amp;quot; and the upcoming Netflix film &amp;ldquo;Lost Girls.&amp;rdquo;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Despite The Losses, So Much Gained | With Marsha Stephanie Blake | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010144/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 19:35:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010144/</guid><description>Podcast Description When people first come into our lives, it&amp;rsquo;s impossible to know how important they&amp;rsquo;ll become. Leah Keith writes about a man who came to matter a great deal to her in her essay, which is read by Marsha Stephanie Blake (&amp;ldquo;When They See Us&amp;rdquo;)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>In A Charmed Life, A Road Less Traveled | With Nikolaj Coster-Waldau | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010145/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 19:53:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nikolaj Coster-Waldau (&amp;ldquo;Game of Thrones&amp;rdquo;) reads an essay about a man&amp;rsquo;s long relationship with his wife — before and after a car accident that changed their lives.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Night Girl Finds A Day Boy | With Logan Browning | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010146/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 19:47:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010146/</guid><description>Podcast Description A lot of things can get in the way of love &amp;ndash; distance, money issues, being in different places in your life. But this week&amp;rsquo;s essayist, Amanda Gefter, writes about facing a very different kind of challenge. It&amp;rsquo;s read by Logan Browning (Netflix&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Dear White People&amp;rdquo;).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Could We Try Again? | With Marcia Cross | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010147/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 19:59:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010147/</guid><description>Podcast Description If Meredith Hall had to point to the year that her life changed, she would probably say that it was 1965. She was sixteen that year, and pregnant with a son. But more than two decades later, in 1987, her life changed again &amp;ndash; and that&amp;rsquo;s the year she writes about in her essay. It&amp;rsquo;s read by Marcia Cross (&amp;ldquo;Desperate Housewives,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Quantico&amp;rdquo;).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>He's Playing Our Song | With Amanda Seyfried | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010148/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 19:47:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010148/</guid><description>Podcast Description High school love is awkward, nervous &amp;ndash; and often unforgettable. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t usually last. But in this week&amp;rsquo;s essay, Mariclare Lawson writes about a high school love that broke all the rules. It&amp;rsquo;s read by Amanda Seyfried (&amp;ldquo;The Art of Racing in the Rain.&amp;rdquo;)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>At What Age Is Love Enthralling? | With Jessica Walter | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010149/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 19:49:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jessica Walter (&amp;ldquo;Archer,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Arrested Development&amp;rdquo;) reads an essay by Sophy Burnham about how an unexpected encounter makes her consider how love and desire change with age.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Tattoo For The Living | With Zosia Mamet | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010150/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 16:49:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alana Dakin writes about two different tattoos in her essay &amp;ldquo;A Tattoo for the Living&amp;rdquo;, which is read by Zosia Mamet (&amp;ldquo;Tales of the City.&amp;rdquo;)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>An Empty Heart | With Zoe Lister-Jones | Encore | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010151/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 19:25:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Zoe Lister-Jones (CBS&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Life in Pieces,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Band-Aid&amp;rdquo;) reads renowned novelist Lily King&amp;rsquo;s story about the silver lining of heartbreak.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>An Affection Multiplier | With Zachary Quinto | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010152/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 19:41:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can a tiny dog change the dynamics of a marriage? Zachary Quinto (&amp;ldquo;NOS4A2&amp;rdquo;) reads Bob Morris&amp;rsquo;s essay.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Platonic, Until Death Do Us Part | With John Cameron Mitchell | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010153/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 17:17:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010153/</guid><description>Podcast Description What do you do when you&amp;rsquo;re struggling to find a romantic relationship as deep as the relationship you have with your best friend? John Cameron Mitchell (&amp;ldquo;Anthem: Homunculus&amp;rdquo;) reads Ephi Stempler&amp;rsquo;s essay about a man considering a platonic life partnership.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Encore | The Doorman With Cecily Strong | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010154/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 19:19:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Saturday Night Live&amp;rsquo;s Cecily Strong reads a story about a woman&amp;rsquo;s friendship with her doorman. This is an encore presentation.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Misery Loves Fried Chicken | With William Jackson Harper | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010155/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 19:31:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010155/</guid><description>Podcast Description How have you gotten through your worst breakups? Tinder? New hobbies? Cheap alcohol? Wallowing in Taylor Swift albums? William Jackson Harper (&amp;ldquo;The Good Place,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Midsommar&amp;rdquo;) is back to read Mark McDevitt&amp;rsquo;s piece about two breakup buddies.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What Luck Means Now | With Jacki Weaver | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010156/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 20:01:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010156/</guid><description>Podcast Description What does luck mean to you? And how does that change depending on your circumstances? That&amp;rsquo;s what Joyce Maynard writes about in this week&amp;rsquo;s essay. It&amp;rsquo;s read by two-time Academy Award nominee Jacki Weaver (&amp;ldquo;Perpetual Grace, LTD&amp;rdquo;).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We Survived The Storm | With Ginnifer Goodwin | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010157/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 19:41:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010157/</guid><description>Podcast Description When you&amp;rsquo;re dealing with a tragedy, it can feel like you would do anything for an ordinary day. But those ordinary days can come with their own complications. Ginnifer Goodwin (&amp;ldquo;The Twilight Zone&amp;rdquo;) reads Monica Wesolowska&amp;rsquo;s essay.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Wisdom Of The Moving Man | With Lake Bell | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010158/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 20:07:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010158/</guid><description>Podcast Description When we take stock of the people who matter most to us, there are the spouses, the family members, the best friends, the partners. And then there are the people who aren’t any of those things, but who change our lives anyway. Emily Raboteau&amp;rsquo;s essay is about one of those people. It&amp;rsquo;s read by Lake Bell (&amp;ldquo;Bless this Mess.&amp;rdquo;)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Agreeing To Accept And Move On | With Sarah Goldberg | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010159/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 19:37:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Under normal circumstances, trying to find love can be challenging &amp;ndash; and stressful. And for Elizabeth Koster, the pressure was even more intense. Sarah Goldberg (HBO&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Barry&amp;rdquo;) reads Elizabeth&amp;rsquo;s essay.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Love Means Never Having To Say ... Anything | With Pedro Pascal | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010160/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 19:29:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010160/</guid><description>Podcast Description Love thrives on good communication. It can take many forms &amp;ndash; but what happens when you suddenly lose what was once your primary means of communication? Pedro Pascal (&amp;ldquo;King Lear,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Game of Thrones&amp;rdquo;) reads Jamison&amp;rsquo;s essay.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Talking to My Fiancé About My New Girlfriend | With DeWanda Wise | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010161/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 18:59:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010161/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happens when you know you want to marry someone, but you are also are falling in love with someone else? Is there a way for you to have everything? Sophie Lucido Johnson&amp;rsquo;s essay is read by DeWanda Wise (&amp;ldquo;She&amp;rsquo;s Gotta Have It&amp;rdquo;).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Race Wasn't An Issue To Him, Which Was An Issue To Me | With Lorraine Toussaint | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010162/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 19:49:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010162/</guid><description>Podcast Description Interracial relationships come with their own complexities, and there are a lot of questions that come up. Questions like: How does your partner think about race? How do you talk about it? What works, and what doesn&amp;rsquo;t? Kim McLarin writes about race and dating in her piece, which is read by Lorraine Toussaint (&amp;ldquo;The Village&amp;rdquo;).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Encore | Sharing The Shame With Anna Chlumsky | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010163/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 19:05:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anna Chlumsky (&amp;ldquo;Veep&amp;rdquo;) reads Brooks Rinehart&amp;rsquo;s essay, on 90 days that changed the entire course of one family&amp;rsquo;s life.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ah, To Be Old, Male, And Single | With Natasha Lyonne | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010164/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 19:25:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010164/</guid><description>Podcast Description When it comes to dating, Amy Cohen says this: &amp;ldquo;We all need to be reincarnated as an older Jewish man with an apartment on the Upper East Side.” Natasha Lyonne (&amp;ldquo;Russian Doll&amp;rdquo;) reads Amy&amp;rsquo;s essay about the difference between her 76-year-old father&amp;rsquo;s dating life and her own.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Comfort, If Not A Cure | With Nazanin Boniadi | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010165/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 19:57:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010165/</guid><description>Podcast Description How much can you give of yourself before it’s too much? And what do you do when you reach your limit? Nazanin Boniadi (&amp;ldquo;Hotel Mumbai&amp;rdquo;) reads Tara Ebrahimi&amp;rsquo;s essay.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Another Voice Had Come Between Us | With Catherine O'Hara | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010166/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 19:11:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010166/</guid><description>Podcast Description Catherine O&amp;rsquo;Hara (&amp;ldquo;Schitt&amp;rsquo;s Creek&amp;rdquo;) reads Patricia Morrisroe&amp;rsquo;s essay, about a piece of technology that complicates a marriage.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Refreshing A Mother's Memory With Love | With Zoe Saldana | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010167/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 19:43:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dementia can alter someone&amp;rsquo;s personality and change how how they interact with the world. But sometimes, it can also lead to moments of profound connection. Jenny McPhee writes about one of those moments in her piece, which is read by Zoe Saldana.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Playing Role Reversal With My Therapist | With Isabelle Huppert | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010168/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 21:21:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Therapists&amp;rsquo; offices are supposed to be places where you can be both vulnerable and safe. But what happens when your therapist crosses a line? That happened to Julianna Baggott &amp;ndash; and she writes about it an an essay that&amp;rsquo;s read by Isabelle Huppert (&amp;ldquo;Greta&amp;rdquo;).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Security In A Bright Yellow Suitcase | With Christina Hendricks | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010169/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 20:23:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010169/</guid><description>Podcast Description You know the phase. The one when you&amp;rsquo;re going back and forth between your place and your partner&amp;rsquo;s, and you have to bring all your stuff with you. But when is it time to make a change? Deanna Clevesy&amp;rsquo;s essay is read by Christina Hendricks (&amp;ldquo;Good Girls&amp;rdquo;).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Your Dog Has Seen Me Naked | With William Jackson Harper | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010170/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 17:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever dated someone living in a studio apartment with a pet? If so, how did you handle the logistics around sex? Ryan Pfeffer writes about how he dealt with that situation in his essay, which was performed by William Jackson Harper (&amp;ldquo;The Good Place&amp;rdquo;) in front of a live audience at the Huntington Avenue Theatre in Boston.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Part II: My Wife Said You May Want to Marry Me | With André Holland | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010171/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 17:51:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010171/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last week, you heard an essay by Amy Krouse Rosenthal &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;You May Want to Marry my Husband.&amp;rdquo; It was published just days before she died of ovarian cancer. Today, André Holland of &amp;ldquo;High Flying Bird&amp;rdquo; reads the essay her husband Jason wrote in response last summer, and we hear from Jason himself about how he&amp;rsquo;s doing today.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Part I: You May Want to Marry My Husband | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010172/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 19:43:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Debra Winger reads the late Amy Krouse Rosenthal&amp;rsquo;s essay about her fairytale love story, which was cut short by cancer. This is an encore presentation.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Oscars Playlist | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010173/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010173/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;re celebrating the 91st Academy Awards by revisiting two of our favorite episodes featuring nominated actors. We&amp;rsquo;ll hear pieces read by Rachel Weisz of &amp;ldquo;The Favourite,&amp;rdquo; and Willem Dafoe, of &amp;ldquo;At Eternity&amp;rsquo;s Gate.&amp;rdquo;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rallying To Keep The Game Alive | With Connie Nielsen | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010174/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 17:53:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010174/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s easy to single out the biggest decisions in a life. But this week&amp;rsquo;s essay by Ann Leary is about little choices, that you might not think about very much in the moment, that end up slowly changing everything. It&amp;rsquo;s read by Connie Nielsen (&amp;ldquo;I Am the Night&amp;rdquo;).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Kiss Deferred | With Joanna Kulig | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010175/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:07:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010175/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nikolina Kulidzan was twelve years old when she fell in love for the first time. Not long after, the Bosnian War changed her life forever. Her essay is read by Joanna Kulig (&amp;ldquo;Cold War&amp;rdquo;).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What The Sea Took Away | With Carmen Ejogo | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010176/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 18:42:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010176/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do you talk to your children about loss? What secrets do you keep, and for how long? And when do you decide to tell them everything? Emily Listfield faces those questions in her essay, read by Carmen Ejogo (&amp;ldquo;True Detective.&amp;rdquo;)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Maternal Wisdom (5 Pounds' Worth) | With Gillian Anderson | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010177/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 18:29:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010177/</guid><description>Podcast Description When you think back to sex ed class, it&amp;rsquo;s not hard to come up with a couple of memories that might have scarred you for life. But actor Gillian Anderson reads an essay that shows it can be equally scarring for the parents.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Modern Love Holiday Playlist | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010178/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2018 16:13:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010178/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Holidays from all of us at Modern Love! We will be back with brand new episodes in 2019, but today, we&amp;rsquo;re bringing you a playlist of our favorite holiday episodes from the past two years.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>I Will Be Your Mother Figure | Encore | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010179/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 15:37:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010179/</guid><description>Podcast Description When people ask for advice, do they really want to hear what you have to say? Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s hardest to find a friend who can give just a simple, sympathetic ear. Actor Laura Dern takes us deep into a friendship that experienced a unique evolution. This is an encore presentation.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Shirt Stays On | With Finn Wittrock | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010180/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 20:35:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Getting undressed in front of your partner can be really hard. And for Jameson Rich, is was even more complicated. He writes about it in his piece, which is read by Finn Wittrock (&amp;ldquo;Write When You Get Work&amp;rdquo;).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Young Man's Game | With Stanley Tucci | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010181/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 19:41:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010181/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Rand Richards Cooper was in his 40s, he was faced with a question: How late is too late to first become a dad? He writes about it in his essay, which is read by Stanley Tucci (&amp;ldquo;A Private War&amp;rdquo;).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>On A Serpentine Road | With Michelle Rodriguez | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010182/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 17:31:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010182/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do we choose what to hold onto from loved ones after they&amp;rsquo;ve died? Doris Iarovici asks that question in her essay, which is read by Michelle Rodriguez (&amp;ldquo;Widows&amp;rdquo;).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Forgotten Prayer, Answered | With Mira Sorvino | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010183/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 19:31:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010183/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Charlotte Bacon went to a temple in Bhutan, the place unlocked feelings in her that she hadn&amp;rsquo;t truly realized were there. Her essay is read by Mira Sorvino (&amp;ldquo;StartUp&amp;rdquo;).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Maddy Just Might Work | Encore | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010184/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 13:41:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010184/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer Finney Boylan &amp;ndash; an accomplished writer, academic and activist &amp;ndash; reads her own essay about coming out as transgender to her two young sons. This is an encore episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How To Break Up With A 2-Year-Old | With Busy Philipps | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010185/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 21:53:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010185/</guid><description>Podcast Description We cross paths with so many people in our lives &amp;ndash; but only a few of them truly change the direction we thought we were headed in. Busy Philipps (&amp;ldquo;Busy Tonight&amp;rdquo;) reads Laurie Sandell&amp;rsquo;s piece, about the little girl who changed her path.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>An Ancient Coda To My 21st-Century Divorce | With Amy Landecker | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010186/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 15:17:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010186/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a divorce, it can feel like the last thing you want to do is revisit the past. But a ritual forced Cindy Chupack to do just that, in an essay read by actor Amy Landecker.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>In The Waiting Room Of Estranged Spouses | Encore | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010187/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 17:01:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010187/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lance Reddick, best known as Lt. Cedric Daniels on HBO&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;The Wire,&amp;rdquo; reads a story about infidelity and healing.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>I Was Hardly a Perfect Fit | With John C. Reilly | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010188/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 14:05:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010188/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tim Elhajj was a divorced dad who was desperate to connect with his son &amp;ndash; and went about it in an unconventional way. His essay is read by John C. Reilly (The Sisters Brothers).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Plain, Unmarked Box Arrived | With Kristen Bell | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010189/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 20:13:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010189/</guid><description>Podcast Description Would you buy a sex chair? Well, Lori Jakiela did &amp;ndash; and she writes about the chair, and the misadventures involved in trying to use it, in an essay that&amp;rsquo;s read by Kristen Bell (&amp;ldquo;The Good Place.&amp;rdquo;)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Escaping From A Dire Diagnosis On Match.com | With Rita Wilson | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010190/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 14:59:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010190/</guid><description>Podcast Description Would you start online dating just to make your best friend feel better? Author Victoria Redel did that, and she writes about in her piece, which is read by actor and singer Rita Wilson (&amp;ldquo;Bigger Picture&amp;rdquo;).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Life Plan For Two | With Olivia Munn | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010191/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 16:53:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010191/</guid><description>Podcast Description Some crushes are brief: the guy at the gym, the girl on Twitter, your barista. But others are epic &amp;ndash; and take on a life of their own. Olivia Munn (&amp;ldquo;The Predator&amp;rdquo;) reads Marina Shifrin&amp;rsquo;s essay.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus: 81 Minutes | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010192/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 14:43:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010192/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re back in your feed to share a project we think you’ll love. It’s a new podcast called “Last Seen,” about the largest unsolved art heist in history &amp;ndash; the theft of thirteen irreplaceable pieces of art from Boston&amp;rsquo;s Isabella Stewart Gardner museum.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Making A Judgment On Love | With Giancarlo Esposito | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010193/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 18:29:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010193/</guid><description>Podcast Description On a normal day in 2004, Lloyd Zimmerman got the chance to fulfill a man&amp;rsquo;s dying wish. Giancarlo Esposito (&amp;ldquo;Better Call Saul&amp;rdquo;) reads his piece, about the complications of a last request.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning Humanity From Dogs | With Ethan Hawke | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010194/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 14:53:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010194/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ethan Hawke (&amp;ldquo;Blaze&amp;rdquo;) reads an essay about how lonely it can be at rock bottom &amp;ndash; and how sometimes, taking care of someone else is the only way out.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Modern Love Playlist: In Sickness And In Health | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010195/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 12:56:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010195/</guid><description>Podcast Description This playlist episode features stories about people whose relationships were challenged by illness &amp;ndash; and where the promise to stand by each other &amp;ldquo;in sickness and in health&amp;rdquo; was tested. It features stories read by Michael Shannon, Sarah Silverman, Chris Messina, Rebecca Hall, and Patina Miller.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Modern Love Playlist: Secrets | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010196/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 18:57:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010196/</guid><description>Podcast Description It can feel easier to leave things unspoken than to find the right words to explain ourselves. But sooner or later, the things we keep from each other can come to define our relationships. This edition of Modern Love features a playlist of three of our favorite episodes about secrets, read by Danielle Brooks, Cynthia Nixon, and Uma Thurman.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Secret To Marriage | With Sandra Oh | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010197/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 20:07:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010197/</guid><description>Podcast Description Communication. Respect. Intimacy. Doing the dishes. Those are all things that have been called the secret to marriage. But Gabrielle Zevin has a different idea. Sandra Oh (&amp;ldquo;Killing Eve&amp;rdquo;) reads her piece.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Test of Time | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010198/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 19:59:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010198/</guid><description>Podcast Description We know you appreciate a good love story &amp;hellip; so we&amp;rsquo;re bringing you two stories of relationships that have stood the test of time, from another podcast from WBUR, called &amp;ldquo;Endless Thread.&amp;rdquo; Hear the story of the couple featured in an iconic photo from Woodstock, and one about a relationship that started with a note sent in second grade.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Single Woman Seeking Manwich | With Awkwafina | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010199/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 15:17:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010199/</guid><description>Podcast Description Let&amp;rsquo;s face it. With the ghosting, inappropriate comments, and awkward small talk &amp;hellip; dating can be so bad it&amp;rsquo;s hilarious. Awkwafina (&amp;ldquo;Crazy Rich Asians,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Oceans Eight&amp;rdquo;) reads Sarah Moses&amp;rsquo;s essay.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>When Mothers Bully Back | With Ellie Kemper | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010200/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 17:50:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010200/</guid><description>Podcast Description The emotions of parenting can feel completely out of control sometimes. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s love, joy &amp;hellip; or, occasionally, rage. Susan Perabo writes about them in her essay, which is read by Ellie Kemper (&amp;ldquo;Unbreakable Kimmy Schmidt&amp;rdquo;).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>GPS For My Lost Identity | With Diane Guerrero | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010201/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 16:35:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010201/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sometimes, our deepest loves aren&amp;rsquo;t people at all &amp;ndash; they&amp;rsquo;re the places that make us feel most like ourselves. Laura Dave tells a story about one of those places in her essay, which is read by Diane Guerrero (&amp;ldquo;Orange is the New Black&amp;rdquo;).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Superheroes, Just for Each Other | With Mike Colter | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010202/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 16:37:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010202/</guid><description>Podcast Description Peter Goodman thought that he could fix any problem by sweeping his wife off her feet. But when his daughter was born, that strategy failed him. His essay is read by Mike Colter (&amp;ldquo;Luke Cage.&amp;rdquo;)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Hiker’s Guide to Healing | With Cameron Esposito | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010203/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 17:23:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010203/</guid><description>Podcast Description Aspen Matis decided to hike the Pacific Crest Trail because she was looking for solitude, safety, and escape. She writes about what she found there in her essay, read by actor and comic Cameron Esposito.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Catfishing Strangers To Find Myself | With Cory Michael Smith | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010204/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 16:17:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010204/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a teenager in Finland, Kalle Oskari Mattila was trying to figure out who he was. For help, he turned to Pamela Anderson. Cory Michael Smith (&amp;ldquo;1985,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Gotham&amp;rdquo;) performed his story live at the Provincetown Film Festival.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>My Back-Seat View Of A Great Romance | With Chloë Grace Moretz | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010205/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 17:35:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010205/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;What did it mean that the most romantic thing I’d ever been a part of hadn’t even happened to me?&amp;rdquo; Chloë Grace Moretz (&amp;ldquo;The Miseducation of Cameron Post&amp;rdquo;) reads Rachel Monroe&amp;rsquo;s essay about watching a love story unfold from the sidelines.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Encore | Between The Bars | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010206/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 20:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010206/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joshua Jackson (&amp;ldquo;The Affair&amp;rdquo;) reads a story about life and love after 26 months in Iran&amp;rsquo;s Evin Prison. This is an encore presentation.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Hunter-Gatherer, Parking Division | With Jason Alexander | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010207/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 15:47:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010207/</guid><description>Podcast Description The challenge of finding the perfect partner is matched only by the challenge of finding the perfect parking space in New York City. Jason Alexander (&amp;ldquo;Seinfeld&amp;rdquo;) reads Andy Raskin&amp;rsquo;s essay, about the search for love and parking in Chinatown.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Finding My Own Rescuer | With Mandy Moore | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010208/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 15:41:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010208/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mandy Moore (&amp;ldquo;This Is Us&amp;rdquo;) reads Anna March&amp;rsquo;s essay about disability, ability, and the misconceptions surrounding both.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Fear Stripped Bare | With Sarah Shahi | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010209/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 15:05:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010209/</guid><description>Podcast Description When she was growing up, Susan Sajadi thought that her mother was fearless. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t until years later that she realized the truth was much more complicated. Her piece is read by Sarah Shahi, who stars in NBC&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Reverie.&amp;rdquo;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Love Stories In 13 Words | Modern Love Bonus Episode | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010210/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 17:13:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010210/</guid><description>Podcast Description For the 13th anniversary of the Modern Love column, readers sent in their love stories, told in just 13 words. More than 9,000 were submitted. We put together an episode featuring some of our favorites.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Modern Love Encore | Marry A Man Who Loves His Mother | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010211/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 12:55:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010211/</guid><description>Podcast Description Constance Wu of the ABC comedy &amp;ldquo;Fresh Off The Boat&amp;rdquo; reads a story about a wife, a mother-in-law and the unlikely story that brought them together.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Language Of Love | With Saoirse Ronan | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010212/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 18:24:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010212/</guid><description>Podcast Description Saoirse Ronan (&amp;ldquo;On Chesil Beach&amp;rdquo;) reads an essay about how a language barrier impacts the relationship between a young woman and an Iraqi doctor.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Measure of Desire | With Kim Dickens | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010213/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 16:05:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010213/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s the things that go unspoken in a relationship that are the most important. Andrea Jarrell found that out not long after moving to Maine with her husband &amp;ndash; and she writes about it in her piece, read by Kim Dickens (&amp;ldquo;Fear the Walking Dead&amp;rdquo;).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>When Eve And Eve Bit The Apple | With Rachel Weisz | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010214/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 14:41:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010214/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kristen Scharold was an evangelical Christian who was starting to look for a husband. Then, a new relationship caused a crisis of faith. Rachel Weisz (&amp;ldquo;Disobedience&amp;rdquo;) reads Kristen&amp;rsquo;s essay.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Signs, Wonders, and Fates Fulfilled | With Linda Cardellini | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010215/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 20:35:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010215/</guid><description>Podcast Description After Stephanie Saldaña moved to an ancient monastery in Syria, she thought she&amp;rsquo;d found her calling. But when she met a novice monk there, she had to rethink everything. Linda Cardellini (&amp;ldquo;Bloodline&amp;rdquo;) reads Stephanie&amp;rsquo;s essay.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Boy, What A Fabulous Baker | With Abbi Jacobson | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010216/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 15:23:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010216/</guid><description>Podcast Description Abbi Jacobson (&amp;ldquo;6 Balloons,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Broad City&amp;rdquo;) reads an essay about a carboholic who falls for a baker &amp;ndash; and his bread.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Cup From The Fountain Of Youth | With Mel Rodriguez | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010217/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 16:28:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010217/</guid><description>Podcast Description When you&amp;rsquo;re at a bar and someone starts paying more attention to you than you expect &amp;ndash; how do you react? Mel Rodriguez (&amp;ldquo;Overboard,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;The Last Man on Earth&amp;rdquo;) reads Andy Christie&amp;rsquo;s essay, about trying to navigate an unexpected flirtation.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Brother As Significant As Any Other | With Jeffrey Bowyer-Chapman | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010218/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 17:11:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010218/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeffrey Bowyer-Chapman (&amp;ldquo;UnREAL&amp;rdquo;) tells the story of the deep friendship between an older and younger brother.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>R We D8ting? | With Krysten Ritter | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010219/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 16:23:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010219/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happens to relationships when they play out entirely over text? Krysten Ritter (&amp;ldquo;Jessica Jones&amp;rdquo;) reads Sandra Barron&amp;rsquo;s essay, about the miscommunications that can come with text message flirtation.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Modern Love Encore: The Boy Who Makes Waves | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010220/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 16:53:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010220/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this encore, Mykelti Williamson (&amp;ldquo;Chicago P.D.&amp;rdquo;) reads an essay about a father&amp;rsquo;s complicated love for his son.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Accidental Older Woman | With Rosie Perez | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010221/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 15:17:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010221/</guid><description>Podcast Description When does it work to date younger? Rosie Perez, of NBC&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Rise,&amp;rdquo; reads Robin Grearson&amp;rsquo;s essay, about negotiating a relationship with a big age gap.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>When A Couch Is More Than A Couch | With Kate Winslet | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010222/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 14:29:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010222/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kate Winslet reads Nina Riggs&amp;rsquo;s essay, about an overwhelming diagnosis &amp;ndash; and a search for the perfect living room couch.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Fighting Chance | With Bobby Cannavale | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010223/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 15:41:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010223/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bobby Cannavale (&amp;ldquo;Jumanji: Welcome to the Jungle,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Mr. Robot&amp;rdquo;) reads Dominick Zarrillo&amp;rsquo;s essay about a father&amp;rsquo;s unconditional love for his son.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>From He To She In First Grade | With Jennifer Beals | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010224/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 17:35:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010224/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer Beals (&amp;ldquo;Taken&amp;rdquo;) reads Laurie Frankel&amp;rsquo;s essay, about facing a challenging parenting dilemma.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Accident No One Talked About | With Uma Thurman | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010225/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 18:17:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010225/</guid><description>Podcast Description Uma Thurman (&amp;ldquo;The Parisian Woman&amp;rdquo;) reads Jessica Ciencin Henriquez&amp;rsquo;s essay, about the silence that grew in the aftermath of a terrible accident.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Overfed On A Mother's Affection | With Kumail Nanjiani and Emily Gordon | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010226/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 17:29:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010226/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kumail Nanjiani and Emily Gordon (&amp;ldquo;The Big Sick&amp;rdquo;) tell the story of how a mother&amp;rsquo;s cooking comes between a husband and wife.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Missing A Father I Hardly Knew | With Willem Dafoe | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010227/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 19:17:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010227/</guid><description>Podcast Description Willem Dafoe (&amp;ldquo;The Florida Project&amp;rdquo;) reads Bruce Eric Kaplan&amp;rsquo;s essay, about waiting for a hilarious secret to be revealed.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Modern Love 100: Your Stories | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010228/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 16:26:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010228/</guid><description>Podcast Description We celebrate the 100th episode of Modern Love: The Podcast by listening to your stories, and the moments from our first 99 episodes that meant the most to you.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Dose Of Empathy | With Andrea Martin | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010229/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2018 17:24:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010229/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrea Martin (&amp;ldquo;Great News&amp;rdquo;) reads Randi Davenport&amp;rsquo;s essay, about a relationship that she says saved her life.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>In My Fantasy, I Caught Up To Reality | With Richard Jenkins | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010230/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 19:30:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010230/</guid><description>Podcast Description Richard Jenkins (&amp;ldquo;The Shape of Water&amp;rdquo;) reads John Gfroerer&amp;rsquo;s essay about going to the gym to cope with loss.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Yes, We Do. Even At Our Age. | With Lois Smith | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010231/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 15:44:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010231/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lois Smith (&amp;ldquo;Marjorie Prime,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Lady Bird&amp;rdquo;) reads an essay about passion in the golden years.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>In The New Year, More Cuddling | With Margarita Levieva | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010232/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 15:55:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010232/</guid><description>Podcast Description Margarita Levieva (&amp;ldquo;The Deuce&amp;rdquo;) reads Kristine Lloyd&amp;rsquo;s essay, about making a New Year&amp;rsquo;s resolution to attend a cuddle party.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sharing A Cab, And My Toes | With Greta Gerwig | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010233/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2017 19:16:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010233/</guid><description>Podcast Description Greta Gerwig (&amp;ldquo;Lady Bird&amp;rdquo;) reads Julia Anne Miller&amp;rsquo;s essay, about sharing an unusual cab ride in New York City.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How The 'Dining Dead' Got Talking Again | With Kristin Scott Thomas | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010234/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 15:08:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010234/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kristin Scott Thomas (&amp;ldquo;Darkest Hour&amp;rdquo;) reads an essay about a woman worried that she and her husband might have nothing left to talk about.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Was I On A Date Or Baby-Sitting? | With Sasheer Zamata | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010235/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 15:50:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010235/</guid><description>Podcast Description Julie Klausner tells the story of dating an &amp;ldquo;indie rock dreamboat&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; who she sees as a bit of a man-child. Sasheer Zamata (&amp;ldquo;United States of Music,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Pizza Mind&amp;rdquo;) reads Julie&amp;rsquo;s essay.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Boyfriend Too Good To Be True | With Caitriona Balfe | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010236/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 18:12:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010236/</guid><description>Podcast Description Caitriona Balfe (&amp;ldquo;Outlander&amp;rdquo;) reads Deenie Hartzog-Mislock&amp;rsquo;s essay, about an imaginary man who helps a family cope with Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Modern Love Encore: 'A Heart Of Gold' | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010237/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 17:08:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010237/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this encore, Ruth Negga (&amp;ldquo;Preacher,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Loving&amp;rdquo;) reads a story about the deep bond between a woman and her unusual pet.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We Didn't Have A Plan, But The Baby Did | With Paul Sun-Hyung Lee | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010238/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 13:56:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010238/</guid><description>Podcast Description Paul Sun-Hyung Lee (&amp;ldquo;Kim&amp;rsquo;s Convenience&amp;rdquo;) reads a story about a man improvising a birth plan.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Urgent Messages Go Unanswered | With Andrew Rannells | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010239/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 16:42:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010239/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrew Rannells (&amp;ldquo;Girls&amp;rdquo;) reads his own essay, about ignoring a string of urgent phone calls during a casual hookup.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Family Fairytale, Twice Told | With Julia Stiles | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010240/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 17:24:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010240/</guid><description>Podcast Description Julia Stiles (&amp;ldquo;Riviera&amp;rdquo;) tells the story of a woman who has a perfect New York City apartment &amp;hellip; and a crush on her roommate.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cropped Out Of My Own Fantasy | With Kirsten Vangsness | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010241/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 15:20:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010241/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirsten Vangsness (&amp;ldquo;Criminal Minds&amp;rdquo;) reads an essay about a relationship where the perfect images posted online don&amp;rsquo;t match the reality.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>My Body Doesn't Belong To You | With Cleopatra Coleman | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010242/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 18:07:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010242/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cleopatra Coleman (&amp;ldquo;The Last Man On Earth,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;White Famous&amp;rdquo;) reads an essay about a woman claiming ownership over her own body.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Let's Not Pretend | With Kimberly Hébert Gregory | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010243/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 19:02:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010243/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kimberly Hébert Gregory (&amp;ldquo;Kevin (Probably) Saves the World,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Vice Principals&amp;rdquo;) reads an essay about an attempt at dirty talk gone awry.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>My Husband Is Now My Wife | With Ann Dowd | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010244/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 15:31:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010244/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ann Dowd (&amp;ldquo;The Handmaid&amp;rsquo;s Tale&amp;rdquo;) reads Diane Daniel&amp;rsquo;s essay about a woman coming to terms with her spouse&amp;rsquo;s gender transition.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nursing A Wound | With Jake Gyllenhaal | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010245/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 18:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010245/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jake Gyllenhaal (&amp;ldquo;Stronger&amp;rdquo;) tells the story of a man recovering from heartbreak in a pediatrics wing.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>When Your Greatest Romance Is A Friendship | With Ali Fazal | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010246/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 17:18:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010246/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ali Fazal (&amp;ldquo;Victoria and Abul&amp;rdquo;) tells the story of an unlikely friendship between a man and his elderly neighbor.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>One Bouquet Of Fleeting Beauty | With Kerry Bishé | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010247/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 18:08:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010247/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kerry Bishe (&amp;ldquo;Halt and Catch Fire,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Narcos&amp;rdquo;) tells the story of one woman&amp;rsquo;s unexpected awakening &amp;ndash; at a flower shop.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Emmy Edition, 2017 | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010248/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 23:25:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010248/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 69th Primetime Emmy Awards are this weekend. To celebrate, we&amp;rsquo;re looking back at two of our favorite episodes featuring nominated actors. Angela Bassett reads Marcia DeSanctis&amp;rsquo; essay, &amp;ldquo;What the Psychic Knew&amp;rdquo; and Jesse Tyler Ferguson reads Jerry Mahoney&amp;rsquo;s essay, &amp;ldquo;Mom/Not Mom/Aunt.&amp;rdquo;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Promises That Can Bend | With Peter Gallagher | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010249/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 17:42:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010249/</guid><description>Podcast Description Peter Gallagher (&amp;ldquo;Grace and Frankie,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;The O.C.&amp;rdquo;) reads the story of one man&amp;rsquo;s effort to stay with his wife in sickness and in health.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>No Bounds, Or Lanes | With Kyra Sedgwick | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010250/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 19:21:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010250/</guid><description>Podcast Description Love, itself, is a leap of faith. But some people take a bigger jump than others. Kyra Sedgwick (TNT&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;The Closer&amp;rdquo;) reads a story about a &amp;ldquo;wild ride&amp;rdquo; of a marriage.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning To Embrace Sexuality's Gray Areas | With Nico Tortorella | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010251/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 18:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010251/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nico Tortorella (&amp;ldquo;Younger&amp;rdquo;) reads an essay about a college student whose ideas about love and sexuality change during the first weeks of his freshman year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dear Dad, We've Been Gay Forever | With Cynthia Nixon | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010252/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 17:26:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010252/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cynthia Nixon (&amp;ldquo;The Last Boy in New York,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;A Quiet Passion&amp;rdquo;) reads an essay about two grown siblings raised in the Mennonite church and their decision to come out to their 95-year-old father.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Lost Child, But Not Mine | With Betty Gilpin | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010253/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 18:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010253/</guid><description>Podcast Description Betty Gilpin of Netflix&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;G.L.O.W.&amp;rdquo; reads a story about life after abortion.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Flowergate | With June Diane Raphael | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010254/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 15:06:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010254/</guid><description>Podcast Description June Diane Raphael of Netflix&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Grace and Frankie&amp;rdquo; reads a story about a flower delivery gone very, very wrong.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Manic Pixie Dream Girl | With Alex Karpovsky | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010255/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 16:02:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010255/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex Karpovsky of HBO&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Girls&amp;rdquo; tells the story of one man&amp;rsquo;s quest to turn his love life into a cinematic event.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>I Need To Woman Up | With Cynthia Addai-Robinson | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010256/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 16:03:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010256/</guid><description>Podcast Description We can&amp;rsquo;t control the curve balls life throws at us, but we can control how we handle them. Cynthia Addai-Robinson (USA Network&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Shooter&amp;rdquo;) reads a story about choosing to face one of life&amp;rsquo;s greatest challenges alone.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>An Empty Heart | With Zoe Lister-Jones | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010257/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 16:54:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010257/</guid><description>Podcast Description Zoe Lister-Jones (&amp;ldquo;Band Aid,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Life in Pieces&amp;rdquo;) reads renowned novelist Lily King&amp;rsquo;s story about the silver lining of heartbreak.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Take My Son To Jail | With Jayne Atkinson | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010258/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 11:55:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010258/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jayne Atkinson (&amp;ldquo;House of Cards&amp;rdquo;) tells the story of a mother who reluctantly uses tough love when her son refuses to follow the law.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Modern Love Encore: Wedding Season | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010259/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 19:25:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010259/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s wedding season! Kathryn Hahn (&amp;ldquo;I Love Dick&amp;rdquo;) and John Cho (&amp;ldquo;Star Trek&amp;rdquo;) read some of our favorite nuptial-themed essays.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>About That Rustle In The Bushes | With Danielle Brooks | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010260/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 16:26:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010260/</guid><description>Podcast Description Danielle Brooks of &amp;ldquo;Orange Is The New Black&amp;rdquo; on a daughter&amp;rsquo;s discovery of her father&amp;rsquo;s secret investigative skills. The target? Her boyfriends.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Before The Web | With Griffin Dunne | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010261/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 17:48:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010261/</guid><description>Podcast Description Griffin Dunne of the Amazon series &amp;ldquo;I Love Dick&amp;rdquo; reads a story about how distance can make the heart grow discouragingly fonder.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Finding Marriage, Losing Self | With Taylor Schilling | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010262/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 16:13:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010262/</guid><description>Podcast Description Taylor Schilling of &amp;ldquo;Orange is the New Black&amp;rdquo; reads a story about unpacking the baggage of your past in a new relationship.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Standing By Your Man | With Chris Messina | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010263/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 17:01:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010263/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris Messina of &amp;ldquo;The Mindy Project&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;The Sweet Life&amp;rdquo; reads a story that explores what it really means to stand by your partner &amp;ldquo;in sickness and in health.&amp;rdquo;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Marry My Husband | With Debra Winger | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010264/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2017 16:44:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010264/</guid><description>Podcast Description Debra Winger reads the late Amy Krouse Rosenthal&amp;rsquo;s essay about her fairytale love story, which was cut short by cancer.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Slow Fade To Black | With Minnie Driver | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010265/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 16:08:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010265/</guid><description>Podcast Description Minnie Driver of ABC&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Speechless&amp;rdquo; tells the story of a woman whose dream life was almost complete &amp;ndash; until reality got in the way.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Just Don't Call Me Mom | With Gideon Glick | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010266/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2017 15:50:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010266/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mother&amp;rsquo;s Day is over &amp;ndash; for this year. Some people really look forward to those chocolates and flowers and others write a Modern Love essay bemoaning the day&amp;rsquo;s existence. Broadway actor Gideon Glick (&amp;ldquo;Spring Awakening,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Significant Other&amp;rdquo;) reads.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sharing The Shame | With Anna Chlumsky | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010267/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 16:18:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010267/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anna Chlumsky (&amp;ldquo;Veep&amp;rdquo;) tells the story of the 90 days that changed the entire course of one family&amp;rsquo;s life.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Prince Charming For The Prom | With Tituss Burgess | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010268/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2017 15:25:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010268/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tituss Burgess, the Emmy-nominated star of the Netflix series &amp;ldquo;Unbreakable Kimmy Schmidt,&amp;rdquo; reads us a story about teenage dreams &amp;ndash; the good, the bad, and the prom.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>It Took A Villain | With Melanie Lynskey | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010269/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 16:38:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010269/</guid><description>Podcast Description Melanie Lynskey of &amp;ldquo;Togetherness&amp;rdquo; and the new film &amp;ldquo;Little Boxes&amp;rdquo; tells the story of a neighborhood bully and the faltering marriage he inadvertently strengthened.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>In A Small Bag | With Harry Lennix | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010270/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 16:54:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010270/</guid><description>Podcast Description Harry Lennix of NBC&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;The Blacklist&amp;rdquo; reads the story of a couple who never saw their 22-year age difference as an issue. That is, until one of them had a heart attack.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Child Of Two Worlds | With Mireille Enos | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010271/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 17:41:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010271/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mireille Enos of ABC&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;The Catch&amp;rdquo; on one expat&amp;rsquo;s decision to embrace risk, get pregnant, and according to the Somali proverb, open &amp;ldquo;the mouth to her grave.&amp;rdquo;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>I Will Be Your Mother Figure | With Laura Dern | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010272/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 17:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010272/</guid><description>Podcast Description Laura Dern of HBO&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Big Little Lies&amp;rdquo; on one priest&amp;rsquo;s commitment to a parishioner in limbo.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Death Bear Will See You Now | With Ry Russo-Young | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010273/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2017 14:09:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010273/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ry Russo-Young, director of the new feature film &amp;ldquo;Before I Fall,&amp;rdquo; tells the story of a break-up, a best friend, and a performance artist.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The End Of Small Talk | With Paul Rust | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010274/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 14:26:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010274/</guid><description>Podcast Description Paul Rust, star of the Netflix comedy hit &amp;ldquo;Love,&amp;rdquo; tells the story of a man who says &amp;rsquo;no&amp;rsquo; to conversations about traffic and weather. Even on a first date.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Elvis And My Husband Have Left The Building | With Malin Akerman | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010275/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2017 13:38:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010275/</guid><description>Podcast Description Malin Akerman of Showtime&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Billions&amp;rdquo; tells the story of a pair of best friends who vow to stay together forever&amp;ndash;at least until the green card arrives.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Single, Female, Mormon, Alone | With Justina Machado | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010276/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 17:55:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010276/</guid><description>Podcast Description Justina Machado, star of the Netflix reboot &amp;ldquo;One Day At A Time,&amp;rdquo; shares the story of one woman&amp;rsquo;s quest to lose her virginity while at the same time finding herself.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Live From The Wilbur Theater (Part Two) | With Emmy Rossum | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010277/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 17:58:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010277/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emmy Rossum, star of the Showtime series &amp;ldquo;Shameless,&amp;rdquo; performs in front of a live audience.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Live From The Wilbur Theater (Part One) | With Brian Tyree Henry and Alysia Reiner | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010278/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 19:02:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010278/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brian Tyree Henry, star of the hit FX show &amp;ldquo;Atlanta,&amp;rdquo; and Alysia Reiner of &amp;ldquo;Orange is the New Black&amp;rdquo; kick off Part I of our live episode recorded live at the Wilbur Theater in Boston.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Modern Love: The Podcast Valentine's Special | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010279/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2017 15:48:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010279/</guid><description>Podcast Description Forget Netflix and chill. Settle in for a binge episode of Modern Love: The Podcast featuring Tony Hale (&amp;ldquo;Veep&amp;rdquo;), Gillian Jacobs (&amp;ldquo;Love&amp;rdquo;), and Colin Farrell (&amp;ldquo;The Lobster&amp;rdquo;)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Seeing The World Through My Wife's Eyes | With David Oyelowo | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010280/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 19:03:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010280/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;Selma&amp;rdquo; star David Oyelowo reads an essay about a blind man navigating his marriage.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>On The Precipice, Wings Spread | With Megan Hilty | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010281/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 19:44:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010281/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tony-nominee Megan Hilty of &amp;ldquo;Smash&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Noises Off&amp;rdquo; reads an essay about a couple with a seemingly perfect relationship&amp;ndash;until the other shoe drops.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Boy Who Makes Waves | With Mykelti Williamson | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010282/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 19:13:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010282/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mykelti Williamson of the Oscar-nominated film &amp;ldquo;Fences&amp;rdquo; reads an essay about a father&amp;rsquo;s complicated love for his son.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Groomzilla | With John Cho | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010283/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 18:31:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010283/</guid><description>Podcast Description John Cho reads an essay about a groom gone bad.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Family That Takes 'No' For An Answer | With Darby Stanchfield | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010284/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 20:30:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010284/</guid><description>Podcast Description Darby Stanchfield of ABC&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Scandal,&amp;rdquo; on an ordinary family hunting trip that turns into an unexpected lesson about hope.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Taking A Break For Friendship | With Sela Ward | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010285/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 18:25:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010285/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sela Ward reads an essay about a beautiful relationship&amp;hellip;or a friendship? Or a wanna-be friendship?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Modern Love Encore: 'A Millennial's Guide To Kissing' | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010286/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 15:37:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010286/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this encore, Emmy Rossum reads an essay about the complexities of millennial love.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Beware Of Big Boxes | With Pamela Adlon | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010287/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 18:52:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010287/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pamela Adlon of the FX series &amp;ldquo;Better Things&amp;rdquo; reads an essay about the dangers of romanticizing romantics.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Decembers | With Haydn Gwynne | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010288/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 19:37:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010288/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tony-nominated actor Haydn Gwynne reads about one woman&amp;rsquo;s quest to reclaim one of the hardest days of her life&amp;ndash;her birthday.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Modern Love Encore: 'Friends Without Benefits' | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010289/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 15:31:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010289/</guid><description>Podcast Description Taissa Farmiga shares a story of friendship and a love never reciprocated. This is an encore presentation.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>DJ's Homeless Mommy | With Dan Savage | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010290/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 15:13:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010290/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan Savage reads his own Modern Love essay about his son&amp;rsquo;s birth mother&amp;ndash;and her troubling path.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Fractured Beauty | With Molly Ringwald | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010291/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2016 13:34:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010291/</guid><description>Podcast Description Molly Ringwald reads an essay about a family vacation &amp;ndash; after divorce.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Out Of The Darkness | With Mark Duplass | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010292/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2016 14:08:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010292/</guid><description>Podcast Description Filmmaker Mark Duplass reads an essay about a husband who never thought &amp;ldquo;for worse&amp;rdquo; could get so bad.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Heart Of Gold | With Ruth Negga | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010293/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 19:09:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010293/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ruth Negga, star of new drama &amp;ldquo;Loving,&amp;rdquo; shares a story about the intimate connection between a woman and her unlikely pet.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Screens Between Us | With Issa Rae | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010294/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 16:04:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010294/</guid><description>Podcast Description Issa Rae, star of the new HBO comedy &amp;ldquo;Insecure,&amp;rdquo; reads an essay about the intimacy and distance synonymous with online dating.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Modern Love Live at Town Hall | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010295/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 16:15:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010295/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Harbour of Netflix&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Stranger Things&amp;rdquo; is featured in this week&amp;rsquo;s excerpt from the New York City production Modern Love Live. He reads the essay, &amp;ldquo;Out From Under the Influence.&amp;rdquo;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Take Me As I Am, Whoever I Am | With Rebecca Hall | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010296/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 20:38:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010296/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rebecca Hall who stars in the new drama &amp;ldquo;Christine,&amp;rdquo; reads a story about dating &amp;ndash; while manic.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Marry A Man Who Loves His Mother | With Constance Wu | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010297/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 17:27:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010297/</guid><description>Podcast Description Constance Wu of the ABC comedy &amp;ldquo;Fresh Off The Boat&amp;rdquo; reads a story about a wife, a mother-in-law and the unlikely story that brought them together.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Path To Fatherhood | With Dash Mihok | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010298/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 18:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010298/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Dash Mihok of Showtime&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Ray Donovan,&amp;rdquo; shares a story about a man, his diagnosis, and his unborn baby.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Wedding Toast | With Kathryn Hahn | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010299/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 14:49:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010299/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kathryn Hahn reads a story about a fantasy wedding toast &amp;ndash; and why it will never be delivered.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Modern Love Bonus Episode: Emmy Edition | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010300/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2016 18:52:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010300/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s Emmy Edition at Modern Love! This week, we hear from three Emmy-award winning readers: Sarah Paulson, Sterling K. Brown, and Tony Hale.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Revenge of the Friend | With Kristin Chenoweth | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010301/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 19:08:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010301/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kristin Chenoweth, the Emmy and Tony Award-winning actor and singer, reads a story about a revenge fantasy coming true.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kept Together By The Bars Between Us | With Cherry Jones | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010302/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2016 16:32:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010302/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cherry Jones, the Tony, Emmy, and Obie-Award winning actor, reads a story about a woman who falls in love with a convicted murderer.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Modern Love Bonus Episode: Near-Death Experiences | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010303/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2016 21:32:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010303/</guid><description>Podcast Description Modern Love listeners share their stories of near-death experiences and how they altered the course of their lives.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What The Psychic Knew | With Angela Bassett | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010304/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 20:15:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010304/</guid><description>Podcast Description Angela Bassett, the Oscar and Emmy Award-nominated actor, reads a story about a psychic and a sickness.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>My First Son, A Pure Memory | With Sterling K. Brown | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010305/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 12:44:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010305/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emmy-nominated actor Sterling K. Brown reads an essay about a new dad and his emotional journey toward fatherhood.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Prince Charming For The Prom | With Tituss Burgess | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010306/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2016 14:27:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010306/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tituss Burgess, the Emmy-nominated star of the Netflix series &amp;ldquo;Unbreakable Kimmy Schmidt,&amp;rdquo; reads us a story about teenage dreams &amp;ndash; the good, the bad, and the prom.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Race Grows Sweeter | With Mary-Chapin Carpenter | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010307/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 15:56:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010307/</guid><description>Podcast Description Singer Mary-Chapin Carpenter reads a story about new love (much) later in life.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>To Fall In Love With Anyone, Do This | With Gillian Jacobs | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010308/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2016 18:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010308/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gillian Jacobs &amp;ndash; known for the Netflix series &amp;ldquo;Love&amp;rdquo; and NBC&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Community&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; reads a story about falling in love with the help of a psychological experiment.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Three Mothers, One Bond | With Gaby Hoffmann | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010309/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2016 19:19:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010309/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gaby Hoffmann, known for her Emmy-nominated role in the Amazon series &amp;ldquo;Transparent,&amp;rdquo; as well as her work in HBO&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Girls,&amp;rdquo; reads an essay about a couple navigating the complex waters of adoption.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Just Friends? | With Tony Hale | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010310/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 17:46:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010310/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emmy Award-winning actor Tony Hale of HBO&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Veep&amp;rdquo; reads an essay about breaking up, moving on (or not), and reading between the lines.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Live Without Me | With Catherine Keener | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010311/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2016 12:15:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010311/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two-time Oscar nominee Catherine Keener reads Katherine Friedman Holland&amp;rsquo;s essay about a near-death experience on an airplane.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>One Last Swirl | With Jason Alexander | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010312/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 15:58:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010312/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jason Alexander &amp;ndash; best known as George Costanza from the iconic 90&amp;rsquo;s sit-com &amp;ldquo;Seinfeld&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; reads a story that explores mortality with the help of a resilient pet fish.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Estranged Spouses | With Lance Reddick | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010313/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2016 13:43:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010313/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lance Reddick, best known as Lt. Cedric Daniels on HBO&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;The Wire,&amp;rdquo; reads a story about infidelity and healing.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Live From New York | With Michaela Watkins, Amirah Vann and Lauren Molina | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010314/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2016 15:13:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010314/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michaela Watkins, Amirah Vann and Lauren Molina read Modern Love essays live in front of a studio audience.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Fighting Words | With Alysia Reiner | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010315/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 19:08:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010315/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alysia Reiner of Orange is the New Black delivers a story about what happens when a stable relationship suddenly takes a hard left turn.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Doorman | With Cecily Strong | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010316/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2016 23:34:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010316/</guid><description>Podcast Description Saturday Night Live&amp;rsquo;s Cecily Strong reads a story about a woman&amp;rsquo;s friendship with her doorman.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Wait | Modern Love Bonus Episode | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010317/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2016 03:46:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010317/</guid><description>Podcast Description We asked you to tell us about a time when you &amp;ldquo;waited for love,&amp;rdquo; and you answered from all over the world. This bonus episode of Modern Love features some of those stories.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Coming Out As A Modern Family | With Maria Bello | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010318/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 21:54:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010318/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress Maria Bello reads her own essay about opening up to her son and the public about her love life.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How I Got To Here | With Katie Couric | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010319/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2016 20:40:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010319/</guid><description>Podcast Description Katie Couric reads Leslie Lehr&amp;rsquo;s Modern Love essay about learning the true depth of her relationship with her husband.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Friends Without Benefits | With Taissa Farmiga | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010320/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2016 22:24:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010320/</guid><description>Podcast Description Taissa Farmiga reads a story about &amp;ldquo;friends without benefits&amp;rdquo; who spend years circling each other without defining their drawn-out, nebulous relationship.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Heart Outrun | With Colin Farrell | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010321/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2016 00:48:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010321/</guid><description>Podcast Description Colin Farrell reads the story of man who had given up on love &amp;ndash; until it showed up at his door.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Second Embrace | With Cheryl Strayed | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010322/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 00:06:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010322/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cheryl Strayed &amp;ndash; co-host of WBUR&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Dear Sugar&amp;rdquo; podcast and author of the best-selling memoir &amp;ldquo;Wild&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; reads a story about taking a second chance on love.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>I See My Superhero | With Sarah Silverman | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010323/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 23:58:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010323/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sarah Silverman brings us a story of unconditional love &amp;hellip; with a few conditions.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Between The Bars | With Joshua Jackson | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010324/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2016 00:34:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010324/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joshua Jackson reads a story about life and love after 26 months in Iran&amp;rsquo;s Evin Prison.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>My First Lesson In Motherhood | With Connie Britton | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010325/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2016 00:06:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010325/</guid><description>Podcast Description Connie Britton narrates a story about a new mom and a tiny infant whose young life is checkered with mysteries both big and small.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Maddy Just Might Work | With Jennifer Finney Boylan | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010326/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 00:22:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010326/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer Finney Boylan &amp;ndash; an accomplished writer, academic and activist &amp;ndash; reads her own essay about coming out as transgender to her two young sons.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Broken, Not Bound | With America Ferrera | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010327/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 02:52:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010327/</guid><description>Podcast Description America Ferrera reads the story of an African aid worker, and an event that drastically shifted her perspective.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mom/Not Mom/Aunt | With Jesse Tyler Ferguson | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010328/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2016 23:16:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010328/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jesse Tyler Ferguson reads a story about a brother&amp;rsquo;s unique need and sister&amp;rsquo;s selfless gift.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Where It All Started | Modern Love Bonus Episode | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010329/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 23:58:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010329/</guid><description>Podcast Description Modern Love listeners share true stories of meeting their significant other.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Millennial's Guide To Kissing | With Emmy Rossum | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010330/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2016 22:36:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010330/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emmy Rossum reads a story about a 12-hour relationship. On an airplane.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Seesawing Libidos | With Stephen Bogardus | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010331/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2016 00:58:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010331/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tony-nominated actor Stephen Bogardus brings us a tale of two sex drives.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Leaps of Faith | Modern Love Bonus Episode | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010332/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 03:52:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010332/</guid><description>Podcast Description We love hearing your stories of love, loss and redemption. This bonus episode features listener-submitted stories involving &amp;ldquo;leaps of faith.&amp;rdquo;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Faithful Leap | With Amber Tamblyn | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010333/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2016 02:38:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010333/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amber Tamblyn brings us the story of a leap of faith so dramatic, it&amp;rsquo;s straight out of a movie.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>In Darkness And In Light | With Patina Miller | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010334/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 02:34:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010334/</guid><description>Podcast Description Patina Miller narrates a story about one woman who has a seemingly average life and marriage &amp;ndash; except for the fact that she&amp;rsquo;s slowly going blind.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Magically Interrupted | With Michael Shannon | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010335/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 00:22:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010335/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael Shannon reads an essay that explores how Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s put one family back together.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A 'Modern Love' Audio Valentine | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010336/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 19:22:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010336/</guid><description>Podcast Description An audio valentine from Modern Love listeners &amp;ndash; for Modern Love listeners.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>'The Plunge' | With Dakota Fanning | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010337/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2016 03:28:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010337/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dakota Fanning narrates an essay about a falling in love and falling off a cliff &amp;ndash; literally.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>'An Interlude Of Clarity' | With Judd Apatow | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010338/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2016 01:52:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010338/</guid><description>Podcast Description Judd Apatow reads a story about a man whose perfect date ends up in the emergency room.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Not So Simple Math | With Sarah Paulson | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010339/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 15:54:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010339/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sarah Paulson narrates this week&amp;rsquo;s episode &amp;ndash; a story about a woman&amp;rsquo;s decision to put up her child for an open adoption.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>One Last Swirl | With Jason Alexander | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010340/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 01:48:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010340/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jason Alexander narrates this story about a man projecting his deepest thoughts of mortality onto his pet fish.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Missed Connection | With Lauren Molina | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010341/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 01:48:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010341/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to our first episode. Lauren Molina narrates a story about a romance that begins on an unlikely website &amp;ndash; Craigslist.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Introducing 'Modern Love: The Podcast' | Modern Love</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3024010342/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2015 21:28:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3024010342/</guid><description>Podcast Description Explore the trials and tribulations of love in these deeply personal essays. A collaboration of The New York Times and WBUR in Boston, Modern Love: The Podcast features the popular New York Times column, with readings by notable personalities and updates from the essayists themselves. Join host Meghna Chakrabarti (WBUR) and Modern Love editor Daniel Jones (NYT) &amp;ndash; and fall in love at first listen.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>