<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/voa-learning-english-podcast-voa-learning-english/</link><description>Recent content in VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/voa-learning-english-podcast-voa-learning-english/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Learning English Podcast - December 19, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190047/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190047/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, what does the trial of an activist publisher on national security charges mean for Hong Kong’s future? ; research suggests millions of Americans suffer long-term tiredness followed by a discussion about the problem; then ‘sneaking around’ on Lesson of the Day.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - December 18, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190048/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190048/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, a short history of climate-related promises made at U.N. climate meetings; scientists have connected nerve cells with an electric circuit to make a biocomputer followed by a discussion about the system’s biological part and its accuracy; then present perfect on Lesson of the Day.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - December 17, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190046/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190046/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, top college presidents face criticism over testimony about antisematism; expression that include the word ‘snowball’ followed by a discussion about what happens when something snowballs; then the presidency of Bill Clinton on America’s Presidents.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - December 16, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190045/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190045/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, a Brazilian indian tribe aims to expand by having female chiefs as it nears disappearing; we answer a listener’s question about ‘wonder’ followed by a discussion about pronouncing wonder and wander; then “The Gift of the Magi” by O. Henry on American Stories.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - December 15, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190044/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learning English use a limited vocabulary and are read at a slower pace than VOA&amp;rsquo;s other English broadcasts. Previously known as Special English.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - December 14, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190042/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190042/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, the Bill &amp;amp; Melinda Gates Foundation aims to donate $100 million; the most mispronounced words of the year; a jury finds Google’s app store illegally blocks competition followed by a discussion on monopolies; then pronunciation and idioms on Lesson of the Day.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - December 13, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190043/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, environmentalists in Michigan learn to live with a nickel mine; hundreds of seals die from bird flu in Brazil; an international test shows math scores have decreased since 2018 followed by a discussion about resilience in education; on Lesson of the Day, ‘supply chain.'
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - December 12, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190041/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pangea: On today’s podcast, Japanese baseball player Shohei Ohtani gets the biggest-ever contract in team sports; the U.S. government approves to gene treatments for sickle cell disease followed by an explanation about the disease; then lend and borrow on Lesson of the Day.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - December 11, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190038/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190038/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, the College Board changes AP Black history classes after questions; ancient male mosquitos were different; scientists discover an unusual planetary system followed by a discussion on the six, newly-found ‘harmonious’ planets; then the future continuous on Lesson of the Day.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - December 10, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190039/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190039/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, more small colleges are closing down because of high costs and other reasons; publishers name ‘AI,’ ‘hallucinate,’ ‘authentic’ and ‘rizz’ as words of the year; then, the presidency of George H.W. Bush on America’s Presidents.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - December 09, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190040/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190040/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, India plans a huge renewable energy project; a rock band aims to perform ‘forever’ using computer avatars; a listener’s question about the difference between ‘ability’ and ‘capability’; followed by a Edith Warton’s piece: ‘The Line of Least Resistance’ on American Stories.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - December 08, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190037/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190037/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, all about the Jewish holiday of Hanukkah; the U.S. government aims to reduce uranium production for nuclear submarines; development of artificial intelligence divides the technology industry; talking about pets followed by a discussion about our animal friends.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - December 07, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190036/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learning English use a limited vocabulary and are read at a slower pace than VOA&amp;rsquo;s other English broadcasts. Previously known as Special English.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - December 06, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190035/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190035/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, a study finds penguins use microsleep to get enough rest; the Associated Press says many home schools in Louisiana operate outside the state education system followed by a discussion about the findings; then, the word ‘legacy’ on Lesson of the Day.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - December 05, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190033/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190033/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, efforts grow in the U.S. to reduce food waste; South Africa, Colombia push drug makers to permit cheap TB, HIV/AIDS drugs followed by a discussion about what patents are; then learn what “plan B” is on Lesson of the Day.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - December 04, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190034/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learning English uses a limited vocabulary and are read at a slower pace than VOA&amp;rsquo;s other English broadcasts. Previously known as Special English.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - December 03, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190032/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190032/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, what foreign college students do when big American holidays come along; bright expressions shine a light on things; followed by the presidency of Ronald Reagan on America’s Presidents.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - December 02, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190031/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190031/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, life expectancy is rising in the U.S. after years of decline; a new book about Dr. Seuss’s Grinch called ‘How the Grinch Lost Christmas’; we answer a listener’s question about the difference between ‘price’ and ‘rate’; &amp;lsquo;The Boarded Window&amp;rsquo; by Ambrose Bierce on American Stories.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - December 01, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190029/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190029/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, statesman Henry Kissinger dies at 100; Young Chinese seek a freer life in the country’s southwest; South Korea uses matchmaking to lift birth rate; then, the grammar of gift giving followed by a discussion about hopes for holiday gifts.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - November 30, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190030/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190030/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, a former Somali refugee wins UN refuge agency prize; passenger jet flies the Atlantic Ocean on fuel made from cooking fat; Google plans to remove unused accounts followed by a details about Google’s plan; then how feedback works on Lesson of the Day.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - November 29, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190027/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190027/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, India road workers rescued from a collapsed tunnel after 17 days; costly water is growing in popularity; a program in Washington, D.C.’s poorest neighborhoods sends journalism students to college followed by more on D.C. neighborhoods; then, ‘cultivation’ on Lesson of the Day.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - November 28, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190028/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190028/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, the latest on the hostage release during a cease-fire in the Hamas-Israel war; Christmas at the White House; new research into an Alzheimer’s disease vaccine followed by a discussion on the report; then, resolutions and fun public speaking tips on Lesson of the Day.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - November 27, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190026/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190026/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, sugar is in short supply in many nations after a poor harvest; NASA is using lasers to send more information from spacecraft followed by a discussion the new technology and a space mission to an asteroid; then prefixes and shortened forms on Lesson of the Day.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - November 26, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190025/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190025/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, the U.S. Department of Education says Black and Latino students lack the tools for success; a clergyman uses music to connect with young people; ‘count your blessing’ and other expressions followed by the presidency of Jimmy Carter on America’s Presidents.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - November 25, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190024/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190024/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, the World Health Organization says nothing unusual about wave of lung infections in northeastern China; herders continue to keep animals in a change world; a listener’s question about ‘danger’ and ‘hazard’; then, ‘Two Thanksgiving Day Gentlemen’ by O. Henry.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - November 24, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190023/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, automakers aim to design electric cars with fewer rare earth metals; coral reefs in the Gulf of Mexico are doing well; the grammar of talking about pets followed by a discussion on those family friends; then famous women placed in the National Women’s Hall of Fame.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - November 23, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190022/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, U.S. companies aim to increase battery production; learn about the Thanksgiving Holiday in America followed by a discussion about the tradition; then hair problems on Lesson of the Day.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - November 22, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190021/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, a “poor” man leaves a New Hampshire town $3.8 million; how did the turkey get its name?; a study finds schools’ reports on student grades do not mean the student is performing at grade level followed by a discussion about report cards; and the word ‘adopt’ on Lesson of the Day.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - November 21, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190001/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190001/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, Argentina’s new president faces high inflation, economic problems; is it the end of China’s panda diplomacy?; experts worry not enough overweight people are included in drug tests; then ways to agree and disagree on Lesson of the Day.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - November 20, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190002/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, extremist groups spread in West Africa; new research on Eris, a distant member of the solar system; Chinese researchers say the made an AI robot that makes oxygen from rocks, and a discussion on similar systems for Mars exploration; then possessive pronouns on Lesson of the Day.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - November 19, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190003/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190003/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, numbers of foreign college students in the U.S. have returned to levels before COVID-19 thanks to Indian students; learn about ‘state-of-the-art’ and similar terms on Words and Their Stories; then, the presidency of Gerald Ford on America’s Presidents.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - November 18, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190004/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190004/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, could a movie about scams be keeping Chinese visitors away from Southeast Asia?; the difference between ‘source’ and ‘resource’ followed by a discussion on sources and plagiarism; then a ‘fountain of youth’ on Nathaniel Hawthorne’s ‘Doctor Heidegger’s Experiment.’
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - November 17, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190005/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190005/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, how Taiwan is attending the APEC economic meetings in San Francisco; is a two-state agreement possible in the Middle East?; cheetahs might be changing hunting habits; Spain’s Canary Islands has too many immigrants; then, all about Happy Thanksgiving.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - November 16, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190006/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, people in Japan are buying fish from Fukushima as some countries ban products from that area; new companies aim to confirm video from social media followed by a discussion misinformation and artificial intelligence; then describing amounts in Lesson of the Day.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - November 15, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190007/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, UN negotiators want a treaty on plastic pollution; in Japan, animals receive blessings; a report finds U.S. men graduate at lower rates than women followed by a discussion on the topic; then hear about the word ‘comply’ on Lesson of the Day.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - November 14, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190008/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, hear about this week’s APEC meeting of Pacific Ocean leaders in San Francisco; the drug ketamine is being increasingly used to treat pain, depression and other conditions followed by a discussion on the drug’s effects; then reading people’s minds on Lesson of the Day.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - November 13, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190009/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190009/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, evidence of a crash with another planet in Earth’s past; Syria’s dry conditions and climate change; a new space telescope begins its search for dark matter and energy followed by a discussion about forces at work in space; certainty and uncertainty on Lesson of the Day.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - November 12, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190010/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190010/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, college students play climate change board games in class; expression for being in a good place followed by a discussion about ‘sitting pretty’&amp;rsquo; and being on &amp;lsquo;cloud nine;&amp;rsquo; then the presidency of Richard Nixon on America’s Presidents.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - November 11, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190011/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190011/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, a Swiss device helps a person with Parkinson’s disease; we answer a listener’s question about the word ‘get’ followed by a discussion about its common uses; then a Civil War veteran returns home in Hamlin Garland&amp;rsquo;s “Return of the Private” on American stories.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - November 10, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190012/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190012/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, an industrial robot crushes a South Korean worker; homes in Florida are being built to withstand strong storms; what do you do with autumn leaves?; how do we express pessimism in English followed by a discussion comparing pessimism and optimism.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - November 09, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190013/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, Kenya declares a surprise holiday to plant trees; should robots look like people?; scientists find a black hole that formed not long after the Big Bang followed by why you call a black hole “an object;” then listen nouns with –er endings on Lesson of the day.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - November 08, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190014/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, people are again wearing masks in New Delhi, India; artist/activist makes an exhibit on the high cost of housing; then, lack of housing in Los Angeles has students missing class followed by a discussion about shaping a story; the word &amp;lsquo;interpret&amp;rsquo; on Lesson of the Day.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - November 07, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190015/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, group will rename all North America birds named after people; Colombia get serious about hippopotamus control; a new treatment for sickle cell disease followed by details about the dangerous disease; then interjections and a poem on Lesson of the Day.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - November 06, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190016/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, Chinese migrants are crossing Panama to get to the U.S. southern border; Navajos in the American Southwest aim to keep sheep herding; Antarctica was once warm followed by a discussion about findings beneath Antarctica’s ice; then, going to a baseball game on Lesson of the Day.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - November 05, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190017/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190017/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, what happens when a foreign student mistakes Miami, Ohio, for Miami, Florida?; the popular expression ‘straight from the horse’s mouth’ on ‘Words and Their Stories;’ then, the presidency of Lyndon Johnson on ‘America’s Presidents.’
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - November 04, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190018/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190018/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, a new university law class on – pop star Taylor Swift?; learn about Italian artist Michelangelo’s secret room; a listener’s question about using ‘which’ followed by a discussion on which preposition to use with ‘which;’ then, ‘The Boy on Graves-End Road’ on American Stories.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - November 03, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190019/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190019/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, what is Daylight Saving Time in the U.S.?; a U.N. report says budget cuts are hurting Rwanda; an environmental group says few companies are use water effectively; the grammar of optimism followed by a discussion on optimism and pessimism.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Learning English Podcast - November 02, 2023 | VOA Learning English Podcast - VOA Learning English</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2531190020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2531190020/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s podcast, Vietnam aims to become a major computer chip manufacturer; a report says Africa is unlikely to increase manufacturing in the future; the way the world gets its electricity – grids – faces problems; then learn about ‘superlatives’ on Lesson of the Day.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>