<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Morrison Mysteries on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/morrison-mysteries/</link><description>Recent content in Morrison Mysteries on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 11:40:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/morrison-mysteries/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>5 – A Christmas Carol: The End of It | Morrison Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9527810001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 11:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9527810001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ebenezer Scrooge awakens in his home on Christmas morning to find he has a second chance. He joyfully makes amends with all those around him and even becomes a father figure to Tiny Tim.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>4 – A Christmas Carol: The Last of the Spirits | Morrison Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9527810002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9527810002/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Ghost of Christmas Future reveals the appalling events that will happen if Scrooge doesn’t become a kinder man. Tiny Tim will die, and so will Scrooge, though no one will mourn him. Scrooge begs the Ghost for a chance to put things right.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>3 – A Christmas Carol: The Second of the Three Spirits | Morrison Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9527810003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 11:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9527810003/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Ghost of Christmas Present shows Scrooge how Christmas should be celebrated – with joy and giving, even when you are poor, like Scrooge’s own kindly clerk Bob Cratchit.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>2 – A Christmas Carol: The First of the Three Spirits | Morrison Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9527810004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 11:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9527810004/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Ghost of Christmas Past visits Scrooge and takes him back to his own childhood. He’s reminded that he was shown kindness as a young man, and had even been in love, before his greed took over.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>1 – A Christmas Carol: Marley’s Ghost | Morrison Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9527810005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9527810005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ebenezer Scrooge hates Christmas with a passion. To him, it’s all a waste of time and money. But when he’s visited by the ghost of his dead business partner, the equally greedy Jacob Marley, Scrooge begins to understand the error of his ways.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Introducing Season 2 of Morrison Mysteries: A Christmas Carol | Morrison Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9527810006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9527810006/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Season 2 of Morrison Mysteries, Dateline NBC’s Keith Morrison takes you back to Victorian England, where it’s Christmas Eve. Everyone is full of joy and cheer, except one miserable man – Ebenezer Scrooge. What happened to make him so mean? Tune in to Charles Dickens’ A Christmas Carol to hear all about Tiny Tim, Bob Cratchit, and the Ghosts who show Scrooge the true spirit of Christmas.</description></item><item><title>Dateline presents: Mortal Sin | Morrison Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9527810007/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9527810007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey, Dateline fans! As a bonus, we’re giving you a special preview clip of our new podcast series Mortal Sin. In Dateline’s latest original podcast series, Josh Mankiewicz tells a twisted tale about a seemingly perfect couple, sex, lies, religion…and murder. If you like what you hear, you can listen to the first 2 episodes now for free, or subscribe to Dateline Premium on Apple Podcasts to get access to new episodes 1 week early.</description></item><item><title>3 – The Legend of Sleepy Hollow: A Ghostly Encounter | Morrison Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9527810008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9527810008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Things with Katrina don’t go the way Ichabod Crane had hoped. As he rides home, stories of local ghosts haunt his thoughts. Panicked, he gallops off into the night, only to encounter the most terrifying sight of all – the Headless Horseman himself!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>2 – The Legend of Sleepy Hollow: Head Over Heels | Morrison Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9527810009/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9527810009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ichabod Crane has fallen hard for Katrina. At a big party at the Van Tassel home, the two dance all night as jealous Brom stews in the corner. By night’s end, Ichabod prepares to profess his love.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>1 – The Legend of Sleepy Hollow: A Teacher Comes To Town | Morrison Mysteries</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9527810010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9527810010/</guid><description>Podcast Description New school teacher Ichabod Crane wastes no time getting to know everyone in town, especially the rich and beautiful Katrina Van Tassel. The only problem is, Katrina has another suitor – the dashing Brom Bones.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>