<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Canadian True Crime on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/canadian-true-crime/</link><description>Recent content in Canadian True Crime on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 06:01:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/canadian-true-crime/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>148 The Murderous Mountie–Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 06:01:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570001/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 1 of 2] The twisted story of Sergeant John Wilson: a mountie at the centre of a sordid love triangle that played out as World War I raged on.&amp;nbsp;
Put together from an archive of hundreds of real love letters, forged letters and police and court memos, this gripping, action-packed miniseries offers a vivid snapshot of Canada at a pivotal moment in history.
Part 2 available now ad-free on CTC Premium feeds - Amazon Music (included with Prime), Apple Podcasts, Patreon and Supercast.</description></item><item><title>Major Case Updates &amp; Feedback 2023—Part 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 06:01:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570002/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 2 of 2] Continuing our look back at cases we've covered that have had major updates or have attracted notable feedback.
Approximate timestamps:
1:20 - Jacob Hoggard Trial10:30 - The Brentwood Five (Matthew de Grood)20:15 - Dellen Millard, Mark Smich and other criminals serving consecutive life sentences29:00 - The Giant Mine Murders - 30th Anniversary32:30 - The Renfrew County Massacre - Inquiry update35:30 - The Survival of Zach Miller38:20 - Feedback around using AI Voices in episodes41:10 - Albert Johnson Walker (the murder of Ronald Platt)45:00 - Paul Bernardo’s recent parole controversy and the aftermath</description></item><item><title>Major Case Updates &amp; Feedback 2023—Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 22:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570003/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 1 of 2] In this two-part series, we report back on cases that have had major updates or have attracted notable feedback over this past year. Kristi will also be addressing some of the most common comments and feedback received.
Part 2 is available ad-free now on CTC premium feeds: Amazon Music (included with Prime), Apple Podcasts, Patreon and Supercast
Available to all in one week - November 21.</description></item><item><title>147 The Very Bad Doctor | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570004/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 21:30:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Additional content warning: this episode includes mention of intimate partner violence, suicidal ideation, and grooming and sexual assault of an underage person. No graphic details will be given. Please take care when listening.
A doctor repeatedly and intentionally betrays his oath to do no harm, setting off a chain reaction that escalates to murder.&amp;nbsp;
More info:
Fatal Prescription: A Doctor Without Remorse, written by John Griffiths &amp;amp; Shelly Charalambus</description></item><item><title>Remembering Beverley Rowbotham: 23 Years Today | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570005/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 04:03:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Special ad-free presentation to commemorate the 23rd anniversary of the murder of Beverley Rowbotham, a wife and mother of two young boys.
About three years ago, Canadian True Crime released an episode about Beverley’s case, and earlier this year we were contacted by members of her family who wanted to discuss the case.
We’ve kept in contact and at their suggestion, we’re republishing the episode ad-free today, re-mastered and slightly updated, to keep Beverley's memory fresh and make sure she isn't forgotten.</description></item><item><title>146 Brampton High School Shootings | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570006/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 21:28:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570006/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1975, a teenager walked into his high school carrying two rifles in a black guitar case.
This is the story of the first ever mass shooting at a secondary school in Canada, and how it spurred changes to Canadian firearms laws.
More info:
1975 SCHOOL SHOOTING: "There were not words to describe this sort of thing..." - Brampton GuardianA TRAGEDY’S LONG SHADOW - Toronto StarBrampton Centennial has built a memorial to help the 1975 school shooting survivors heal - CBC News</description></item><item><title>145 The Truth About Canada's Opioid Crisis—Part 3 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570007/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 05:01:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570007/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 3 of 3 ] The truth about Canada’s Opioid Crisis is complicated and multi-faceted, but many experts in the field are clear about what’s going wrong.
In this final part, we'll explore the evidence and data, and delve into what addiction is and where it originates.
We'll look at what grief-stricken families are saying about Canada's slow and limited response to the opioid crisis—and what they are demanding be done instead.</description></item><item><title>144 The Truth About Canada's Opioid Crisis—Part 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 21:19:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Content warning: this episode includes mentions of Indigenous trauma, residential schools and the 60s scoop.
[ Part 2 of 3 ] Through the stories of four young Canadians from completely different walks of life—who all met the same devastating fate, we explore how Canada got itself into the mess that is the opioid crisis. In this episode, you'll hear the stories of Skye Crassweller and Morgan Goodridge.
Resources for those affected by the Opioid Crisis:</description></item><item><title>143 The Truth About Canada's Opioid Crisis—Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 21:59:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570009/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 1 of 3 ] Through the stories of four young Canadians from completely different walks of life—who all met the same devastating fate, we explore how Canada got itself into the mess that is the opioid crisis. Sophie Breen, Seth MacLean, Skye Crassweller and Morgan Goodridge were among the almost 40,000 Canadians who have died of toxic drug poisoning since 2016. Most of these deaths were accidental, caused by street drugs contaminated with deadly illegal fentanyl.</description></item><item><title>142 The Legacy Christian Academy Scandal—Part 3 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 23:44:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570010/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 3 of 3 ] The allegations result in criminal charges.
#legacyofabuse
Content Warning: This series is about allegations of physical, sexual, psychological and spiritual abuse of students and minors at their church-run Christian school. There is heavy focus on corporal punishment, details of grooming and sexual assault of minors, mention of anti-LGBTQ+ and racist rhetoric, mention of self-harm and suicidal ideation. While these allegations have resulted in criminal charges, they haven’t yet been proven or tested in court.</description></item><item><title>141 The Legacy Christian Academy Scandal—Part 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 23:37:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570011/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 2 of 3 ] Caitlin Erickson makes a discovery that prompts her to give a statement to police.
#legacyofabuse
Content Warning: This series is about allegations of physical, sexual, psychological and spiritual abuse of students and minors at their church-run Christian school. There is heavy focus on corporal punishment, details of grooming and sexual assault of minors, mention of anti-LGBTQ+ and racist rhetoric, mention of self-harm and suicidal ideation.</description></item><item><title>140 The Legacy Christian Academy Scandal—Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570012/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 1 of 3 ] Since August of 2022, a cascade of distressing allegations have come to light by former students of a deeply intertwined evangelical Christian school and the church that runs it.&amp;nbsp;So far, criminal charges have been laid on four men in positions of authority.... and more are likely to come.
CONTENT WARNING: This series is about allegations of physical, sexual, psychological and spiritual abuse of students and minors at their church-run Christian school.</description></item><item><title>139 Antonio Scopelliti | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570013/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 15:28:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Three emergency phone calls, two dead teenagers, one smoking gun, and no witnesses—besides the man who was responsible.
This is a landmark case that famed criminal defence lawyer Edward L Greenspan would cite as being one of two he worked on over his career that he found to be especially satisfying.
Although this particular case flew under the radar, it would have a profound impact on another very high-profile case that we covered last year in this podcast.</description></item><item><title>138 Mary Davis Nelles | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 17:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dream husband, dream wedding, dream honeymoon, dream home - Mary had it all by the age of 26. But a nightmare was waiting for her just around the corner…
More information:
Madison Scott Update:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Article in the Prince George Citizen&amp;nbsp;Anyone with information to further the investigation should contact the RCMP Tipline at 778-290-5291 or 1-877- 543-4822.Listen to episode 80: The Disappearance of Madison Scott.&amp;nbsp;
Mary Nelles:&amp;nbsp;
Philanthropist's cousin......&amp;nbsp;by Tamara Cherry, Toronto StarEccentric Millionaire "</description></item><item><title>137 Colin Thatcher and the Murder of JoAnn Wilson—Part 3 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570015/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 05:01:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570015/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 3 of 3 ] Accusations of coaching witnesses and shaky alibis are levelled at the defenders and supporters of Colin Thatcher. His own contribution from the stand? Deny, deny, deny. And though the jury comes to a verdict, this story doesn’t end there.
Content Warning: this episode contains mentions of domestic abuse.
Canadian True Crime donates monthly to help those facing injustice.
This month we have donated in memory of JoAnn Wilson to the Regina Transition House, an emergency crisis shelter for women and children in the city.</description></item><item><title>136 Colin Thatcher and the Murder of JoAnn Wilson—Part 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570016/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 05:01:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570016/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 2 of 3 ] After JoAnn Wilson was shot in the shoulder in her kitchen, she backed down from the custody fight. Colin Thatcher was rewarded for outlasting her, but his fixation was far from over. A series of witnesses would come forward with information almost impossible to believe, revealing a political liability hiding a multitude of secrets behind closed doors.
Content Warning: this episode contains mentions of domestic abuse.</description></item><item><title>135 Colin Thatcher and the Murder of JoAnn Wilson—Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570017/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 05:01:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570017/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 1 of 3 ] This is the high-profile tale of one of Canada’s most controversial political families. Several twisted tragedies are wrapped up in this decades-long saga with themes of love and hate, violence and revenge, power and control, divided families and shattered lives—all set against the 1980s backdrop of rural Saskatchewan.
Content Warning: this episode contains mentions of domestic abuse.
This is a weekly series: Parts 2 and 3 will be released to all on May 14 and 21.</description></item><item><title>134 The Murder of January Lapuz | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 15:53:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570018/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2012, a beloved community figure was killed in her own home in an extremely violent attack. It would take a while to learn what happened to her and who was responsible, but the immense loss of her absence was felt immediately by all who knew her - or knew of her.
"Hi. My name is January. I know it's a cold month, but I make it hot!"</description></item><item><title>133 The Lake Family Murders—Part 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570019/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 05:01:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570019/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 2 of 2] Sensational trials are held for three members of the Bannister family to get to the truth of what happened to the Lake family that night—and why a baby was at the centre of it all.
Warning: this series includes the death of a young child. Please take care when listening.
﻿Old Dorchester County Jail, New Brunswick:
https://dorchesterjail.com/
Canadian True Crime donates monthly to help those facing injustice.</description></item><item><title>132 The Lake Family Murders–Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570020/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 05:01:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570020/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 1 of 2] One snowy night, a young family fell victim to a terrible accident…. or so it seemed. What really happened to this family - and why - would become fodder for national and international headlines that only got more curious as the investigation progressed.
This two-part series covers a historical case that resulted in the first ever kidnapping trial in the province of New Brunswick and the last double hanging in Canada.</description></item><item><title>131 Kelly Favro's Story—Part 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 06:02:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Content warning: This series includes graphic descriptions of sexual violence.&amp;nbsp;Please see resources below.
Victoria, British Columbia
[Part 2 of 2]&amp;nbsp;Kelly Favro learns she is not alone. Along the way, she meets other sexual assault survivors who also discovered publication bans had been put on their names without their consent - including Jade Neilson and Samantha Geiger. They all experienced negative impacts in completely separate ways, but they agreed that no other sexual assault survivors should have to go through the same experience of law-enforced silence and isolation that they’ve been told is for their own good.</description></item><item><title>130 Kelly Favro's Story—Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 06:01:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Content warning: This series includes graphic descriptions of sexual violence.&amp;nbsp;If you or anyone you know is experiencing sexual violence and abuse, help is available. Please see resources below.
Victoria, British Columbia
[Part 1 of 2] In this two-part series, we explore Kelly Favro's harrowing journey from surviving a two-hour sexual assault to becoming the first person in British Columbia to have a publication ban removed from her name - by herself.</description></item><item><title>129 The Rallo Family Murders—Part 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 06:01:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570023/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 2 of 2] The trial of Jon Rallo continues. Jon testifies in his own defence, but the crown would present evidence that suggested a very different version of events. &amp;nbsp;What really happened to Sandra, Jason and Stephanie? Would there be justice in this case?
This two-part series provides a snapshot of Canadian history at a pivotal time for both the burgeoning city of Hamilton and the criminal justice system.</description></item><item><title>128 The Rallo Family Murders—Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 06:01:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570024/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 1 of 2]&amp;nbsp;In the summer of 1976, the Rallo family appeared to be living the picture perfect family life in the “Golden Horseshoe” area of Southern Ontario.
Parents Jon and Sandra with young children Jason and Stephanie had enjoyed a warm family summer full of trips to visit grandparents and swimming... that is, until one morning when Jon woke up to an empty house, and a devastating note.</description></item><item><title>UPDATED: The Renfrew County Massacre | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570025/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 06:01:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570025/</guid><description>Podcast Description ONTARIO&amp;nbsp; The updated story of the worst-ever case of intimate-partner violence in Ontario—and one of the worst in Canadian history. &amp;nbsp;In 2015, the lives of three women - Nathalie Warmerdam, Anastasia Kuzyk and Carol Culleton - were snuffed out within hours of each other in a violent murder spree that could have been prevented.
Resources for Domestic Violence
Canada: https://endingviolencecanada.org/getting-help-2/
US: https://www.thehotline.org/
Signs you’re in an abusive relationship - and how to get help</description></item><item><title>Revisiting Canada's Largest Manhunt | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 06:01:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570026/</guid><description>Podcast Description NORTHWEST TERRITORIES AND YUKON&amp;nbsp;|&amp;nbsp; A six week manhunt for a mysterious fugitive who seemed to have superhuman abilities, set against the icy backdrop of the Arctic North in winter. The remarkable search party included RCMP, Indigenous trackers, fur trappers, and even legendary WWI pilot Captain Wop May.
Please note: this is a re-mastered and updated re-release of a previous episode. Canadian True Crime will be back with a new episode February 15.</description></item><item><title>127 The Maple Syrup Heist of 2011 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 06:01:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Quebec This is the story of Canada’s most valuable theft—perhaps the most Canadian crime ever committed.
It was July of 2011, and Avik Caron had a kind of nervous excitement. An opportunity had fallen into his lap to stick it to the “Maple Syrup Mafia” – and, of course, line his pockets with cash as he did so. The problem was, he didn't quite know how to do it.</description></item><item><title>126 The Rise and Fall of Hedley's Jacob Hoggard—Part 5 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570028/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 06:03:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Content warning: graphic details of sexual violence
[Part 5 of 5] This final part of the series wraps up the 2022 trial of Jacob Hoggard, exploring how the jury may have arrived at that split verdict and the new information that came out at sentencing. We'll circle back to tie up some loose ends, including the intended testimony from one particular witness who was excluded from the trial, and lastly.</description></item><item><title>125 The Rise and Fall of Hedley's Jacob Hoggard—Part 4 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570029/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 08:02:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Content warning: This episode includes graphic details of alleged sexual assault specifically involving a minor.
[Part 4 of 5] The May 2022 trial of Jacob Hoggard continues, with testimony from complainant “Emma”, Jacob Hoggard himself, and the jury's verdict.&amp;nbsp;
Resources for Sexual Violence and Abuse:
REES Community
Ending Violence Canada&amp;nbsp;
More information:
Court documentsCourt reporting of Alyshah Hasham for the Toronto StarLive tweets from Sean O'Shea for Global NewsDispelling the myths about sexual assault | Ontario.</description></item><item><title>124 The Rise and Fall of Hedley's Jacob Hoggard—Part 3 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570030/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 06:01:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Content warning: This episode includes graphic details of alleged sexual assault specifically involving a minor.
[Part 3 of 5] The trial of Jacob Hoggard started in May of 2022. The first complainant to testify would be the underage complainant who was only 15 and 16 years old at the time of her encounters with Hoggard.&amp;nbsp;
More information:
Court reporting of Alyshah Hasham for the Toronto StarDispelling the myths about sexual assault | Ontario.</description></item><item><title>123 The Rise and Fall of Hedley's Jacob Hoggard—Part 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570031/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 06:01:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570031/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 2 of 5 ] CONTENT WARNING: Graphic details of violent sexual assault and allegations involving a minor. After the allegations of Jacob Hoggard’s inappropriate behaviour with fans surfaced on social media, a survivor finds the courage to come forward and detail her own violent experience with the Hedley frontman. And she isn’t alone for long.
More information:
"Emma's" story: 'I said stop': Ottawa woman accuses Hedley singer Jacob Hoggard of rape by Judy Trinh"</description></item><item><title>122 The Rise and Fall of Hedley's Jacob Hoggard—Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570032/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 05:01:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570032/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 1 of 5] CONTENT WARNING: Graphic details of violent sexual assault and allegations involving a minor.
FROM CANADIAN IDOL TO CONVICTED SEX OFFENDER
As frontman for the pop-rock band Hedley, Jacob Hoggard was known for pushing boundaries—both on and off the stage. By 2022 he would also be known as one of Canada's most notorious sex offenders. How did his behaviour go unchecked for so long? This series explores how the rise and downfall of Jacob Hoggard in the era of #metoo, and how myths around consent, rape and groupie culture continue to dominate the social discourse.</description></item><item><title>121 The Murder of Robert LeVoir | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570033/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 05:01:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570033/</guid><description>Podcast Description FORT McMURRAY | In 2002, the family of 25-year-old DJ Robert LeVoir reported him missing after they hadn't heard from him for two weeks. But the RCMP didn't seem to be doing much to help, in fact they didn't publicly announce Robert's disappearance for 8 months.&amp;nbsp;
Understandably frustrated by the lack of progress, his family had no way of knowing that an elaborate plan to discover what had happened to Robert was already being set in motion behind closed doors.</description></item><item><title>Major Case Updates and Feedback 2022—Part 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570034/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 00:15:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570034/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 2 of 2] Cases that have had notable or major updates.
Approximate timestamps:
1:00 The Johnson Bentley Family Murders
5:30 The Abbotsford Killer
9:00 The Murder of Jagtar Gill
15:00 Lush &amp;amp; Whiteway Families
20:00 The Renfrew County Murders - 2022 Inquiry
28:00 The Brentwood Five
36:00 The Death of Ezekiel Stephan
AD-FREE episodes are available via our Premium Feeds
Sign up via Apple Podcasts, Patreon or Supercast</description></item><item><title>Major Case Updates and Feedback 2022—Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570035/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 00:01:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570035/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 1 of 2] These episodes take you through cases we've covered that have had major or notable updates, or have attracted notable feedback. Kristi will also be responding to some of the most common feedback received. Approximate timestamps:
(Give or take a few minutes)
3:00 National Day for Truth and Reconciliation - September 30
&amp;nbsp;24-Hour National Residential School Crisis Line 1-866-925-4419
&amp;nbsp;Take Action: The T&amp;amp;R Commission Calls to Action</description></item><item><title>120 The Murder of Samantha Walsh | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570036/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 05:01:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570036/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the winter of 2000, 13-year-old Samantha Walsh was supposed to walk a short distance home from her grandmother’s house—but she never made it.
This is the gripping story of how the tiny seaside town of Fleur De Lys, NL came together to support a local family during a devastating time.
More information:
Into the Night: The Samantha Walsh Story by Gordon Walsh
Sam's Place website
Samantha's Saltwater Joys facebook page</description></item><item><title>119 FLIGHT 108: The Sault-au-Cochon Tragedy | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570037/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 05:01:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570037/</guid><description>Podcast Description QUEBEC &amp;nbsp;| The story of one of the first instances of in-flight bombing, one of the worst mass murders in Canadian history, and the last woman to hang. &amp;nbsp;In 1949, a passenger plane fell from the sky in the Sault-au-Cochon area of Quebec, killing everyone on board...
Full list of resources and information sources and credits:
See the page for this episode &amp;nbsp;at canadiantruecrime.ca
AD-FREE episodes are available via our Premium Feeds</description></item><item><title>118 The Death of Darcy Allan Sheppard—Part 6 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570038/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 23:26:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570038/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 6 of 6 ] &amp;nbsp;The conclusion.&amp;nbsp;
Review the evidence:
WATCH: The Surveillance Footage at the mid-block pedestrian crossway
WATCH: Eyewitness statements and 911 call audio
READ: &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Collision Reconstruction Report
READ: &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Transcript from May 25 2010 Court Proceeding
Media referenced in this episode:
READ: Lost Boy: The death of Darcy Allan Sheppard, by Jennifer Wells, December 26, 2013
WATCH: Michael Bryant's Ted X Talk
READ: 28 Seconds: A True Story of Addiction, Tragedy, and Hope by Michael Bryant, published by Viking, Toronto, 2012</description></item><item><title>117 The Death of Darcy Allan Sheppard—Part 5 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570039/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 5 of 6 ]&amp;nbsp;After the court proceeding comes to a close, things continue to snowball, leading Darcy Allan Sheppard's loved ones and supporters to press harder for the truth.&amp;nbsp;
Review the available evidence*:
WATCH:&amp;nbsp;The Surveillance Footage&amp;nbsp;at the mid-block pedestrian crossway
Michael Bryant's book 28 Seconds states:&amp;nbsp;"It was Darcy Sheppard who, moments later, drove within inches of my driver’s-side door, as our Saab was stopped a little farther west on Bloor Street at an intersection near Avenue Road.</description></item><item><title>116 The Death of Darcy Allan Sheppard—Part 4 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 05:01:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570040/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 4 of 6 ]&amp;nbsp;The rest of Michael Bryant's version of events is provided to the court by the special independent prosecutor, as he explained his decision to withdraw the charges. At the time, the court heard that Bryant's version of events lined up with the evidence, but years later when documents containing details of a large amount of that evidence were publicly released, a different story emerges.</description></item><item><title>115 The Death of Darcy Allan Sheppard—Part 3 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570041/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 05:01:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570041/</guid><description>Podcast Description TORONTO, ONTARIO
[ Part 3 of 6 ]&amp;nbsp;In this episode, the Collision Reconstruction experts determine what happened in the incident that led to Darcy's death, Michael Bryant finally reveals his side of the story, and more.
Resources referenced:
WATCH: Surveillance video released briefly by the media
WATCH: Eyewitness statements and 911 call audio
READ: Collision Reconstruction Report
READ: Transcript from May 25 2010 Court Proceeding
Full list of resources and information sources and credits:</description></item><item><title>114 The Death of Darcy Allan Sheppard—Part 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 05:01:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570042/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 2 of 6 ]&amp;nbsp;Unravelling the aftermath of the incident that caused Darcy Allan Sheppard’s death—the twists and turns that came with each new day, and how investigators worked to get to the truth of exactly what happened.
Important articles mentioned:
Cyclist may have grabbed Bryant, wheel: police, uncredited, CBC News, September 2, 2009
Spinning the first week of Michael Bryant’s new life, by Linda Diebel, September 5, 2009</description></item><item><title>113 The Death of Darcy Allan Sheppard—Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 05:01:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570043/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 1 of 6 ] On a warm summer evening in 2009 there was a violent collision on a downtown Toronto street, an incident so unimaginable that it left bystanders shocked and confused. The evening’s events dominated the headlines and would be hotly debated for years to come but one thing was certain: the very different lives of the two men involved would never be the same.</description></item><item><title>Revisiting the Shell Lake Massacre | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570044/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 05:01:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today in this special episode, we take a look back at one of the early Canadian True Crime episodes - the story of Saskatchewan’s worst mass murder. You'll hear a never-before-told story about why this episode was very different from the rest.
Early one morning in 1967, 21-year-old Victor Hoffman was in the midst of a serious mental health crisis, a crisis that would have tragic consequences for an unsuspecting local family.</description></item><item><title>112 The Murder of Helen Betty Osborne—Part 3 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570045/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 05:01:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570045/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 3 of 3] &amp;nbsp;In 1971, Indigenous high school student Helen Betty Osborne was abducted &amp;nbsp;and brutally murdered near The Pas, Manitoba.
When Betty’s body was found hours later at nearby Clearwater Lake, it was clear she had been the victim of a heinous crime. But it would take many, many years for the truth of what really happened to Betty to come to light—ultimately exposing the depths of racial injustice in the small town.</description></item><item><title>111 The Murder of Helen Betty Osborne—Part 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570046/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 05:01:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Manitoba&amp;nbsp;|&amp;nbsp;In 1971, Indigenous high school student Helen Betty Osborne was abducted and brutally murdered near The Pas, Manitoba.
When Betty’s body was found hours later at nearby Clearwater Lake, it was clear she had been the victim of a heinous crime. But it would take many, many years for the truth of what really happened to Betty to come to light—ultimately exposing the depths of racial injustice in the small town.</description></item><item><title>110 The Murder of Helen Betty Osborne—Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570047/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 05:01:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570047/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 1 of 3 ] In 1971, Indigenous high school student Helen Betty Osborne was abducted and brutally murdered near The Pas, Manitoba.
When Betty’s body was found hours later at nearby Clearwater Lake, it was clear she had been the victim of a heinous crime. But it would take many, many years for the truth of what really happened to Betty to come to light—ultimately exposing the depths of racial injustice in the small town.</description></item><item><title>109 The Beatle Bandit—Part 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570048/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 05:01:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570048/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 2 of 2 ] The shocking conclusion to this historical Canadian crime saga.
&amp;nbsp;AD-FREE episodes are available via our Premium Feeds
Sign up via Apple Podcasts, Patreon or Supercast
&amp;nbsp;
Full list of credits and information sources
See the applicable page for each episode at canadiantruecrime.ca/episodes.
&amp;nbsp;
Research and writing: Kristi Lee
Theme song, audio editing and production: We Talk of Dreams&amp;nbsp;
Disclaimer: voiced by the host of True</description></item><item><title>108 The Beatle Bandit—Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570049/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 05:01:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570049/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 1 of 2 ] The unbelievable but true story of a bizarre-looking bank robber who terrorized 1964 Toronto as Beatlemania was gripping the nation. One heist went terribly wrong, ending in a wild shootout that sparked a national debate around gun control, mental health and the death penalty.
Part 2 available to everyone March 22
Get it ad-free, right now on one of our Premium Feeds: Apple Podcasts, Patreon or Supercast</description></item><item><title>107 Alberta Naked Kidnappings | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570050/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 06:01:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570050/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2017, a bizarre incident occurred near Nisku, Alberta when five people - four of them naked - decided to kidnap their neighbours. The story that unravelled would make international headlines.
Podcast recommendation:
Connections: The Podcast by We Talk of Dreams
Ukrainian aid:
Donate to Red Cross
&amp;nbsp;
Thanks for supporting our sponsors!
See the special offer codes here
&amp;nbsp;
Ad-free episodes:
All episodes, ad-free and often early on Patreon and Supercast.</description></item><item><title>106 The Gakhal Family Massacre | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570051/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 06:02:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570051/</guid><description>Podcast Description BRITISH COLUMBIA | In 1996, a family in Vernon, BC were preparing for a large wedding—but unbeknownst to them, a man was waiting in the sidelines to ruin it all. This is the tragic story of Canada’s third-largest mass shooting and the many lost opportunities that may have prevented it.
Podcast recommendation
Dealing Justice - a podcast about cold cases featured on decks of cards
Canadian True Crime donates monthly.</description></item><item><title>105 The Murder of Liu Qian | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570052/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 06:01:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sometime after midnight in 2011, 23 year old York University student Liu Qian was chatting to an old friend via webcam as she studied in her tiny basement dorm room in Toronto.
But there was a knock at her door—and her friend on the other side of the computer screen would be the only witness to the terror that would unfold.
Further information:
Open Letter, Artworks and Photos of Liu Qian from her father Liu Jianhui, translated by Professor Charles Burton and published by the Toronto Star</description></item><item><title>104 Karen and Krista Hart—Part 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570053/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 06:11:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570053/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 2 of 2 ] The conclusion of this case of a murder investigation that forever changed the face of the Canadian justice system.
&amp;nbsp;
Further reading:
Mr. Big: The Investigation into the Deaths of Karen and Krista Hart by Colleen Lewis and Jennifer Hicks
&amp;nbsp;
Podcast recommendation:
Casefile - Daniel Morcombe episode 54&amp;nbsp;
&amp;nbsp;
Credits:
Research and writing: Emily G. Thompson and Eileen Macfarlane
Content advice: Aja Romano</description></item><item><title>103 Karen and Krista Hart—Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570054/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 06:01:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570054/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 1 of 2 ] On August 4, 2002, Nelson Hart took his three-year-old twin daughters, Karen and Krista to play by Gander Lake. They both ended up in the water, and the decisions Nelson made in the aftermath baffled everyone—including the RCMP.
&amp;nbsp;
This is the shocking case of a murder investigation that forever changed the face of the Canadian justice system.
&amp;nbsp;
Part 2 will be released on Saturday January 22, and it's available now, ad-free on Supercast and Patreon.</description></item><item><title>102 The Crimes of Noel Winters | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570055/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 06:02:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570055/</guid><description>Podcast Description NEW BRUNSWICK&amp;nbsp; | In 1984, human remains were found in garbage bags in a dump in New Brunswick. The story that would unravel would shock locals and leave a lasting legacy on the province.
Resources referenced:
Review of “Bodies in the Backyard” - by Rachel M Friars on True Crime Index - Twitter: @TrueCrimeIndex Email: truecrimeindex@gmail.com
Bodies in the Backyard by Brian O’Neill
Montreal’s Irish Mafia: The True Story of the Infamous West End Gang by Darcy O’Connor</description></item><item><title>101 The Ryan Family Crossbow Murders | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570056/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 06:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570056/</guid><description>Podcast Description TORONTO | In 2016, a disturbance on a quiet street in Scarborough would decimate a family, leaving three dead and another injured. And then, within hours, a bomb squad would be called to an upmarket, waterfront condo in downtown Toronto, revealing a complex web of lies. When a person’s unsettling past catches up with them, what lengths will they go to to prevent the truth from coming out?</description></item><item><title>100 The Rivera and Regier Murders | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570057/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 06:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570057/</guid><description>Podcast Description ONTARIO &amp;amp; QUEBEC | In 2007, residents of Southwest Ontario were gripped by panic as police worked to capture 22 year old Jesse Imeson—an armed, dangerous and unpredictable fugitive.
Crisis resources:
Crisis services Canada
Healing Childhood Trauma - healthline.com and psychologytoday.com
Carlos Rivera’s book:
Breaking Down the Wall of Silence
Thanks for supporting our sponsors!
See the special offer codes here
&amp;nbsp;
Ad-free episodes:
All episodes, ad-free and often early on Patreon and Supercast.</description></item><item><title>99 The Nanaimo Mill Shooting | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570058/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570058/</guid><description>Podcast Description BRITISH COLUMBIA | In 2014, a disgruntled and disillusioned former employee of a Nanaimo sawmill returned to his workplace to seek revenge.
Canadian True Crime donates monthly. This month we have donated to:
Canadian Resource Centre for Victims of Crime If you or someone you know might be suffering from depression:
Understanding and Finding Help For Depression - CAM-H
Supporting a family member or friend with depression - Mayoclinic</description></item><item><title>98 The Murder of Ronald Platt | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570059/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570059/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1996, a body washed up in a fishing net off the south coast of Devon in the UK. Through intrepid detective work, English police would link it back to a diabolical Canadian criminal who left an unbelievable trail of destruction behind in Southwestern Ontario.
This is the story of the crimes of Albert Johnson Walker. If you recognize the name and think you know this case, stay tuned until the end.</description></item><item><title>Debrief with special guest Métis journalist Danielle Paradis | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570060/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 18:10:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Danielle Paradis is a journalist based in Edmonton, Alberta with a special interest in Indigenous and women's issues.
She's been published by Chatelaine, CANADALAND, BUSTLE, Star Metro Edmonton, Gig City, The Spraw and more.
Dani has also pitched, researched and contributed to the writing of several episodes for Canadian True Crime - including Saskatoon Freezing Deaths and Mayerthorpe Tragedy... with more to come.
Approximate timestamps of our discussion:</description></item><item><title>97 The Murder of Maranda Shelly Peter | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570061/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yukon | In 1996, 15 year old Maranda Shelly Peter waved to her mother as she left to go to the movies with her boyfriend. But the next morning, Maranda hadn't returned home.
It would take some time, but the discovery of where Maranda really was would shake the territory.&amp;nbsp;
Resources on intergenerational or transgenerational trauma:
Breaking the Chains of Generational Trauma by Elizabeth Dixon for Psychology TodayHow residential school trauma of previous generations continues to tear through Indigenous families by Marcy Cuttler for CBC NewsWhat is Intergenerational trauma—and how do you heal from it?</description></item><item><title>What happened at Residential Schools: a primer | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570062/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 21:11:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570062/</guid><description>Podcast Description #TruthandReconciliationDay |
September 30, 2021 is the first National Day for Truth and Reconciliation here in Canada, and we all have a part to play in educating ourselves and spreading the message.&amp;nbsp;
This is an overview of how Residential Schools came to be and what happened, and below are some recommended resources for further learning.
Recommended listening:
Residential Schools Historica Canada podcast
Missing &amp;amp; Murdered: Finding Cleo by CBC Podcasts</description></item><item><title>96 The Klaus Family Murders — Part 3 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570063/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570063/</guid><description>Podcast Description *Part 3 of 3
Jason Klaus and Joshua Frank go to trial with completely new stories.
What was the truth?
Thanks for supporting our sponsors!
See the special offer codes here
&amp;nbsp;
Don't like the ads?
Access early episodes without the ads plus occasional bonus content on Patreon and Supercast. Learn more
Credits:
Research: Gemma Harris
Writing: Kristi Lee
Audio editing and production: We Talk of Dreams&amp;nbsp;
Disclaimer voiced by the host of True</description></item><item><title>95 The Klaus Family Murders — Part 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570064/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570064/</guid><description>Podcast Description *Part 2 of 3. Part 3 will be released on September 15, and is available now for supporters on Patreon or Supercast ALBERTA |&amp;nbsp;In 2013, a tragedy struck a tight-knit farming family near Castor, Alberta and before too long, a twisted story would unravel.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Podcast recommendation:&amp;nbsp;
Do you know Mordechai?&amp;nbsp;
Thanks for supporting our sponsors!
See the special offer codes here
&amp;nbsp;
Get AD-FREE episodes
Plus bonus content on Patreon and Supercast.</description></item><item><title>94 The Klaus Family Murders — Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570065/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570065/</guid><description>Podcast Description ALBERTA |&amp;nbsp;In 2013, a tragedy struck a tight-knit farming family near Castor, Alberta and before too long, a twisted story would unravel.
*Part 1 of 3: Part 2 will be released on September 8
Part 3 will be released on September 15
Ad free version of all three parts now available now for supporters on Patreon or Supercast Learn more
Canadian True Crime donates monthly to help those facing injustice.</description></item><item><title>Case Updates 2021 — Part 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570066/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we'll go over the significant updates to cases covered before 2020!
Podcast recommendation:
CBC's The Village - Season 2
Order of cases covered:
Alloura Wells / Toronto's Gay VillageEzekiel StephanRichard OlandThe DonnellysLoretta SaundersSara &amp;amp; TaliyahThe Brentwood Five (Calgary Stabbings)Erin ChorneyMichelle BarnoskiReena VirkPaul Bernardo
-----------------------------------------------------
Thanks for supporting our sponsors!
See the special offer codes here
&amp;nbsp;
Access the ad-free extended version
On Patreon or Supercast. Learn more</description></item><item><title>Case Updates 2021 &amp; Feedback — Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570067/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570067/</guid><description>Podcast Description We're discussing cases covered in the past year - going through updates, clarifying some things, and chatting about your feedback.
Order of cases discussed in this episode Chapais Fire Tragedy
Murder of Robin Greene&amp;nbsp;
Mayerthorpe Tragedy
Storming the Capital (1966 Parliamentary Bombing)
Johnson-Bentley Family Murders
Murder of Brayton Bullock
Lush &amp;amp; Whiteway Families
Madison Scott - Tenth anniversary message from her parents.
Mad Trapper of Rat River
Murder of Laura Letts&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>93 The Chapais Fire Tragedy | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570068/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Back September 1 | Thanks for your support!
QUEBEC | New Year’s Eve, 1979. The rural mining town of Chapais was preparing to bring in 1980 in style with a fundraiser for 300 people. But just after midnight, the careless actions of one guest caused a fire that would leave the community forever changed.
Residential Schools resources &amp;amp; support:
Podcast: Residential Schools by Historica Canadahosted by Shaneen Robinson-Desjarlais</description></item><item><title>92 The Murder of Robin Greene - Part 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570069/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570069/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 2 of 2 ]
MANITOBA&amp;nbsp;|&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The court hears testimony from Sydney Teerhuise and Dan Zupansky, the jury decides whether Sydney Teerhuise had intent to commit murder that day, and Dan Zupansky tells us what his theories are about the case.
More information:
Dan Zupansky’s book:&amp;nbsp;Trophy Kill: The Shall We Dance Murder by Dan Zupansky
True Murder podcast: https://www.spreaker.com/show/truemurder
Podcast recommendation:
COMMONS: Real Estate!
Thanks for supporting our sponsors!</description></item><item><title>91 The Murder of Robin Greene - Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570070/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570070/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 1 of 2 ]
MANITOBA &amp;nbsp;| &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;In 2003, the day after Canada Day, a 33 year old man walked through the front door of the Winnipeg Remand Centre. He said he’d woken up in his hotel room and there was a dead, dismembered body in the bathtub. &amp;nbsp;He insisted he blanked out and couldn’t remember committing the murder.
The circumstances of the case were shocking and unbelievable enough, but within a few days a hollywood angle involving a stolen celebrity necklace ended up being the main headline.</description></item><item><title>90 The Mayerthorpe Tragedy - Part 3 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570071/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 05:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570071/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 3 of 3 ]
The conclusion.
Watch:
The Fifth Estate episode "collateral damage"&amp;nbsp;
Credits:&amp;nbsp;
Research: Danielle Paradis
Additional research and writing: Kristi Lee
Audio editing and production: We Talk of Dreams&amp;nbsp;
Disclaimer voiced by the host of True
Theme Song: We Talk of Dreams
S﻿ocial medias:
Facebook: facebook.com/CanadianTrueCrime
Twitter: @CanadianTCpod
Instagram: @CanadianTrueCrimePod
Instagram: @kristileehello&amp;nbsp;
All credits and information sources can be found on the page for this episode at canadiantruecrime.</description></item><item><title>89 The Mayerthorpe Tragedy - Part 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570072/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 05:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570072/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 2 of 3 ] ALBERTA&amp;nbsp;|&amp;nbsp;With everyone questioning how the Mayerthorpe Tragedy was permitted to happen, the RCMP were convinced James Roszko must have had someone helping him—and they were determined to do whatever it took to find this person and bring them to justice.
Watch:
The Fifth Estate episode "collateral damage" &amp;nbsp;
Thanks for supporting our sponsors!
See the special offer codes here
&amp;nbsp;
Don't like the ads?</description></item><item><title>88 The Mayerthorpe Tragedy - Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570073/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 05:01:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570073/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 1 of 3 ] ALBERTA&amp;nbsp;|&amp;nbsp;In 2005, bailiffs were sent to the property of a man called James Roszko to repossess a truck, but the situation devolved into a devastating tragedy that made international headlines.
Podcast recommendation:
Criminal Conduct - Season 2
Thanks for supporting our sponsors!
See the special offer codes here
&amp;nbsp;
Don't like the ads?
Access ad-free episodes, early, plus bonus content and more on Patreon and Supercast.</description></item><item><title>87 The 1966 Bombing on Parliament Hill | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570074/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570074/</guid><description>Podcast Description ONTARIO | In 1966, a disgruntled man purchased ten sticks of dynamite, assembled a bomb, and travelled with it to Ottawa—headed for the Parliament of Canada.
Podcast recommendation:
Corpus Delecti - Robin "Rocky" Myers investigation special series
Canadian True Crime donates monthly. This month we have donated to:
True North Aid - serves and supports northern Indigenous communities in Canada through practical humanitarian support like clean drinking water, food, health, housing, and more.</description></item><item><title>86 The Johnson-Bentley Family Murders | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570075/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570075/</guid><description>Podcast Description BRITISH COLUMBIA | In August 1982, a family of six set out on what was supposed to be an idyllic two-week camping trip. They never returned home.
This sparked what would be the most expensive and highly-publicized manhunt in Canadian history.
Petition: Help the Johnson and Bentley Family
Read and sign the petition here Thanks for supporting our sponsors!
See the special offer codes here
&amp;nbsp;
Don't like the ads?</description></item><item><title>85 The Murder of Brayton Bullock | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570076/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 05:01:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570076/</guid><description>Podcast Description ONTARIO | In 2006, a close-knit family tried to deal with an escalating crisis, but they could only do so much before the situation ended in a devastating and senseless tragedy.
Resources related to Canadian Victims of Crime
Canadian Victims Bill of Rights (Bill C-32)
Get involved: pre-written email to send to members of parliament
Canadian Resource Centre for Victims of Crime
Office of the Federal Ombudsman for Victims of Crime</description></item><item><title>84 The Lush and Whiteway Families | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570077/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 06:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570077/</guid><description>Podcast Description NEWFOUNDLAND AND LABRADOR |&amp;nbsp;In&amp;nbsp;2019, Josh Whiteway and Suzanne Lush were ready to return to Calgary after spending a wonderful week with their families in Lewisporte, NL. But on the way to the airport, they would be involved in a tragic crash that would change their lives forever.
PLEASE NOTE: This episode referrs to a “car accident” or “accident” a few times, but we’ve since been informed that “accident” should not be used when it comes to impaired driving.</description></item><item><title>83 The Murder of Beverley Rowbotham | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570078/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 06:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570078/</guid><description>Podcast Description MANITOBA | In 2000, Beverley Rowbotham moved her family from Saskatchewan to Manitoba after her husband Mark Stobbe was offered a high-profile job there. But as they started settling into their new house, the problems started…. and it was one thing after another.
Canadian True Crime donates monthly to organizations helping those facing injustice.
This month we have donated to:
The Alpha House Project - Winnipeg - a year-long program for women and their children leaving an abusive relationship.</description></item><item><title>82 The Murder of Joe Rose | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570079/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 06:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570079/</guid><description>Podcast Description QUEBEC | In 1989, 23-year-old Joe Rose and a friend boarded a Montreal bus home in the early morning hours. What happened next would be described as a turning point for the LGBTQ+ rights movement in Quebec.
Recommended resources for further reading:
Prejudice to pride: The forgotten murder of Joe Rose, by Richard Burnett, special to the Montreal Gazette
Sex Garage raid a turning point in Montreal’s LGBT activism by Richard Burnett, special to the Montreal Gazette</description></item><item><title>81 The Murder of Richard Humble | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570080/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 06:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570080/</guid><description>Podcast Description ONTARIO | 82 year old Richard Humble needed knee surgery, but because he lived alone, he would need a caregiver to help him as he recovered. An old friend recommended someone who might be able to help him—but what she ended up doing was the exact opposite.
*Please note - some names in this episode have been changed to protect the privacy of innocent parties. Any links between names chosen and real people involved in the story are coincidental.</description></item><item><title>80 The Death of Madison Scott | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570081/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 06:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570081/</guid><description>Podcast Description BRITISH COLUMBIA | In May of 2011, 20 year old Maddy Scott and a friend attended a party at Hogsback Lake in British Columbia. They were supposed to camp for the night, but the friend decided to leave, and Maddy was eventually left by herself. This was the last time anyone saw her alive.
UPDATE - MAY 2023:
The RCMP has confirmed the remains of Madison Scott were found on a rural property not far from Hogback Lake, where she had been camping with friends.</description></item><item><title>Chat about William Fyfe with a forensic psychologist | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570082/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 06:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Make sure you listen to Episode 79 first!
Find Lili Knighton:
Website: www.LiliKnighton.com
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/knightonmentalhealth/
Approximate timestamps:
0.00 Lili talks about her background including trials of Paul Bernardo and Bradley Edwards (Claremont Serial Killer trial)
4:00 Serial Killers and their motivations
10:00 Was Fyfe really determined to avoid the spotlight?
11:45 Serial Killer “patterns” and escalation from break and enters to rapes and murders (re Golden State Killer)</description></item><item><title>79 The Crimes of William Patrick Fyfe | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570083/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570083/</guid><description>Podcast Description QUEBEC&amp;nbsp;In 1999, four women were found murdered in the greater Montreal area. They all lived alone, there were no signs of forced entry, and the crime scenes were so violent that even the most seasoned of investigators were shocked. But one day, the killer would make a mistake. This is the story of the crimes of the Quebec serial killer known as “The Killer Handyman”.
SURVEY: Tell us what you think about Canadian True Crime - skip any question you don't want to answer!</description></item><item><title>78 The Mad Trapper of Rat River | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570084/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570084/</guid><description>Podcast Description NORTHWEST TERRITORIES AND YUKON
The story of Canada's longest manhunt. In 1931 a strange man arrived at Fort McPherson in the Northwest Territories—and disrupted the status quo.
SURVEY: Tell us what you think about Canadian True Crime!
Take survey now
Thanks for supporting my sponsors!
See the special offer codes here
&amp;nbsp;
AD FREE Exclusive feed - Canadian True Crime supporters
Access ad-free episodes, bonus episodes, and more on Patreon and Supercast.</description></item><item><title>77 The Death of Laura Letts - Part 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570085/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 06:01:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Part 2 of a 2-part series
The RCMP continue their investigation into the death of Laura Letts, and make an interesting discovery. From there, things would spiral completely out of control.
SURVEY: Tell us what you think about Canadian True Crime!
Take survey now
Canadian True Crime donates each month to a local justice-focused organization. This month's donation has gone to:
Alberta Council of Women's Shelters
Thanks for supporting my sponsors!</description></item><item><title>76 The Death of Laura Letts - Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570086/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 06:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570086/</guid><description>Podcast Description BRITISH COLUMBIA
After a painful breakup, Laura Letts decided to take leave from her job and travel abroad. While on tour in New Zealand, she would meet someone new, and her life would forever be changed.
Canadian True Crime donates each month to a local justice-focused organization. This month’s donation has gone to: Alberta Council of Women's Shelters
&amp;nbsp;
Thanks for supporting my sponsors!
See the special offer codes here</description></item><item><title>75 Saskatoon Freezing Deaths | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570087/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570087/</guid><description>Podcast Description SASKATCHEWAN:&amp;nbsp;In 2000, Darrell Night was having a night out with friends, when he was picked up by police. He thought they were going to take him to the drunk tank… but instead, the car went in the opposite direction.
More resources on this case:
BOOK: Starlight Tour: The Last, Lonely Night of Neil Stonechild by Rob Renaud and Susanne Reber
DOCUMENTARY:&amp;nbsp;Two Worlds Colliding directed by Tasha Hubbard
PODCAST: COMMONS - The Police</description></item><item><title>74 Renfrew County Murders | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570088/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570088/</guid><description>Podcast Description ONTARIO
In 2015, Renfrew County in the Ottawa Valley would be the backdrop for the worst-ever case of intimate-partner violence in Ontario, and one of the worst in Canadian history.
Resources for Domestic violence
Canada: https://endingviolencecanada.org/getting-help-2/
US: https://www.thehotline.org/
Signs you’re in an abusive relationship - and how to get help
&amp;nbsp;
Canadian True Crime monthly donation has gone to:
Women’s Women's Sexual Assault Centre of Renfrew County
&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>73 The Harshbarger Family | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570089/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570089/</guid><description>Podcast Description NEWFOUNDLAND &amp;amp; LABRADOR:
In 2006, a family left the US for a hunting trip in Newfoundland. Not all of them would come back.&amp;nbsp;
Thanks for supporting my sponsors!
See the special offer codes here
AD FREE Exclusive feed - Canadian True Crime supporter
Access ad-free episodes, bonus episodes, and more Learn more
Read the award-winning long-form article from Outdoor Canada
https://www.outdoorcanada.ca/harshbarger/
Scroll to halfway down the page to see the link to download the PDF.</description></item><item><title>Q&amp;A | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570090/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi everyone! It's been 2.5 years since I did a Q&amp;amp;A, and I know you have questions, so I thought I'd answer them. Enjoy!&amp;nbsp;
New podcast recommendation
One Strange Thing
Thanks for supporting my sponsors!
See the special offer codes here
Access the Extended Q&amp;amp;A
Also get ad-free episodes, Chats with Kristi after show, bonus episodes, and more&amp;nbsp;Learn more
&amp;nbsp;
APPROXIMATE IMESTAMPS:
2:00 – How did I get into true crime and why</description></item><item><title>Case Updates &amp; Reflections 2020 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570091/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Approximate Timestamps for each case discussed in this episode:
72 Alloura Wells - 3:00 minute mark
71 Jagtar Gill - 7:45
70&amp;nbsp;Zach Miller - 11:00
67-69 Ezekiel Stephan - 15:45
60-62 Richard Oland - 29:00
59 The Donnellys - 39:00
56 Loretta Saunders - 40:00
19-20 Laura Babcock - 44:00
6 Reena Virk - 46:30
Youtube recommendation:
Canadiana - Canadian History Videos&amp;nbsp;
Thanks for supporting my sponsors!
See the special offer codes here</description></item><item><title>72 The Death of Alloura Wells | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570092/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570092/</guid><description>Podcast Description TORONTO, ONTARIO: In 2017, a woman found a body in a ravine. The journey to figure out who the body belonged to would take many twists and turns.
Mental Health Resources
Canada
United States
Australia
United Kingdom
+ Find a therapist:
Online @BetterHelp (10% off your first month)
In person @ Psychology Today
+ 10 minute Yoga videos on youtube
Links to resources and initiatives from this episode:</description></item><item><title>71 The Murder of Jagtar Gill | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570093/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570093/</guid><description>Podcast Description ONTARIO - In 2014, a 15 year old went to the grocery store with her father. It was her parents’ 17th wedding anniversary - but her mother was recovering at home from a hernia operation she’d had the day before, so the teenager and her father went to pick out a cake and bring flowers back to her. But what they would be confronted with when they returned, would change their lives forever.</description></item><item><title>70 The Survival of Zach Miller | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570094/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570094/</guid><description>Podcast Description SASKATCHEWAN - It was 2006, and ten year old Zachary Miller was enjoying the summer on his family’s farm near the tiny town of Whitewood, Saskatchewan. A man walked up the driveway with a teenage boy, wanting to buy eggs—and Zach's life would never be the same again.
Child Personal Safety Resources: Canadian Centre for Child Protection is a national charity dedicated to the personal safety of all children, and provides resources and education.</description></item><item><title>69 The Death of Ezekiel Stephan - Part 3 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570095/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570095/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 3 of 3 ] ALBERTA - In 2012, a toddler would get sick, and the decisions of his parents would inspire much debate in the years to come.
Links to Tawny Platis fundraiser
GoFundMe
FaceBook Event
GetVokl event
Podcast recommendation:
Fetal Abduction
Thanks for supporting my sponsors!
See the special offer codes here
Credits:
Research: Haley Gray and Portia Bejanny
Research and writing: Haley Gray and Kristi Lee</description></item><item><title>68 The Death of Ezekiel Stephan - Part 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570096/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 17:12:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570096/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 2 of 3 ] ALBERTA - In 2012, a toddler would get sick, and the decisions of his parents would inspire much debate in the years to come.
Thanks for supporting my sponsors!
See the special offer codes here
Credits:
Research: Haley Gray and Portia Bejanny
Research and writing: Haley Gray and Kristi Lee
Audio editing and production: We Talk of Dreams&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Disclaimer voiced by the host of Beyond Bizarre True Crime&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>67 The Death of Ezekiel Stephan - Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570097/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570097/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 1 of 3 ] ALBERTA - In 2012, a toddler would get sick, and the decisions of his parents would inspire much debate in the years to come.
Thanks for supporting my sponsors!
See the special offer codes here
Credits:
Research: Haley Gray and Portia Bejanny
Research and writing: Haley Gray and Kristi Lee
Audio editing and production: We Talk of Dreams&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Disclaimer voiced by the host of Beyond Bizarre True Crime&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>66 The Murder of Sina Parsi | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570098/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570098/</guid><description>Podcast Description TORONTO, ONTARIO - In 2015, successful construction entrepreneur Sina Parsi left for a soccer game, but didn't return home. An unexpected story would unravel.
Thanks for supporting my sponsors!
See the special offer codes here
Find out what perks you can get as a patron:
www.patreon.com/CanadianTrueCrime
Credits:
Research and writing: Stephanie Moore and Kristi Lee
Narration, music arrangement: Kristi Lee
Audio editing: We Talk of Dreams
All credits and information sources can be found on the page for this episode at www.</description></item><item><title>65 The Murder of Hannah Leflar - Part 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570099/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570099/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 2 of a 2 part series ]
REGINA, SASKATCHEWAN
Part 2 of the story of a sweet 16 year old girl would become the focal point of a devastating story of twisted obsession and revenge.
Find out more about:&amp;nbsp;
The Robb Nash Project&amp;nbsp;
Needhelpnow.ca
kidshelpphone.ca
Credits:&amp;nbsp;
Research: Enya Best
Research and writing: Kristi Lee
Audio editing and production: We Talk of Dreams&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Disclaimer voiced by the host of Beyond Bizarre True Crime&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>64 The Murder of Hannah Leflar - Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570100/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 05:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570100/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 1 of a 2 part series ]
REGINA, SASKATCHEWAN
In 2015, a much-loved 16 year old girl would become the focal point of a devastating story of twisted obsession and revenge would shock the city of Regina and leave her loved ones heartbroken.
Find out more about:&amp;nbsp;
The Robb Nash Project&amp;nbsp;
Credits:&amp;nbsp;
Research: Enya Best
Research and writing: Kristi Lee
Audio editing and production: We Talk of Dreams&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>63 The Boyd Gang | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570101/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570101/</guid><description>Podcast Description TORONTO, ONTARIO&amp;nbsp;In the late 1940s and early 1950s, Edwin Alonzo Boyd terrorized Toronto through a series of daring bank robberies... bringing along a band of bank-robbing misfits known as the Boyd Gang.
Thank you to my generous sponsors!
You can find the codes, where applicable, at www.canadiantruecrime.ca/sponsors
Find out more about:&amp;nbsp;
Book: Edwin Alonzo Boyd: The Life and Crimes of Canada’s Master Bank Robber by Nate Hendley
Podcast recommendation: Mens Rea - an Irish True Crime podcast&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>62 The Murder of Richard Oland - Part 3 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570102/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570102/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 3 of a 3 part series]
SAINT JOHN, NEW BRUNSWICK&amp;nbsp;In the summer of 2011, the residents of Saint John would be alerted to a crime and ensuing scandal that would thrust their normally quiet city, and one of its most prominent and powerful families, into the spotlight in a way that no one could have anticipated.&amp;nbsp;
Thank you to my generous sponsors!
You can find the codes, where applicable, at www.</description></item><item><title>61 The Murder of Richard Oland - Part 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570103/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 06:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570103/</guid><description>Podcast Description [PART 2 OF 3]
SAINT JOHN, NEW BRUNSWICK&amp;nbsp;
In the summer of 2011, the residents of Saint John would be alerted to a crime and ensuing scandal that would thrust their normally quiet city—and one of its most prominent and powerful families—into the spotlight in a way that no one could have anticipated.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
I appreciate the support of my sponsors!
You can find applicable codes and information here.</description></item><item><title>60 The Murder of Richard Oland - Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570104/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 06:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570104/</guid><description>Podcast Description [PART 1 OF 3]
SAINT JOHN, NEW BRUNSWICK&amp;nbsp;
In the summer of 2011, the residents of Saint John would be alerted to a crime and ensuing scandal that would thrust their normally quiet city—and one of its most prominent and powerful families—into the spotlight in a way that no one could have anticipated.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
I appreciate the support of my sponsors!
You can find applicable codes and information here.</description></item><item><title>Donnellys Debrief with author Nate Hendley | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570105/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 03:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570105/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a conversation with Nate Hendley - who researched and wrote the episode, and criminologist Dr Lee Mellor.&amp;nbsp;
Also in this audio is me, Jordan from Nighttime, and Aaron from The Generation Why.
Learn more about:
Nate Hendley and his books&amp;nbsp;
Lee Mellor's podcast Murder Was the Case&amp;nbsp;
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>59 The Donnellys | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570106/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 06:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570106/</guid><description>Podcast Description An Irish immigrant family arrived in Lucan, Ontario in the 1840s, and almost immediately clashed with members of the local community. A fiery dispute erupted that would last for decades and escalate into madness, leaving a pile of bodies in its wake.
I appreciate the support of my sponsors!
You can find applicable codes and information here.
Find out more about: Toronto true crime author Nate Hendley's collection of booksDocumentary: The Donnellys (2017) Want more Canadian True Crime?</description></item><item><title>58 The Murder of Hanna Buxbaum | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570107/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 06:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570107/</guid><description>Podcast Description SOUTHWESTERN ONTARIO:&amp;nbsp;Millionaire nursing home operators Helmuth and Hanna Buxbaum were driving back from Toronto airport after picking up their nephew. Seeing a stranded motorist, they pulled over to see if they could help. But it wasn't a stranded motorist.
&amp;nbsp;
Podcast recommendations: Brew Crime
&amp;nbsp;
Sponsor codes :
I appreciate all the support of my sponsors and collaborators - see a list with any applicable codes here :)</description></item><item><title>57 The Murder of Kirk Morin | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570108/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 06:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570108/</guid><description>Podcast Description BRITISH COLUMBIA: In 2015, RCMP near Fort St John pulled up a white pickup truck for a routine traffic stop. The woman driving it was not the owner. As the RCMP investigated, a strange story unravelled.
Find out more about: BLOOD&amp;nbsp;TIES: A scripted audio series starring Gillian Jacobs, Josh Gad, and Amy Landecker. When legendary pediatric cardiologist and businessman, Dr. Peter Richland, is killed in a plane crash two days before Christmas, secrets begin to emerge about his dealings with female colleagues throughout his career.</description></item><item><title>The Murder of Loretta Saunders - Part 2: Interview with Delilah | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570109/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 22:46:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570109/</guid><description>Podcast Description *Part 2 of the story, produced by Nighttime.
The story of Loretta Saunders is expanded upon via an in depth conversation between Jordan of Nighttime and the person who vowed to carry on Loretta’s advocacy work… her sibling Delilah Saunders.&amp;nbsp;
&amp;nbsp;
Credits:
Musical Theme: Tremors by&amp;nbsp;Vox Somnia&amp;nbsp;https://voxsomniamusic.bandcamp.com/
Contact:
Website:&amp;nbsp;https://www.nighttimepodcast.com
Twitter:&amp;nbsp;https://twitter.com/NightTimePod
Facebook:&amp;nbsp;https://www.facebook.com/NightTimePod
Instagram:&amp;nbsp;https://www.instagram.com/nighttimepod
Email: NightTimePodcast@gmail.com
Support the show:&amp;nbsp;https://www.patreon.com/nighttimepodcast
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>56 The Murder of Loretta Saunders - Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570110/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 06:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Halifax, Nova Scotia - In 2014, 26 year old Loretta Saunders – a proud Inuk woman – was in Halifax completing her university thesis on missing and murdered indigenous women and girls. She went out to run an errand and didn’t return. What happened to her – and the resulting activism of her family – would have far-reaching effects.
*A collaboration with Nighttime Podcast. Find out more about:</description></item><item><title>55 Misty Cockerill and Tanya Smith - Part 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570111/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 06:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570111/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 2 of 2 ] The conclusion to the story of The Abbotsford Killer. Find out who he was, how he was brought to justice, and where everyone is today.
Thanks for supporting my sponsors!
The current discount codes can be found here
Find out more about:
+ BOOK: Rod Gehl's book "Through the Valley of the Shadow - The Search for the Abbotsford Killer
+ The Papaya Podcast - GUEST APPEARANCE: Kristi's "</description></item><item><title>54 Misty Cockerill and Tanya Smith - Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570112/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570112/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 1 of 2 ] The Abbotsford Killer, BC - On October 13, 1995, two teenage girls were walking along a familiar street as they were heading to a party. Along the way, they encountered a man who would change not only their lives, but the lives of their two families, multiple police districts and an entire community. For the next seven months that man played a game of cat and mouse, terrorizing the community.</description></item><item><title>53 The Murder of Joseph Rosenthal | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570113/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 06:17:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570113/</guid><description>Podcast Description TORONTO, ON - A late-night business meeting in a 1912 hydro yard ends in a serious crime. The case inspired an unprecedented public outcry at a time when hanging was still routinely applied for the most serious of offences. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
To support my sponsors:
See the list of my sponsors and discount codes
Find out more about:
Hot Docs Podcast Festival - Toronto, Ontario
True Crime Podcast Festival - Kansas City, Missouri</description></item><item><title>Russell Williams Debrief - with Criminologist Lee Mellor | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570114/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 13:30:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570114/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Bonus content between episodes ] I had lots of questions after covering Russell Williams - so I had a conversation with Dr Lee Mellor - Canadian profiler, author, criminologist and serial killer expert. He's also the host of Murder Was The Case.
In typical Lee fashion, he doesn't hold back on any of his opinions. Definitely lots of food for thought. Disclaimer voiceover: Robin Warder from The Trail Went Cold</description></item><item><title>Introduction to Canadian True Crime | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570115/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 18:25:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Canadian True Crime is a fully independent podcast that explores some of the most heinous, controversial, heartbreaking and thought-provoking true crime cases in Canada.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>52 The Crimes of Russell Williams - Part 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570116/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570116/</guid><description>Podcast Description [ Part 2 of 2 ] The interrogation of Russell Williams continues, and after that comes the fallout from his crimes.
Find out more about:
The Mysterious Mr Epstein - a new podcast from Wondery that answers all your questions about Jeffrey Epstein. Listen now at Wondery.fm/tcrime.
Jim Can't Swim - YouTube Criminal Psychology - analysis of Russell Williams interrogation
The Mob Reporter - YouTube channel
Redhanded Podcast&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>51 The Crimes of Russell Williams - Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570117/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome back to a new season of Canadian True Crime!
In 2010, 27 year old Jessica Lloyd was reported missing from her home in Belleville, Ontario. She hadn't shown up for work, and the last time anybody heard from her was a late evening text message the night before.
A week after Jessica disappeared, the OPP called a man in for questioning. What he revealed to police over the next 10 hours would not only come to shock the nation, but many thousands of employees of the Canadian Forces to their core.</description></item><item><title>Case Updates and Reflections 2019 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570118/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 14:21:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Back with the next full episode on Septmeber 15, but here's all of the major updates from the cases I've covered - as well as some of my thoughts and reflections.
Approx timestamps of cases discussed:
02:00 The Murder of Tori Stafford - update from her father, Rodney
11:00 Elizabeth Wettlaufer - release of report after inquiry into what happened
14:00 Sara and Taliyah - sentencing of Edward Downey</description></item><item><title>50 The Murder of Tracy Tom | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570119/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570119/</guid><description>Podcast Description VANCOUVER, BRITISH COLUMBIA
In 2003, a local dry cleaner was opening up his shop for the morning, when he saw an abandoned shopping cart with a large object slumped into it.
Find out more about:
True Crime Podcasts - Live in Toronto - August 18
The Royal Cinema’s monthly signature series
Trans Pulse Project
Gender Bandit.com
Podcast recommendations
Crime Writers On (true crime podcast and documentary reviews, pop culture, and more)</description></item><item><title>49 The Crimes of Elizabeth Wettlaufer - Part 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570120/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 05:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bethe Wettlaufer finally comes to the attention of the police, and the full extent of her crimes is revealed.
Want to support my sponsors? Here's where the discount codes are:
www.canadiantruecrime.ca/sponsors
Credits:&amp;nbsp;
Research and writing: Gemma Harris
Narration, music arrangement, audio production: Kristi Lee
Audio editing: Erik Krosby
Disclaimer voiced by the host of Beyond Bizarre True Crime
CTC Theme song by We Talk of Dreams&amp;nbsp;
Other credits and sources can be found on the page for this episode at&amp;nbsp;www.</description></item><item><title>48 The Crimes of Elizabeth Wettlaufer - Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570121/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570121/</guid><description>Podcast Description WOODSTOCK, ONTARIO
The decision to place an elderly relative in care is often a difficult and emotional process. That's why it’s vital that long term care facilities offer families peace of mind and reassurance that their loved one is safe and well cared for.
This is a tale of where it all went terribly wrong.
Find out more about:
The Band Played On - a CBC Investigative Podcast</description></item><item><title>47 Jane Hurshman - Part 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570122/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 04:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570122/</guid><description>Podcast Description BANGS FALLS, NOVA SCOTIA
The continuation of the story of one Canadian woman's life living with domestic violence.
Learn more about:
Sheltersafe.ca - services to support women trying to leave an abusive relationship
Warning signs you might be in an abusive relationship
Want to support my sponsors? Here's where the discount codes are:
www.canadiantruecrime.ca/sponsors
Live shows this summer:
True Crime Podcasts - Live in Toronto | August 18, 2-5 pm</description></item><item><title>46 Jane Hurshman - Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570123/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 04:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570123/</guid><description>Podcast Description BANGS FALLS, NOVA SCOTIA
This is the story of one Canadian woman's life living with domestic violence.
Learn more about:
True Crime Podcasts - Live in Toronto | August 18, 2-5 pm
True Crime Podcast Festival - Chicago | July 13, all day
Podcast recommendation: OPPO - a politics discussion by CANADALAND
Want to support my sponsors? Here's where the discount codes are:
www.canadiantruecrime.ca/sponsors
Credits:&amp;nbsp;
Research and writing: Haley Grey</description></item><item><title>45 Sara and Taliyah | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570124/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 06:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570124/</guid><description>Podcast Description CALGARY, ALBERTA - In 2016, a single mother failed to drop off her 5 year old daughter at daycare, and from there began a family's worst nightmare.&amp;nbsp;
Learn more about:
True Crime Podcast Festival&amp;nbsp;|&amp;nbsp;Chicago, July 13
True Crime Podcasts - Live in Toronto&amp;nbsp;|&amp;nbsp;Toronto, August 18 (tickets coming soon!)
Unresolved Podcast &amp;nbsp;
Want to support my sponsors? Here's where the discount codes are:
www.canadiantruecrime.ca/sponsors
Credits:
Research and writing: Charlie Worroll</description></item><item><title>44 The Brentwood Five | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570125/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 08:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570125/</guid><description>Podcast Description CALGARY, ALBERTA - Early in the morning in 2014 police in responded to three separate 911 calls. There had been a stabbing incident at a house in Brentwood, a suburb in the northwest of the city. It only took police a few minutes to arrive, and once they did, the scene that greeted them would be something they would never forget.
Learn more about:
Quinterra Legacy Garden
Espionage by Parcast Network</description></item><item><title>43 The Jenkins Family | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570126/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 04:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570126/</guid><description>Podcast Description CHATHAM, ONTARIO In 1998, a shocking tragedy would occur that would turn immediately a family upside down and divide a community along the way.
Want to support sponsors? Here's where the discount codes are:
www.canadiantruecrime.ca/sponsors
Learn more:
Level 16 - new Canadian film | Watch the trailer | Follow on Facebook | Follow on Instagram
Rodney Stafford’s Ottawa Protest&amp;nbsp;and how you can help
Life With Murder&amp;nbsp;- 2009 documentary on the Jennifer Jenkins / Mason Jenkins story directed by John Kastener</description></item><item><title>42 Brent and Brendan McGuigan | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570127/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 05:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570127/</guid><description>Podcast Description From PEI, the story of a family feud that lasted for decades - in the eyes of one man who couldn’t get past his obsession.
Want to support sponsors? Here's where the discount codes are:
www.canadiantruecrime.ca/sponsors
Learn more:
Hostage by Parcast
Misconduct True Crime Podcast
Get ad free episodes for $2 a month: www.patreon.com/canadiantruecrime
Credits:
Research and writing: Charlie Worroll from Impact Statement
Narration, music arrangement, audio production: Kristi Lee</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Interview with Bret McCann (Travis Vader case) | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570128/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 03:26:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570128/</guid><description>Podcast Description As promised, this is the follow up to episode 41. This Impact Statement episode that features an interview with Bret McCann - the son of Lyle and Marie McCann, who were murdered by Travis Vader.
Subscribe to Impact Statement so you don't miss an episode.
See you tomorrow - March 15 - for the next scheduled episode of Canadian True Crime!
Support the show.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>41 The Murder of Lyle and Marie McCann | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570129/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 10:13:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570129/</guid><description>Podcast Description ALBERTA |&amp;nbsp;In 2010, a retired couple embarked on a leisurely road trip in their RV from Alberta to British Columbia. When they didn’t arrive on schedule for an agreed meeting point, their family and friends were left wondering what happened.
Meanwhile, who was Travis Vader, and how did he come to be driving their RV?
Support my sponsors! Here's where the discount codes are:
www.canadiantruecrime.ca/sponsors
Learn more:
Crimes of Passion</description></item><item><title>40 Harrison Family Murders | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570130/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 06:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mississauga, Ontario - A separated couple have ongoing issues with custody of their children, setting a chain of events in motion that would destroy an entire family.
Support my sponsors! Here's where the discount codes are:
www.canadiantruecrime.ca/sponsors
Learn more:
Nighttime Podcast's series on Lindsay Souvannarath
One Eye Open - a British true crime podcast
Join my patreon for $2 a month to get ad-free, early-release episodes: www.patreon.com/canadiantruecrime
Credits:</description></item><item><title>39 Giant Mine Murders | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570131/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yellowknife, NWT&amp;nbsp;
A labour union strike at a gold mine escalates over time, turning bitter and violent, eventually leading to a tragic incident.
Support my sponsors! Here's where the discount codes are:
www.canadiantruecrime.ca/sponsors
Learn more:
Music producer from Australia: Soularflair
Join my patreon for $2 a month to get ad-free, early-release episodes: www.patreon.com/canadiantruecrime&amp;nbsp;
Credits:
Research: Enya Best
Writing, narration, music arrangement: Kristi Lee
Audio production: Erik Krosby
Disclaimer voiced by the host of&amp;nbsp;Beyond Bizarre True Crime</description></item><item><title>The Murder of Daniel Levesque - Part 2: Interview with Daniel's mom | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570132/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 03:37:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570132/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this second part of the story, Jordan from The Nighttime Podcast interviews Daniel's mom, Stacey—revealling more details that will make anyone with a respect for justice scream.
Subscribe to The Nighttime Podcast on Apple Podcast.
Visit The Nighttime Podcast website
Support the show.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>38 The Murder of Daniel Levesque - Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570133/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Victoria, British Columbia
A young musician moves from Revelstoke to Victoria, British Columbia, and meets a man called Joshua Bredo, who offers him a job.
Support my sponsors! Here's where the discount codes are:
www.canadiantruecrime.ca/sponsors
Podcast recommendations:
Rusty Hinges
Lagered Tales podcast
Nighttime Podcast: Taylor Samson episodes
Join my patreon for $2 a month to get ad-free, early-release episodes:
www.patreon.com/canadiantruecrime
Credits:
Research, writing, narration, music arrangement: Kristi Lee</description></item><item><title>37 Tracy Latimer | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570134/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 02:45:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wilkie, Saskatchewan
The story of a farming family who find themselves in a heartbreaking situation, in what would become one of the most controversial court cases in Canadian history.
Podcast recommendations:
True Crime Bullsh**: The Story of Israel Keyes
Uncover: Bomb on Board
Additional resources:
Book: Robert Latimer: A story of justice and mercy, by Gary Bauslaugh
Dark Topic episode: Dr Kevorkian
Support my sponsors! Here's where the discount codes are:</description></item><item><title>36 The Murder of Jennifer Cusworth | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570135/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 05:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kelowna, British Columbia. A pumpkin farmer finds the body of a young woman at the end of his driveway, prompting an investigation that would take years.
Learn more:
True Crime Podcast Festival - July 13 2019, Chicago
Canadian True Crime Merchandise Store
Podcast recommendations:
Let’s Talk About Sects: A podcast about cults
Support my sponsors! Here's where the discount codes are:
www.canadiantruecrime.ca/sponsors
Join my patreon for $2 a month to get ad-free, early-release episodes: www.</description></item><item><title>35 The Murder of Frank and Jocelyn Toope | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570136/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Beaconsfield, Quebec. The car of a 75 year old retired Anglican minister and his 70 year old wife was found abandoned in a car park. A twisted tale would unravel... Also includes an update on Paul Bernardo's first parole hearing held in October 2018.
Podcast recommendations:
Don't Talk to Strangers – The Oakland County Child Murders
KINGPINS by Parcast
My interview on CANADALAND
Support my sponsors! Here's where the discount codes are:</description></item><item><title>34 The Murder of Erin Chorney | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570137/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brandon, Manitoba. An independent 18 year old tells her mom she’ll be back in an hour, gets into a car, and is never seen again. Was she just out partying for several days, or was there something more sinister at play? Where was Erin Chorney?
See more information on gender-based violence and where to get help
Support my sponsors! Here's where the discount codes are:
www.canadiantruecrime.ca/sponsors
Podcast recommendations:</description></item><item><title>33 Dellen Millard and the Murder of his Father | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570138/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 04:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570138/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 6 of 6] He's already in jail for two consecutive life sentences for two murders - Tim Bosma and Laura Babcock. In this final episode, we find out what happened with the murder of Dellen Millard's father, Wayne Millard.
This episode is part one in a multi-part series that covers three cases over six episodes. All episodes, in order, are:
07 - The Murder of Tim Bosma</description></item><item><title>32 The Shafia Family | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570139/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 05:34:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570139/</guid><description>Podcast Description A large family journeys from Afghanistan to Quebec, before the family descends into chaos, ending in a catastrophe. What went so wrong in the Shafia family?
&amp;nbsp;
Learn more about:
The Search for Ryan Shtuka (Night Time Podcast)
The Wrongful Conviction of Ronald Moffatt (Impact Statement Podcast)
Music in this episode was by Soularflair
Support my sponsors! Here's where the discount codes are:
www.canadiantruecrime.ca/sponsors
Podcast recommendations:
Murder Road Trip</description></item><item><title>31 The Crimes of Peter Woodcock: Canada's youngest serial killer | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570140/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 05:01:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570140/</guid><description>Podcast Description TORONTO, ONTARIO. The story of Canada's youngest serial killer, Peter Woodcock, and the wrongful conviction of Ron Moffatt. In the mid 1950s in Toronto, a black-haired teenager on a bicycle terrorized downtown neighborhoods. How long would it take the police before they caught him? And who would get caught in the crossfire?
&amp;nbsp;
Learn more about:
The Boy on the Bicycle: A Forgotten Case of Wrongful Conviction in Toronto book by Nate Hendley</description></item><item><title>Case Updates, Mistakes, Opinions :) | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570141/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 13:08:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi everyone! There have been quite a few updates to cases I've covered, so I thought I'd take this opportunity to update you all.
&amp;nbsp;
Sponsor &amp;amp; resources:
Tweed.com - for all your cannabis information
WATCH: How to talk about Indigenous people&amp;nbsp;
BOOK: Stephen Truscott - Decades of Injustice by Nate Hendley
BOOK: The Boy on the Bicycle: A Forgotten Case of Wrongful Conviction in Toronto&amp;nbsp;by Nate Hendley</description></item><item><title>30 The Murder of Johnny Altinger | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570142/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 03:32:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Truth and reality blended in a murder case in Edmonton that came to be known internationally as the “Dexter Murder”. It all started on October 3, 2008.
&amp;nbsp;
Dating profile as mentioned
Pictures of Canadian Crime Podcast Event - July 22
&amp;nbsp;
Support my sponsors! Here's where the discount codes are:
www.canadiantruecrime.ca/sponsors
&amp;nbsp;
Podcast recommendations:
Australian True Crime
Southern Fried True Crime
The Westside Fairytales
&amp;nbsp;
Join my patreon to get early, ad-free episodes and more:&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>29 École Polytechnique Massacre - Part 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570143/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 05:04:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570143/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 2 of 2] The conclusion to the 1989 Montreal Massacre story that took place at École Polytechnique, exploring the massacre itself and the aftermath.
&amp;nbsp;
TIME STAMP: To forward just past the massacre - 26:50
&amp;nbsp;
Support my sponsors! Here's where the discount codes are:
www.canadiantruecrime.ca/sponsors
Podcast recommendations:
Distorsion Podcast Join my patreon to get early, ad-free episodes and more:&amp;nbsp;
www.patreon.com/canadiantruecrime&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
&amp;nbsp;
Credits:
Narration and music arrangement, writing, additional research: Kristi Lee</description></item><item><title>28 École Polytechnique Massacre - Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570144/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 11:33:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570144/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1989, a 25-year-old man with a rifle entered the École Polytechnique engineering school with a specific target in mind: women. The ensuing massacre would go on to have lasting effects on the province of Québec, as well as the entire nation.&amp;nbsp;
Support my sponsors! Here's where the discount codes are:
www.canadiantruecrime.ca/sponsors
&amp;nbsp;
Podcast recommendations:
Pretend Radio
We're All Just Pretending
&amp;nbsp;
Join my patreon to get early, ad-free episodes and more:&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>27 Angela Nicholson &amp; Curtis Vey | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570145/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 05:05:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Melfort, Saskatchewan. Two farming families found themselves linked together under the most shocking of circumstances.
Support my sponsors! Here's where the discount codes are:
www.canadiantruecrime.ca/sponsors
Podcast recommendation:
Swindled
&amp;nbsp;
For information sources, credits and more, please visit www.canadiantruecrime.ca.
Support the show.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>26 The Murder of Michelle Barnoski | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570146/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 05:52:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Warkworth, Ontario. In 2011, a 33-year-old single mother went missing in a small village in Ontario. As the mystery slowly unraveled, the truth would be revealed about what happened to her, and how things got to that point.&amp;nbsp;
Support my sponsors! Here's where the discount codes are:
www.canadiantruecrime.ca/sponsors
Podcast recommendations:
Emma Fillipoff is Missing
The Westside Fairytales
Pleasing Terrors
&amp;nbsp;
For information sources, credits and more, please visit www.</description></item><item><title>25 The Murder of Victoria Shachtay | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570147/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 06:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Innisfail, Alberta. A 23 year old quadriplegic single mother receives a package disguised as a Christmas gift on her doorstop.&amp;nbsp;What happened next, and the story behind who sent this mysterious package, would stun the small community of Innisfail.
* Clarification: Please note that Evan Shielke was a FORMER volunteer firefighter at the time of the incident. The media incorrectly chose to focus on this aspect when reporting on him, but he clarified with me that he actually hadn't volunteered for ten years.</description></item><item><title>24 The Murder of Lynne Harper | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570148/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 05:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Steven Truscott was a 14 year old boy in Ontario, Canada, and in 1959 he&amp;nbsp;was&amp;nbsp;linked to a tragedy that ended the life of a 12 year old girl. This would turn into the longest legal drama in Canadian history.
Recommended reading:&amp;nbsp;
Steven Truscott: Decades of Injustice, by Nate Hendley&amp;nbsp;Amazon.ca&amp;nbsp;Amazon.com
Support my sponsors! Here's where the discount codes are:
www.canadiantruecrime.ca/sponsors
Podcast recomendations:
Felon True Crime
Murder was the Case</description></item><item><title>23 Andrea Giesbrecht - Part 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570149/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2018 14:59:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570149/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 2 of 2] The shocking conclusion to the case of a woman charged with concealing infant remains in a storage locker.&amp;nbsp;
Support my sponsors! Here's where the discount codes are:
www.canadiantruecrime.ca/sponsors
Podcast recommendation:
Information sources&amp;nbsp;
Please visit the episode page on&amp;nbsp;www.canadiantruecrime.ca&amp;nbsp;in the week after the episode is released.
Join my patreon to get early, ad-free episodes and more:&amp;nbsp;
www.patreon.com/canadiantruecrime&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Credits:
Research, writing, narration and music arrangement: Kristi Lee</description></item><item><title>22 Andrea Giesbrecht - Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570150/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2018 06:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570150/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 1 of 2]&amp;nbsp;Employees of a Winnipeg self-storage facility were cleaning out an unpaid locker in 2014, when they made a shocking discovery.
Support my sponsors! Here's where the discount codes are:
www.canadiantruecrime.ca/sponsors
Podcast recommendations:
The Fall Line
Impact Statement
Information sources&amp;nbsp;
Please visit the episode page on www.canadiantruecrime.ca&amp;nbsp;in the week after the episode is released.
&amp;nbsp;
Join my patreon to get early, ad-free episodes and more:&amp;nbsp;
www.patreon.com/canadiantruecrime&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>21 Ernest DesRoches | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570151/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570151/</guid><description>Podcast Description From the tiny province of Prince Edward Island comes this story of a tragedy and a survival. It’s the story of a family called The Ellsworths, and a man who would change their lives forever.
Support my sponsors! Here's where the discount codes are:
www.canadiantruecrime.ca/sponsors
Podcast recommendation:
True Crime Fan Club
Information sources
Can be found on the episode's page on&amp;nbsp;www.canadiantruecrime.ca&amp;nbsp;in the week after the episode is released.</description></item><item><title>20 The Murder of Laura Babcock - Part 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570152/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 04:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570152/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 5 of 6] Continuation of the Dellen Millard, Mark Smich and Laura Babcock story featured in episode 19 (and before that, episodes 7,8 and 9). 23-year-old Laura Babcock disappeared in July 2012 - and finally it is announced that Dellen Millard and Mark Smich are charged with her first degree murder. In this part, you'll find out what happened in the trial and aftermath.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
This episode is part one in a multi-part series that covers three cases over six episodes.</description></item><item><title>19 The Murder of Laura Babcock - Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570153/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 05:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570153/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 4 of 6] Continuation of the Tim Bosma, Dellen Millard and Mark Smich story featured in episodes 7, 8 and 9. 23-year-old Laura Babcock disappeared in July 2012 - and finally it is announced that Dellen Millard and Mark Smich are charged with her first degree murder. In this two-parter, you'll find out the story behind Laura Babcock's final months, and what happened at the trial.&amp;nbsp;
This episode is part one in a multi-part series that covers three cases over six episodes.</description></item><item><title>Q&amp;A Anniversary Special! | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570154/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 08:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yay! I made it to a year of podcasting!
I'm announcing a couple of format changes, and then I launch into the Q&amp;amp;A session.
Thanks to my patrons and members of the facebook discussion group for submitting the questions.
Support the show.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>18 Robert Pickton - Part 4 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570155/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2018 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570155/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 4 of 4]&amp;nbsp;In this final episode, we find out about Robert Pickton's interrogation, processing&amp;nbsp;Canada's largest crime scene, what happened in the trial, and the aftermath.&amp;nbsp;
Support my sponsors! Here's where the discount codes are:
www.canadiantruecrime.ca/sponsors
Recommended additional resources:
BOOK: On the Farm - Robert William Pickton and the tragic story of Vancouver's Missing Women, by Stevie Cameron
DOCUMENTARY: The Pig Farm
PODCAST: CANADALAND Commons &amp;nbsp;Episode:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Invisible Victims: How Police Botched the Robert Pickton Case</description></item><item><title>17 Robert Pickton - Part 3 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570156/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570156/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 3 of 4]&amp;nbsp;In this part, we find out what led to Robert Pickton's eventual arrest.
Support my sponsors! Here's where the discount codes are:
www.canadiantruecrime.ca/sponsors
Podcast recommendations:
Suicide by Cop
The Marble Garden
The Secret Life of Weddings -&amp;nbsp;Episode 2 featuring Dellen Millard
Dark Poutine
Join my patreon to get early, ad-free episodes, video AMAs and more:&amp;nbsp;
www.patreon.com/canadiantruecrime&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Social media and contact information:
Visit: www.canadiantruecrime.ca
Facebook page:&amp;nbsp;www.facebook.com/canadiantruecrime/</description></item><item><title>16 Robert Pickton - Part 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570157/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 08:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570157/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 2 of 4]&amp;nbsp;We continue our journey through Robert Pickton’s life, and that of the missing women of the Downtown Eastside. More mistakes are made by the Vancouver Police Department. And two people will come into Robert Pickton’s life who will provide very important evidence later on.
Support my sponsors! Here's where the discount codes are:
www.canadiantruecrime.ca/sponsors
Podcast recommendation:
The Dirty Bits Podcast Join my patreon to get early, ad-free episodes, video AMAs and more:&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>15 Robert Pickton - Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570158/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 02:34:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570158/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 1 of 4] Canada's most prolific serial killer was active from the late 80s until his capture in 2002. Robert Pickton was a pig farmer who lived in Port Coquitlam, a suburb of Vancouver. Over 20 years, he hand-picked the most vulnerable and desperate women from Vancouver's downtown eastside, lured them to his farm, and "disposed of them" there. Who was he? And how did he get away with it for so long?</description></item><item><title>14 The Murder of Tori Stafford - Part 3 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570159/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 22:16:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570159/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 3 of 3] The shocking conclusion to the story of an 8 year old girl who went missing from Woodstock, Ontario in 2009. If you haven’t listened to Part 1, I encourage you to listen to that first.
CONTENT WARNING: this podcast contains coarse language, adult themes and content of a violent and disturbing nature.
....
More information:
Abduction Prevention Tips&amp;nbsp;www.childsafecanada.com/alerts.aspx
Canadian Jury Help -&amp;nbsp;Facebook page&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;Twitter&amp;nbsp;
Podcasts to check out:</description></item><item><title>13 The Murder of Tori Stafford - Part 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570160/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 22:16:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570160/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 2 of 3] The shocking conclusion to the story of an 8 year old girl who went missing from Woodstock, Ontario in 2009. If you haven’t listened to Part 1, I encourage you to listen to that first.
CONTENT WARNING: this podcast contains coarse language, adult themes and content of a violent and disturbing nature.
....
Support my sponsors! Here's where the discount codes are:
www.canadiantruecrime.ca/sponsors
More information:</description></item><item><title>12 The Murder of Tori Stafford - Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570161/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 08:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570161/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 1 of 3] In 2009 in the city of Woodstock, Ontario, an 8 year old girl would go missing. This shocking story that unfolded would decimate the façade of the sleepy, blue-collar city, exposing a network of cracks that had long lay just below the surface. The damage would be both widespread and irrecoverable.
CONTENT WARNING: this podcast&amp;nbsp;contains coarse language, adult themes and content of a violent and disturbing nature.</description></item><item><title>11 Shell Lake Massacre | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570162/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570162/</guid><description>Podcast Description The story of Saskatchewan’s worst mass murder. 21-year-old Victor Hoffman suffered from paranoid schizophrenia which saw him descend into madness, leading to a collision with an unsuspecting family that would have tragic consequences.
…..
Support my sponsors! Here's where the discount codes are:
www.canadiantruecrime.ca/sponsors
Learn more about:
Rampage: Canadian Mass Murder and Spree Killing by Lee Mellor
Vincent Li episode on The Minds of Madness
The Greyhound Bus Beheading episode on Dark Topic</description></item><item><title>10 The Murder of Paula Gallant | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570163/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2017 22:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nova Scotia&amp;nbsp;|&amp;nbsp;Two days after Christmas in 2005, 36-year-old schoolteacher Paula Gallant went shopping and never returned. Just hours after she was reported missing by her husband Jason MacRae, her body was found in the trunk of her car. How did she die? And who would have cause to harm someone so beloved by her wide network of family, friends and the local community? This is a heartbreaking tale of two sisters who wouldn’t give up, and a family bond that can’t be broken—no matter what.</description></item><item><title>09 The Murder of Tim Bosma - Part 3 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570164/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 05:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570164/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 3 of 6] Conclusion to the Tim Bosma and Dellen Millard trilogy; you’ll hear what Dellen Millard and Mark Smich got up to after Tim Bosma was murdered, and how they went about covering up their crime. We’ll also go through the trial - and find out what their stories were about what happened the night Tim Bosma went missing. Finally, we’ll go through where the case is up to now - particularly with Laura Babcock and Wayne Millard.</description></item><item><title>08 The Murder of Tim Bosma - Part 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570165/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 22:54:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570165/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 2 of 6]&amp;nbsp;We learn more about Dellen - a party boy rich kid who decides he wants a particular make and model of truck, and doesn’t want to pay for it. So he arranges a test drive with one he sees online. Tim Bosma, the seller of the truck, never returns from the test drive. Who is Dellen Millard? And why did he want that truck?
This episode is part one in a multi-part series that covers three cases over six episodes.</description></item><item><title>07 The Murder of Tim Bosma - Part 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570166/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 13:31:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570166/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 1 of 6] In 2013, a 32-year-old family man took two potential buyers for a test drive in the truck he was selling. He never returned from that test drive. What happened? Was it about the man or the truck? This is a heinous, senseless murder that shocked the nation and still continues to do so.
This episode is part one in a multi-part series that covers three cases over six episodes.</description></item><item><title>06 The Murder of Reena Virk | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570167/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 01:01:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570167/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1997, a 14 year old girl is invited by a group of peers she thinks are her friends to meet under a bridge in Victoria, British Columbia. What happened next was unthinkable. The crime was a watershed&amp;nbsp;event that changed peoples' attitudes about youth violence and incited controversy in Canada.
Support my sponsors:
www.canadiantruecrime.ca/sponsors
…..
This episode was brought to you by:
Death in the Family by John Chipman</description></item><item><title>05 Teen Boys Who Kill | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570168/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 17:29:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570168/</guid><description>Podcast Description All about young offenders in Canada, this episode tells the stories of two disturbed teenaged murderers who were connected to the controversial Young Offenders Act. This episode contains content of a disturbing and violent nature, and includes child murder with a sexual component. Listener discretion is advised.
…..
Support my sponsors! Here's where the discount codes are:
www.canadiantruecrime.ca/sponsors
For more information, please follow us on social media:
Facebook:&amp;nbsp;www.facebook.com/canadiantruecrime/</description></item><item><title>04 Douglas Garland | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570169/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2017 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570169/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is about the heinous and senseless murders of Alvin and Kathy Likness and their grandson, five-year-old Nathan O’Brien, who were snatched one night from their beds by a psychopathic man with a criminal past. The crime shocked the province of Alberta and made national news.
Support my sponsors! Here's where the discount codes are:
www.canadiantruecrime.ca/sponsors
For more information, please follow us on social media:
Facebook:&amp;nbsp;www.facebook.com/canadiantruecrime/
Twitter:&amp;nbsp;https://twitter.com/CanadianTCpod</description></item><item><title>03 Cody Legebokoff | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570170/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 03:20:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570170/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the story of Cody Alan Legebokoff: Canada's teenaged serial killer.&amp;nbsp;Cody had a normal childhood, a loving family, and was described as popular and easy going. A typical Canadian teenager who was into sports. But he was hiding a darkness inside him.&amp;nbsp;Cody had a double life and the people who knew him were shocked when his murderous crimes came to light.
Support my sponsors! Here's where the discount codes are:</description></item><item><title>02 Paul Bernardo and Karla Homolka - 2 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570171/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2017 06:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570171/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 2 of 2] The conclusion of the story of two married sexual sadist serial killers who terrorized the Greater Toronto and Niagara areas in Canada in the late 80s and early 90s.&amp;nbsp;This episode goes into their marriage, the psychopathic, diabolical crimes they are known for, their arrests, trials, controversy and “where are they now”.&amp;nbsp;There’s also a cameo by Luka Magnotta. If you think you know this story, you’ll definitely hear some information you haven’t heard before.</description></item><item><title>01 Paul Bernardo and Karla Homolka - 1 | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570172/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 19:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570172/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 1 of 2]&amp;nbsp;They call them the Ken and Barbie killers. The perpetrators of one of Canada’s most heinous and notorious crime sprees.&amp;nbsp;They were a good-looking couple and seemed to have it all… but behind the mask was a cesspool of depravity and evil.&amp;nbsp;This story is about Paul Bernardo and Karla Homolka, a couple of sexual sadists who terrorized the Greater Toronto and Niagara areas in the late 80s and early 90.</description></item><item><title>00 Obligatory Intro Episode | Canadian True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3299570173/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 06:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3299570173/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to Canadian True Crime - a new podcast that will take you on a journey through Canada’s most notorious murder stories. There'll be a bit of everything - serial killers, murders and more.
This boring introduction gives you a bit of background into Canada and debunks the stereotype of the “nice Canadian”. You'll get to find out why someone with an Aussie accent is producing a Canadian True Crime podcast.</description></item></channel></rss>