<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Garden of Eden on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-garden-of-eden/</link><description>Recent content in The Garden of Eden on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 07:43:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-garden-of-eden/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introducing - Catching Dad's Killer | The Garden of Eden</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521750001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 07:43:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521750001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Robert Dickie went missing from his farm just outside of Dubbo, NSW, in 2016.
Bob's family always believed something bad happened to him, and then in April 2020, a woman was arrested for his murder.
Almost 4 years later, after an 8-week trial and revelations that shocked the family,the judge delivers his verdict.
Coming to Apple podcast subscriptions on December 19, 2023 See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Fake Social Profiles | The Garden of Eden</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521750002/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 12:04:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521750002/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, we get a tip from another listener about some of the people that are on Eden’s social media. Are they who they say?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Piecing It Together | The Garden of Eden</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521750003/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521750003/</guid><description>Podcast Description As more information comes in about some of the allegations across the last 16 episodes, we start to try to piece everything together.
In this episode, a former friend of Paul Reynolds makes contact, and a new anonymous person comes forward with information that could help.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Story So Far - A Catchup Episode | The Garden of Eden</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521750004/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521750004/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this catch-up episode, we run through the past 16 episodes and what's happened so far.
If you are a new listener to the podcast, this is the perfect place to start See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Disturbing New Allegation | The Garden of Eden</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521750005/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521750005/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Eden’s sister Hunter's moving tribute, We hear from a new witness who recounts a disturbing encounter with a police officer, and we think we have cracked a vital piece of information about the night Eden went missing.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>New Evidence, A New Investigation and Eden’s Social Media | The Garden of Eden</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521750006/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521750006/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, our pro-bono barrister heads back to Tasmania to speak to more witnesses with new information about Eden, plus a new investigation gets commissioned into Paul Reynolds, and we access Eden’s social media and find some shocking new information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Shocking News That Might Provide Some Answers | The Garden of Eden</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521750007/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521750007/</guid><description>Podcast Description **Content Warning**
This podcast contains details of alleged child abuse, grooming, and exploitation. Listener discretion is advised.
You can sign the petition to reopen Edens case here https://chng.it/gjZkDsvDWy
We have received an email that led us to talk to a new person who might help us find the answers we have been looking for. In this episode, we also have more details about Senior Seargent Paul Reynolds and the outcome of a commision of enquiry into child abuse in government institutions and schools in Tasmania, plus we put some questions to the girl we are calling Kate.</description></item><item><title>A Response From "Kate" | The Garden of Eden</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521750008/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521750008/</guid><description>Podcast Description For months, we have been trying to speak with the girl we have called Kate. In this episode, we finally get her on the phone, but it doesn’t go as planned.
There’s more about the police officer who was involved in Eden’s case and took his own life, as well as some unusual circumstances that have yet to be explained We have also set up a petition to ask the Tasmanian officials to reopen a public inquiry into Eden's death and the investigation.</description></item><item><title>Your Questions Answered and What About That Phone? | The Garden of Eden</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521750009/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521750009/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, we ask Jason and Amanda some of your questions about the rope, the autopsy, and questions that have arisen over the cremation of Eden's phone. We have also set up a petition to ask the Tasmanian officials to reopen a public inquiry into Eden's death and the investigation. You can help by signing it here https://chng.it/LV6SqjgQVJ
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tasmanian Police Respond | The Garden of Eden</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521750010/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521750010/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Taspol reply to our 16 questions on all of the questions that have been raised in the last 10 episodes of the podcast. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Introducing - Out Of The Ordinary | The Garden of Eden</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521750011/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521750011/</guid><description>Podcast Description You may not know the name, Brandon Truaxe, but you most likely will know some of the brands he created – Brandon was behind the international skin care brand – The Ordinary which is part of the Deciem group of companies.
This is the true story of the rise and demise of a man that was once lauded business genius.
Across 15 months from 2017, he went from skincare savant to taking over his companies Instagram account, with daily disturbing messages, he fired staff via social media, accused his fellow shareholders of financial impropriety, was arrested outside the British Pm’s house, and was sanctioned in the Uk and then taken to court in a bitter court battle which saw him ousted from his own company.</description></item><item><title>Another Perspective | The Garden of Eden</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521750012/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521750012/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you have a question about the podcast or Eden’s case, please email: whathappenedtoeden@gmail.com
In this episode we get another perspective on a few questions that have been raised during the podcast, we reach out to police and the mayor of St Helens for comment and address some of the recent media coverage on Eden’s case and the podcast.
In our next episode we hope to bring you response for the Tasmanian Police and will try to answer any questions sent to us about the podcast to whathappenedtoeden@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Two New Witnesses And Another Cops Opinion | The Garden of Eden</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521750013/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521750013/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, we speak with two new witnesses who shed more light on the days before and after Eden was found.
We also get another detective's view on the sorts of things that should be done in a case like this.
You can now watch shorts from each episode here https://bit.ly/3KrQ3s6
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>This Town Hates US | The Garden of Eden</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521750014/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521750014/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Peter has a run-in with the police, and two new witnesses come forward. and there's hope that someone might take more action to find out what really happened to Eden You can now watch shorts from each episode here https://bit.ly/3KrQ3s6
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Whistleblower | The Garden of Eden</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521750015/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521750015/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, a person comes forward to the Westbrooks to corroborate what others have told them.
It's new evidence that has not been heard before.
Lavac, the pro bono barrister, sits down with the new witnesses to gain more information.
You can now watch shorts from each episode here https://bit.ly/3KrQ3s6
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We Just Want Answers | The Garden of Eden</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521750016/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 22:30:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521750016/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Jason and Amanda question the investigation into Eden's death. They share their thoughts on what should have happened and what they want next. You can now watch shorts from each episode here https://bit.ly/3KrQ3s6
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Pro-Bono Barrister | The Garden of Eden</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521750017/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 19:42:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521750017/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode we find out how Peter Lavac met the Westbrook family and why he felt compelled to help find the answer to what really happened to Eden. You can now watch shorts from each episode here https://bit.ly/3KrQ3s6
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Missing CCTV | The Garden of Eden</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521750018/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521750018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the past 8 years, the sad story of Eden Westbrook's death and the new discoveries made by the family have left some unanswered questions.
In this episode, there's more about the missing CCTV, what happened to Eden's phone, and some dark theories that haven’t been explored. You can now watch shorts from each episode here https://bit.ly/3KrQ3s6
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Mystery Girl | The Garden of Eden</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521750019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521750019/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, the community of St. Helens hears about Eden’s shocking death. In the days after, a family is left shattered, a mystery girl is talked about as being the last person to see Eden that night. You can now watch shorts from each episode here https://bit.ly/3KrQ3s6
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cut her Down, NOW! | The Garden of Eden</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521750020/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 20:45:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521750020/</guid><description>Podcast Description 15-year-old Eden left home after a minor argument with her parents. What happened next is every parent's worst nightmare: she is found dead, but then the 8-year journey to find answers begins. What really happened to Eden Westbrook? You can now watch shorts from each epsiode here https://bit.ly/3KrQ3s6
Content warning: This podcast contains graphic descriptions of suicide and suicidal ideation; listener discretion is strongly advised.
If you or someone around need to talk, call lifeline 24 hours on 13 11 14</description></item><item><title>Our Little Edey | The Garden of Eden</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521750021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521750021/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this first episode meet Eden’s Mum and Dad, Jason and Amanda. Hear about their quiet humble life and the moments before their daughter Eden was found dead in their peaceful seaside town.
You can now watch shorts from each episode here https://bit.ly/3KrQ3s6
Content warning - This podcast contains graphic descriptions of suicide and suicidal ideation; listener discretion is strongly advised.
If you or someone around need to talk, call lifeline 24 hours on 13 11 14</description></item><item><title>Introducing -The Garden of Eden | The Garden of Eden</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521750022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 03:33:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521750022/</guid><description>Podcast Description ******CONTENT WARNING *******
This podcast refences suicide and suicidal ideation
Listener discretion is advised
Contacts for mental health and crisis support can be found here https://findahelpline.com
15-year-old Eden Westbrook, lived in a small seaside town in Tasmania.
One night after a minor disagreement with her family she left home. The next morning, she was found dead hanging from a tree on the main road into the town. The family don’t believe she took her own life.</description></item></channel></rss>