<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Riddler: Secrets in the Dark on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-riddler-secrets-in-the-dark/</link><description>Recent content in The Riddler: Secrets in the Dark on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-riddler-secrets-in-the-dark/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>01. The King of Arkham Asylum | The Riddler: Secrets in the Dark</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2084760002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2084760002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Edward Nygma, alias The Riddler, learns that his friend the Calendar Man has been murdered. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>02. Make it Make Sense | The Riddler: Secrets in the Dark</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2084760003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2084760003/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Riddler vows to stop Calendar Man&amp;rsquo;s killer, and all signs point to the Caped Crusader himself. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>03. Angel of Justice | The Riddler: Secrets in the Dark</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2084760004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2084760004/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Riddler&amp;rsquo;s investigation uncovers a conspiracy that forces him to form an unexpected alliance. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>04. Sewers and Socialites | The Riddler: Secrets in the Dark</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2084760005/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2084760005/</guid><description>Podcast Description After piecing together The Messenger&amp;rsquo;s trail of corpses and clues in the sewers of Gotham City, The Riddler crashes a fundraising gala and runs into an important person from his painful past. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>05. Family History | The Riddler: Secrets in the Dark</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2084760006/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2084760006/</guid><description>Podcast Description To save the life of a friend, Edward Nygma must reflect on his own early life and the circumstances that led him to become The Riddler. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>06. Make Your Choice | The Riddler: Secrets in the Dark</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2084760007/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2084760007/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a slight detour, The Riddler finds himself in grave danger at the Heed Estate. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>07. A Head Full of Riddles | The Riddler: Secrets in the Dark</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2084760008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2084760008/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Riddler and Batman risk everything to end The Messenger&amp;rsquo;s apocalyptic crusade. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>08. The Final Retribution | The Riddler: Secrets in the Dark</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2084760009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2084760009/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Riddler discovers a secret that calls everything he thought he knew into question. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hasan Minhaj Introduces The Riddler: Secrets in the Dark | The Riddler: Secrets in the Dark</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2084760010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2084760010/</guid><description>Podcast Description A masked vigilante is on the loose, murdering notorious super-villains all over Gotham City… and all clues point to the suspect being the Caped Crusader himself, Batman. Now, with a target on his head, the charming yet deadly Edward Nygma, better known as The Riddler, is forced to break out of Arkham Asylum and team up with the Caped Crusader. The unlikely duo must solve the mystery before they too, become victims.</description></item><item><title>Introducing The Riddler: Secrets in the Dark | The Riddler: Secrets in the Dark</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2084760001/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2084760001/</guid><description>Podcast Description A masked vigilante is on the loose, murdering notorious super-villains all over Gotham City… and all clues point to the suspect being the Caped Crusader himself, Batman (Colman Domingo). Now, with a target on his head, the charming yet deadly Edward Nygma, better known as The Riddler (Hasan Minhaj), is forced to break out of Arkham Asylum and team up with the Caped Crusader. The unlikely duo must solve the mystery before they too, become victims.</description></item></channel></rss>