<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Time to Walk on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/categories/time-to-walk/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Time to Walk on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/categories/time-to-walk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Time to Walk - Time to Walk with Carmelo Anthony</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000400030/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000400030/</guid>
        <description>Carmelo Anthony: Well, walking, for me, is a opportunity for me to kind of recenter myself, re-focus, observe, think, take some me time. I take walks at night by myself. People always say, &amp;ldquo;Why you… Why you always walking?&amp;rdquo; But that&amp;rsquo;s my time to kind of reflect on the day or reflect on the day that&amp;rsquo;s ahead of me and just think.
​
[INTRO MUSIC]
​
Sam Sanchez: It&amp;rsquo;s Time to Walk, where some of the world&amp;rsquo;s most interesting and inspiring people share stories, photos, and songs that have influenced their lives.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Time to Walk - Time to Walk with Gabrielle Union</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000400029/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000400029/</guid>
        <description>Gabrielle Union: Depending on what&amp;rsquo;s happening that day, sometimes I need a walk to find clarity. There&amp;rsquo;s challenges that we face that you just can&amp;rsquo;t quite figure out the right approach or the right answer, or you know d*** well what the answer is, but you got to make peace with it. And, for me, fitness, walking, just moving every day in some kind of meaningful way brings me peace.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Time to Walk - Time to Walk with Naomi Campbell</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000400028/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000400028/</guid>
        <description>Naomi Campbell: I so appreciate walking now, especially since this past year. I remember last year when I came out to Los Angeles after not going past my door for three and half months in New York, just to put my feet on the grass, I cried. It was just like we take that for granted, don&amp;rsquo;t we?
​
Like, I feel like the whole world is going to just appreciate trees, air, oxygen, much more than they ever have before.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Time to Walk - Time to Walk with Michaela Jaé Rodriguez</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000400027/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000400027/</guid>
        <description>Mj Rodriguez: A walk to me means taking all the time that you need to center your mind, free all of your inhibitions and just make sure you focus on the thing that&amp;rsquo;s most important to you, which is your body, and aligning your body. I used to walk from 31st Street all the way to 151st Street simply because I just loved to walk. It helped me get through the day.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Time to Walk - Time to Walk with Kurt Fearnley</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000400026/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000400026/</guid>
        <description>Kurt Fearnley: When I go out and take a push, it&amp;rsquo;s like going for a walk. You know, I&amp;rsquo;m in my day chair right now. The day chair is a separate wheelchair. It&amp;rsquo;s the thing that you think of as your walking legs. And for somebody that&amp;rsquo;s never been in a chair, it&amp;rsquo;s just a stroll. It&amp;rsquo;s out here to enjoy the environment, to look around and just have a moment to yourself.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Time to Walk - Time to Walk with Greg Louganis</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000400025/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000400025/</guid>
        <description>Greg Louganis: When I start getting down and I don&amp;rsquo;t feel quite right, then the most important thing… get outside, go for a walk. It really changes your body chemistry just to get out into nature and also out of your head so you&amp;rsquo;re not so caught up in thinking the same thoughts over and over again.
​
[INTRO MUSIC]
​
Sam Sanchez: It&amp;rsquo;s Time to Walk, where some of the world&amp;rsquo;s most interesting and inspiring people share stories, photos, and songs that have influenced their lives.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Time to Walk - Time to Walk with Brandi Chastain</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000400024/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000400024/</guid>
        <description>Brandi Chastain: I love a great walk. For me, a walk is allowing me to let my shoulders fall down, to take a deep breath, being open. There&amp;rsquo;s a freedom to a walk.
​
[INTRO MUSIC]
​
Sam Sanchez: It’s Time to Walk, where some of the world&amp;rsquo;s most interesting and inspiring people share stories, photos, and songs that have influenced their lives.
​
As part of a series on World Class Athletes, this episode features soccer champion and two-time Olympic gold medalist, Brandi Chastain, who played for the U.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Time to Walk - Time to Walk with Anthony Joshua</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000400023/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000400023/</guid>
        <description>Anthony Joshua: Walking is, in a way, a ritual thing. Before a fight or after I&amp;rsquo;ve completed a tough training camp, it&amp;rsquo;s like a, whew, sense of relief. I walk for therapeutic reasons. I walk to reconnect with my ancestors. It’s the way my ancestors used to get around and move their legs before horses and cars. So walks, for me, brilliant. I love them especially now we&amp;rsquo;ve got some got some good weather in London.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Time to Walk - Time to Walk with Joan Benoit Samuelson</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000400022/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000400022/</guid>
        <description>Joan Benoit Samuelson: Well, a walk for me is really downtime, and I know that when I go for a walk with friends, I&amp;rsquo;m sometimes slowing them down because I… I tend to walk slowly. And I don&amp;rsquo;t know if it&amp;rsquo;s because I&amp;rsquo;m taking everything in or because I do so much running that it&amp;rsquo;s nice to change the speed by a huge measure.
​
And it&amp;rsquo;s my opportunity to commune with nature.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Time to Walk - Time to Walk with Randall Park</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000400021/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000400021/</guid>
        <description>Randall Park: Walking is, for me, just this wonderful gift.
​
During the pandemic, I actually, for the first time in my life, experienced panic attacks. They were really jarring and scary for me. I started incorporating long walks into my life. They really make me feel more relaxed, more in touch with the Earth and the world. And it&amp;rsquo;s something that we all take for granted, including myself, far too often.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Time to Walk - Time to Walk with Dr. Sanjay Gupta</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000400020/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000400020/</guid>
        <description>Dr. Sanjay Gupta: Walking, for me, represents, first of all, just the chance to feel like I have some control. I live a really busy life, and I think when you feel like you can go take a walk, it kind of… it sends a message, I think, to my whole way of thinking that I&amp;rsquo;ve regained some control. I can go for this walk. So I love that part of it.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Time to Walk - Time to Walk with Gina Rodriguez</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000400019/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000400019/</guid>
        <description>Gina Rodriguez: Walking has always been an opportunity to just go through my thoughts, work out problems and just kind of let it go away with the wind, you know, leave it on that walk. It&amp;rsquo;s kind of a release, a moment to reflect but then also to let go. I think both are so important. I need this time to just, like, listen and to be present and to remember how blessed you are to walk, to breathe, to take another day.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Time to Walk - Season 1 Highlights</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000400018/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000400018/</guid>
        <description>[INTRO MUSIC]
​
Sam Sanchez: It’s Time To Walk, where some of the world’s most interesting and inspiring people share stories, photos, and songs that have influenced their lives. In Season One of Time to Walk, we’ve heard from special guests that include activists, actors, musicians, a race car driver, and even a ballet dancer. This special episode is a collection of favorite moments so far. It includes inspiring life lessons, words of wisdom, and thought-provoking ideas.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Time to Walk - Time to Walk with Nick Jonas</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000400017/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000400017/</guid>
        <description>Nick Jonas: When I was a kid I used to love walking with my dad. We lived at this little brick house in Wyckoff, New Jersey, two doors down from the church that my dad was the pastor at. And there was this back pathway through the woods that neighbored a cemetery. The cemetery was kind of frightening to me, but the time spent with my father walking down this back path, talking about life and music and creativity were some of my favorite memories growing up.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Time to Walk - Time to Walk with Jane Fonda</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000400016/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000400016/</guid>
        <description>Jane Fonda: I&amp;rsquo;ve always loved walking mostly because I&amp;rsquo;ve always loved exploring. I&amp;rsquo;ve always loved nature. My favorite place to walk is in the depths of a deep, dark forest because I become very conscious of layers of time and of life.
​
[INTRO MUSIC]
​
Sam Sanchez: It&amp;rsquo;s Time To Walk, where some of the world’s most interesting and inspiring people share stories, photos, and songs that have influenced their lives.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Time to Walk - Time to Walk with Jon M. Chu</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000400015/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000400015/</guid>
        <description>Jon M. Chu: Walking always grounds me. There&amp;rsquo;s a certain sound of the gravel, of the grass, of the leaves blowing and the rustling of the trees, and you can hear birds scatter in the bushes or lizards run across. And to me, those are the, the reminders that you&amp;rsquo;re not alone, that there is a planet and lives all around you and that you are one piece of this.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Time to Walk - Time to Walk with Wanda Sykes</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000400014/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000400014/</guid>
        <description>Wanda Sykes: Oh, I love going for walks. Not just good exercise for you, but I get a chance to catch up with my friends. You know, I love walking with my wife. I like the companionship, is what I really like. So I&amp;rsquo;m glad I have you guys here to talk to, and I guess you enjoy companionship, too, because that&amp;rsquo;s why you&amp;rsquo;re listening to me run my yap.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Time to Walk - Time to Walk with Malcolm Gladwell</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000400013/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000400013/</guid>
        <description>Malcolm Gladwell: My father was a walker, and he would come home every night from work and go for an hour or more, and he would also walk to church every Sunday. And as soon as I was old enough to walk with him, I walked every Sunday morning, just me and my father. I think it was probably three miles and then three miles home. He would never slow down for me.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Time to Walk - Time to Walk with Kesha</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000400012/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000400012/</guid>
        <description>KESHA: I like going for a walk to get myself out of my head.
​
I also just have started walking around my neighborhood and found little cool, old houses from the &amp;rsquo;40s I never noticed before. One woman has a rose garden, and we started talking, and now I go visit her and her roses every day. So it&amp;rsquo;s a way of connecting with my community, too. Just any time I can shake up the energy, I think it&amp;rsquo;s positive for me.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Time to Walk - Time to Walk with Anthony Ramos</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000400011/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000400011/</guid>
        <description>Anthony Ramos: You know, I love walking because I think there’s a, there&amp;rsquo;s a freedom… The body’s moving, your mind is flowing and you’re just allowing yourself to go wherever your mind and your body wants to go, without you putting any stipulations or restrictions on it.
​
That’s what’s kind of dope about just getting your body moving.
​
[INTRO MUSIC]
​
Sam Sanchez: It&amp;rsquo;s Time To Walk, where some of the world’s most interesting and inspiring people share stories, photos and songs that have influenced their lives.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Time to Walk - Time to Walk with Min Jin Lee</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000400010/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000400010/</guid>
        <description>Min Jin Lee: Any day in which I walk outside the house is a victory because I think I&amp;rsquo;m slightly agoraphobic, and, also, I really like sitting. So I think I&amp;rsquo;m really proud of myself when I put on walking shoes and get off the sofa. That&amp;rsquo;s major.
​
[INTRO MUSIC]
​
Sam Sanchez: It’s Time to Walk, where some of the world’s most interesting and inspiring people share stories, photos and songs that have influenced their lives.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Time to Walk - Time to Walk with Anderson Cooper</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000400009/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000400009/</guid>
        <description>Sam Sanchez: This episode has a brief mention of a sensitive topic.
​
Anderson Cooper: I love to go for walks, especially in New York, because it’s meditative for me. I&amp;rsquo;ve spent a lot of my life just kind of rushing from one place to another and trying to get to a story, trying to get to a country where something is happening. And when I&amp;rsquo;m there, I&amp;rsquo;m focused on working and crafting a story and, and writing something that does justice to, to the events that are unfolding all around me.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Time to Walk - Time to Walk with Misty Copeland</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000400008/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000400008/</guid>
        <description>Misty Copeland: Walking has always been a way for me to escape, kind of breaking away from that, that structure that I&amp;rsquo;m so used to, which is in a box covered with mirrors, the ballet studio. And movement is always an escape for me, and walking is kind of a more subtle dance form.
​
[INTRO MUSIC]
​
Sam Sanchez: It&amp;rsquo;s Time to Walk, where some of the world&amp;rsquo;s most interesting and inspiring people share stories, photos, and songs that have influenced their lives.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Time to Walk - Time to Walk with Bubba Wallace</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000400007/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000400007/</guid>
        <description>Bubba Wallace: Being outside, you know, it&amp;rsquo;s the exact opposite of… of what I do in my, I guess, normal career life, going fast, turning left, turning right, whatever it may be. And being outside is slowing down, looking all around, enjoying the sights, enjoying the sounds.
​
[INTRO MUSIC]
​
Sam Sanchez: It&amp;rsquo;s Time To Walk, where some of the world’s most interesting and inspiring people share stories, photos, and songs that have influenced their lives.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Time to Walk - Time to Walk with Ruby Bridges</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000400006/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000400006/</guid>
        <description>Ruby Bridges: I love to walk. I like being out in nature. My granddaughter always says, &amp;ldquo;Mami&amp;rdquo;—she calls me Mami—&amp;ldquo;Mami, whenever you are really upset, things are bothering you, you should get out. Go to the park, and if you can, take your shoes off so you can feel the grass.&amp;rdquo; And she&amp;rsquo;s right. It just calms my spirit.
​
[INTRO MUSIC]
​
Sam Sanchez: It&amp;rsquo;s Time To Walk, where some of the world’s most interesting and inspiring people share stories, photos and songs that have influenced their lives.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Time to Walk - Time to Walk with Ibram X. Kendi</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000400005/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000400005/</guid>
        <description>Ibram X. Kendi: When I go for a walk, I think of it as a time in which I can think and I can figure out how to solve problems, whether it&amp;rsquo;s the problems of our time or problems that I&amp;rsquo;m facing within my own life. Going for a walk is a time to be still, it&amp;rsquo;s a time to really just be one with yourself. And in many ways, our lives are on overdrive, and there are times in which we really need to settle ourselves and focus ourselves and certainly when we go for a walk, we&amp;rsquo;re able to do that.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Time to Walk - Time to Walk with Shawn Mendes</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000400004/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000400004/</guid>
        <description>Shawn Mendes: I think we just forget how easy mindfulness is and the practice of it is because there&amp;rsquo;s so many books and meditations and things you can do to kind of calm your body and calm your soul. But like one of the original, legendary things to do to calm down is go for a walk.
​
[INTRO MUSIC]
​
Sam Sanchez: It&amp;rsquo;s Time To Walk, where some of the world’s most interesting and inspiring people share stories, photos and songs that have influenced their lives.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Time to Walk - Time to Walk with Uzo Aduba</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000400003/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000400003/</guid>
        <description>Uzo Aduba: I love to walk, and when I first moved to New York I didn&amp;rsquo;t always have the money for the subway fare and would walk from the city home to Queens from my waiting job. But then it really became this private, personal opportunity to talk through with myself some of the conversations I didn&amp;rsquo;t have time to have during the busy day. And so what I would find is that, at the end of my walks, I would usually have the answers to a lot of the questions or decisions that I was trying to make.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Time to Walk - Time to Walk with Draymond Green</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000400002/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000400002/</guid>
        <description>Draymond Green: I try to go on a walk maybe once every couple weeks.
​
It&amp;rsquo;s your time to lose yourself in nature, free your thoughts, take all the great things that this world has to offer in and just breathe and kind of let everything out. All the daily stresses that we all go through, just go on your walk and kind of let them all out.
​
[INTRO MUSIC]</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Time to Walk - Time to Walk with Dolly Parton</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000400001/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000400001/</guid>
        <description>Dolly Parton: I think everybody loves to walk. You think good when you walk. I write a lot of songs when I walk, think about a lot of stories. And I’m gonna share them with you.
​
[INTRO MUSIC]
​
Sam Sanchez: It&amp;rsquo;s Time to Walk, where some of the world&amp;rsquo;s most interesting and inspiring people share stories, photos, and songs that have influenced their lives. Dolly Parton is much more than a country music superstar.</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
