<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Serial on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/serial/</link><description>Recent content in Serial on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 11:15:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/serial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Kids of Rutherford County - Ep. 4: Dedicated Public Servants | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 11:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140001/</guid><description>Podcast Description The lawyers settle with the county, which agrees to pay the kids who were wrongfully arrested and illegally jailed; the hard part is actually getting the kids paid.
From Serial Productions and The New York Times in partnership with ProPublica and Nashville Public Radio, “The Kids of Rutherford County” is reported and hosted by Meribah Knight, a Peabody-award winning reporter based in the South.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Kids of Rutherford County - Ep. 3: Would You Like to Sue the Government? | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 11:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wes Clark reads a telling line in a police report about how Rutherford County’s juvenile justice system really works. He and his law partner Mark Downton realize they have a massive class action on their hands.
From Serial Productions and The New York Times in partnership with ProPublica and Nashville Public Radio, “The Kids of Rutherford County” is reported and hosted by Meribah Knight, a Peabody-award winning reporter based in the South.</description></item><item><title>The Kids of Rutherford County - Ep. 2: What the Hell Are You People Doing? | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140003/</guid><description>Podcast Description A young lawyer named Wes Clark can’t get the Rutherford County juvenile court to let his clients out of detention — even when the law says they shouldn’t have been held in the first place. He’s frustrated and demoralized, until he makes a friend.
From Serial Productions and The New York Times in partnership with ProPublica and Nashville Public Radio, “The Kids of Rutherford County” is reported and hosted by Meribah Knight, a Peabody-award winning reporter based in the South.</description></item><item><title>The Kids of Rutherford County - Ep. 1: The Egregious Video | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140004/</guid><description>Podcast Description A police officer in Rutherford County, Tenn., sees a video of little kids fighting, and decides to investigate. This leads to the arrest of 11 kids for watching the fight. The arrests do not go smoothly.
From Serial Productions and The New York Times in partnership with ProPublica and Nashville Public Radio, “The Kids of Rutherford County” is reported and hosted by Meribah Knight, a Peabody-award winning reporter based in the South.</description></item><item><title>The Kids of Rutherford County - Trailer | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140005/</guid><description>Podcast Description For over a decade, one Tennessee county arrested and illegally jailed hundreds, maybe thousands, of children. A four-part narrative series reveals how this came to be, the adults responsible for it, and the two lawyers, former juvenile delinquents themselves, who try to do something about it.
From Serial Productions and The New York Times, “The Kids of Rutherford County” is reported and hosted by Meribah Knight, a Peabody-award winning reporter based in the South.</description></item><item><title>The Retrievals - Ep. 5: The Outcomes | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140006/</guid><description>Podcast Description In fertility treatment, a successful outcome is defined as a healthy baby. In this story, the outcomes are complicated for everyone involved.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Retrievals - Ep. 4: The Clinic | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 10:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140007/</guid><description>Podcast Description What we know about what happened at the clinic.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Retrievals - Ep. 3: The Sentence | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140008/</guid><description>Podcast Description At the nurse’s sentencing hearing, the patients learn a shocking detail that forces them to confront the limits of their compassion.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Retrievals - Ep. 2: The Nurse | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140009/</guid><description>Podcast Description The patients know what happened to them. Now they learn who did it. The story of the nurse whose own pain was also unseen.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Retrievals - Ep. 1: The Patients | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Patients at a fertility clinic experience excruciating, unexpected pain. For months the reason for that pain remains hidden. Then they get a letter from the clinic.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Retrievals - Trailer | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140011/</guid><description>Podcast Description The patients in this story came to the Yale Fertility Center to pursue pregnancy. They began their I.V.F. cycles full of expectation and hope. Then a surgical procedure called egg retrieval caused them excruciating pain.
Some of the patients screamed out in the procedure room. Others called the clinic from home to report pain in the hours that followed. But most of the staff members who fielded the patients’ reports did not know the real reason for the pain, which was that a nurse at the clinic was stealing fentanyl, and replacing it with saline.</description></item><item><title>The Coldest Case In Laramie - Episode 8 | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kim interviews Fred Lamb and takes a fresh look at the case.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Coldest Case In Laramie - Episode 7 | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kim takes stock of the evidence against Fred Lamb and gets to the bottom of the stories she’s heard about him — including one from his wife of more than 30 years.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Coldest Case In Laramie - Episode 6 | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140014/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 09:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kim examines the bizarre interrogation that led to Fred Lamb’s arrest.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Coldest Case In Laramie - Episode 5 | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 09:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kim talks to someone who confessed to Shelli’s murder from a jail in Arizona.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Coldest Case In Laramie - Episode 4 | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 09:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kim digs into the early stages of the investigation into Shelli’s murder and follows up with old suspects.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Coldest Case In Laramie - Episode 3 | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 09:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kim heads to Laramie and hears two very different versions of the case against Fred Lamb.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Coldest Case In Laramie - Episode 2 | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140018/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 09:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kim talks to Shelli’s former roommate, who connects Kim with a man who was at the crime scene and has troubling memories about Fred Lamb and the police.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Coldest Case In Laramie - Episode 1 | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140019/</guid><description>Podcast Description A Times investigative reporter, Kim Barker, revisits the murder of Shelli Wiley — a long-unsolved case from Kim’s time in high school. She reaches out to Shelli’s family to understand why the police arrested a man named Fred Lamb for Shelli’s murder in 2016, and why prosecutors abruptly dropped the charges against him.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Coldest Case In Laramie - Trailer | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kim Barker, a Pulitzer Prize-winning investigative reporter for The New York Times, revisits an unsolved murder that took place while she was in high school in Laramie, Wyoming, nearly 40 years ago. She confronts the conflicting stories people have told themselves about the crime because of an unexpected development: the arrest of a former Laramie police officer accused in the murder. All eight episodes of &amp;ldquo;The Coldest Case in Laramie,&amp;rdquo; a new show from Serial Productions and The New York Times, are available on Thursday, February 23rd wherever you get your podcasts.</description></item><item><title>We Were Three - Ep. 3: I Am All That Is Left. Amen. | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 06:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rachel goes back to California, to the place where she grew up and where her brother and father died, to find answers.
For more information on &amp;lsquo;We Were Three&amp;rsquo;: https://www.nytimes.com/2022/10/11/podcasts/we-were-three.html
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We Were Three - Ep. 2: Assassin | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rachel retraces how her family, over decades, fell apart and came back together.
For more information on &amp;lsquo;We Were Three&amp;rsquo;: https://www.nytimes.com/2022/10/11/podcasts/we-were-three.html
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We Were Three - Ep. 1: Black Box | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rachel goes back to California, to the place where she grew up and where her brother and father died, to find answers.
For more information on &amp;lsquo;We Were Three&amp;rsquo;: https://www.nytimes.com/2022/10/11/podcasts/we-were-three.html
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We Were Three - Trailer | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140024/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 05:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140024/</guid><description>Podcast Description A three-part series from This American Life producer Nancy Updike. When Rachel McKibbens’s father and brother died suddenly last fall, two weeks apart, from Covid, she’d had no idea her father was sick, and no idea her brother was dying. They were unvaccinated, but the story of what happened started long before that. All three episodes of &amp;ldquo;We Were Three,&amp;rdquo; a new show from Serial Productions and The New York Times, are available now wherever you get your podcasts.</description></item><item><title>The Trojan Horse Affair - Part 8 | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140025/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140025/</guid><description>Podcast Description A man banned from working in education in the aftermath of the Trojan Horse letter inspires Brian and Hamza to track down one last witness with him – in Australia. And all three travelers find their faith tested.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Trojan Horse Affair - Part 7 | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140026/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Birmingham authorities struggle to explain why they disavowed their own findings about the Trojan Horse plot. But when Brian and Hamza make a discovery deep inside some court documents, everything suddenly makes sense.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Trojan Horse Affair - Part 6 | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140027/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 09:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamza takes a long, hard look at what the government found when it investigated more than 20 majority-Muslim schools in Birmingham. And our two reporters have a confrontation – with each other.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Trojan Horse Affair - Part 5 | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140028/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 09:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamza and Brian learn that the Trojan Horse letter wasn’t the only unsigned letter alleging an extremist operation was afoot in Birmingham. An interview with a couple who lodged complaints against their school starts out cordially, but six hours later, the atmosphere is so tense that not even an offer of tea can smooth things over. And Hamza stops pretending he’s not angry about what he’s hearing.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Trojan Horse Affair - Part 4 | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140029/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 09:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140029/</guid><description>Podcast Description A series of frustrating interviews with Birmingham politicians leaves Brian and Hamza wondering if crucial information about the Trojan Horse letter was kept from officials in London. Then one rainy Friday afternoon, Brian hears back from a government source who wants to meet right away.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Trojan Horse Affair - Part 3 | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140030/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 09:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140030/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a state of surprise, Hamza and Brian leave a meeting with the man the Trojan Horse letter was first sent to. And they learn about an internal investigation report that local officials have kept hidden, but which they think could contain a bombshell.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Trojan Horse Affair - Part 2 | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140031/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 09:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamza and Brian think the source of the Trojan Horse letter might be hiding in plain sight. After learning about the petty personnel dispute that probably gave rise to the letter, they’re even more bewildered about how it ever could have been taken seriously.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Trojan Horse Affair - Part 1 | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140032/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140032/</guid><description>Podcast Description A strange letter appears outlining a plot by Islamic extremists to infiltrate Birmingham schools. Hamza and Brian visit the supposed mastermind of the plot, and he tells them he did take over a bunch of schools – just not for the reasons in the letter.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Trojan Horse Affair - Trailer | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140033/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140033/</guid><description>Podcast Description A mysterious letter detailing a supposed Islamist plot to take over schools shocked Britain in 2014. But who wrote it? From Serial Productions and The New York Times, “The Trojan Horse Affair,” an investigation that became bigger than we ever imagined. All eight parts are available now, wherever you get your podcasts. Search &amp;ldquo;The Trojan Horse Affair.&amp;rdquo;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Improvement Association - Ep. 5: ‘Democrat, Republican, White, Black, Green’ | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140034/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 10:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140034/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Improvement Association PAC’s power in the county is threatened when an unlikely candidate enters the race for county commissioner. Plenty of people outside the PAC now have their own ideas about how to build Black political power here. Zoe examines what this election could mean for the PAC’s future.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Improvement Association - Ep. 4: ‘Let Them Pull the Red Wagon’ | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140035/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 10:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140035/</guid><description>Podcast Description With the PAC’s reputation suffering because of years of cheating accusations and resentment stirring within its ranks, a prominent member turns against the leadership. Nevertheless, Horace and his closest allies make a bold move by supporting a political upset at the center of the county.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Improvement Association - Ep. 3: ‘The Ballad of the Nursing Home Ballots’ | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140036/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 10:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Zoe delves into one of the most serious allegations against the Bladen Improvement PAC: an accusation about stealing votes from vulnerable people that goes back 10 years. In trying to track down the veracity of this particularly persistent rumor, she comes to understand how and why election cheating allegations are so sticky.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Improvement Association - Ep. 2: ‘Where Is Your Choice?’ | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140037/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 10:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Zoe talks to people in the county who believe the Bladen Improvement PAC has been cheating for years. She tries to get beyond the rumors and into specifics, and comes face to face with the intense suspicion and scrutiny leveled against the organization. In the middle of another election, Zoe goes out with members of the PAC to watch how they operate and try to make sense of all these allegations against them.</description></item><item><title>The Improvement Association - Ep. 1: ‘The Big Shadoo’ | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140038/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 10:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Following a notorious case of election fraud in Bladen County, North Carolina, in 2018, the reporter Zoe Chace gets an invitation from Horace Munn, the leader of the Bladen County Improvement Association PAC, a Black political advocacy group whose name was dragged into the scandal. Horace asks Zoe to come down and investigate for herself and find out who is really cheating.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Improvement Association - Trailer | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140039/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Listen to the trailer for our newest show, &amp;ldquo;The Improvement Association.&amp;rdquo; From Serial Productions and The New York Times, hosted by Zoe Chace.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nice White Parents - Ep. 5: ‘We Know It When We See It’ | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140040/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140040/</guid><description>Podcast Description An unexpected last chapter. Some white parents start behaving differently.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nice White Parents - Ep. 4: ‘Here’s Another Fun Thing You Can Do’ | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140041/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 08:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is it possible to limit the power of white parents?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nice White Parents - Ep. 3: ‘This Is Our School, How Dare You?’ | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140042/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 08:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140042/</guid><description>Podcast Description We saw what happens when white families come into the school. What happens when they stay out?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nice White Parents - Ep. 2: ‘I Still Believe in It’ | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140043/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 08:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140043/</guid><description>Podcast Description White parents in the 1960s fought to be part of a new, racially integrated school. Where’d they go?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nice White Parents - Ep. 1: The Book of Statuses | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140044/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 08:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140044/</guid><description>Podcast Description A group of parents take one big step together.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S-Town - Chapter VII | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140045/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140045/</guid><description>Podcast Description “You’re beginning to figure it out now, aren’t you?”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S-Town - Chapter VI | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140046/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 10:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140046/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Since everyone around here thinks I’m a queer anyway.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S-Town - Chapter V | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140047/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140047/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Nobody’ll ever change my mind about it.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S-Town - Chapter IV | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140048/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 10:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140048/</guid><description>Podcast Description “If anybody could find it, it would be me.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S-Town - Chapter III | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140049/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140049/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Tedious and brief.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S-Town - Chapter II | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140050/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140050/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Has anybody called you?”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S-Town - Chapter I | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140051/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140051/</guid><description>Podcast Description “If you keep your mouth shut, you’ll be surprised what you can learn.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial S03 - Ep. 9: Some Time When Everything Has Changed | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140052/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140052/</guid><description>Podcast Description The state of Ohio decides where Joshua belongs.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial S03 - Ep. 8: A Madman’s Vacation | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140053/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140053/</guid><description>Podcast Description A teenager decides to cooperate.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial S03 - Ep. 7: The Snowball Effect | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140054/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140054/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you listen closely to the trash-talking, you start to get the message.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial S03 - Ep. 6: You in the Red Shirt | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140055/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Life after you put a cop in jail.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial S03 - Ep. 5: Pleas Baby Pleas | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140056/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Don’t tell the judges, but the prosecutors have the most power in the building.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial S03 - Ep. 4: A Bird in Jail Is Worth Two on the Street | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140057/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140057/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happens when the right evidence points to the wrong man?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial S03 - Ep. 3: Misdemeanor, Meet Mr. Lawsuit | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140058/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140058/</guid><description>Podcast Description The smell of raw marijuana + acting nervous + hands in pockets = ?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial S03 - Ep. 2: You’ve Got Some Gauls | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140059/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140059/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a judge believes he knows you better than you know yourself.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial S03 - Ep. 1: A Bar Fight Walks into the Justice Center | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140060/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 09:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140060/</guid><description>Podcast Description A young woman at a bar is slapped on the butt. So why’s she the one in jail?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial S02 - Ep. 11: Present for Duty | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140061/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140061/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Season Two finale: What is Bowe’s fault, and what isn’t?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial S02 - Ep. 10: Thorny Politics | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140062/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you hearing what I’m hearing?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial S02 - Ep. 9: Trade Secrets | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140063/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2016 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140063/</guid><description>Podcast Description You don’t make peace with your friends.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial S02 - Ep. 8: Hindsight, Part 2 | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140064/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Woulda, coulda, shoulda…
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial S02 - Ep. 7: Hindsight, Part 1 | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140065/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140065/</guid><description>Podcast Description It makes sense if you’re Bowe Bergdahl.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial S02 - Ep. 6: 5 O’Clock Shadow | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140066/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2016 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why did Bowe Bergdahl walk off?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial S02 - Ep. 5: Meanwhile, in Tampa | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140067/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140067/</guid><description>Podcast Description CIA, FBI, YouTube, the Portland PD? There was no handbook for getting Bergdahl back.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial S02 - Ep. 4: The Captors | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140068/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2016 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140068/</guid><description>Podcast Description What&amp;rsquo;s happening on the other side of the door?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial S02 - Ep. 3: Escaping | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140069/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2015 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bergdahl’s first year in captivity starts with an escape and ends with an escape. In between, he learns necessary, twisted lessons of survival.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial S02 - Ep. 2: The Golden Chicken | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140070/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140070/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the move with Bergdahl, the Taliban slip past the U.S. Army’s massive effort to find him. During those days and weeks, each side is asking, what is Bergdahl worth to us?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial S02 - Ep. 1: DUSTWUN | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140071/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2015 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140071/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the middle of the night, Pfc. Bowe Bergdahl grabs a notebook, snacks, water, some cash. Then he quietly slips off a remote U.S. Army outpost in eastern Afghanistan and into the dark, open desert. About 20 minutes later, it occurs to him: he’s in over his head.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial S01 Ep. 13: Adnan Is Out | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140072/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2014 10:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140072/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s Baltimore, 2022. Adnan Syed has spent the last 23 years incarcerated, serving a life sentence for the murder of Hae Min Lee, a crime he says he didn’t commit. He has exhausted every legal avenue for relief, including a petition to the United States Supreme Court. But then, a prosecutor in the Baltimore State’s Attorney’s office stumbled upon two handwritten notes in Adnan’s case file, and that changes everything.</description></item><item><title>Serial S01 Update 3: Day 03, Adnan Syed’s Hearing | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140073/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2014 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140073/</guid><description>Podcast Description February 2016: Sarah Koenig ducks back into the Adnan Syed case for a few days. There’s a hearing in Baltimore—a court proceeding that’s been nearly sixteen years in the making. Syed’s attorney will introduce new evidence, and present a case for why his conviction should be overturned. Sarah and producer Dana Chivvis will discuss what happens, day by day.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial S01 Update 2: Day 02, Adnan Syed’s Hearing | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140074/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2014 10:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140074/</guid><description>Podcast Description February 2016: Sarah Koenig ducks back into the Adnan Syed case for a few days. There’s a hearing in Baltimore—a court proceeding that’s been nearly sixteen years in the making. Syed’s attorney will introduce new evidence, and present a case for why his conviction should be overturned. Sarah and producer Dana Chivvis will discuss what happens, day by day.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial S01 Update 1: Day 01, Adnan Syed’s Hearing | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140075/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2014 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140075/</guid><description>Podcast Description February 2016: Sarah Koenig ducks back into the Adnan Syed case for a few days. There’s a hearing in Baltimore—a court proceeding that’s been nearly sixteen years in the making. Syed’s attorney will introduce new evidence, and present a case for why his conviction should be overturned. Sarah and producer Dana Chivvis will discuss what happens, day by day.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial S01 - Ep. 12: What We Know | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140076/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2014 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140076/</guid><description>Podcast Description On January 13, 1999, Adnan Syed was a hurt and vengeful ex-boyfriend who carried out a premeditated murder. Or he was a bewildered bystander, framed for a crime he could never have committed. After 15 months of reporting, we take out everything we’ve got - interviews and documents and police reports - we shake it all out, and we see what sticks.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial S01 - Ep. 11: Rumors | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140077/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2014 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Almost everyone describes the 17-year-old Adnan the same way: good kid, helpful at the mosque, respectful to his elders. But a couple of months ago, Sarah started getting phone calls from people who knew Adnan back then, and told her stories of a different kind of boy.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial S01 - Ep. 10: The Best Defense is a Good Defense | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140078/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adnan’s trial lawyer was M. Cristina Gutierrez, a renowned defense attorney in Maryland – tough and savvy and smart. Other lawyers said she was exactly the kind of person you’d want defending you on a first-degree murder charge. But Adnan was convicted, and a year later, Gutierrez was disbarred. What happened?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial S01 - Ep. 9: To Be Suspected | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140079/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2014 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140079/</guid><description>Podcast Description New information is coming in about what maybe didn’t happen on January 13, 1999. And while Adnan’s memory of that day is foggy at best, he does remember what happened next: being questioned, being arrested and, a little more than a year later, being sentenced to life in prison.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial S01 - Ep. 8: The Deal With Jay | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140080/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2014 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140080/</guid><description>Podcast Description The state’s case against Adnan Syed hinged on Jay’s credibility; he was their star witness and also, because of his changing statements to police, their chief liability. Naturally, Adnan’s lawyer tried hard to make Jay look untrustworthy at trial. So, how did the jurors make sense of Jay? For that matter, how did the cops make sense of Jay? How are we supposed to make sense of Jay?</description></item><item><title>Serial S01 - Ep. 7: The Opposite of the Prosecution | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140081/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adnan told Sarah about a case in Virginia that had striking similarities to his own: one key witness, incriminating cell phone records, young people, drugs - and a defendant who has always maintained his innocence. Sarah called up one of the defense attorneys on that case to see if she could offer any insight into Adnan’s case, and got much more than she bargained for.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial S01 - Ep. 6: The Case Against Adnan Syed | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140082/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2014 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140082/</guid><description>Podcast Description The physical evidence against Adnan Syed was scant - a few underwhelming fingerprints. So aside from cell records, what did the prosecutors bring to the jury, to shore up Jay&amp;rsquo;s testimony? Sarah weighs all the other circumstantial evidence they had against Adnan, including curious behavior, a disconcerting note, and an unexplained mid-afternoon phone call.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial S01 - Ep. 5: Route Talk | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140083/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2014 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adnan once issued a challenge to Sarah. He told her to test the state’s timeline of the murder by driving from Woodlawn High School to Best Buy in 21 minutes. It can’t be done, he said. So Sarah and Dana take up the challenge, and raise him one: They try to recreate the entire route that Jay said he and Adnan took on January 13th, 1999.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial S01 - Ep. 4: Inconsistencies | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140084/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2014 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140084/</guid><description>Podcast Description A few days after Hae’s body is found, the detectives get a lead that opens the case up for them. They find Jay at work late one night and bring him down to Homicide. At first, he insists he doesn’t know anything about the murder. But eventually he comes clean. He tells them what happened on January 13th. A few weeks later, he’s back at Homicide and his story has changed.</description></item><item><title>Serial S01 - Ep. 3: Leakin Park | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140085/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2014 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140085/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s February 9, 1999. Hae has been missing for three weeks. A man on his lunch break pulls off a road to pee, and stumbles on her body in a city forest. His odd recounting of the discovery makes Detectives Ritz and MacGillivary suspicious. For instance, why did he walk so far into the woods - 127 feet - to relieve himself? And that’s just the start. A look into the man’s past reveals some bizarre behavior.</description></item><item><title>Serial S01 - Ep. 2: The Breakup | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140086/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Their relationship began like a storybook high-school romance: a prom date, love notes, sneaking off to be alone. But unlike other kids at school, they had to keep their dating secret, because their parents disapproved. Both of them, but especially Adnan, were under special pressure at home, and the stress of that spilled over into their relationship. Eventually Hae broke up with Adnan. And then, depending on who you ask, Adnan was either understandably sad and moping around, or full of rage and plotting to kill her.</description></item><item><title>Serial S01 - Ep. 1: The Alibi | Serial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5246140087/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 13:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5246140087/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s Baltimore, 1999. Hae Min Lee, a popular high-school senior, disappears after school one day. Six weeks later detectives arrest her classmate and ex-boyfriend, Adnan Syed, for her murder. He says he&amp;rsquo;s innocent - though he can&amp;rsquo;t exactly remember what he was doing on that January afternoon. But someone can. A classmate at Woodlawn High School says she knows where Adnan was. The trouble is, she’s nowhere to be found.</description></item></channel></rss>