<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dateline NBC on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/dateline-nbc/</link><description>Recent content in Dateline NBC on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/dateline-nbc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Talking Dateline: The Last Weekend | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990488/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990488/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrea Canning sits down with Keith Morrison to talk about his recent episode, “The Last Weekend.” This marks Dateline’s fourth episode in the mountains of Greeley, Colorado, where Keith traveled to report on the murder of Scott Sessions, a beloved local trumpet player. Keith shares his approach to storytelling and what he’s learned from some of his favorite mystery authors.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Last Weekend | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990486/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990486/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a trumpet player fails to show up for a scheduled gig, his family learns his body was abandoned in the mountains. Then, a second murder catches police by surprise. Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Special sneak peek of “Morrison Mysteries” | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990487/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990487/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey, Dateline fans! As a bonus, we’re giving you a special preview clip from season 2 of our podcast Morrison Mysteries. This season, Keith Morrison is taking us to Victorian England for Charles Dickens’ classic, A Christmas Carol. If you like what you hear, just search “Morrison Mysteries” for the full story or click here: https://link.chtbl.com/mms2_fdlw
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Keith Morrison reads “A Christmas Carol” | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990485/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990485/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey Dateline fans! As a bonus for you, we’re sharing the trailer for season 2 of our podcast Morrison Mysteries… Each season, Keith Morrison takes listeners on a captivating ride through some of the most suspenseful and chilling works of fiction you’ll ever hear. Haunting stories of ghosts, love triangles, jealousy and rage – and now in the spirit of the holidays, he’s taking us to Victorian England for Charles Dickens’ classic, A Christmas Carol.</description></item><item><title>Talking Dateline: The Day Alissa Disappeared | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990483/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990483/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josh Mankiewicz talks with Andrea about her latest episode, “The Day Alissa Disappeared” which looks at the case of Alissa Turney, the Arizona teen who vanished from her Paradise Valley home in May 2001. Andrea tells Josh about the dramatic moment, more than 20 years later, that left a courtroom stunned. The two share what they’ve learned over the years from talking with the families of the missing.</description></item><item><title>Dateline presents: Mortal Sin | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990481/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990481/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey, Dateline fans! As a bonus, we’re giving you a special preview clip of our new podcast series Mortal Sin. In Dateline’s latest original podcast series, Josh Mankiewicz tells a twisted tale about a seemingly perfect couple, sex, lies, religion…and murder. If you like what you hear, you can listen to the first 2 episodes now for free, or subscribe to Dateline Premium on Apple Podcasts to get access to new episodes 1 week early.</description></item><item><title>The Day Alissa Disappeared | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990482/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990482/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 17-year-old Alissa Turney is reported missing in Phoenix, it takes years before detectives treat her case as a homicide. A new investigation unearths dark family secrets, leading to a dramatic courtroom drama and an outcome no one saw coming. Andrea Canning reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Secrets in Pleasant Prairie | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990480/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990480/</guid><description>Podcast Description The investigation into the poisoning death of a Wisconsin mother takes a surprising turn when detectives learn she wrote a letter just days before her death pointing to a possible suspect. Andrea Canning reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Mortal Sin | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990478/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990478/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a bonus for you, we’re sharing the trailer for Mortal Sin, an all-new original podcast series from Dateline. Dawn and Nick Hacheney are the perfect couple: spiritual, loving, and devoted to the church where Nick is a pastor. When Dawn is killed in a house fire the day after Christmas, the pastor and his flock are devastated. What few knew at the time was the dark prophecy that foretold it&amp;hellip; Follow now to get the first two episodes on December 5th completely free, or you can subscribe to Dateline Premium on Apple Podcasts to start listening now, ad-free: https://link.</description></item><item><title>The Note | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990479/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990479/</guid><description>Podcast Description When an Illinois high schooler vanishes, her mother finds a note saying she ran away. But a grisly discovery made years later changes the course of the investigation. Andrea Canning reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Talking Dateline: The Murdaugh Murders: Inside the Investigation | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990477/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990477/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josh Mankiewicz talks with South Carolina natives Craig Melvin and producer Carol Gable about their recent episode, “The Murdaugh Murders: Inside the Investigation.” Craig reveals why state investigators agreed to sit down with Dateline to discuss the case, and talks about what it’s been like to be back reporting in his home state on such a high-profile story.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Murdaugh Murders: Inside the Investigation | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990476/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990476/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lead detectives speak out about the investigation into once-prominent South Carolina attorney Alex Murdaugh, who was convicted of murdering his wife, Maggie, and son Paul. Craig Melvin reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Talking Dateline: The Hunt for the Gilgo Beach Killer | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990474/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990474/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josh Mankiewicz and Andrea Canning discuss Andrea’s recent episode, “The Hunt for the Gilgo Beach Killer.” In July 2023, architect Rex Heuermann was charged with the murders of three women whose bodies were found on Long Island’s Gilgo Beach 13 years earlier. Andrea tells Josh what made this episode different from others she’s worked on, and reveals additional details about the investigation and Heuermann, who has pleaded not guilty to all charges.</description></item><item><title>The Hunt for the Gilgo Beach Killer | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990473/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990473/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrea Canning sits down with family members and key insiders connected to the investigation of the murders of several women found dead along Gilgo Beach in Long Island, New York.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Talking Dateline: The Case of the Man with No Name | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990471/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990471/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josh Mankiewicz and Keith Morrison discuss Keith’s recent episode, “The Case of the Man with No Name.” The story takes Keith back to his homeland to report on the mysterious disappearance and murder of a Canadian man and the international manhunt to track down his elusive killer and bring him to justice. Keith talks about his upbringing in Canada…and you’ll learn the answer to the age-old question: has Keith ever been on a jet ski?</description></item><item><title>The Case of the Man with No Name | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990472/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990472/</guid><description>Podcast Description The investigation into the mysterious disappearance of Canadian limo driver Dwayne Demkiw sparks an international manhunt for an elusive killer with multiple false identities. Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dangerous Secret | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990001/</guid><description>Podcast Description A small town in the Ohio River Valley is left in shock after beloved local coal miner Brad McGarry is found fatally shot in the basement of his home. As investigators dig into his personal life, a secret affair reveals a surprising suspect. Dennis Murphy reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>On the Hunt for the Zombie Hunter | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990002/</guid><description>Podcast Description The murders of two young women near a Phoenix canal in the early 1990s remain unsolved for over 20 years until a team of cold case detectives take on the case. Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Talking Dateline: 65 Seconds | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josh Mankiewicz and Blayne Alexander take us behind the scenes of Blayne’s recent episode, “65 Seconds.” The story chronicles the 13-year investigation into the murder of Heidi Firkus in her St. Paul, Minnesota home. Blayne and Josh discuss the unexpected twists in the case and Blayne’s experience reporting the story for Dateline.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>65 Seconds | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990004/</guid><description>Podcast Description After an apparent home invasion leaves 25-year-old Heidi Firkus dead and her husband Nick hospitalized, detectives learn the young couple was facing financial troubles. Blayne Alexander reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Talking Dateline: The Footprint at the Lake | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josh Mankiewicz and Andrea Canning give us an inside look at Andrea’s recent episode, “The Footprint at the Lake.” The story is about Manuela Allen, a beloved teacher who disappeared from her Olney, Texas, home and was later found dead at a nearby lake. In their conversation, Josh and Andrea discuss the details of the case and go behind the scenes of the making of the episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Footprint at the Lake | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990006/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990006/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a teacher vanishes from her home and police make a gruesome discovery at a lake, investigators in a small Texas town are left with more questions than answers. Andrea Canning reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Talking Dateline: The Clearing | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josh and Dennis take us behind the scenes of Dennis’s recent episode “The Clearing.” The story is about the mysterious death of Ohio woman Emily Noble. After a monthslong search, Emily’s body was found in the woods near her home. Was it murder or suicide? In their conversation, Dennis and Josh discuss the puzzling details surrounding Emily’s death and Dennis’s interview with Emily’s husband, Matt. If you or someone you know is in crisis, call the Suicide &amp;amp; Crisis Lifeline at 988 or visit 988lifeline.</description></item><item><title>The Clearing | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990008/</guid><description>Podcast Description When three women discover the body of Emily Noble in a wooded area near her home nearly four months after she went missing, investigators must determine if her death was a suicide or homicide. Dennis Murphy reports about the case that rocked a small Ohio town.
If you or someone you know is in crisis, call the Suicide &amp;amp; Crisis Lifeline at 988 or visit 988lifeline.org for more resources.</description></item><item><title>Talking Dateline: Losing Faith | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrea and Josh take you behind the scenes of Josh’s recently aired “Losing Faith” episode about the murder of Jamie Faith, a Dallas man who was shot to death in broad daylight while he and his wife were taking their dog for her morning walk. In their conversation, Andrea and Josh share their insights about the case and reveal details you haven’t heard.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Losing Faith | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josh Mankiewicz reports on the fatal shooting of Jamie Faith, who was brazenly gunned down while he and his wife were taking their dog for her morning walk outside their Dallas home.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>DATELINE SNEAK PEEK! | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990011/</guid><description>Podcast Description The new season is upon us! New mysteries, extra episodes, new original podcasts and a big reveal… Josh Mankiewicz sits down with Andrea Canning, Dennis Murphy, and Keith Morrison ahead of our season premiere on Friday, September 29 at 9/8c to dish all things Dateline.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Gathering Storm | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990012/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a Florida man is holed up in a hotel room seeking shelter from a hurricane and hiding from his past. Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on February 15, 2013.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Page Turner | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990013/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrea Canning reports on the ongoing case of a Utah mother of three who wrote a children’s book about coping with grief following the sudden death of her husband.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Death &amp; the Dentist | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two young women leading rich, full lives are found dead years apart, both apparent suicides. The two had never met, but it turns out they did have one thing in common. Rob Stafford reports in this Dateline classic that originally aired on NBC on December 2, 2007.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Streets of Laredo | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990015/</guid><description>Podcast Description An unexpected suspect comes to light as investigators work to solve a string of deadly shootings targeting women in the border city of Laredo, Texas. Josh Mankiewicz reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mystery at Payson Canyon | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990016/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Kay Mortensen, a brilliant retired professor, a man who was prepared for just about anything finds himself in the most unimaginable situation. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on June 28, 2013.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Body of Evidence | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990017/</guid><description>Podcast Description One preacher. Two wives. And a mystery that leads investigators deep into the desert to uncover the truth about the disappearance of wife number two. Keith Morrison reports in this Dateline classic that originally aired on NBC on January 9, 2007.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tangled | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990018/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a sudden marriage sows tension in two families in a small-town in Colorado. Then a murder uncovers secrets, lies, and a mystery that had been buried for years. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on April 15, 2016.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Mysterious Music Man | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990019/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Dennis Murphy tells the story of a group of smart, successful women with big dreams who, with a click or two, met a man who they believed could make their dreams a reality. But was any of it real? Originally aired on NBC on April 12, 2009.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Ultimatum | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990020/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a mother is discovered dead inside her home, it appears to be a suicide. But when investigators start to interview those closest to her, an evil plot emerges. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on November 16, 2018.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Blood Ties | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990021/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, when Lisa Seabolt went missing in Bakersfield, California, her twin sister came up with a brilliant and dangerous plan to catch the person responsible. Few people could do what she did, and it almost got her killed. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on April 29, 2006.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Return to the Farm | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990022/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Shirley Carter is gunned down in her kitchen in rural Iowa, the whole town is stunned. But when police and her family are left with no leads, Shirley’s husband does something even more shocking &amp;ndash; he points the finger at their son. Dennis Murphy reports on the major developments in the case, and the family feud that led to a murder trial. Originally aired on NBC on June 14, 2019.</description></item><item><title>The Mystery on Reminisce Road | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Crime fighting becomes personal for FBI Agents in Wilmington, North Carolina, when their own office manager is murdered. Josh Mankiewicz reports in this Dateline classic. Originally aired on NBC on July 12, 2010.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Dead of Night | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990024/</guid><description>Podcast Description A mother of two goes missing in Monrovia, California. As detectives investigate, the woman&amp;rsquo;s friends and family reveal that she feared she was being stalked. Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on October 9, 2020.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Searching for Allen | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990025/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990025/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Dennis Murphy reports on the disappearance of filmmaker Allen Ross. When police come up with no answers, Allen’s friends and family devise a plan of their own to help solve the mystery. Originally aired on NBC on February 25, 2005.
Additional Footage: “Missing Allen”/Tangram Films The Sundance Channel, L.L.C.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Killer Among Us | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990026/</guid><description>Podcast Description It haunted the city of Spokane, Washington for years, as one after another women turned up dead with few clues and few answers for grieving families. The search for the killer would lead investigators to a most unlikely suspect. Keith Morrison reports in this Dateline classic that originally aired on NBC on November 10, 2000.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Summer of Manson | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990027/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Keith Morrison reports on the mind and myth of Charles Manson. Updated to include the 2023 release from prison of former Manson follower Leslie Van Houten who participated in the murders of Leno and Rosemary LaBianca on August 10, 1969. Originally aired on NBC on August 4, 2017.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Common Denominators | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990028/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a 13-year-old girl is murdered on Valentine’s Day, the investigation leads to a high-profile trial and a conviction. But to one veteran cold case detective, something didn’t look right. Could the wrong person have been in prison? Keith Morrison reports in this Dateline classic. Originally aired on NBC on June 8, 2008.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Circle of Friends | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990029/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990029/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a circle of friends from a Miami high school are about to embark on a new beginning at college. But one friend surprises them all. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on August 22, 2014.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deadly Hollywood Dreams | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990030/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990030/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Keith Morrison tells the story of dozens of women who followed their Hollywood dream of becoming a model. Many disappeared after posing for one particular photographer. Could a team of committed detectives track down the truth of what happened to them? Originally aired on NBC on March 13, 2009.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>On the Trail of the Bike Path Rapist | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990031/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990031/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Keith Morrison reports on a series of rapes and murders on a peaceful bike path that went unsolved for decades. Could they all have been committed by the same man? Originally aired on NBC on June 8, 2008.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Diabolical | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990032/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990032/</guid><description>Podcast Description A bizarre cyber-revenge case lands a young woman in jail and makes national headlines. In this Dateline classic, Dennis Murphy reports on the unexpected twist that revealed the real culprit. Originally aired on NBC on April 20, 2018.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Death in the Hollywood Hills | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990033/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990033/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a predator strikes in the glamourous hills of Hollywood targeting young women with big dreams. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on November 11, 2006.
Listen to Keith Morrison’s conversation with Kristi’s mother, Terry Hall, who discusses her life in the 20 years since her daughter’s murder and her determination to keep Paleologus behind bars. After the Verdict is available now only by subscription to Dateline Premium on Apple Podcasts.</description></item><item><title>The Trap | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990034/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kate Snow interviews former journalist Amanda Lindhout and the undercover agent who spearheaded the international manhunt for the person responsible for her 2008 kidnapping and torture in Somalia. Originally aired on NBC on January 13, 2019.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Long, Dark Stretch of Road | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990035/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990035/</guid><description>Podcast Description A well-known defense attorney and his wife of nearly 30 years live a comfortable life with their children. One night, that life is torn apart when they are both shot on the side of the road leaving one of them dead. Could it be an angry former client, or something much more twisted? Dennis Murphy reports in this Dateline classic. Originally aired on NBC on April 24, 2009.</description></item><item><title>Into Thin Air | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990036/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990036/</guid><description>Podcast Description After two young girls go missing two months apart in a Portland, Oregon suburb, a private eye is convinced it’s only a matter of time before someone else gets hurt. Can she crack the case before the FBI does? Keith Morrison reports in this Dateline classic. Originally aired on NBC on January 27, 2006.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Something Wicked | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990037/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990037/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a popular 16-year-old goes missing in the dead of night in rural West Virginia. Andrea Canning reports. Originally aired on NBC on March 7, 2014.
Andrea Canning catches up with the Neeses to discuss Rachel Shoaf’s parole hearing, their advice to parents of teenagers, and their continued advocacy for change following their daughter’s murder. After the Verdict available now only by subscription to Dateline Premium on Apple Podcasts.</description></item><item><title>What Happened to Tara Grant? | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990038/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990038/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, it looked like a model modern family from the outside &amp;ndash; but it’s what happened inside Tara and Stephen Grant’s home that led to an ending no one expected. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on February 29, 2008.
Additional footage: WDIV-TV, Detroit, MI
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Behind the Closet Door | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990039/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990039/</guid><description>Podcast Description After Andrea Cincotta is found murdered in her Virginia home, her son embarks on a 20-year quest for justice that leads him down a dark and twisted path. Josh Mankiewicz reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Mystery of Katrina Montgomery | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990040/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a young prosecutor, and a savvy investigator are willing to do almost anything to find out what happened to 20-year-old Katrina Montgomery, and bring those responsible for her disappearance to justice. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on November 4, 2007.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deadly Secret | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990041/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Before the Menendez brothers, the Bobbitts or even O.J., Pamela Smart was television&amp;rsquo;s first true crime fascination after her husband was found murdered. When police began to investigate, they discovered that Smart was keeping a big secret. She speaks out to Andrea Canning about the case that made worldwide headlines and inspired a Hollywood movie. Originally aired on NBC on July 29, 2019.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Father's Day | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990042/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a woman from Washington State takes a DNA test, hoping to learn more about her family history. A remarkable discovery would change her family forever – and send her father halfway around the world to confront a past he thought he left behind. Harry Smith reports. Originally aired on NBC on June 17, 2018.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bad Intentions | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990043/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990043/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a Texas D.A. and his wife are killed two months after a prosecutor’s murder in the same town, law enforcement fears they may be in the sights of a serial killer. Andrea Canning reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Alibi | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrea Canning reports on the homicide of private first class soldier and young mother Karlyn Ramirez. Originally aired on NBC on January 11, 2019.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Secrets in the Ozarks | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990045/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990045/</guid><description>Podcast Description When the body of 22-year-old college student Rebekah Gould is found a week after she vanished, theories about her murder run rampant through the Arkansas Ozarks. Dennis Murphy reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bodies of Evidence | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990046/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990046/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a fiery car crash with a badly charred body seems like a tragedy for one family…but is it? Investigators follow a trail of clues to a grave and beyond. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on April 8, 2006.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The House on Sidney's Cove | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990047/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990047/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a wife and mother of three disappears without a trace. Could her home’s security cameras hold the key to solving the mystery? Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on May 8, 2016.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Model &amp; the Millionaire | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990048/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990048/</guid><description>Podcast Description It was an unlikely union: a 23-year-old beauty and a 57-year-old real estate tycoon. The love affair would end with three people shot and one of them dead, in a bloody whodunnit. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on June 27, 2008.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Killings on King Road | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990049/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Keith Morrison reports the latest on the investigation into the case that caught the world’s attention — the murders of four college students in Moscow, Idaho.
UPDATE: On May 22, 2023 a judge entered not guilty pleas on all murder charges on behalf of Bryan Kohberger as the defense stood silent.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Return to the Early Shift | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990050/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990050/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a Kentucky man is convicted of murdering his co-worker, it appears the mystery is solved until a stunning disclosure years later turns the closed case upside-down. Josh Mankiewicz reports on the new trial that had both sides of the courtroom bracing for what would come next. Originally aired on NBC on June 28, 2019.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Trial of Lori Vallow Daybell | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990051/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Keith Morrison returns to Idaho for the case against Lori Vallow Daybell, who was on trial for the murders of two of her children, Tylee Ryan and JJ Vallow, and conspiracy to commit the murder of her husband Chad’s previous wife, Tammy Daybell. On July 31, 2023, Vallow Daybell was sentenced to five terms of life in prison without the possibility of parole.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Motive | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990052/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990052/</guid><description>Podcast Description A young woman finds out that her boyfriend might have shot and killed a college football player out of revenge. She struggles with coming forward to officials, fearing she could lose her life. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on March 22, 2019.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Killing Time | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990053/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amy Preasmyer and friends place a frantic call to 911 after discovering her boyfriend in a pool of blood. The killer speaks out for the first time to Keith Morrison about what really happened. Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Dream House Mystery | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990054/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990054/</guid><description>Podcast Description 24-year-old Lindsay Buziak was just starting out as a real estate agent and thought she landed the assignment of her dreams &amp;ndash; clients who wanted to buy a million dollar home. But golden opportunities are not always what they seem. Josh Mankiewicz reports in this Dateline classic. Originally aired on NBC on September 17, 2010.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Along Came Sarah | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990055/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990055/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a woman&amp;rsquo;s fifth husband dies in a hospital under suspicious circumstances, an investigation reveals a checkered past full of spurned lovers and wild allegations. Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Talking Dateline: Dead Man Talking | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990056/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josh Mankiewicz and Andrea Canning take us behind the scenes of Andrea’s “Dead Man Talking” episode. They discuss Andrea’s memorable interview with Arthur Knight, the man who claims he is not American fugitive Nicholas Alahverdian, also known as Nicholas Rossi. They also talk about the incredible strength of the women who shared their stories with Dateline.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dead Man Talking | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990057/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Investigators search for an American fugitive accused of faking his own death to evade law enforcement agencies. Andrea Canning confronts the man at the center of the international mystery. If you or someone you know is experiencing domestic violence please contact the National Domestic Violence Hotline at 1-800-799-SAFE (7233) or www.thehotline.org
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Last Dance in the Rockies | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990058/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990058/</guid><description>Podcast Description For Miriam and Alan Helmick, both widowed, life gave them a second chance at love – until Alan was found dead, and details from Miriam’s past revealed she had some dark secrets. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on May 14, 2010.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Who Killed Courtney Coco? | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990059/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990059/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a young woman&amp;rsquo;s body is discovered in an abandoned building, it sparks an investigation that lasts nearly two decades and pushes one family’s own search for justice. Andrea Canning reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Laci Peterson: A New Turn | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990060/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990060/</guid><description>Podcast Description The latest in the murder of Laci Peterson, including new details on the appeals of convicted killer Scott Peterson. Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Behind Door 813 | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990061/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990061/</guid><description>Podcast Description After 27-year-old Jonathan Crews dies mysteriously in his Texas apartment, his family takes matters into their own hands in an effort to find answers. Josh Mankiewicz reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Complicated | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990062/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990062/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Josh Mankiewicz reports on the story of a mother’s fight for justice after her daughter and 10-month-old grandson are found strangled to death in their home. Originally aired on NBC on March 18, 2011.
Josh Mankiewicz’s original interview with Tori’s mother, Dayna, led to an enduring friendship. They reunited in 2023 for an episode of After the Verdict, an exclusive series for Dateline Premium podcast subscribers available only on Apple Podcasts.</description></item><item><title>Justice for Kristin Smart | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990063/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990063/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a network exclusive, Kristin Smart’s parents sit down with Josh Mankiewicz following the arrest and conviction of their daughter’s killer.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>One Moment | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990064/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990064/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Crystal Taylor is murdered, her sisters are determined to find the killer. Josh Mankiewicz reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Secrets of the Snake Farm | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990065/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990065/</guid><description>Podcast Description The lead investigator takes Andrea Canning inside the investigation of the murder of world-renowned snake breeder Ben Renick, who was found shot to death in his snake facility.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Prime Suspect | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990066/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ann Racz loved her children more than anything. So why would she leave them so suddenly, without a word? Getting the answer to that question would take more than 16 years, as Keith Morrison reports in this Dateline classic. Originally aired on NBC on April 18, 2008.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Murder of Lorenzen Wright | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990067/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrea Canning reports on the latest developments in the lengthy search for justice in the murder of former NBA star and hometown hero Lorenzen Wright.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Talking Dateline: Finding Rita | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990068/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josh and Keith take you behind-the-scenes of the making of Keith’s recently aired “Finding Rita” episode, about a Colorado mother whose disappearance was a mystery until a detective found a connection to a previous crime. In their revealing conversation, Keith and Josh also share insights and anecdotes from memorable stories they’ve reported on over the years.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Finding Rita | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990069/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990069/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a Colorado mother vanishes without a trace, the detective investigating her disappearance discovers a connection to a previous assault. Keith Morrison reports.
If you or someone you know is experiencing domestic violence, sexual assault, or is in crisis, please contact the following for help and resources: National Domestic Violence Hotline: 1-800-799-SAFE (7233) or www.thehotline.org National Sexual Assault Hotline: 1-800-656-4673 or https://rainn.org/ Suicide &amp;amp; Crisis Lifeline: Call 988 or go to https://988lifeline.</description></item><item><title>Cliffhanger | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990070/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990070/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, when a young newlywed falls to her death from a 1,000-foot cliff questions emerge. Was it an accident, or was she pushed? Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on June 11, 2007.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Trial of Alex Murdaugh | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990071/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990071/</guid><description>Podcast Description A once-prominent South Carolina attorney, Alex Murdaugh, faces a trial for the murders of his wife, Maggie, and son, Paul. Craig Melvin reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Window | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990072/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990072/</guid><description>Podcast Description A Florida father is determined to find out what happened to his daughter after her fatal fall from a penthouse apartment in Belgium. Dennis Murphy reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Flight to Nowhere | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990073/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990073/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, an airplane mechanic goes missing. His wife says he left on a flight with a mysterious passenger. But when details emerge about the mechanic’s life on the ground, police begin to question his marriage. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired May 30, 2008.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Web of Deceit | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990074/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990074/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Victoria Corderi talks with couples who had hoped to find a birth mother through independent adoptions online. They thought they found the perfect person, but after giving their money and their trust, a cold-hearted scam was exposed that left them all devastated. Originally aired on NBC on July 7, 2006.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Footprints in the Snow | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990075/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990075/</guid><description>Podcast Description The missing persons case of 12-year-old Jonelle Matthews in Colorado remains a mystery for more than 3 decades until detectives narrow in on a suspect whose bizarre behavior after her disappearance hints at something much more sinister. Dennis Murphy reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Murdaugh on Trial: The Prosecution Rests | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990076/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Go inside the courtroom for the trial of the year. Today Show Anchor and Dateline Correspondent Craig Melvin and Dateline Producer Carol Gable — two proud natives of South Carolina — dissect the just-concluded prosecution case against Alex Murdaugh for the murders of his wife and son, charges to which he has pleaded not guilty. They analyze key moments, review dramatic testimony, and assess the trial so far, with the defense about to take center stage.</description></item><item><title>The Santa Strangler | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990077/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990077/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, two women believe they have information on a decades-old cold case that has been virtually forgotten. And when the Los Angeles Police Department opens a new cold case unit, the stories the women tell would give detectives a chance to catch a serial killer. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on June 20. 2008.
Additional footage: San Luis Obispo Chamber of Commerce
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Who Killed Mindy Morgenstern? | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990078/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990078/</guid><description>Podcast Description A college town is left in fear after a student is murdered. Detectives investigate neighbors, friends, and boyfriends before they find the killer hiding in plain sight. Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deadly Deception | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990079/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990079/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Julie Keown succumbs to a mysterious illness after growing more debilitated and depressed by the day. Doctors later find antifreeze in her system. Was it murder, an accident or, in her despair, did she take her own life? Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on January 9, 2009.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>On a Dark, Deserted Highway | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990080/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990080/</guid><description>Podcast Description A deadly high-speed chase in Montana leads Dateline on a search to unravel the mystery of how one man turned into a monster and committed one of the state’s most notorious crimes. Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deadly Affair | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990081/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Twelve hours after a South Dakota wife and mother is reported missing, police make an arrest in her murder. What happened next would shock the entire community. Josh Mankiewicz reports in this Dateline classic. Originally aired on NBC on February 13, 2009. Additional footage: South Dakota National Guard
Listen to Josh’s conversation with Haylee Reay Cole about how she’s doing today as a 29-year-old mother, how she’s emerged from her ordeal stronger and more driven as she shares her story as a tribute to her mother.</description></item><item><title>The Crossbow Incident | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990082/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990082/</guid><description>Podcast Description A wife and mother is found dead in her Virginia beach home, shot through the back by a crossbow. Her husband insists it was an accident, but the prosecutor calls it murder. Keith Morrison reports in this Dateline classic. Originally aired on NBC on September 8, 2008.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Detective's Daughter | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990083/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990083/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a sheriff detective&amp;rsquo;s daughter &amp;ndash; who&amp;rsquo;d been kidnapped &amp;ndash; did what she&amp;rsquo;d been taught. She called 911. So did her husband. So did horrified witnesses. They all thought help would be on the way. They were wrong. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on July 26, 2009.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Terror at the Mall | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990084/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990084/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a killer targets mothers in their SUV&amp;rsquo;s who are out for a day of shopping at the mall in southern Florida. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on August 7, 2009. Additional footage: WTVJ-TV, MIAMI, FL
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Secrets of Birch View Drive | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990085/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990085/</guid><description>Podcast Description After an apparent brazen home invasion in a quiet Connecticut community leaves Connie Dabate dead, investigators discover a silent witness that cracks the case wide open. Andrea Canning reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Face of Evil | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990086/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990086/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a 21-year-old student is found murdered along a Texas road, detectives begin to hunt for her killer. Andrea Canning reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jagged | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990087/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990087/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Ohio mother Heather Bogle goes missing, a detective identifies multiple suspects, until he himself comes under scrutiny for his investigation. Josh Mankiewicz reports, and interviews Bogle’s family, and four potential suspects in the early stages of the investigation, including her brother and ex-girlfriend.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Unspeakable | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990088/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990088/</guid><description>Podcast Description A couple&amp;rsquo;s anniversary celebration ends in murder, in what appears to be a home invasion. Yet, investigators think the suspect might be much closer to the victim. Will justice be delivered or denied? Dennis Murphy reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"The Night Before Christmas" read by Keith Morrison | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990089/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Grab your kerchief or cap and then settle down for a long winter’s nap. Keith Morrison will take care of the rest… Watch the video here: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0Jo4r46476o
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr. Seuss' "How The Grinch Stole Christmas!" read by Keith Morrison | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990090/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Every year Random House Children&amp;rsquo;s Books celebrates the Dr. Seuss classic by encouraging young readers and their families to “Grown their hearts three sizes” by doing good deeds throughout the holidays. Follow #grinchgooddeeds and share your good deed! Watch the video here: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ty_V5h12RHw
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Rudolph The Red-Nosed Reindeer" read by Keith Morrison | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990091/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Listen to Robert L. May’s original story of Rudolph, the red-nosed reindeer who was not allowed to join in any reindeer games. Until one Christmas Eve when Santa came calling… Watch the video here: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ab-vkvYGFGs
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Black Friday | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990092/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fort Worth, TX police are called to the scene of a brutal murder on Black Friday. The victim is beloved by her friends, girlfriends, and co-workers. She had no enemies - or did she? Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Last Walk | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990093/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Keith Morrison reports on the 2009 spring break disappearance of 17-year-old Brittanee Drexel, whose murder would take 13 years to solve.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Devil's Bathtub | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990094/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990094/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a father goes missing, his body is found in a field several miles away. Investigators start putting the pieces together and uncover multiple suspects – even within his own family. Andrea Canning reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Safari Story | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990095/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990095/</guid><description>Podcast Description A hunting safari in Zambia’s Kafue National Park ends in a nightmare when a shot rings out from the cabin of dentist Larry Rudolph and his wife, Bianca. Andrea Canning reports. In June 2023, Lori Milliron was sentenced to 17 years in prison. She has filed an appeal. In August 2023, Larry Rudolph was sentenced to life in prison and plans to appeal.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Feud | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990096/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Just south of Glacier National Park in Montana, tempers flare and personalities clash. One man shoots, another dies…but the story can’t be that cut and dry, can it? Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Evil Was Waiting | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990097/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990097/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a soldier who just returned from Afghanistan is gunned down on the side of the road in Kentucky; detectives quickly uncover a secret that could solve the case. Andrea Canning reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Figure in the House | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990098/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990098/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a woman is found murdered in her South Florida home, her son tells investigators that footage from the home’s security camera could hold the key to finding a killer. Dennis Murphy reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deadly Circumstances | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990099/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990099/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a Tennessee resident is murdered in her bedroom, investigators struggle to find answers with little evidence at the scene to link any possible suspects to the crime. Could it have been a burglary gone bad? Or, something else? Andrea Canning reports. Originally aired on NBC on April 20, 2018.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>On the Outskirts of Town | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990100/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990100/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a young woman is found dead near a soccer field in Indiana, detectives try to piece together a puzzle that leads them to an unexpected suspect. Andrea Canning reports. Originally aired on NBC on September 28, 2018.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Fire &amp; Ice | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990101/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Firefighters make a grisly discovery while responding to a fire at the house of Carmela and David Knight in a Toronto, Canada suburb. Andrea Canning reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Haunting | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990102/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990102/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1979, Pastor Richard Douglass, his wife Marilyn, and their children, Brooks and Leslie, lived peacefully just outside of Okarche, Oklahoma &amp;ndash; until two drifters arrived at their home. Keith Morrison reports in this Dateline classic. Originally aired on NBC on May 27, 2011.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Righteous Obsession | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990103/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990103/</guid><description>Podcast Description The investigation into a deadly home invasion involving business owner Milton Sawyer takes a turn when an unlikely witness on the other side of the country comes forward. Dennis Murphy reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Girl in the Little Blue Dress | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990104/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990104/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a 3-year-old named Michelle Pulsifer disappeared, her father couldn&amp;rsquo;t even get police to search for her &amp;ndash; but he never gave up looking. John Larson reports in this Dateline classic. Originally aired on NBC on July 19, 2009.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Walk in the Rain | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990105/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990105/</guid><description>Podcast Description The disappearance of 19-year-old Alaska Native Sonya Ivanoff sends shockwaves through the small coastal city of Nome. Josh Mankiewicz reports.
Get resources to help stop the missing and murdered Indigenous women crisis: https://www.nbcnews.com/dateline/mmiw-how-help-how-get-help-n1277833
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Graduation Night | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990106/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990106/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a woman attempts to connect with old neighborhood friends on Facebook, she has no idea it will dredge up a shocking, long buried truth. Keith Morrison reports in this Dateline classic. Originally aired on NBC on April 4, 2014.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Cool Desert Morning | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990107/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990107/</guid><description>Podcast Description A family begins a relentless pursuit of justice after the death of Nevada attorney Susan Winters is ruled a suicide. Josh Mankiewicz reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The People vs. O.J. Simpson: What the Jury Never Heard | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990108/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990108/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Josh Mankiewicz sits down with O.J. Simpson prosecutor Marcia Clark and other key players and witnesses from the criminal trial that consumed and divided a nation more than a quarter century ago.
Additional footage: KCOP-TV, Los Angeles, CA
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Sisterhood | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990109/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990109/</guid><description>Podcast Description After the death of 44-year-old mother Stacy Feldman in her Denver home is ruled as “undetermined,” friends and family join forces to piece together what happened. Keith Morrison reports.
If you or someone you know is experiencing domestic violence, call the National Domestic Violence Hotline at 1-800-799-SAFE (7233) or visit www.thehotline.org.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Suspicion in Silver City | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990110/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990110/</guid><description>Podcast Description When the mysterious death of a 23-year-old mother in New Mexico goes unsolved, her family searches for answers. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on December 7, 2018.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Wreckage | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990111/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990111/</guid><description>Podcast Description While investigating the rape and murder of a 22-year-old woman in Texas, detectives uncover a trail of sexual assault crimes pointing to a repeat offender. Josh Mankiewicz reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dark Valley | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990112/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990112/</guid><description>Podcast Description When film executive Gavin Smith vanishes, Los Angeles detectives search for clues amid reported sightings and suspicious circumstances. The case takes a dramatic turn when Gavin&amp;rsquo;s wife reveals painful secrets. Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Last Ride | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990113/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Keith Morrison reports on the murder of star gravel cyclist Anna Moriah Wilson and interviews insiders in the case that sparked worldwide headlines.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Mystery in Effingham County | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990114/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Publicly, they were a prominent family, highly respected. Privately, a jury would hear something else in a case &amp;ndash; that pit father against son, husband against wife, brother against brother. And at the heart of it all was a terrible family secret. Dennis Murphy reports in this Dateline classic. Originally aired on NBC on April 1, 2011.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Collision | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990115/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Years after a love triangle involving trucking magnate Bill Hall Jr. ends in a deadly car chase, insiders speak out about the latest twist in the story. Andrea Canning reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deadly Obsession | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990116/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990116/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, no one could figure out why a college student died in her bed – until a tiny spot launched an epic investigation. Hoda Kotb reports. Originally aired on August 21, 2009.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Day Jennifer Disappeared | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990117/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990117/</guid><description>Podcast Description The lead investigator in the case of Jennifer Dulos reveals key details about the day the Connecticut mother-of-five disappeared. Dennis Murphy reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Out of the Darkness | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990118/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990118/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a wife calls 911 to report her husband has been shot on a country road in Texas, officers rush to the scene. Could the dramatic police footage end up being key in the investigation? Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on August 12, 2019.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Case of the Missing D.A. | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990119/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990119/</guid><description>Podcast Description A decade before the scandal of coach Jerry Sandusky dismantled the Penn State community, a local attorney, Ray Gricar, was the first to investigate his case. But a few years later, Gricar disappeared. Was there a connection? Lester Holt reports in this Dateline classic. Originally aired on NBC on December 16, 2011.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Love Lay Dying | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990120/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990120/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Keith Morrison reports on the story of a creative woman who fell in love with a young, successful surgeon. They seemed to need each other, but also developed another kind of need that culminated in a fatal weekend that raised the question, was the doctor also a killer? Originally aired on NBC on April 25, 2008.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Years of Living Dangerously | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990121/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Barbara Bentley is swept off her feet by a retired naval officer. But she is also swept into the swirling tide of his mysterious and secretive life&amp;hellip; and a world of subterfuge and intrigue from which it would take decades for her to surface. Dennis Murphy reports in this Dateline classic. Originally aired on NBC on June 7, 2009.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deep in the Woods | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990122/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990122/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a young Army medic based at Ft. Bragg, North Carolina goes missing. Police have a suspect but can’t solve the case, until an unorthodox private investigator steps in to help. Andrea Canning reports. Originally aired on NBC on March 16, 2018.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Last Voyage | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990123/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Retired couple Tom and Jackie Hawks were living their dream of buying a boat and setting off on an adventure at sea. Until one afternoon when they went out on the water and never came back. Josh Mankiewicz reports in this Dateline classic. Originally aired on NBC on June 19, 2009.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What Happened to Anton Black? | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990124/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lester Holt reports on what happened to Anton Black, a 19-year-old Black man who died while being taken into police custody in Maryland in 2018.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deadly Sanctuary | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990125/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990125/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a congregation copes with shock and suspicion as investigators search for answers to the death of a female parishioner in the office of a country church. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on February 20, 2009.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Before the Storm | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990126/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990126/</guid><description>Podcast Description A mother of two who vanishes during a storm turns out to be a victim of something sinister. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on July 15, 2019.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Mystery of the Lost Weekend | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990127/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990127/</guid><description>Podcast Description After Vincent Brothers’ wife, children and mother-in-law are murdered on a weekend when he was out of town, his Bakersfield, California community is shocked to learn he is a suspect. Keith Morrison reports in this Dateline classic that originally aired on NBC on July 24, 2009.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Night Lynsie Disappeared | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990128/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990128/</guid><description>Podcast Description The mystery of a college student who disappeared after a night out clubbing stumps investigators for years. Her mother thought she was at a sleepover with friends and it took an eagle-eyed detective to find the truth buried in a pile of lies. Josh Mankiewicz reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Flying High at Cocktail Cove | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990129/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marcus Schrenker had it all: money, a beautiful wife, a mansion in a ritzy neighborhood. So why did this financier, a pilot, put in motion a daring plan to fake his own death and hide a double-life, like investigators say he did? Keith Morrison reports in this Dateline classic. Originally aired on NBC on August 28, 2009.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Someone Was Out There | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990130/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990130/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a young missionary is murdered and another woman goes missing in the same town, police investigate a deadly connection. Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Murder in the Family | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990131/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990131/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a wife and mother is found dead in her Coral Gables home, police had one suspect from the beginning. But there was also undeniable proof that he couldn’t have done it. Dennis Murphy reports in this Dateline classic. Originally aired on NBC on August 21, 2009.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rear Window | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990132/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990132/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a young woman is found dead inside her Jacksonville Beach apartment, it takes police more than a year to find a microscopic clue, along with a huge stroke of luck, to solve the case. Andrea Canning reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Secret Keepers | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990133/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990133/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a 59-year-old father is found dead in his home, family members assume it is related to his ongoing health issues. But when the coroner reveals he didn’t die of natural causes, police begin an investigation questioning some of his family members. Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Through the Pouring Rain | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990134/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over 14 years, more than a dozen women were raped in their own homes by a stranger who terrorized a Tennessee neighborhood. In this Dateline classic, Keith Morrison tells the story of the man known as the Wooded Rapist, who came out of the woods, in the night, in the rain. Originally aired on NBC on October 9, 2009.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Figure in the Garage | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990135/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990135/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a beloved former firefighter is found dead in his garage, police are desperate for answers until they discover that a neighbor’s home security camera captured a figure near the crime scene. Was it the killer? Dennis Murphy reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The House on the Lake | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990136/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Keith Morrison reports on one man&amp;rsquo;s extraordinary journey through the courts in upstate New York and his children who stood by him to the end.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Mystery at Pictured Rocks | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990137/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990137/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a hard-working couple cherished the chance to get away from it all. But what happened on one hiking trip stunned everyone, and left police thinking there was just one explanation. Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on June 29, 2008.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What They Saw | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990138/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990138/</guid><description>Podcast Description NBC News’ Dennis Murphy speaks to a Georgia father accused of murdering his ex-wife. While his friends come together to prove he is innocent, prosecutors count on his young children to testify against their own father.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Murder in Kitchen One | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990139/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990139/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a Portland, Oregon chef is murdered in his kitchen at work, investigators uncover a potential clue written years earlier. Josh Mankiewicz reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Before Midnight | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990140/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990140/</guid><description>Podcast Description A successful business woman and mother of three is found shot in her office. She was the center of her kids&amp;rsquo; universe, dedicated to her financial planning firm and had recently gotten engaged. The investigation into her death leaves a family divided as they question if justice will be served. Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Jacket | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990141/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990141/</guid><description>Podcast Description When an 18-year-old disappears from her Virginia home, the investigation into her inner circle of trusted friends and family reveals a sinister betrayal. Andrea Canning reports.
Listen to Andrea Canning’s conversation with Corey French about AJ’s brutal murder, the killer’s attempt to frame him, and his struggles to overcome darkness and move toward healing. After the Verdict available now only by subscription to Dateline Premium on Apple Podcasts. LINK: https://apple.</description></item><item><title>Justice for Sparkle | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990142/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990142/</guid><description>Podcast Description A young woman leaves home, hoping for a bright future. She falls in love, has a baby, and begins life as a mother. But soon, her parents get a dreadful phone call: Sparkle Rai has been killed. Keith Morrison reports in a Dateline classic originally aired on NBC on February 6, 2009.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Finding Savanna | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990143/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990143/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a woman disappears with her 11-month-old daughter after losing a hotly contested custody battle. Andrea Canning reports. Originally aired on NBC on August 7, 2015.
(Additional Footage: SEVEN NETWORK AUSTRALIA)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>She Never Left | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990144/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990144/</guid><description>Podcast Description A missing mother in Jacksonville, Florida leaves behind a three-year-old son, whose memory of their last night together offers some clues as to what happened to her. The case remains cold until two decades later when the son, Aaron Fraser, solves the mystery that haunted his childhood. Dennis Murphy reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The House on Shalimar Way | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990145/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990145/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a woman dies after what appears to be an accidental fall, evidence comes to light that suggests it could have been homicide. Andrea Canning reports on the latest chapter in the case.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>“Murder in Studio One” From TODAY | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990146/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hostage | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990147/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990147/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, survivors of the 2013 Westgate Mall attack in Nairobi, Kenya, share their stories with Kate Snow. Originally aired on NBC on November 22, 2013.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Day the Music Died | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990148/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990148/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a prominent plastic surgeon is murdered in his Asheville, North Carolina home, investigators uncover a trail of clues pointing to an unlikely killer. Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Swept Away | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990149/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990149/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, two young people from opposite sides of the world find themselves falling in love on the eve of one of the biggest natural disasters in recent memory. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on April 27, 2014.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Undoing | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990150/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990150/</guid><description>Podcast Description After Oregon mother Annastasia “Annie” Hester is stabbed to death in her home, investigators uncover personal details that point to multiple suspects and possible motives. Josh Mankiewicz reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Evil Was Watching | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990151/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two young girls in Washington are snatched in broad daylight while riding their bikes. The case goes unsolved for decades, until a new detective with a local connection to the story tries to solve the mystery that haunted her childhood. Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Blue Blanket Mystery | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990152/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990152/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a New Jersey mother reports that her five-year-old son vanished from a carnival, detectives embark on a decades-long investigation. Andrea Canning reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Death of a Heartsong | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990153/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990153/</guid><description>Podcast Description Together for more than 20 years, free-spirited Bob and Toni Heartsong had one of those legendary marriages everyone envied, or so it seemed. Keith Morrison reports in this Dateline classic that originally aired on NBC on April 3, 2009.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Curious Case of Sherri Papini | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990154/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990154/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2016, 22 days after Sherri Papini vanished from her home, she reappeared, claiming she’d been kidnapped. The detectives who cracked the case discuss the details with Keith Morrison.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Secrets in Pleasant Grove | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990155/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990155/</guid><description>Podcast Description A former beauty queen turns 50 and decides to have plastic surgery. The decision changes everything in her picture perfect life. Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Real Thing About Pam | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990156/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990156/</guid><description>Podcast Description The latest in the case of Pam Hupp, charged with murdering her friend Betsy Faria. Keith Morrison interviews Leah Askey, the prosecutor behind the wrongful conviction of Betsy’s husband, Russ.
Listen to the original 6-episode podcast on the case: https://link.chtbl.com/ttap_31422
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Secrets of Lake Seminole | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990157/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990157/</guid><description>Podcast Description When experienced outdoorsman Mike Williams disappears on a duck hunting trip on Lake Seminole, authorities first believe he could have drowned or been eaten by alligators until his mother presses law enforcement to reopen the case. Dennis Murphy reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Hands of a Killer | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990158/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990158/</guid><description>Podcast Description When former Arkansas State Senator Linda Collins is found fatally stabbed outside her home, investigators must determine if her murder is connected to her political career or her personal life. Dennis Murphy reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Into the Wild | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990159/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990159/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, McKenzie Morgan wants more than anything to learn how to fly. So in August 2013 she takes off on her final solo flight before getting her pilot’s license. All seems well, until her Cessna 172 vanishes. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on August 24, 2014.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hit List | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990160/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990160/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrea Canning reports on the case of a former NYC police officer who was accused of an alleged murder-for-hire plot against her husband.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bad Chemistry | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990161/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990161/</guid><description>Podcast Description She was the breadwinner and he took care of the children. It all worked fine until rumors of an affair, fights over the kids and, finally, an ugly divorce. The marriage was ending, but a crime even seasoned detectives find hard to believe was just beginning. Keith Morrison reports in this Dateline classic. Originally aired on NBC on September 18, 2009.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>In the Light of Day | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990162/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990162/</guid><description>Podcast Description A family gathering ends with one man dead, leading to more than a decade of questions – was it suicide or murder? Keith Morrison reports on the latest twist in the case.
This episode discusses suicide. If you or someone you know is in crisis, call the National Suicide Prevention Lifeline at 800-273-TALK.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Stealing Paradise | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990163/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990163/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, when two Americans go missing in Panama, locals discover the dark side of a fun-loving bartender. Kate Snow reports. Originally aired on NBC on October 22, 2010.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Haunting Stretch of Road | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990164/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990164/</guid><description>Podcast Description While investigating the disappearance of a Washington D.C. woman, detectives discover a puzzling connection to a Virginia woman who vanished two decades earlier. Dennis Murphy reports.
If you or someone you know is experiencing domestic violence, call the National Domestic Violence Hotline at 1-800-799-SAFE (7233) or visit www.thehotline.org.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Friday the 13th Murder | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990165/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990165/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, after a failed marriage, a young woman feels lucky to have a second chance when she gets back together with the man she’d loved since high school. Until one morning, when a single shot rings out in a parking garage. Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on November 13, 2009.
(Additional Footage: AVRphotography.com)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Siren Song | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990166/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990166/</guid><description>Podcast Description A mystery in paradise unfolds when a British woman vanishes from her boyfriend’s luxury yacht in the U.S. Virgin Islands. Andrea Canning reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Thing About “The Thing About Pam” | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990167/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Keith Morrison talks with Renée Zellweger about how and why she made the scripted series based on Dateline’s hit podcast The Thing About Pam airing Tuesdays on NBC.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>At the Edge of Town | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990168/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990168/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a college student is found dead after a party, his mother is determined to try to find out what happened. With the help of a new friend, she manages to get the case in front of a jury. Dennis Murphy reports on the unexpected twist that no one saw coming.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Prairie Confidential | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990169/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990169/</guid><description>Podcast Description A murder case considered closed by North Dakota detectives is suddenly reopened when a confidential informant comes forward with a tip about an unlikely suspect. Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bitter Pill | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990170/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990170/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, when a mother of two dies after a minor fender bender, her loved ones search for answers. The more they learn, the more it seems that it wasn’t her accident that needed investigating, it was her marriage. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on April 23, 2010.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>In the Bedroom | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990171/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990171/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Josh Mankiewicz reports on a case that seems like a straightforward crime of passion. A husband straying, a wife betrayed, and a body found in their bedroom. What happened to Adam Kostewicz? Originally aired on NBC on August 24, 2009.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Mystery at Lost Dog Road | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990172/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990172/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a well-liked young man loses his wife and son on a family outing, an entire town mourns. But there is someone who suspects the tragedy was no accident. Keith Morrison reports in this Dateline classic. Originally aired on NBC on October 30, 2009.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Valentine's Day Mystery | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990173/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990173/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a prominent doctor’s wife is murdered on Valentine’s day. Investigators had plenty of theories to work with, but the suspect they brought into custody shocked everyone. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on March 26, 2010.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Mystery in Rock Hill | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990174/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990174/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, one thing is clear in a case of disputed evidence and contradictory testimony: 12-year-old Amanda Cope was brutally murdered, and she deserved justice. Her father confessed to her murder, but was he really a killer? Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on July 9, 2010.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rosemary and the Motorcycle Man | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990175/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990175/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rosemary Christiansen, an admired and worldly woman who came to America for a fresh start, suddenly vanishes from her Florida home. Had she taken off for another new life, or was it something more sinister? Keith Morrison reports in this Dateline classic. Originally aired on NBC on August 7, 2009.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>After the Dance | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990176/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990176/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fort Worth, Texas, investigators desperately search for answers after a 17-year-old high school student is kidnapped and murdered following a Valentine’s Day dance. Josh Mankiewicz reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hope Whispers | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990177/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990177/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a fight with her mother, Angela, Ellie Green stays with her boyfriend’s family until things settle down at home. But when days go by with no word from her mom, Ellie begins to worry. Then she’s given the awful news: her mother is dead. But is that the truth? What really happened to Angela Green? Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>No Way Out | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990178/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990178/</guid><description>Podcast Description Beautiful Montecito, California, seems like the last place disaster wouldn&amp;rsquo;t strike. But four families, along with their whole community, are about to find out otherwise. Keith Morrison reports in this Dateline classic. Originally aired on NBC on April 15, 2018.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What Happened in Vegas | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990179/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990179/</guid><description>Podcast Description A chance encounter on the Pacific Coast Highway with a woman he first spoke to in a jail cell leads Keith Morrison to reexamine the mysterious death of Las Vegas casino magnate Ted Binion.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Trouble on the Hill | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990180/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990180/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a feud between neighbors turns a quiet canyon road into a deadly battleground. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on June 8, 2009.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Recipe for Murder | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990181/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990181/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Keith Morrison reports on a dramatic undercover operation in Palm Beach, Florida to save a wife and mother who had no idea she was in danger. Originally aired on NBC on March 26, 2010.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Root of All Evil | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990182/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990182/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a young real estate investor and father is found dead in the kitchen of his Jonesboro, Arkansas home. Who could have committed such a crime? Sometimes the most dangerous people in our lives are the ones who should love us the most. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on November 14, 2014.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Disappearance at the Dairy Queen | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990183/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990183/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Dennis Murphy reports on the mysterious cold case of 13-Year-Old Cindy Zarzycki who disappeared one day in 1986 after telling friends she was meeting someone at the local Dairy Queen. Originally aired on NBC on April 17, 2009.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deadly Concoction | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990184/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990184/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrew and Rob Kissel shared more than blood. They each had the trappings of success; nice homes; wealth; luxury lifestyles. Who would want to kill either man, let alone both of them? Dennis Murphy reports on the lives and strange deaths of two brothers in this Dateline classic. Originally aired on NBC on April 22, 2011.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Overlook | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990185/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990185/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two young women are shot and left for dead on a beach in Texas. After one miraculously survives, she is determined to find out who the attacker is. When a young man is eventually convicted, the long road to justice seems to be complete until a stunning twist raises a question - could the wrong man be in prison? Josh Mankiewicz reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mystery at Bootleggers Cove | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990186/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990186/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a young woman disappears in Alaska, police look at two brothers as suspects, but would anyone be able to breach their loyalty and find the truth? Keith Morrison reports in this Dateline classic. Originally aired on NBC on May 26, 2008.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Secrets of Nygard Cay | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990187/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990187/</guid><description>Podcast Description An investigation into allegations against fashion mogul Peter Nygard, accused of sex trafficking dozens of women over several decades, reveals new details in the case. Natalie Morales reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Too Fat to Kill? | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990188/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990188/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a devoted father is gunned down in his New Jersey home. An unusual defense brought the case into the national spotlight when the suspect agued he was simply too obese to carry out the killing. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on April 23, 2010.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Murder in the House of Gucci | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990189/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990189/</guid><description>Podcast Description Insiders close to the Gucci family speak out about the murder of Maurizio Gucci, the former CEO of the fashion empire. Natalie Morales reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Family Secret | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990190/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990190/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a traumatic secret tears a family apart after 27 years. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on April 2, 2010.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Mystery on Horseshoe Drive | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990191/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990191/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a man is shot and killed while picking up his daughter for a court-ordered visit. Rob Stafford reports. Originally aired on NBC on October 8, 2010.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>When the Smoke Clears | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990192/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990192/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a young woman is killed in her home. Detectives thought they knew who had killed her, but they had to prove it. And with help from the victim herself, they would. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC October 23, 2009.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Infamous | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990193/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990193/</guid><description>Podcast Description Convicted Murder Drew Peterson speaks to Natalie Morales about the death of his ex-wife, Kathleen Savio, and the disappearance of his fourth wife, Stacy.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Night Brianna Vanished | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990194/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990194/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Police and FBI in Reno, Nevada search for a brazen criminal following the disappearance of college student Brianna Denison. Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on October 29, 2010.
Josh Mankiewicz sits down with Brianna’s mother, Bridgette Denison, to find out how she’s doing these days, and to talk about how she channeled her pain into positive change. After the Verdict available now only by subscription to Dateline Premium on Apple Podcasts.</description></item><item><title>The Doomsday Files | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990195/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990195/</guid><description>Podcast Description New evidence, exclusive interviews, and an in-depth look at Lori Vallow and Chad Daybell, the Idaho couple charged in the murders of Lori’s children JJ &amp;amp; Tylee. Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Secrets in the Suitcase | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990196/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990196/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Keith Morrison reports on the 1980 murder of Karin Strom that left detectives baffled, and heartbroken loved ones wondering if justice would ever be served. Originally aired on NBC on June 18, 2010.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Horror at the Lake | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990197/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990197/</guid><description>Podcast Description Investigators desperately search for a killer after Florida teacher Denise Hallowell is found murdered. Dennis Murphy reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Night Before Halloween | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990198/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990198/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a detective and a deputy district attorney work to solve the 1984 murder of Robin Hoynes at a fast food restaurant that left few clues, except for a strange and unexplainable piece of foam left at the crime scene. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on April 15, 2011.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deadly Current | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990199/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990199/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, an atheist and a born-again preacher set out on the project of their lives, but no one thought that Satan might come a long for the ride. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on August 20, 2010.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The House on Murder Mountain | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990200/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990200/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Josh Mankiewicz reports on the tragic deaths of three neighbors in Salem, Oregon, and the mysterious landlord who many believe knows more than she’s told investigators. Originally aired on NBC on August 2, 2010.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Secrets from the Grave | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990201/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990201/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1985, Scott Purk calls 911 to report that his pregnant wife, Meg Purk, has died by suicide. The case is closed until a suspicious house fire 24 years later leads police to question what really happened that day. Josh Mankiewicz reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kill Switch | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990202/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990202/</guid><description>Podcast Description A man goes overboard on a romantic sunrise cruise with his wife on Lake Coeur d&amp;rsquo;Alene in Idaho. Investigators begin to think his death may not have been an accident. Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Blind Justice | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990203/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990203/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a husband celebrates his wife’s birthday with an intimate party held at their exclusive Coral Gables home in Florida. As the night winds down, an armed intruder suddenly enters their bedroom firing shots that kill the wife and leave the husband severely wounded. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on October 15, 2010.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Bridge | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990204/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990204/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrea Canning reports on a family’s search for answers in the 2014 disappearance of 28-year-old Fayetteville, North Carolina construction worker James Chambers.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What Happened to Amy? | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990205/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990205/</guid><description>Podcast Description For more than 30 years, Ohio investigators have searched for answers in the murder of 10-year-old Amy Mihaljevic. Now they’re enlisting your help to solve the case. Josh Mankiewicz reports.
Examine the evidence in this case: https://www.nbcnews.com/dateline/in-the-news/watch-dateline-episode-what-happened-amy-now-n1279797
If you have any tips for investigators in Amy’s case, call Bay Village PD at (440) 871-1234
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Evil That Watches | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990206/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990206/</guid><description>Podcast Description A triple murder divides a small town in Kentucky. As secrets come tumbling out, residents begin to wonder: How well do we really know our neighbors? Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dateline@30: The Podcast | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990207/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990207/</guid><description>Podcast Description As Dateline launches its 30th season, Lester Holt joins correspondents Andrea Canning, Josh Mankiewicz, Natalie Morales, Keith Morrison and Dennis Murphy for a revealing, lively and thoughtful conversation about some of their most memorable stories and experiences.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Scorned | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990208/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990208/</guid><description>Podcast Description In one of his most memorable classic episodes, Keith Morrison reports on a love triangle that led to years of stalking, destruction of property, threats and, murder.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Unraveled | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990209/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990209/</guid><description>Podcast Description In one of his most memorable classic episodes, Josh Mankiewicz reports on the race against time to make a connection between several separate murders in the Phoenix, Arizona area &amp;ndash; before the killer strikes again.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Villainous Plan | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990210/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990210/</guid><description>Podcast Description A Connecticut bank executive is targeted by a crew of criminals who invade his home, take him and his mother hostage and order him to rob his own bank. If he doesn’t commit the crime, they threaten to blow him up with a bomb strapped to his waist. Investigators think it looks like an inside job but after a string of similar crimes in Tennessee, they learn the victims were picked based on social media posts.</description></item><item><title>Point Blank | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990211/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990211/</guid><description>Podcast Description After Todd Chance is murdered, police follow a trail of video evidence as they work to track down the killer. Andrea Canning speaks exclusively with Todd’s wife, elementary school principal Jenea Chance. Andrea Canning reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Family Business | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990212/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990212/</guid><description>Podcast Description An explosion in a rice field in Colusa County, California kills the manager of a multi-million dollar farm. Police soon discover his death was no accident. Keith Morrison has chosen this episode as one of his most memorable classic episodes.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Detective Story | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990213/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990213/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Sherri Rasmussen is found murdered, police are convinced it’s a burglary gone wrong. The case remains unsolved for over two decades until another detective finds the key that unlocks the mystery of what actually happened to her. Josh Mankiewicz reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Even the Devil Went to Church | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990214/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990214/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the small town of Morris, Alabama, faith is a way of life. But when resident Michael Reese is murdered in his home, rumors involving a local pastor begin to swirl as the truth ends up turning the community upside down. Andrea Canning has chosen this episode as one of her most memorable episodes.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>In the Dead of Night | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990215/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990215/</guid><description>Podcast Description The investigation into the murder of a prominent couple on their Nebraska farm is upended after the discovery of a small, gold ring at the crime scene. Keith Morrison has chosen this episode as one of his most memorable classic episodes.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Woman at the Bar | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990216/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990216/</guid><description>Podcast Description A nationwide manhunt is launched after a woman dubbed the “killer grandma” goes on the run through the Gulf Coast. Dennis Murphy reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Over the Edge | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990217/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990217/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rangers in Rocky Mountain National Park question if the death of a woman who fell from a cliff while hiking with her husband was an accident or a heinous act of violence. Andrea Canning has chosen this episode as one of her most memorable classic episodes.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Phone Call | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990218/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990218/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Kathleen Schroll makes a phone call that names her killer right before her death, it leads to the arrest of a father for murder. But two trials and 12 years later, authorities begin to wonder if he was the victim, not the villain. Natalie Morales has chosen this episode as one of her most memorable episodes.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Vanished: Michelle Le | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990219/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990219/</guid><description>Podcast Description When nursing student Michelle Le vanishes from a parking garage after leaving her training hospital, investigators track security camera footage and her cellphone to find out the truth. Keith Morrison has chosen this episode as one of his most memorable episodes.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Bronx Tale | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990220/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990220/</guid><description>Podcast Description In one of his most memorable classic episodes, Josh Mankiewicz tells the story Eric Glisson, who was wrongly convicted of the 1995 murder of a Bronx cab driver. From behind bars, and with the help of those who believed in him, he was able to prove his innocence after serving 18 years of his life in jail for a crime he didn&amp;rsquo;t commit. Eric opens up to Dateline about his life after his release.</description></item><item><title>Angels &amp; Demons | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990221/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990221/</guid><description>Podcast Description Multiple mysterious deaths occur inside a traveling commune, spurring a decade-long investigation that uncovers deadly and devastating secrets. Dennis Murphy has chosen this episode as one of his most memorable episodes.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Twisted Loyalty | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990222/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990222/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chicago police search for a killer after Robert O’Dubaine, a nightclub owner, is gunned down in his home. As detectives investigate the motive, they discover it was a targeted killing, connected to a twisted sense of loyalty and tradition. Natalie Morales has chosen this episode as one of her most memorable episodes.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Women &amp; Dirty John | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990223/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990223/</guid><description>Podcast Description In one of his most memorable classic episodes, Keith Morrison reports on conman John Meehan, who made national headlines last year after his crimes and their final, deadly culmination were featured in the popular podcast, ‘Dirty John.’
Seven years after her brutal attack, Keith Morrison catches up with Terra Newell to talk about her life, the road to healing, and her advice to survivors of violent crime. After the Verdict is available now only by subscription to Dateline Premium on Apple Podcasts.</description></item><item><title>While He Was Sleeping | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990224/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990224/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a luxury car dealer is found dead, detectives suspect one of his lovers, but lack of evidence stalls the case for a year until one clue breaks it wide open. Josh Mankiewicz has chosen this episode as one of his most memorable classic episodes.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Down the Back Staircase | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990225/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990225/</guid><description>Podcast Description Novelist and former mayoral candidate Michael Peterson finds his wife, Kathleen, dead at the bottom of the back staircase in their North Carolina mansion. Dennis Murphy has chosen this episode as one of his most memorable classic episodes.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lauren's Promise | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990226/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990226/</guid><description>Podcast Description When University of Utah athlete Lauren McCluskey is found murdered on campus, investigators learn that she had reached out to the campus police for help multiple times before her death. Josh Mankiewicz reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Death Trap | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990227/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990227/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a pizza delivery man, Brian Wells, robs a bank while claiming he has a bomb locked around his neck, it turns into one of the strangest cases the FBI has ever encountered. Dennis Murphy has chosen this episode as one of his most memorable episodes.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Night of the New Moon | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990228/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990228/</guid><description>Podcast Description A former marine, who once was the hero for a woman in an abusive marriage, is back on ‘Dateline.’ But this time, has his desire to help gone too far? Andrea Canning has chosen this episode as one of her most memorable classic episodes.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Prussian Blue Mystery | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990229/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990229/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Brigida Uto arrives at an emergency room, she is near death. While her vital signs are fading, there are no signs of an infection or injury. Doctors, the FBI and local law enforcement are all called in to not only try to solve a medical mystery, but also a horrendous crime..Natalie Morales has chosen this episode as one of her most memorable episodes.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ransom | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990230/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990230/</guid><description>Podcast Description In one of his most memorable classic episodes, Josh Mankiewicz reports on a kidnapping mystery that changes the lives of a Florida couple.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Sting | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990231/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990231/</guid><description>Podcast Description Newlywed Dalia Dippolito returns home from the gym to the awful news that her husband has been killed. In a case where almost nothing is as it seems, investigators want to know: Was Dalia diabolical or an unwitting pawn in a hoax gone wrong? Dennis Murphy has chosen this episode as one of his most memorable classic episodes.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deadly Valentine | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990232/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990232/</guid><description>Podcast Description A missionary&amp;rsquo;s wife and mother of three is found dead in her house on Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day. As authorities investigate, questions surrounding the murder hit close to home. Andrea Canning has chosen this episode as one of her most memorable classic episodes.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deadly Connection | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990233/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990233/</guid><description>Podcast Description A terrifying mystery begins when 19-year-old Kenia Monge disappears after heading out to meet her friends. Months later, when Lydia Tillman survives a brutal attack nearby, it becomes clear that the two cases are connected. Keith Morrison has chosen this episode as one of his most memorable classic episodes.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Heroes: The Story of Flight 93 | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990234/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990234/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lester Holt interviews family members, including the now-grown children of some of the passengers and crew of Flight 93, as they honor the lives and courage that inspired the world on 9/11.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Vengeance | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990235/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990235/</guid><description>Podcast Description It started out with a couple who seemed made for each other: smart, good looking and in love. But a secret was uncovered, and passion turned to violence. Then, an elaborate plot to get revenge so twisted and devious, it nearly succeeded. Lester Holt reports in this Dateline classic. Originally aired on NBC on April 6, 2012.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Disappearance of Debbie Hawk | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990236/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990236/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, friends and family of Debbie Hawk are left searching for answers when she vanishes. Investigators discover Debbie had planned to reveal secrets and wondered if silencing her was a motive for murder. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on July 19, 2010.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Haunting Images | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990237/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990237/</guid><description>Podcast Description Using DNA testing and a photographer&amp;rsquo;s diary, a retired detective reopens an unsolved murder case in this Dateline classic reported by Keith Morrison. Originally aired on NBC on March 4, 2011.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Secrets of Spirit Lake | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990238/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990238/</guid><description>Podcast Description A woman who helps solve cases searches for her missing niece and pushes for change as part of the growing movement to save missing and murdered Indigenous women. Andrea Canning reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Mystery on Albion Road | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990239/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990239/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, investigators try to piece together events that led to a woman being found on the side of a road covered in blood and severely brain damaged. Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on March 25, 2011.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lost &amp; Found | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990484/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990484/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Keith Morrison reports on Pepper Smith’s search for her family and her true identity after being kidnapped at age 4. Originally aired on NBC on June 3, 2011.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lost and Found | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990240/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990240/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Keith Morrison reports on Pepper Smith’s search for her family and her true identity after being kidnapped at age 4. Originally aired on NBC on June 3, 2011.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Investigation | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990241/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990241/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lester Holt reports on how the investigation into the murder of four-year-old Barbara Jean Horn revealed decades of misconduct across Philadelphia’s criminal justice system.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Fugitive Millionaire | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990242/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990242/</guid><description>Podcast Description While living in paradise, a tech giant&amp;rsquo;s neighbor was found dead. Then, suddenly, the entrepreneur extraordinaire was on the run, taunting authorities and tantalizing the press. It was a riveting game of hide-and-seek, but were police chasing the right man? Keith Morrison reports in this Dateline classic. Originally aired on NBC on March 26, 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deadly Liaisons | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990243/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990243/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Rhoni Reuter, the long time girlfriend of former Chicago Bear Shaun Gayle, is murdered in her own home. Who would have killed a woman with no enemies? Rob Stafford reports. Originally aired on NBC on April 15, 2011.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Killer Role | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990244/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990244/</guid><description>Podcast Description After filming wraps on an indie horror film, the cast and crew learn their killer star isn’t who she says she is. It’s a plot twist that reveals a real-life killer. Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>As Darkness Fell | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990245/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990245/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mark and Mary Beth Harshbarger had a passion for hunting. They were both excellent shots and rarely missed, until one tragic outing changed everything. Keith Morrison reports in this Dateline classic. Originally aired on NBC on April 22, 2011.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lost in Sin City | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990246/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990246/</guid><description>Podcast Description Theresa Insana was smart, fashionable and full of faith. But life took a fatal turn when the girl who grew up in Niagara Falls moved to Las Vegas to pursue a career as a casino sales executive. Josh Mankiewicz reports in this Dateline classic. Originally aired on NBC on June 17, 2011.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Cliff’s Edge | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990247/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990247/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a romantic night out goes terribly wrong when Jody Scharf falls from the edge of a cliff. But was it an accident &amp;ndash; or was she pushed? Chris Jansing reports. Originally aired on NBC on August 12, 2011.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Justice for Bonnie | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990248/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990248/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Keith Morrison reports from Alaska on a mother’s emotional crusade to find her daughter’s killer. Originally aired on NBC on January 13, 2012.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deadly Betrayal | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990249/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990249/</guid><description>Podcast Description When loving mother Lisa Knoefel is stabbed to death in her home outside Cleveland, her family is shattered. Josh Mankiewicz reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>House of Horrors | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990250/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990250/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Nichole Payne and her son Taylor are found dead in their home, it takes nearly a decade to unravel what happened. For the first time, Nichole’s children Remington and Jackson share what they saw the day their mother and brother were murdered. Andrea Canning reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Mystery of the Murdered Major | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990251/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990251/</guid><description>Podcast Description Army Major David Shannon is executed while asleep in bed. His wife Joan escapes unscathed but doesn’t see the shooter. The crime scene offers few leads until detectives make a bizarre discovery. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on August 12, 2011
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Day She Disappeared | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990252/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990252/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a missing persons case quickly becomes a homicide investigation. Police have no suspects, but a grieving family has suspicions. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on August 19, 2011.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Player | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990253/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990253/</guid><description>Podcast Description It was a double murder that was both shocking and puzzling. There were no witnesses, and few clues. The victims were a respected couple. Their son, it turned out, played poker for a living. Could that lifestyle have had something to do with it? Keith Morrison reports in this Dateline classic. Originally aired on NBC on December 28, 2011.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Suspicion | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990254/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990254/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a loft apartment building in downtown Salt Lake City, Utah, is home to an eclectic group of residents. When a wealthy businessman starts working with two of them, a chain of events is set in motion that leaves one of them dead and another arrested for murder. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on February 3, 2012.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deadly Exposure | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990255/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990255/</guid><description>Podcast Description Accidental carbon monoxide poisoning is the cause for hundreds of American deaths every year, but according to police in Lima, Ohio, one of those deaths wasn’t an accident – in this Dateline classic, they say it was murder. Kate Snow reports. Originally aired on NBC on June 24, 2011.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Taken | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990256/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990256/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a 7-day mystery grips the city of Detroit after a young talented drummer with dreams of rock-and-roll stardom suddenly goes missing. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on September 17, 2010.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Breakout | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990257/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990257/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a Kansas prisoner escapes in a van driven by a wife and mother who volunteers at the prison, investigators scramble to track down the pair. Andrea Canning reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Crossing the Line | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990258/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990258/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, after a fatal car crash, investigators find a series of revealing text messages that lead them to believe it may not have been an accident. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on November 11, 2011.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Pink Gun Mystery | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990259/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990259/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a complicated Texas love triangle ends in murder, a pink gun leads to an arrest, until new evidence prompts investigators to rethink the case. Josh Mankiewicz reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Goldfinger Mystery | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990260/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990260/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, California entrepreneurs James and Pamela Fayed live a golden life. In a few short years they turn a fledgling coin company into a gold trading empire. But when Pamela is brutally stabbed to death and it’s captured on tape, questions about her murder reveal a federal fraud investigation and a marriage filled with lies. Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on January 20, 2012.</description></item><item><title>Deadly Triangle | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990261/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990261/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Gary McFarland awakens on a December morning in 1985 to find his father Archie stabbed to death in the driveway. As police arrive Gary suddenly realizes he knows who did it. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on December 30, 2011.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deadly Conspiracy | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990262/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990262/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a woman leaves her ailing father for just 15 minutes and during that brief time he is stabbed to death. A buried clue indicates the murder was a conspiracy. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on July 15, 2012.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Secrets by the Bay | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990263/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990263/</guid><description>Podcast Description Elizabeth Sullivan, a mother of two, suddenly vanishes in 2014. Nearly two years later, her body is found in the San Diego Bay, but medical examiners say she had only been dead for about a month or two. Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kidnapped | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990264/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990264/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, 24-year-old Elisa Levy thinks she’s headed to a meeting about an environmental project. But the “meeting” is really a setup for abduction. Kate Snow reports. Originally aired on NBC on July 22, 2011.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Wanted Man | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990265/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990265/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Mark Weinberger and his wife Michelle were vacationing in the Greek Islands when he vanished, leaving behind financial ruin and a growing number of malpractice suits. The question of his whereabouts remains unanswered for five years, until a woman halfway across the world discovers the truth. Rob Stafford reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Murder in Broad Daylight | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990266/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990266/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Rusty Sneiderman was a young entrepreneur whose world comes crashing down one morning with four gunshots. A fatal triangle is revealed: Was this a crime of passion? Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on March 16, 2012.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Window of Opportunity | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990267/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990267/</guid><description>Podcast Description A Michigan community is shocked when a local mother is found stabbed to death. After the case goes cold for more than a decade, a bombshell reignites the investigation. Andrea Canning reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Shattered Bonds | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990268/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990268/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Stephen Moore suddenly disappears in New Jersey, his whereabouts remain a mystery until a car erupts in flames in a nearby town, leading to a major break in a case. Andrea Canning reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mystery in Mustang | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990269/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990269/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, beloved fire chief, Keith Bryan, is a pillar of his community. Then, when he is shot in his home, police are left to wonder who would want to hurt the local hero? Turns out, someone was living a secret life, and it was about to be exposed. Andrea Canning reports. Originally aired on NBC on August 2, 2013.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Behind Closed Doors: The Phony Rockefeller | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990270/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990270/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, young newlyweds, John and Linda Sohus simply vanish. There was no reason to suspect foul play until an eerie discovery tied to a case that made international headlines, and was linked to the name of one of America’s most famous families. Mike Taibbi reports. Originally aired on NBC on January 27, 2012.
Justice came in August 2013 for John Sohus. His wife Linda is still missing.</description></item><item><title>The Necklace | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990271/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990271/</guid><description>Podcast Description Private investigator and former police officer Taylor Wright could handle herself, and if necessary, she knew how to disappear. But when she does vanish, detectives think there is more to the story after her girlfriend receives strange text messages from Taylor’s phone. Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Obsession: The Jodi Arias Story | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990272/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990272/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Josh Mankiewicz takes an in-depth look into the case and trial of Jodi Arias, the 32-year-old Arizona woman who admitted to killing her former boyfriend, Travis Alexander. Originally aired on NBC on May 10, 2013.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Someone Was Watching | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990273/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990273/</guid><description>Podcast Description A Dateline classic with a plot straight out of an Alfred Hitchcock film. A young woman peers into her neighbor&amp;rsquo;s yard, and sees something for a few mysterious seconds. Was it some kind of accident, or a crime? Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on October 14, 2011.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sex, Lies &amp; Murder | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990274/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990274/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a woman is murdered, a web of sex and lies is uncovered, revealing a prominent family’s dark secrets. Detectives and an FBI informant tell Dennis Murphy about the case for the first time.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Plot Thickens | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990275/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990275/</guid><description>Podcast Description A Hollywood stuntman is shot four times in his own home and left to die. Who would want him dead? And the most stunning twist in this Dateline classic is what didn’t happen. Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on September 28, 2012.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Story of Poison | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990276/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990276/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, lawyer Larry McNabney, had money, a successful practice and a beautiful wife. But Larry also struggled with alcohol that sometimes caused him to disappear for days on end. When days stretched into weeks and no one heard from him, people began to worry. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on May 18, 2012.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Return to Poplar River | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990277/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990277/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, the small town of Poplar, Montana is shaken when police find the battered body of 17-year-old Kim Nees on the outskirts of town. Keith Morrison reports.
Keith Morrison sits down with Barry Beach to talk about his life as a free man after serving 31 years in prison. After the Verdict is available now only by subscription to Dateline Premium on Apple Podcasts. LINK: https://apple.</description></item><item><title>Mommy Doomsday | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990278/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990278/</guid><description>Podcast Description Exclusive new interviews and details on the deaths surrounding Chad and Lori Vallow Daybell, a case Keith Morrison has been on since it drew national attention after Lori’s children disappeared.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Devil and Bobbi Parker | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990279/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990279/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, convicted murderer Randolph Dial escapes from prison on a hot summer day in 1994, taking the deputy warden’s wife with him. But was she a kidnapped hostage or a willing accomplice? Edie Magnus reports. Originally aired on NBC on September 21, 2012.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Conduct Unbecoming | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990280/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990280/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a family in Ontario, Canada returns home to discover some of their personal items are missing. Was it a random attack, or something more sinister? Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on February 18, 2011.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Night Hannah Hill Disappeared | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990281/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990281/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, an 18-year-old woman disappears one night and her boyfriend confesses to being verbally abusive and once kicked her. But he seems to have a solid alibi and there is evidence that points to someone else. Police work is heavily criticized. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on February 1, 2013.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Woman with No Name | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990282/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990282/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amateur internet investigators, new DNA technology and a dogged investigator help police find a killer – and identify a victim for years known only as &amp;ldquo;Lavender Doe.&amp;rdquo; Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deception | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990283/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990283/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a young sister and brother are torn apart when their mother disappears, and an elaborate sting operation traps a most unlikely villain. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on June 14, 2013.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Life She Wanted | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990284/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990284/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wife and mother Sherri Dally is handcuffed in a parking lot in front of witnesses on a Monday morning and taken into an unmarked car by a blond woman. But when her family reaches out to police, detectives aren’t able to find any record of the arrest. Where could Sherri be?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>In the Middle of the Night in Albuquerque | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990285/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990285/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Albuquerque police are quick to set out for answers after 41-year old Scott Pierce is killed in his home just six days after his wedding. Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on December 7, 2012.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Betrayal | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990286/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990286/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Deede Keller had a loving family, a tight circle of friends and a new man in her life. When she vanished, disturbing clues point investigators to a suspect with a dark secret leading to a case that would provide a twist leaving the courtroom astonished. Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on June 7, 2013.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Fatal Attraction | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990287/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990287/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Beth Lochtefeld seemed to find everything she wanted in a man – looks, money and he was crazy about her. But what she saw, was not what she got. Hoda Kotb reports. Originally aired on NBC on July 19, 2013.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Manner of Death | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990288/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990288/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, the family of 31-year-old Matthew Podolack searches for answers after a mysterious illness sends the healthy, happy amateur hockey player and family man to the emergency room. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on September 27, 2013.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Collateral Damage | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990289/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990289/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former NXIVM members tell Kate Snow about life inside the controversial self-help group, and life since founder Keith Raniere’s conviction on charges including sex trafficking and forced labor.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Widower Ep. 3: The Trial | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990290/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990290/</guid><description>Podcast Description Thomas Randolph strikes back against his accusers in exclusive jailhouse interviews. His trial features revealing and testimony from his accusers, an emotional verdict, and a surprising twist.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Widower Ep. 2: 6 Wives, 4 Funerals | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990291/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990291/</guid><description>Podcast Description Detectives investigating a woman’s murder hit the road to learn about her husband’s 5 other marriages and 3 dead wives. They discover he’s been on trial, in a case that resembles their own.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Widower Ep. 1: “My Wife’s Been Shot” | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990292/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990292/</guid><description>Podcast Description The murder of a Las Vegas wife and mother pits detectives against her wily husband who has many secrets and four dead wives.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Mystery at Ascot Estates | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990293/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990293/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a chilling double murder takes place in an upscale home. The evidence seems to tell a clear story, but investigators discover a marriage that’s filled with secrets, and a story that doesn’t add up. Andrea Canning reports. Originally aired on NBC on July 26, 2013.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Secret in Albuquerque | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990294/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990294/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Mike Snyder, a respected auto mechanic in an upscale subdivision in Albuquerque New Mexico, falls in love with co-worker Ellen Sheffield. They soon marry, but Ellen’s success at work creates tension at home. Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on September 30, 2011.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Shannon's Story | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990295/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990295/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emory University sophomore Shannon Melendi goes missing in broad daylight from her off-campus job at a softball field. As police are interviewing everyone in Shannon’s orbit, they receive a mysterious phone call that changes everything. Dennis Murphy reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Night of the Summer Solstice | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990296/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 18:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990296/</guid><description>Podcast Description Just a few hours after the longest day of the year in 1990, hikers find 21-year-old UCLA student Ron Baker’s body in a Los Angeles area train tunnel. As detectives investigate, they begin to wonder if Ron’s interest in an alternative religion is connected to the murder, but soon discover the suspects are much closer to home. Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>While She Was Sleeping | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990297/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990297/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, the snow covered playground of Aspen, Colorado is a safe haven for well-heeled owners and celebrities. That is until one cold February night when a frantic woman calls 9-1-1 about a discovery at a secluded chalet. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on October 10, 2014.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Grudge | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990298/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990298/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrea Canning speaks with U.S. District Court Judge Esther Salas about the deadly shooting at her home in 2020 that killed her son Daniel and critically injured her husband Mark.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Family Affair | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990299/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990299/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, the scion of the family behind the famous Fontainebleau Hotel on Miami Beach, Ben Novack Jr., grew up with the likes of Frank Sinatra and the Rat Pack. But his murder years later in a New York hotel, launches an investigation that would lead to surprising places and turn his stepdaughter’s life upside down. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on October 12, 2012.</description></item><item><title>Toxic | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990300/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 15:59:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990300/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Kevin and Morgan Mengel were happy at first, but when the marriage went bad, he went missing. Police wondered if he simply left, but a family’s relentless pursuit lead to a stunning confrontation and, eventually, the truth. Hoda Kotb reports. Originally aired on NBC December 27, 2013.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Open Water | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990301/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 15:57:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990301/</guid><description>Podcast Description A romantic Mediterranean cruise was intended to rekindle the love between Micki Kanesaki and her ex-husband Lonnie Kocontes. But when Micki vanishes, an investigation reveals secret recordings, a surprising star witness, and an undercover hitman. Josh Mankiewicz reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Journey for Justice | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990302/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 15:50:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990302/</guid><description>Podcast Description Craig Melvin speaks with the families of George Floyd, Jacob Blake and Eric Garner about police brutality, racial injustice and a shared commitment to turn their pain into advocacy work.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Miles From Nowhere | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990303/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990303/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a young father in the California mountains calls 911 to report that he had been in a shoot-out with a car full of strangers. With one man dead and two others injured, authorities wonder if this was self-defense or something else. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on October 18, 2013.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Secret Life of the Homecoming Queen | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990304/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990304/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a football player and homecoming queen fall in love, but when the husband is found stabbed to death, authorities begin to investigate a trail of evidence. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on May 21, 2010.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Stranger | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990305/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990305/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Brittany Tavar disappears from her home, along with her dogs, leaving friends and family baffled and worried. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on March 17, 2013.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Man Who Talked to Dogs | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990306/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990306/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, life seemed perfect for Mark Stover. He had a successful career as a “dog trainer to the stars” on a beautiful island paradise. After a tough divorce, he’d recently found love again. Yet friends said he walked around in a constant state of fear. Could he sense the danger no one else could see? Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on January 21, 2011.</description></item><item><title>The Wire | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990307/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990307/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a young nurse in southern California is taking in the sun and surf, tackling a new job and making new friends. Everything seems to be going great for Lynne Knight until her screams shatter a summer night. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on October 3, 2014.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Beauty and the Beast Mystery | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990308/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990308/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Lisa and Scott Pattison marry on a fairy tale day and build a life together in central Indiana. But one day in July 2009, their marriage comes to a horrifying end as Scott races his gravely injured wife to the hospital, calling 911. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on February 25, 2011.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Secrets in the Smoky Mountains | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990309/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990309/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, the death of a beloved Tennessee man is believed to be a suicide. But when a son questions his mother, he uncovers a dark family conspiracy. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on October 21, 2016.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Life and Death of Princess Diana | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990310/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990310/</guid><description>Podcast Description More than two decades since the tragic death of Princess Diana, Dateline reveals new insights into the real story of the very private royal, including a look at Diana’s troubled marriage, her turbulent life in the royal family and the investigation into her death. With the rise in popularity of The Crown, Andrea Canning reports on how much of it is true and what was really happening behind the palace gates.</description></item><item><title>The Eastlake Conspiracy | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990311/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990311/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Ohio resident Pat Sabo is offered $50,000 to kill someone hundreds of miles away, he calls the police to report the incident. Acting quickly, investigators set up an elaborate sting operation to bring down those behind the murder-for-hire plot. Andrea Canning reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Secret | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990312/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990312/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Patricia Esparza believed she had escaped poverty and abuse, attending elite schools and becoming a respected psychology professor. But a dark secret comes back to haunt her when a determined investigator and prosecutor in Orange County work to solve a 20-year-old murder case. Andrea Canning reports. Originally aired on NBC on May 15, 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mystery on Sunrise Drive | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990313/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990313/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a Tucson, Arizona native, Gary Triano was a successful real estate developer and entrepreneur. He was known around town for his big spending ways and the elite company he kept. And then came the day that changed everything. Gary’s car was blown to pieces, with him inside, just days before his 53rd birthday. Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on June 20, 2014.</description></item><item><title>Into the Night | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990314/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990314/</guid><description>Podcast Description Following a night at her friend’s bachelorette party, 23-year-old Kaylee Sawyer disappears. Soon after, an intense multi-state manhunt leads investigators to the killer. Friday’s broadcast features new interviews with Kaylee’s mom and the family’s lawyer after they reached a settlement with the killer’s employer, as well as never-before-released deposition tapes with the killer’s co-workers. Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bringing Brooke Home | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990315/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990315/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, 19-year-old Brooke Wilberger returns home to Oregon for summer break from college. While cleaning apartments in Corvallis she vanishes, leaving behind her flip flops. Kate Snow reports. Originally aired on NBC on February 4, 2011.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Far from Spider Lake | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990316/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990316/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the small town of Brewster, Minnesota, 40-year-old Jan Kruse is shot to death in her bed while her husband and teenage daughter are home. When investigators rule out robbery as a motive, it leaves them asking – who would want to kill Jan? Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Behind Closed Doors | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990317/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990317/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a terrible crime has occurred in a Florida suburb, which makes little sense to police. Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on April 10, 2013.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>In the Middle of the Night | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990318/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990318/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, after college student Angie Samota was stabbed to death, police had no shortage of suspects; a crucial clue narrowed their list to one name, but it would be years before technology and a tenacious friend came together to help unravel this mystery. Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on June 8, 2012.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Officer's Wife | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990319/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990319/</guid><description>Podcast Description When police officer Levi Chavez finds his wife, Tera, shot to death in their home, an investigation into her murder begins as buried secrets are revealed. Josh Mankiewicz reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Who Killed the Radio Star? | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990320/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990320/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, weekend boaters just off California’s fabled Catalina island discover a body floating in the water. The victim turns out to be a well-known radio personality. What happened to Steven B. Williams? Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on June 3, 2012.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Vanished: Amber Dubois &amp; Chelsea King | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990321/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990321/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, when Amber Dubois vanished in San Diego County, a search turned up nothing. Then, a year later, Chelsea King disappeared in a neighboring town. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on September 3, 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>10 Minutes to Sunset | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990322/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990322/</guid><description>Podcast Description When pediatric dentist Kendra Hatcher is found dead in Dallas, Texas, police uncover a complex plot that leads them on an international manhunt. Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Buried Secrets | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990323/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990323/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a Florida man disappears into thin air, leaving behind a young son and a grieving ex-wife. When his bones are identified years later, a rookie detective is determined to uncover the truth. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on July 6, 2012.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Secrets in a Small Town | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990324/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990324/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Teresa Mayfield’s death on a dirt road was a mystery for more than a year until a strange sequence of events led investigators to an unlikely suspect. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on January 8, 2012
Transcript</description></item><item><title>In an Instant | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990325/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990325/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Keith Morrison reports on the case of a wife who supposedly died from an allergic reaction to a spray tan. So why was her husband charged with murder? Originally aired on NBC on June 8, 2012.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Comic Book Murder | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990326/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990326/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Barbara George is rushed to the hospital after being found bleeding in the back of the comic book store she owned in suburban Detroit. What the nurse finds launches a decade long mystery. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on January 25, 2013.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Mystery on Bridle Path | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990327/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990327/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Carol Kennedy returns from an evening jog in Prescott, Arizona and calls her mother Ruth. Their nightly phone ends abruptly. So begins the Mystery on Bridle Path. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on March 28, 2014.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deadly Trust | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990328/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990328/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, wealthy residents felt safe in their gated community but it was not safe for one millionaire, murdered in his waterfront home. Police investigated but the case grew cold. Turned out the key to solving it, or two keys, were right at the front door. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on April 13, 2012.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Fallen | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990329/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990329/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, when a pastor loses two wives in suspicious accidents, authorities begin to wonder if it was terrible luck or something else. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on February 8, 2013.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Strangers on a Train | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990330/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990330/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, when a young woman disappears following a chance encounter with a stranger on a train, her desperate family hires a dream team of detectives to follow the mysterious trail she left behind. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on October 7, 2011.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lone Star Obsession | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990331/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990331/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a doctor is found murdered, investigators are stumped as to who would want him dead. Police discover simmering jealousies and a love triangle. Andrea Canning has the latest developments. Originally aired on NBC on October 8, 2020.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Burning Suspicion | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990332/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990332/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, investigators question what went wrong when a young wife and mother is found dead after a house fire in a small Kansas town. Was it an act of murder? Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on October 11, 2013.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Double Lives | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990333/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990333/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, police discover a mother of three was living a dangerous double life after she vanishes in Colorado. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on March 31, 2017.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Secrets of Cottonwood Creek | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990334/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990334/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Fred and Leslie Mueller are weeks away from celebrating their 27th wedding anniversary when a photo-op during a hike goes horribly wrong. Andrea Canning reports. Originally aired on NBC on May 30, 2014.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Left for Dead | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990335/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990335/</guid><description>Podcast Description A young woman survives a brutal attack and detectives work tirelessly to find a suspect. But when they finally do, the victim is convinced they have the wrong man. Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trouble at the 7-11 Ranch | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990336/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990336/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a Colorado rancher mysteriously disappears, his friends know something isn’t right and spend years fighting for answers. Josh Mankiewicz reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Queen of the County | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990337/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990337/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, the matriarch of a prominent pecan growing family in San Saba, Texas goes missing and her caretaker is murdered. Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on April 23, 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>And Then There Were Three | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990338/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990338/</guid><description>Podcast Description Just days before Christmas, high school senior Michelle Martinko is found stabbed to death in her car after visiting the mall. It would take almost 40 years for investigators to identify the killer – and when they did, Martinko’s family and friends were stunned. Dennis Murphy reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Rise &amp; Fall of Oscar Pistorius | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990339/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990339/</guid><description>Podcast Description Oscar Pistorius, nicknamed “Blade Runner,” is an international celebrity when he shoots and kills his girlfriend just 8 months after competing in the London Olympics. Charged with murder, he tells police it was a tragic mistake and that he was acting in self-defense as he believed he was firing at an intruder. Keith Morrison reports on the aftermath of the judge’s verdict and the ensuing court battle.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Mansion on Ocean Boulevard | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990340/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990340/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, when two tragic deaths occur within one week of each other in a wealthy area in California, families begin to wonder what happened inside a beachfront mansion. Josh Mankiewicz reports. Updated on January 24, 2021.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Death in the Driveway | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990341/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990341/</guid><description>Podcast Description Police in a quiet Southern town, find a prominent lawyer brutally murdered and his girlfriend bound in duct tape. Who could have done it? Andrea Canning reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mystery in Orange County: Behind the Scenes | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990342/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990342/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josh Mankiewicz reflects on one of his most memorable episodes: the case of 36-year-old Iraq War veteran Maribel Ramos who calls 911 to reveal she is scared for her safety. When she later disappears, investigators have to figure out who exactly she was afraid of.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deadly House of Cards | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990343/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990343/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, when Johnny Altinger sent strange emails to friends saying he skipped off to Costa Rica with a new girlfriend and doesn’t respond to phone calls, a missing person investigation begins that leads detectives into a hall of mirrors where fact and fantasy merge. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on September 16, 2011.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Man Who Wasn't There | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990344/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990344/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a family’s American dream turns into a nightmare when their mother is murdered in their home one night. The mystery goes unsolved for years until a new detective reopens the case, resulting in an undercover sting operation and unexpected twists and turns. Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on July 25, 2014.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Written in Blood | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990345/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990345/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Karen Pannell, a one-time model and flight attendant, is found murdered in her kitchen. On the wall next to her body is a message written in her own blood: the letters R O C. What does it mean? Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on August 17, 2012.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Inside Man | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990346/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990346/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Jimmy Keene, a popular, superstar high school athlete, seemed to have it all growing up in the river city of Kankakee, Illinois. But then, he began selling drugs and moved to Chicago, where his business boomed but a danger lurked 150 miles south that would change his life forever. Lester Holt reports. Originally aired on NBC on September 14, 2012.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Without a Trace | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990347/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990347/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, an entire community pulls together in the search for 29 year-old Carrie Olson after she is reported missing when doesn’t show up for work. Detectives suspect foul play and soon focus their investigation on two men in her life. Andrea Canning reports. Originally aired on NBC on October 23, 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Death of a Golden Girl | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990348/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990348/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Dennis Murphy reports on the case of a 26 year-old model and aspiring Playboy Playmate who goes missing after visiting a Miami nightclub with her boyfriend. Within 24 hours of her disappearance, police find her brutally murdered. Originally aired on NBC on March 19, 2010.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deadly Desire | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990349/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990349/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, after a Idaho woman falls in love with her married boss, the affair leads to a violent confrontation. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on May 3, 2013.
Listen to Keith and Ashlee discuss how she and her children are doing today, her story of loss, resilience, and the desire to help others heal from tragedy.
After the Verdict available now only by subscription to Dateline Premium on Apple Podcasts.</description></item><item><title>Mystery in South Beach | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990350/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990350/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a young bride is found beaten to death just days after the wedding. As detectives begin their investigation, suspicious details are uncovered. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on May 11, 2014.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Hometown Hero &amp; The Homecoming Queen | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990351/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990351/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, an Olympic athlete and a homecoming queen share a life in the charming suburb of Oxnard, California until gunshots are fired in their backyard on a late summer night in 2009. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on April 1, 2016.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>In Cold Blood | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990352/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990352/</guid><description>Podcast Description A firefighter returns home after a long shift to find a disturbingly violent scene and his wife unresponsive in their bedroom. What could have happened? Andrea Canning reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deadly Devotion | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990353/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990353/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a decorated army captain returns home safe and sound from Saudi Arabia. But a few months later &amp;ndash; tragedy strikes. Who would want to hurt this beloved commander? Andrea Canning reports. Originally aired on NBC on March 11, 2016.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Place on the Sand | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990354/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990354/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Florida motel owner, Sabine Musil-Buehler, suddenly disappears, leaving family, friends and detectives wondering what could have happened to her. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on February 19, 2016.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Footprint in the Dust | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990355/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990355/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Susie Casey, a mother of four, goes missing in the small town of Glendive, Montana, it begins an investigation with many twists and turns. Keith Morrison reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Good Husband | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990356/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990356/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Tom Kolman is found dead in his car, there is no evidence that points to unnatural causes. But as detectives begin to look into his inner circle, they uncover a love triangle that turns the tragedy into a tangled mystery. Andrea Canning reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Sister's Search | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990357/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990357/</guid><description>Podcast Description When actress Aasha Davis and her sister Lesley move to Hollywood, things appear to be going well. But just as Aasha’s star is rising, Lesley suddenly vanishes. Josh Mankiewicz reports.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Killing in Cobb County | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990358/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990358/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a story of obsession boils over into a brutal crime. Right away, one woman said she knew what happened. Yet, it takes years to bring the alleged killer to trial with a verdict that was far from the end of this case. Andrea Canning reports. Originally aired on NBC on November 29, 2013.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Dangerous Man | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990359/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990359/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, the investigation into the mysterious murder of a Spokane, WA businessman exposes a tangled web of evil that extends from the Pacific Northwest into the North Dakota oil patch. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on October 14, 2016.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Shot in the Dark | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990360/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990360/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, after Cara Ryan shoots her ex-husband and accuses him of threatening to kill her, police question her motive. Ryan speaks out to Keith Morrison about the outcome of the stunning trial. Originally aired on NBC on May 12, 2017.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Troubled Waters | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990361/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990361/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a romantic getaway on a boat turns tragic when a young wife &amp;amp; mother is lost at sea. The case goes cold for years — until a model with a checkered past goes undercover. Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on November 20, 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Twisted | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990362/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990362/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, an Iowa mother, home alone with her three children, is attacked. The confrontation turns fatal. But is the truth more twisted than anyone could imagine? Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on June 1, 2012.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Last Dance | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990363/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990363/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a mother of two vanishes from her home, leading investigators to uncover a disturbing connection between her recent weight loss and her mysterious disappearance. Andrea Canning reports. Originally aired on NBC on April 3, 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Long Road to Freedom | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990364/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990364/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two Tulsa, Oklahoma brothers fight for more than 20 years to prove their innocence after they were each wrongfully convicted for separate murders. Craig Melvin reports. Originally aired on NBC on June 19, 2020.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>After Midnight | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990365/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990365/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a mother’s intuition leads campus cops in Western New York to a terrible discovery in a dorm room. How could a boyfriend’s weekend visit to see his girlfriend go so horribly wrong? Andrea Canning reports. Originally aired on NBC on January 4, 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Vanished | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990366/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990366/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Sandi Johnson, a devoted mother, mysteriously vanishes the day before her son’s 5th birthday party. Andrea Canning reports. Originally aired on NBC on May 9, 2014.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Promise | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990367/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 15:37:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990367/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, two tenacious daughters set out on a quest to fulfill a promise they made to their mom. Listen as these daughters-turned-detectives try to solve the mystery surrounding their mother’s death. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on May 2, 2014.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Secrets on Hot Springs Drive | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990368/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990368/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Kay Parsons and Becky Sears are best friends and neighbors in quiet, residential Grovetown, Georgia. One morning, both of their homes are burglarized. Inside one of them, investigators find a bloody trail leading to the garage. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on May 8, 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Secrets in the Snow | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990369/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990369/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, after Stephanie Bruner goes missing in the Colorado mountains, three suspects and a love triangle complicate the investigation. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on October 5, 2012.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Indiscretion | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990370/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990370/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a young woman is found brutally murdered in her Baltimore home. Police find themselves stumped for over a decade &amp;ndash; until a DNA breakthrough leads to surprising suspects. Could two determined detectives crack the cold case? Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on July 31, 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Someone Was Waiting | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990371/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990371/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, detectives in Frisco, Texas uncover a series of suspects after a woman is found dead in her garage &amp;ndash; all of them connected in different ways to her complicated and secretive life. Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on December 9, 2016.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dangerous Liaisons | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990372/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990372/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, when a 33-year-old Catholic high school tutor in Grand Rapids, Michigan is charged with having an illegal relationship with a 15-year-old student, her stunning defense leads to an emotional courtroom battle. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on June 4, 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mystery in Big Sky Country | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990373/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990373/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Bryan Rein, a young Montana veterinarian, is found dead at his home with a gun nearby, police quickly discover there is more to this case than meets the eye. As the investigation spans more than two decades, police sort through conflicting evidence to find out what really happened. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on May 22, 2020.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Secrets in Seattle | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990374/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990374/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Nicole Pietz appeared to be on top of the world, but when her body is found miles from home, detectives are determined to dig into her past. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on November 20, 2013.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deadly Denial | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990375/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990375/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, when Raven Abaroa comes home to find his wife stabbed to death, detectives began digging into the couple’s complicated past. Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on April 25, 2014.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Silent Witness | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990376/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990376/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Michelle Young, pregnant with her second child, is brutally murdered while her husband Jason is away on business. Who would kill this beloved young mother? Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on March 30, 2012.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Promise Kept | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990377/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990377/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Cathy Torrez was a beautiful, smart and responsible 20-year-old student. So why didn&amp;rsquo;t she come home after work like she was supposed to? Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on April 24, 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>At Close Range | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990378/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990378/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, the body of a school superintendent is found by his home in western New York. As his family struggles to make sense of the horror, investigators look for answers. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on March 21, 2014.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Unbreakable | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990379/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990379/</guid><description>Podcast Description The story of Rebecca Musser vs. FLDS leader and notorious FBI fugitive Warren Jeffs. Rebecca opens up to Keith Morrison about life in the church and why she decided to leave the denomination. Originally aired on NBC on May 8, 2020.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mystery at Heath Bar Farm | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990380/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990380/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Tom Foley, once a hometown hero in Coldwater, Michigan, is shocked to find himself as the lead suspect in the case of his wife Darlene&amp;rsquo;s murder. Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on November 18, 2011.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Last Day | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990381/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990381/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, when Erin Corwin tells her husband she is going out to scout hiking trails in Joshua Tree National Park, she vanishes without a trace. Andrea Canning reports. Originally aired on NBC on December 2, 2016.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Infatuation | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990382/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990382/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Shelley Nance, a talented young art student, is found stabbed to death in her bed, sparking a police investigation with many twists and turns. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on March 13, 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Informant | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990383/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990383/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Heidi Allen, an 18-year-old college student and convenience store clerk in Oswego County, NY goes missing in broad daylight on Easter Sunday 1994. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on May 20, 2016.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Before Daylight | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990384/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990384/</guid><description>Podcast Description When college student Jesse Valencia is found murdered in a residential neighborhood, investigators are left without any answers in sight. But as police search for the truth, they are stunned to learn that one of their own might be involved. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on April 24, 2020.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Perfect Spot | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990385/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990385/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a romantic Valentine’s Day evening at the park turns into a horrifying crime scene for married couple, Stacey and Richard Schoeck. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on April 9, 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Deed | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990386/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990386/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a couple in rural South Carolina is brutally murdered in their home, the investigation into who committed this heinous act tears a family apart. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on March 4, 2016.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mystery on the Jordan River | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990387/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990387/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a teenage girl is murdered at a scenic spot on a Utah river. The case almost goes cold until Jaclyn Moore, a hairdresser turned detective, finds the truth. Originally aired on NBC on May 6, 2016.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Missing Mickey | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990388/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990388/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, when college student Mickey Shunick vanishes, her sister becomes the driving force in a multinational search effort. Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on January 29, 2013.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Secrets at the Sunshine Motel | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990389/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990389/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, the family of a beloved and successful Yakima real estate agent is left in disbelief when he is attacked while showing a home. Who would want to hurt Vern Holbrook? Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on February 13, 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>BONUS Interview: Josh Mankiewicz and Joe Exotic | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990390/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990390/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shortly after his April 2019 conviction on two counts of murder for hire, “Tiger King” Joe Exotic spoke from prison with Dateline’s Josh Mankiewicz.
Watch Josh’s interview with Joe Exotic here: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P-KBOpkoM2s&amp;t=2s
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Secrets of the Snake River | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990391/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990391/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, strange, unsettling things were happening to Rachael. Then, the young mother vanishes. What could have happened? Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on January 9, 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Road Trip | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990392/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990392/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Dr. Teresa Sievers is found murdered in her kitchen, detectives struggle to find any leads until an unexpected tip changes everything. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on April 3, 2020.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Bathtub Mystery | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990393/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990393/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Ryan and Sarah are newlyweds of just 114 days. Home together on a quiet Monday evening, no one could ever imagine how their lives would soon take a turn for the worst. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on May 6, 2011.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What Lies Beneath | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990394/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990394/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a young mother in South Florida disappeared just days before she planned to move to a new city with her son. Law enforcement agencies set out for clues, but it was a chance encounter by custom agents patrolling the night sea that led to a major break. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on February 6, 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Return to the Lonely Road | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990395/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990395/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brittany Stork’s decades-long quest to find out more about her mother’s mysterious death leads to a dramatic courtroom decision. The man at the center of the case tells his story to Dennis Murphy. Originally aired on NBC on March 27, 2020.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Haunting | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990396/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990396/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a pair of double homicides in Nebraska, five years apart, lead police to fear a serial killer may be on the loose. Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on March 17, 2017.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>In Broad Daylight | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990397/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990397/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a quiet, leafy street in Long Beach, California where violent crimes are nearly unheard of, is shocked one November morning when a terrible murder happens. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on March 6, 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Ranch | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990398/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990398/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Valseca siblings’ lives are changed when their father is taken hostage in an orchestrated abduction. For the first time, they open up about how their mother faced a band of international criminals to bring their father home. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired March 20, 2020.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Killing in Cottonwood | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990399/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990399/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a family many saw as &amp;lsquo;perfect&amp;rsquo; in an All-American town experiences a tragedy that shakes their faith and family. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on January 3, 2014.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Miami Heat | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990400/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990400/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a drive by shooting tears a Miami family apart and Cindy Carballo is left wondering who could have killed her husband. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on July 10, 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Perfect Guy | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990401/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990401/</guid><description>Podcast Description A fugitive steals millions of dollars by conning numerous women and businesses over 25 years. Will law enforcement finally be able to catch him? Andrea Canning reports. Originally aired on NBC on March 6, 2020.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Finding Sarah Goode | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990402/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990402/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a large, tight-knit family on Long Island goes to extraordinary lengths to find their youngest sister after she goes missing. Andrea Canning reports. Updated on May 15, 2020.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The House on the Hill | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990403/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990403/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Karl Karlsen’s wife, Christina, dies in a catastrophic house fire, he moves to upstate New York. Nearly 20 years later, his oldest son dies in a freak accident, leading police to question if Karl is involved. Andrea Canning reports. Originally aired on NBC on February 28, 2020.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Before Dawn | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990404/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990404/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, newlyweds Seth and Lisa Techel are expecting their first child, but a shotgun blast shatters their dreams on Memorial Day weekend, 2011. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on September 26, 2014.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Frantic | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990405/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990405/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Christina Morris vanishes while at a high-end shopping mall. Her family members search for her, while police try to find out who might have been responsible for her disappearance. Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on March 24, 2017.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Woman Who Couldn’t Scream | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990406/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990406/</guid><description>Podcast Description After hearing someone break into their apartment, two women call 911 and barricade themselves in the bathroom until help arrives. Little do they know, their call for help holds the key to solving the mysterious murder of a young graduate student named Katie Sepich.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Under the Prairie Sky | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990407/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990407/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a mother of three mysteriously disappears. The only clue is her abandoned vehicle on a lonely Montana highway. Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on May 21, 2017.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Evil to Come | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990408/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990408/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, successful businesswoman and caring mom Peggy Nadell is found murdered in her Rockland County home. Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on May 28, 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Devil's Bargain | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990409/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990409/</guid><description>Podcast Description Family members and the lead investigators who cracked the Kelsey Berreth case speak out for the first time and take Andrea Canning inside the murder investigation. Originally aired on NBC on February 7, 2020.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Heart of Darkness | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990410/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990410/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a man in Virginia learns that his wife and son have been kidnapped by a group of international terrorists demanding millions in ransom while on vacation in the Philippines. With time running out, the FBI joins the case, which comes to a heart-stopping conclusion. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on May 28, 2017.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deadly Twist | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990411/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990411/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, California mother, Rachel Winkler, is found dead in her home. Her husband tells law enforcement he killed her in self-defense, but they soon find something from his past that changes everything. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on March 20, 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Abducted | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990412/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990412/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrea Canning reports on the case that made national headlines in December 2019, when a Texas mother was found murdered after she and her newborn daughter disappeared. Originally aired on NBC on January 31, 2020.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Poison | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990413/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990413/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, newlyweds Paul and Linda Curry come down with a mysterious illness. Paul recovers but Linda is hospitalized and the strange symptoms won’t go away. Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on December 12, 2014.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Mystery Man | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990414/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990414/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a woman looking for love finds Mr. Right – but he soon pulls her into a dark world of undercover espionage where nothing is as it seems. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on January 25, 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>After the Party | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990415/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990415/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, hours after saying goodbye to her guests at her New Years Eve Party, Ashley Fallis is dead. Years later it would be up to a jury to decide whether it was suicide or murder. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on May 22, 2016.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Betrayed | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990416/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990416/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, something seems off when rising star attorney Melissa Lewis doesn&amp;rsquo;t show up for work one day. What friends and family find sets off major alarms and the beginning of a bizarre mystery. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on March 3, 2017.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mystery on the Mississippi | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990417/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990417/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a mother of four dies unexpectedly on Valentine’s Day. Everyone in town assumes she died of natural causes until a detective suspects someone has gotten away with murder. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on October 6, 2017.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mystery on Lockhart Road | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990418/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990418/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, former Indiana State Police trooper David Camm arrives home and finds his wife and children murdered in their garage. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on January 31, 2014.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nightfall | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990419/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990419/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, investigators scramble to find a killer after a young mother is found dead 40 miles from Knoxville, Tennessee on the side of a country road. Andrea Canning reports. Originally aired on NBC on April 14, 2017.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Death of Gianni Versace | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990420/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990420/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Gianni Versace’s longtime partner Antonio D’Amico speaks about the murder of the fashion icon. Versace’s murder came amid a months-long manhunt for Andrew Cunanan, who was accused of committing four other murders throughout the country in 1997. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on April 28, 2017.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Music Box | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990421/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990421/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Lisa Ziegert is abducted during her evening shift at a gift shop, local detectives, state police and the FBI work relentlessly to find her. Her family keeps the case in the public eye for decades, until the dogged investigators finally solve the mystery. Andrea Canning reports. Originally aired on NBC on January 10, 2020.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Silhouette | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990422/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990422/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a husband shoots his wife, saying he mistook her for an intruder one early morning in San Antonio, Texas. Was this a terrible accident or a case of deliberate murder? Andrea Canning reports. Originally aired on NBC on June 16, 2017.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>At the Bottom of the Pool | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990423/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990423/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a model and up and coming YouTube celebrity is found dead. Police question her husband to see if he can provide any answers. Keith Morrison reports on what could have led to her death. Originally aired on NBC on October 13, 2017.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>After the Storm | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990424/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990424/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, when a beautiful woman is strangled to death in her Texas home, police look at the men in the victim’s life, while also considering that a stranger may have killed her. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on September 23, 2016.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mystery on Blood Mountain | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990425/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990425/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, hiker Meredith Emerson goes missing on Georgia&amp;rsquo;s Blood Mountain on New Year&amp;rsquo;s Day 2008. Law enforcement officers become concerned after finding a police baton with some her possessions on a trail. Dateline NBC&amp;rsquo;s Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on August 26, 2011.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>As Night Fell | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990426/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990426/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a young woman is shot in her home just outside Salt Lake City, Utah. Was it an accident? Or something far more sinister? Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on June 23, 2017.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Poisoned | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990427/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990427/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, the unexplained death of a beloved chiropractor becomes a criminal investigation when authorities discover she’d been poisoned. Andrea Canning reports. Originally aired on NBC on December 1, 2017.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Shadow | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990428/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990428/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a home in a small Iowa town is disturbed in the middle of the night by an intruder. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on September 11, 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bad Blood | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990429/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990429/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Twin sisters Jasmiyah and Tasmiyah Whitehead discover their mother Nikki savagely murdered in their home. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on August 1, 2014.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deadly Exchange | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990430/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990430/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, foreign exchange student Diren Dede’s dream to study in America came true when he started his junior year at a Montana high school. When he takes a midnight walk with a friend, a Saturday night turns into a tragedy. Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on April 30, 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Unusual Suspect | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990431/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990431/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, investigators question if there is a serial killer in a suburb of Maryland when two mothers and their teenage daughters are murdered. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on January 23, 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Family Secrets | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990432/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990432/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a father and his sons have a dream to build an extreme sports theme park. But reality hits when the dad is found dead on the floor of their Skim-X warehouse. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on September 16, 2016.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Final Curtain | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990433/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990433/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Rachel Buffett speaks to Dateline about being at the center of a murder investigation involving both her former fiancée and her friend, a 26-year-old Army veteran. Josh Mankiewicz reports on the details of the gripping and twisted case that made international headlines. Originally aired on NBC on November 30, 2018.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Devil Was Watching | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990434/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990434/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Tina Sandoval disappears, her parents and loved ones spend years searching for any signs of her. Law enforcement is convinced she is the victim of foul play, but the prosecution has a problem. How can they convince a jury that she was murdered if there is no body, no crime scene and no physical evidence? Meanwhile, Tina was keeping a dark secret, one that might lead to clues about what happened to her.</description></item><item><title>Smoke and Mirrors | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990435/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990435/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, when a Chicago pharmaceutical representative stops returning calls, her large and loving family begin to worry. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on March 18, 2016.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Knock at the Door | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990436/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990436/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, the case of a young woman found murdered turns cold soon after she is found. Will her mother’s search for answers bring justice? Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on July 7, 2017.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>In a Lonely Place - Update | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990437/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990437/</guid><description>Podcast Description When California entrepreneur Chris Smith is murdered, his family is shocked. They had believed he had sold his company, broken up with this girlfriend and was traveling the world with a Playboy Playmate. In a December 6, 2019 update, the man convicted of his murder speaks with Keith Morrison.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tangled Web | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990438/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990438/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, investigators discover a twisted tale of secrets, lies and infidelity after a beloved firefighter is murdered just outside Sarasota, Florida. Andrea Canning reports. Originally aired on NBC on February 5, 2016.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deadly Intent | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990439/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990439/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a car bomb explodes in front of a suburban San Diego day care home. Josh Mankiewicz reports on the driver, a married mother of three children. Originally aired on NBC on October 4, 2013.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>While They Were Sleeping | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990440/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990440/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Melissa Oxley wakes up to find her husband, Ben Oxley, shot in the head next to her. No one in the house sees or hears anything. Who could have committed this brutal murder? Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC May 4, 2012.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The House in the Woods | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990441/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990441/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a former hockey player discovers his wife murdered in their own home. His young daughter says she saw a robber, but the killer&amp;rsquo;s true identity turns out to be far more complicated. Andrea Canning reports. Originally aired on NBC on March 24, 2017.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>At the Bottom of the Lake | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990442/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 22:11:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990442/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a pilot flees after a deadly plane crash, and becomes a fugitive living a double life for decades. He tells his story to Keith Morrison. Originally aired on NBC on October 12, 2018.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Secrets &amp; Lies | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990443/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990443/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a woman is found dead in the debris of her house that burned to the ground early one frigid morning in a small rural New York town. Andrea Canning reports. Originally aired on NBC on November 6, 2013.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Black Widow of Lomita | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990444/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990444/</guid><description>Podcast Description A California woman’s two former husbands are mysteriously murdered, nearly 20 years apart. She becomes known as the “Black Widow of Lomita” and is able to elude police, until fate catches up with her. Keith Morrison reports from the Philippines on this international story which features the sister of one of the victims who never stopped fighting to learn what really happened to her brother. Originally aired on NBC on November 8, 2019.</description></item><item><title>Obsession | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990445/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990445/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a young Wisconsin college student with a passion for music is mysteriously found dead in her bed, but it&amp;rsquo;s another woman&amp;rsquo;s unbelievable courage that ultimately leads police to her killer. Andrea Canning reports. Originally aired on NBC on January 30, 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Consumed | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990446/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990446/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a home in Kentucky is ravaged by fire in the middle of the night. Firefighters work their way to the master bedroom where they make a grisly discovery. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on April 8, 2016.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Box | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990447/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990447/</guid><description>Podcast Description Years after a Montana man is found dead, his son dreads what he’ll find when he opens up the box of case files, giving him insight into what really happened. Keith Morrison reports on his journey and the murder investigation that unraveled a revenge plot. Originally aired on NBC on October 25, 2019.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Halloween Party | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990448/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990448/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, detectives settle in for a long investigation while a Michigan town searches for clues when one of their residents goes missing from a Halloween party. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on October 27, 2017.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Shining Star | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990449/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990449/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, an up-and-coming Baton Rouge defense attorney is found dead in her office after a long night at work. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on July 17, 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Pink Skirt Plot | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990450/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990450/</guid><description>Podcast Description The murder of a young businessman in Old San Juan, Puerto Rico marks the start of a 15-year-long hunt to find the killer. As his devoted father’s quest for justice uncovers secrets and spans continents, the FBI begins an international game of cat and mouse to catch those responsible for his son’s murder. Natalie Morales reports. Originally aired on NBC on October 18, 2019.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The House on Badger Lane | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990451/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990451/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, the three young children of a couple who live in a gated community in California hear a thump one morning that becomes the first clue in a mystery that will expose family secrets. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on January 31, 2016.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Something Sweet | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990452/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990452/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a retired corrections officer mysteriously dies from antifreeze poisoning in rural Ohio. Detectives uncover multiple suspects during a five-year investigation that causes two families to collide. Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on December 11, 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Devil in Disguise | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990453/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990453/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, an ex-Navy man marries the love of his life. Five months later, his new bride finds him dead on their bedroom floor leaving family and authorities puzzled. Who would want him dead? Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on June 12, 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Plan | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990454/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990454/</guid><description>Podcast Description A double homicide in upstate New York leads detectives on a cross country investigation to piece together a case with a surprising suspect at the center. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on October 11, 2019.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Crack in Everything | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990455/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990455/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, when a woman is found dead in her home, it&amp;rsquo;s ruled a suicide. But when a new investigation begins, police question if this is a murder case. Will the truth be revealed? Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on March 30, 2018.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Haunted | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990456/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990456/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nearly 10 years after Utah mother Susan Powell vanished, private journals, home videos and emails shed new light on what happened to her. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on October 4, 2019.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Thing About Pam | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990457/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990457/</guid><description>Podcast Description The unbelievable story of how the murder of one woman, Betsy Faria, set off a chain of events leaving one man dead, another man implicated and a diabolical scheme exposed. Keith Morrison unravels the latest chapter, including why Betsy’s friend, Pam Hupp, impersonated a real-life Dateline producer. Listen in conjunction with the hit 6-episode behind-the-scenes podcast of the same name. Originally aired on NBC on September 27, 2019.</description></item><item><title>Finding Venus | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990458/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990458/</guid><description>Podcast Description A mother of two mysteriously vanishes from her parents&amp;rsquo; home in Michigan while going to check the mailbox, leaving her phone and identification behind. Police declare her dead before they even find her body. The disappearance and complicated investigation takes years for detectives to unravel. Dennis Murphy reports on the most recent developments in the case. Originally aired on NBC on January 20, 2019.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Creek | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990459/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990459/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Danielle Locklear, a popular and charismatic high school freshman leaves home to drop off a notebook at her classmate’s house and never returns. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on April 4, 2018.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Watcher | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990460/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990460/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a recent law school graduate in Georgia with a promising future disappears without a trace. What could have happened? Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on June 8, 2018.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Match | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990461/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990461/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, a high school girl, who was nearly beaten to death in her own home, goes under hypnosis in an attempt to identify her attacker. Andrea Canning reports. Originally aired on NBC on September 7, 2018.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Deal with the Devil | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990462/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 13:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990462/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, Keith Morrison reports on a notorious serial killer, nicknamed Hannibal, who murdered several people while working as a confidential informant for the FBI. The two-hour broadcast tells the inside story of how he was ultimately caught. Originally aired on NBC on September 21, 2018.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Under the Desert Sky | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990463/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 13:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990463/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, the murder of a Nevada teenager shakes the community to its core when the two most unlikely people make a shocking confession. Keith Morrison reports. Originally aired on NBC on January 4, 2013.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Secrets of the Desert | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990464/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 17:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990464/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, the mystery surrounding the deaths of three women deep in the Sonoran desert takes 17 years to untangle, and is only solved when a fourth woman comes forward with the truth. Dennis Murphy reports. Originally aired on NBC on May 19, 2017.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Twisted in Texas | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990465/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 17:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990465/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Dateline classic, when one woman breaks off her relationship with a boyfriend she says abused and stalked her, he goes on to something even worse. His accused accomplice? His new girlfriend. Andrea Canning reports. Originally aired on NBC on April 29, 2018.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>11 Minutes | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990466/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 17:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990466/</guid><description>Podcast Description The father of an Alabama teenager calls the police after he returns home to find his son had thrown a party, leaving the place trashed. Just 11 minutes after the deputy leaves their house, there is another 911 call placed. What could have happened? Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally aired on NBC on April 19, 2019.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Into the Night | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990467/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 13:53:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990467/</guid><description>Podcast Description The disappearance of a young woman from Bend, Oregon leads to an intense manhunt after the suspect sets off on a two state crime spree. Keith Morrison reports on the latest updates in the case. Originally aired on NBC on May 19, 2019.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Betrayal of Sarah Stern | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990468/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 13:44:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990468/</guid><description>Podcast Description The discovery of a nineteen-year-old’s car abandoned on a bridge in New Jersey turns into a missing person case that evolves into a months-long homicide investigation. As the case tears apart a Jersey Shore town, police discover a plot involving money, close friends and a fatal betrayal. Keith Morrison reports on the investigation and the extraordinary undercover video that helped solve the crimes. Originally aired on NBC on May 17, 2019.</description></item><item><title>She Didn't Come Home | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990469/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 13:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990469/</guid><description>Podcast Description A mother in Pennsylvania disappears one afternoon after she is last seen by her co-workers leaving for lunch. The case remains cold even after 60 investigators try to crack it. Could the 61st detective finally have the answers? Josh Mankiewicz reports. Originally Aired on NBC on April 26, 2019.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Introducing Dateline NBC | Dateline NBC</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5124990470/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 22:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5124990470/</guid><description>Podcast Description Current and classic episodes of Dateline NBC, featuring compelling true-crime mysteries, powerful documentaries and in-depth investigations.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>