<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Classy with Jonathan Menjivar on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/classy-with-jonathan-menjivar/</link><description>Recent content in Classy with Jonathan Menjivar on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 08:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/classy-with-jonathan-menjivar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Queen for a Day | Classy with Jonathan Menjivar</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7168900001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7168900001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why are we so attracted to stories of people suffering on television? And what happens after the cameras turn off? In our final episode, Jonathan explores the origins of reality TV and uncovers his family’s shocking connection to a very early reality TV game show. Angelina is an educator and poet. You can find her books of poetry at https://angelinasaenz.com/
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Parmesan Foam and Shredded Cheddar | Classy with Jonathan Menjivar</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7168900002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7168900002/</guid><description>Podcast Description What we eat can say a lot about who we are and where we’re from. This week, Jonathan and comedian Chris Gethard face their fear of fancy restaurants as they try to eat their way through their class anxieties. Plus, an exploration of what it’s like when the government decides what you can or can’t eat.
You can hear more from Chris Gethard on his podcast, Beautiful/Anonymous, new episodes are out every Tuesday.</description></item><item><title>Class and Combat | Classy with Jonathan Menjivar</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7168900003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7168900003/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode, we’re looking into one of the biggest chasms between us in this country – who serves in the military and who doesn’t. Every year, the United States military has to convince thousands of young people to enlist. They want a group of recruits that looks like the country, across race, class, and geography. Jonathan heads to New Jersey with reporter and Army veteran Adam Linehan to see how that’s working out.</description></item><item><title>Common Person | Classy with Jonathan Menjivar</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7168900004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7168900004/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happens when your wildest dreams become a reality? This week Jonathan talks with one of his teenage heroes, Jarvis Cocker of the band Pulp, about how fantasy drove his journey from working-class kid to famous pop star. And how he funneled all of his class frustration into the anthem “Common People.” Jarvis is currently on tour with Pulp, you can find more information at https://linktr.ee/welovepulp. His book is Good Pop, Bad Pop.</description></item><item><title>Am I a Classhole? | Classy with Jonathan Menjivar</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7168900005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7168900005/</guid><description>Podcast Description No matter your class background, you’re bound to cross some lines and make mistakes. In this episode, Comedian Wyatt Cenac talks about where he went wrong and encourages us to be open about our financial fumbles. And advice columnist JP Brammer aka Hola Papi answers listener questions to find out who might be a Classhole. If you have a juicy question or story about class, leave us a message.</description></item><item><title>Hemmed In | Classy with Jonathan Menjivar</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7168900006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7168900006/</guid><description>Podcast Description We can’t talk about class without talking about race. Through eye-opening conversations with two people of color in the fashion industry, Jonathan realizes some hard truths about the ways he’s adapted in order to blend in. And he reveals how one small, but bold act is helping him to reclaim his cultural identity.
You can find more on Brenda Equihua’s clothing brand on her website https://equihua.us/ You can stay up to date with Amechi Ugwu on Instagram @amechi</description></item><item><title>A Classy (and Uncomfortable) Laugh with Terry Gross | Classy with Jonathan Menjivar</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7168900007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7168900007/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do we change ourselves to fit in at work? Jonathan unpacks class divisions in the workplace with his former boss and public radio legend, Terry Gross.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Are Rich People Bad? | Classy with Jonathan Menjivar</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7168900008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7168900008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jonathan has some hangups about class. In the first episode of this series, he takes us from a nightclub outside LA to the halls of a fancy Manhattan prep school, and asks sociologist Rachel Sherman &amp;lsquo;are rich people bad?&amp;rsquo;
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Classy with Jonathan Menjivar | Classy with Jonathan Menjivar</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7168900009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 18:32:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7168900009/</guid><description>Podcast Description People like to pretend class doesn’t exist. But really, most of the time, we’re just ignoring it because it’s uncomfortable. Hosted by Jonathan Menjivar, Classy is a show about the chasms between us that are really hard to talk about, but too big to ignore. Coming out Wednesday, June 21st.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.</description></item></channel></rss>