<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/tags/all-in-with-chamath-jason-sacks-friedberg/</link>
        <description>Recent content in All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 18:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/all-in-with-chamath-jason-sacks-friedberg/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E70 EMERGENCY POD! Russia invades Ukraine Reactions, Putin&#39;s ambition, Biden&#39;s response and more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000071/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000071/</guid>
        <description>All right, everybody, welcome to another episode of the all in
podcast episode number 70. We made it to 70 episodes, which is
just shocking to me. And we&amp;rsquo;re recording a little bit earlier,
because one of our besties had to change their schedule,
Chamath. And it&amp;rsquo;s a crazy day to be doing this last night, Putin
decided to invade the Ukraine. Late Wednesday night, early to
Thursday morning, Putin started a special military operation in</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E68: Trudeau invokes emergency powers, Bitcoin vs. government, Tiger Global&#39;s new strategy &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000069/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000069/</guid>
        <description>So, Sax, are we going to talk with each other today or, you know, or is an ISO
player?
He turned into an ISO player.
He&amp;rsquo;s like the Carmelo Anthony of this.
He&amp;rsquo;s the Carmelo Anthony of the all in pod.
Sax, you want to pass the ball or you just want to you want to clank it off the room?
Raymond, I think we should have a focus on having a dialogue with each other</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E67: Revisiting Rogan, Canadian truckers&#39; protest, fusion breakthrough, $MSFT&#39;s savvy move &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000068/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000068/</guid>
        <description>We had a nice dinner.
Chamath hosted a little
and we played a little bit of the cards
and there&amp;rsquo;s this new kid there.
Oh, big shout out to
co-founder is there.
Great guy.
How do you wind up here at the game
sitting here, you know,
having a beautiful dinner with us?
And he&amp;rsquo;s like, well,
and then Chamath goes.
And he points to Helmuth.
Helmuth found a billionaire.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E66: $FB&#39;s major pullback, Rogan/Spotify mess, Xi/Putin meetup and understanding supply chain issues with Bestie Guestie Ryan Petersen (Flexport CEO)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000067/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000067/</guid>
        <description>fact that sacks his greatest moment in life was beating Peter
TL in a multi game chess. You ever see that picture of? Yeah,
of him with his arms raised. I can&amp;rsquo;t believe he beat Pete. I
mean, tell us about that moment. Nick, show that picture of
sacks. I mean, listen, here&amp;rsquo;s what I say when I saw when I
saw that picture. I had a couple thoughts. Number one, I&amp;rsquo;ve seen</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E65: VC markup dynamics, Russia/US tensions over Ukraine, Altos Labs raises $3B, Stripe mafia &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000066/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000066/</guid>
        <description>We don&amp;rsquo;t want to talk about Andrew. I think that guy Palmer
lucky is super fascinating. The Oculus. Why do you want to talk
about that company? Because I think he&amp;rsquo;s launching a syndicate
soon. No, why are you an investor? Lucky hates me. He
won&amp;rsquo;t come on this week and startups. He literally what did
you call him Parma lucky. Palmer lucky cosplay Palmer. He&amp;rsquo;s a
cosplayer. I like the fact that he does.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E64: Antitrust standards &amp; enforcement, tech repricing, lab leak obfuscation, E63 reactions &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000065/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000065/</guid>
        <description>Is Chamath in a room with his PR crew right now like rehearsing and practicing and this pod is ruined
Hey everybody, so I just wanted to make sure based on last week&amp;rsquo;s pod
It was absolutely clear. I care about human rights
Many of you know my origin story. But for those of you that don&amp;rsquo;t I
Was born in a country that&amp;rsquo;s no stranger to civil war and religious and political persecution</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E63: Insurrection indictments, human rights in the US and abroad, groundbreaking MS study &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000064/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000064/</guid>
        <description>Look at free bird. He&amp;rsquo;s like, this is so awkward. I can&amp;rsquo;t wait.
He&amp;rsquo;s got literally brought popcorn.
Did I was watching the show.
You brought popcorn.
He&amp;rsquo;s like, I want to see round three.
I have nothing to say today.
I&amp;rsquo;m just going to sit here and watch.
I brought popcorn.
I got my chili roasted pistachio nuts.
I&amp;rsquo;m going to sit back and enjoy the J.
Cal Sacks.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E62: Elizabeth Holmes verdict, fraud origins &amp; takeaways, navigating &#39;The Great Markdown&#39; &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000063/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000063/</guid>
        <description>Happy New Year. Happy New Year. Happy New Year. Guys, listen,
look at this. It&amp;rsquo;s now it&amp;rsquo;s candle season. Oh god. Look at
the equanimity. This is equanimity. This candle costs
$24, 000. It is an extremely rare Brazilian sandalwood. You
literally have to go into the Amazon and like, you know, you
you basically have to like, I mean, find extinct trees. No,
bro, you gotta you gotta tear out like two acres of</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E61: 2022 Predictions! Business, politics, science, tech, crypto, &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000062/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000062/</guid>
        <description>So I was not going to bring this up. SAC said, bring it up.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. You&amp;rsquo;re already creating mischaracterizations. You
said you want to bring it up. I&amp;rsquo;m like, sure, I don&amp;rsquo;t, I&amp;rsquo;m not going to veto it.
I said, well, we have to bring up my COVID. Obviously, I&amp;rsquo;m the second bestie to get COVID.
And I told you offline without the other two besties, I will just say I got it out of social</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E60: The 2021 Bestie Awards PLUS Jack Dorsey starts the Web3 Wars</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000061/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000061/</guid>
        <description>Hey, everybody, welcome to another episode of the all in
podcast. And it is our year end episode. It is our 2021 bestie
awards. This is where we give our awards for the best and
worst of what happened in 2021. We did it last year, kind of
halfheartedly, but this year, hopefully we put a little bit
more work into it with me again, of course, David Friedberg, the</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E59: Twitter&#39;s content warning algo, equity audits, politicians trading stocks, Fed&#39;s next move, mRNA &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000060/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000060/</guid>
        <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about the sweaters. Okay. Let David, let&amp;rsquo;s start with you because I love it.
I love it, David. I love it. I decided to up my sweater game for Chamath. This is Tom Ford.
Love it. Tom Ford. Tom Ford. The buttons are made out of endangered rhino horn.
We just lost a third of the audience.
So my sweater is a very light Italian cashmere made by a company called Doriani.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E58: November&#39;s CPI, operating in a downturn, macro outlook, Better.com&#39;s botched layoffs &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000059/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000059/</guid>
        <description>Actually, the funny story from Art Basel, so I was hanging with J. Cal, and we&amp;rsquo;re talking
to Beeple.
Yep.
And for some reason, J. Cal was being nice to me, and he said to Beeple, he said, you
know who this guy is?
This guy is a legend in Silicon Valley, and he introduces me.
Yeah.
And then I said to Jason, I&amp;rsquo;m like, you know, this is Beeple, and he who just sold like</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E57: Understanding Omicron, tech stocks plummet, VC&#39;s great resignation, Jack Dorsey&#39;s departure</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000058/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000058/</guid>
        <description>Yeah, Chamath goes to those sorts of events and they all pick some endangered animal and
then they skin it and they make a sweater out of it for him.
That&amp;rsquo;s that Illuminati sh**, Illuminati.
So this is Kashmir, it&amp;rsquo;s Loro Piana.
The lining is chinchilla.
Oh, chinchilla.
I knew it.
Geez.
I knew it was some poor animal.
I mean, it is so phenomenal.
Some poor animal.
Probably nicer than a dog.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E56: Constitution DAO, Rittenhouse trial coverage, private sector efficiency vs the government</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000057/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000057/</guid>
        <description>It was very interesting going to Sax&amp;rsquo;s kid&amp;rsquo;s birthday party.
Freeberg and I were there for about two or three hours. Sax showed up for the last half hour.
I think I was there for two hours and didn&amp;rsquo;t see Sax. And then I saw him on my way out the door.
But he had some YouTubers there who were pretty cool.
Yeah. Papa Jake and Logan. Thank you.
Papa Jake was great.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E55: Valuing crypto projects, Rivian worth $100B&#43;, inflation: causes and corrections and more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000056/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000056/</guid>
        <description>Zsaks is old do do do.
Zsaks is old do do do.
Zsks is old do do do do.
Zsaks is old.
Zsaks is almost dead.
Jkals fat do do do do do.
Jkals fat do do do do do dae.
Jkals is fat, oh my god.
He&amp;rsquo;s not fat anymore he&amp;rsquo;s getting the canons back.
Do do do do do.
Friedbergs not human, do do do do.
He&amp;rsquo;s a robot, do do do do do.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E54 Spread trading big tech, capital allocation, Zillow&#39;s misfire, Progressives suffer losses</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000055/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000055/</guid>
        <description>my body is a wonderland if that wonderland is white soft and mushy sure and hairy too
you know the worst thing about skin on skin sleeping with the newborn is that
you know sometimes she roots and she goes after the man the male nip
i know problem is my nipples covered in hair it&amp;rsquo;s really awkward for everybody
did you start gagging i&amp;rsquo;ll tell telly that story when she&amp;rsquo;s 18 we&amp;rsquo;re at her wedding it&amp;rsquo;ll be even</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E53: Wealth tax, inflation as a capital allocator, big tech earnings, paternity leave &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000054/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000054/</guid>
        <description>Oh baby. No skin on skin. You just got to keep the shirt on.
Listen to me. Only the best for my daughter. This is 100% Loro Piana Vicuna.
She&amp;rsquo;s going to puke on it any minute. You&amp;rsquo;re using Loro Piana to wipe her when she vomits.
No, this is the sweater that she&amp;rsquo;s got her face on, but this is the softest material,
human, you know, I mean, natural material on earth.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E52: Trump&#39;s SPAC, peak venture liquidity, tech as an economic ladder, Dems overplaying their hand</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000053/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000053/</guid>
        <description>Only sacks can lose 20 pounds and look worse.
Sacks, you know, with with all with all these gains and all your funds,
I would really love for you to cash them out and buy a belt.
Ask your wife or your house manager to help you find slim fit shirts at the local Macy&amp;rsquo;s.
You literally look like you&amp;rsquo;re wearing a parachute.
I&amp;rsquo;ve never I&amp;rsquo;ve never worn some fit anything.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E51: Supply Chain Shortages, Inflation, DeSantis, Ted Sarandos Netflix Memo, Cancel Culture, Fan Q&amp;A</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000052/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000052/</guid>
        <description>Yesterday, the game went off the chain.
It was, it&amp;rsquo;s, we started off at 500 and a thousand,
and then we were like, ah, these $500 chips are so annoying.
Then we started to play a thousand, a thousand.
Then it was a thousand, two thousand.
Then it&amp;rsquo;s a 1,000, 2,000, 4,000.
Then one, two, four, eight.
Then one, two, four, eight, 16.
One, two, four, eight, 16, 32,000 coming around.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E50: Crypto investing deep dive, Facebook&#39;s whistleblower fallout, Chappelle&#39;s new special &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000051/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000051/</guid>
        <description>Our daughter&amp;rsquo;s head is dropped because our doctor,
she felt the head and she was like, yeah, it&amp;rsquo;s&amp;hellip;
Hey Chamath, whose head has gotten bigger?
Yours or your daughter&amp;rsquo;s?
What do you mean?
Don&amp;rsquo;t quit your day job, Sax.
Yeah, Sax.
That didn&amp;rsquo;t quite land.
That didn&amp;rsquo;t land.
He&amp;rsquo;s trying out material, total flow.
We are not in rhythm.
You know why?
It&amp;rsquo;s mercury retrograde.
Our 50th episode is gonna suck because of this.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E48: The role of decentralization, China/US breakdown &amp; more with Bestie Guestie Balaji Srinivasan</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000049/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000049/</guid>
        <description>So we have Balaji here. And obviously, Balaji is an expert
in everything. But Balaji, you&amp;rsquo;re used to being
interviewed. One on one. I&amp;rsquo;ve had you on my podcast a couple
years ago, we had some major great discussions. You&amp;rsquo;ve been
on a bunch of other people&amp;rsquo;s but today we&amp;rsquo;ll see how you do on on
the squad here with five people passing the ball. You&amp;rsquo;ve listened
to the pod before.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E49: Coinbase CEO reflects on controversial blog, state of the markets, 1000 unicorns, tax reform &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000050/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000050/</guid>
        <description>Guys, my fucking dog in jail Joker&amp;rsquo;s in jail. Joker got in
jail again. Okay, so he&amp;rsquo;s been jailed in Italy. He was jailed
in Palo Alto. When will that dog learn? I&amp;rsquo;ve spent quality
time with my dog. He&amp;rsquo;s out of control. Why do you got jailed?
Because he&amp;rsquo;s a runner. He went to he&amp;rsquo;s a runner. He&amp;rsquo;s a runner.
He&amp;rsquo;s a track star. He uh the the we we we send him to like a</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E47: Facebook&#39;s week from hell, Ellen Pao on sexism in Elizabeth Holmes coverage, Newsom&#39;s win, frauds &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000048/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000048/</guid>
        <description>Where were you on Thursday?
Were you in L.A.?
I was at home.
I got like a family to do.
Well, family, have you met him?
What were they like?
Are they everything you expected?
I had to meet the new kid.
He&amp;rsquo;s 19.
What&amp;rsquo;s his major?
Hey, everybody, welcome to another episode of the All In Podcast.
Yes, we made it to episode 47 in three episodes.
It&amp;rsquo;ll be episode 50.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E46: False Ivermectin narratives, regulatory grift, wartime mentality in solving issues &amp; more | LIVE from TPB Symposium!</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000047/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000047/</guid>
        <description>J. Cal looks like he&amp;rsquo;s going to a night at the Roxbury.
Absolutely.
I mean, you look horrible.
Thank you.
Absolutely fucking horrible.
Okay. Appreciate it.
Here we go.
Thanks for coming.
This is the Production Board Symposium 2021.
Tell us just a little bit about why we&amp;rsquo;re here, David,
and what this is and what it represents for the Production Board.
The Production Board Symposium, second ever.
Thank you all for being here.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E45: Theranos &amp; VC fraud risks, China bans video games, Texas SB8, Apple app store, CA fires, Rogan</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000046/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000046/</guid>
        <description>Hold on, let&amp;rsquo;s see if we can get Sax on the line.
Alright guys, I guess Sax is blowing it off because he&amp;rsquo;s too busy with his app.
No, fuck Sax.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start without Sax.
Let&amp;rsquo;s start.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start without Sax.
Okay.
Three.
Two.
Hey everybody, hey everybody, welcome to the All In Podcast.
With us today, the queen of quinoa on fire in California, which also happens to be on</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E44: USA&#39;s Afghanistan embarrassment, China&#39;s new algo laws, future of robots &#43; Italy recap!</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000045/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000045/</guid>
        <description>By the way, black, look at this.
I&amp;rsquo;m down. I&amp;rsquo;m up a button, up a button.
This is why the all in pod is falling apart is we got one best
to you thinks he&amp;rsquo;s fucking Hemingway.
We got another one who thinks he&amp;rsquo;s Italian nobility.
We got another one who only wants to do is geek out about science
and discuss nothing topical.
I mean, you guys are a total mess and you&amp;rsquo;re a total mess.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E43: Innovative venture strategies, Zymergen&#39;s implosion, Square acquires AfterPay, future of fintech &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000044/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000044/</guid>
        <description>He&amp;rsquo;s optimizing the view.
I&amp;rsquo;m optimizing for shade, actually.
Trying to get out of the.
Oh, fucking Christ, you look like a moron.
I mean, this dipshit showed up.
He showed up to my beach club yesterday, and it was basically like someone had taken a mummy
and then wrapped a mummy inside of a white sheet and then presented him at this place.
Oh, he lathered in his like SPF 500.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E42: China&#39;s tech crackdown, CRISPR breakthrough, practical climate change solutions &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000043/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000043/</guid>
        <description>Pick up your phone, dipshit.
Hello?
Sax.
Yeah, I&amp;rsquo;ll be ready in like two minutes.
Let&amp;rsquo;s go.
Splash some water on your face.
Take a couple of whatever you need, some and let&amp;rsquo;s go.
We&amp;rsquo;re waiting.
Okay.
Hurry up.
It&amp;rsquo;s your chance to get max airtime.
Listen, free birds out.
That means you&amp;rsquo;re going to get by default 33.3% of airtime.
It&amp;rsquo;s going to be your biggest week ever.
Fly.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E41: Vaccine policy, Big Tech, DeepMind&#39;s latest breakthrough, wealth creation, opportunity &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000042/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000042/</guid>
        <description>sacks, I am going to give you $1,000 each to the charity of
your choice for every correct answer. Fuck it. 10,000. But you
have to answer you have to answer in real time and you
can&amp;rsquo;t fuck around. Okay. No stalling. This is this is to any
charity chooses included Tucker Carlson 2024. Okay, let&amp;rsquo;s go to
give the answers right away. You cannot fucking think about this.
Here we go.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E40: A Bestie gets COVID, Delta breakthrough, Billionaire Space Race &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000041/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000041/</guid>
        <description>This week we&amp;rsquo;re going to play our favorite new game show.
Guess who&amp;rsquo;s got COVID?
Yes, that&amp;rsquo;s right.
Somebody on the pod.
Hey, hey, hey, somebody&amp;rsquo;s got COVID.
Hey, hey, hey, it&amp;rsquo;s not the me.
Oh, you&amp;rsquo;re ruining the game, Jamal.
Oh, sorry.
So here&amp;rsquo;s the game.
Person who got COVID.
Have they been vaccinated or not?
Okay, all four of us have been vaccinated.
We covered that on our previous pod.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E39: West coast super drought &amp; climate crisis, Nuclear virtue signaling, chaos in SF &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000040/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000040/</guid>
        <description>What did your doctor give you to make you lose all this weight?
What is your celebrity doctor giving you?
Tell the truth.
Did you get that new shot?
People on Twitter are like,
your Twitter account&amp;rsquo;s sounding a lot more like J-Cow.
And I&amp;rsquo;m like, I think we&amp;rsquo;re on the same diet.
I think that&amp;rsquo;s what&amp;rsquo;s going on here.
In three, two&amp;hellip;
Love you, Wesley.
Hey, everybody.
Hey, everybody.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E38: Bestie brawl, Robinhood&#39;s $70M fine &amp; S-1, Delta variant, future of the political parties, FTC takes two losses against big tech &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000039/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000039/</guid>
        <description>Is is Jake out here? I can&amp;rsquo;t see him
Why do the two fat guys have to ruin everything I mean get your shit together you
The show started free burger
If
You&amp;rsquo;d like to skip the bestie Twitter drama and get right into the episode jump to 20 minutes and 48 seconds
Hey everybody. Hey, we&amp;rsquo;ve got a great show for you today. What a treat
This is gonna be here at the all-in podcast.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E37: NYC rejects far-left mayoral candidates, new developments in lab leak theory, Apple&#39;s breakup potential &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000038/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000038/</guid>
        <description>As you guys know, I get panic attacks at the dentist, but she was able to navigate me through
where I didn&amp;rsquo;t. I only sweat through half my shirt. You have panic attacks at the dentist?
No, but I sweat profusely and I get very nervous. Why? What is that about? We all have weaknesses,
Jason. We all have weaknesses. This is my Achilles heel. My Achilles heel is a dentist.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E36: New FTC Chair, breaking up big tech, government silent spying, Jon Stewart, wildfires &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000037/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000037/</guid>
        <description>What&amp;rsquo;s called a sax LP meeting?
Is it an LP meeting or you go? Are you going to like Peter Thiel a little layer?
It&amp;rsquo;s 9 a.m. You must be there must be a call going on. It&amp;rsquo;s actually booted to Ben. Eh, it&amp;rsquo;s a dish sacks
Every week that Chamath is in Italy another button guts undone
We open sources
Hey everybody, hey everybody, welcome to another episode of the all-in podcast episode 36 back with us today on the</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E35: Biogen&#39;s controversial Alzheimer&#39;s drug approval, the billionaire space race, real estate, Bitcoin &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000036/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000036/</guid>
        <description>I mean, like, could you get any closer to the camera?
I mean, your face is like right up in it.
We can see your bloodshot eyes.
Oh, God, it&amp;rsquo;s really a 9 a.m.
Start time.
It&amp;rsquo;s a little rough on Jacob.
A little rough on Jacob.
That&amp;rsquo;s true.
I want my second cup of coffee or any.
This is this is a lifestyle choice.
We may regret.
Let your winners ride</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E34: Wuhan lab leak theory, India&#39;s &#39;traceability&#39; law, Coinbase&#39;s fact check, media consolidation &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000035/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000035/</guid>
        <description>Okay, so Jason you&amp;rsquo;re gonna send a zoom link great. I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make love to not that would take 70 minutes
And then I&amp;rsquo;m gonna stretch and shower
I&amp;rsquo;ll be ready at 115. Okay. Awesome. Thanks. I just puked in my coffee a little bit, but okay
It&amp;rsquo;s just that he does he gets seconds and minutes mixed up, you know
To the all-in podcast. We got a cold open. Somebody&amp;rsquo;s gonna be a highlight.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E33: Apple&#39;s hypocrisy, America&#39;s math failure, crypto&#39;s regulatory correction, Clubhouse&#39;s future, UFOs &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000034/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000034/</guid>
        <description>Friberg Friberg, what&amp;rsquo;s up? It seems like you have a piece of shit on the side of your mouth, or is that a birthmark?
It&amp;rsquo;s oh, no, that&amp;rsquo;s birth. I got you
Did you record that
Look at this guy
He takes his shirt off for one fucking selfie and now everybody who&amp;rsquo;s fat and pale on the show
The other three of us is gonna be ridiculed. I&amp;rsquo;m having steak tonight as te aka tonight</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E32: Behind the scenes of Elon hosting SNL, CDC failures, America&#39;s real-time UBI experiment, post-COVID boom in jeopardy &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000033/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000033/</guid>
        <description>Look at this red on my stock screen, I can&amp;rsquo;t believe what&amp;rsquo;s going on.
Stocks are down, doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean I&amp;rsquo;m a loser, I don&amp;rsquo;t know, I need some self-worth now.
Oh God.
In 3, 2, 1.
Let your winners ride.
Rainman David Sachs.
And it&amp;rsquo;s said we open-sourced it to the fans and they&amp;rsquo;ve just gone crazy with it.
Love you guys.
Queen of Kinwan.
I&amp;rsquo;m going all in.
Hey everybody, hey everybody, welcome back.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E31: Post-vaccination virtue signaling, pandemic lessons, immigration, Caitlyn Jenner for CA Governor, Big Tech earnings &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000032/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000032/</guid>
        <description>This is an incredible fashion disaster.
We have to be David Sachs is dressed like where&amp;rsquo;s Waldo.
OK, Friedberg, Friedberg is dressed like
driving a fucking Subaru Outback.
Oh, God. Unbelievable.
I mean, this is ridiculous.
Let your winners ride
Rain Man, David Sachs.
And it&amp;rsquo;s said we open source it to the fans
and they&amp;rsquo;ve just gone crazy.
I love you.
And I mean, we know
everybody, everybody.
It&amp;rsquo;s another episode of the all in podcast.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E30: Ramifications of Biden&#39;s proposed capital gains tax hike, federal budget, India&#39;s COVID surge, founder psychology &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000031/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000031/</guid>
        <description>Shout out to a company Saxon
Despite how tired of am you I&amp;rsquo;ve woken up now now. I&amp;rsquo;m awake. You&amp;rsquo;ve awakened. I&amp;rsquo;m done. I quit
I&amp;rsquo;ll give a shout out to
You which just got acquired by
Plugs
Rain man David
Hey everybody, welcome to the all-in podcast, I&amp;rsquo;m Jason Calacanis with us today
The rain man himself calling in from an undisclosed location the queen of quinoa and of course the dictator himself Chamath</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E29: Coinbase goes public, direct listings vs. IPOs, portfolio management, unions &amp; more with Bestie Guestie Brad Gerstner</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000030/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000030/</guid>
        <description>Any word from the dictator or should we just do a I don&amp;rsquo;t know man. I got it
I I cannot spend my whole day sitting on zoom waiting for chamath
Or I could have brad gerson or come on and sitting for isn&amp;rsquo;t he richer than chamath?
He is now the largest spack in the world. Should we do that? Should I just have brad come on the pod?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E28: Public &amp; private markets update, Archegos debacle, US debt issues, wealth tax &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000029/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000029/</guid>
        <description>My name is David Sachs, and I have a broomstick in my b****.
That is why my voice is so deep. I have never had friends in my life.
Somebody be my friend who I don&amp;rsquo;t pay.
What a mood we&amp;rsquo;re in today, huh?
What a vibe.
And instead, we open source it to the fans, and they&amp;rsquo;ve just gone crazy with it.
Love you guys.
Nice.
Queen of Quinoa.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E27: The Great Inflation Debate, Amazon gets spicy on Twitter, rethinking supply chains &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000028/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000028/</guid>
        <description>Hey, everybody. Hey, everybody. Welcome to the all in podcast with us today again.
The Queen of Kinhwa, David Freeberg, David Sachs, the rain man himself.
And of course, the dictator here, Chamath. And let&amp;rsquo;s get ready. It&amp;rsquo;s time.
Chamath and Sachs. Here it comes, everybody. Sachs is ready in the red corner.
Representing Richard Nixon, Ronald Reagan, and rich people everywhere.
David, the rain man, Sachs. And in the blue corner, representing the underserved,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E26: State of Venture Capital, plus fan questions on longevity, decentralization &amp; quantum computing</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000027/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000027/</guid>
        <description>Sachs, is there something you object to here?
The poker one and net worth?
No, I mean, it&amp;rsquo;s fine.
I don&amp;rsquo;t give a shit about longevity or quantum computing.
But here&amp;rsquo;s the good news, David.
It&amp;rsquo;s not all about you.
There&amp;rsquo;s four people.
You could have two people who like the topic
and then you could just ask them a probing.
It&amp;rsquo;s fine. It&amp;rsquo;s fine.
Just just tell me when it&amp;rsquo;s over.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E25: Biden&#39;s vaccine mandate, &#39;equity&#39; in distribution, NFT speculation, impact of inflation &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000026/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000026/</guid>
        <description>Does anybody have any thoughts on this? I mean, I think it&amp;rsquo;s incredible.
So does Friedberg&amp;rsquo;s dog.
Hey, everybody. Hey, everybody. Welcome to another episode of the All In podcast.
It&amp;rsquo;s been a week. It&amp;rsquo;s been a minute with us today. Of course,
the queen of Kinwa David Friedberg and the rain man himself calling in from a nondescript
mansion in one of 17 cities, the rain man himself, David Sachs, and cackling like a dictator</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E24: Markets trend down, political manipulation via COVID “Zeroism,&#34; stimulus breakdown, biological Patriot Act</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000025/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000025/</guid>
        <description>I got a counter to the other another billion dollars. I lost. I&amp;rsquo;ve lost two
Two billion dollars in the last two days. Are you guys recording? Please record this looks like
Looks like we need a poker game tomorrow
Imagine how tilted your mouth is gonna go. Yeah
He&amp;rsquo;s gonna buy it for two million just to try and get even
Rain man David
I
Hey everybody, hey everybody, welcome to another episode of the all-in podcast.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E23 Radical DAs, breaking down FBGoogle vs. Australia, sustained fear post-vaccine &amp; fan questions!</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000024/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000024/</guid>
        <description>Jake, how are you going to do your Trump impression?
We&amp;rsquo;re going to do your your. OK. Yeah.
Everybody, I&amp;rsquo;m getting my Twitter.
Don&amp;rsquo;t get a derangement syndrome right before we start the pod.
I want to warm him up.
Ted Cruz. This doesn&amp;rsquo;t warm him up.
I get some deranged.
Get your show notes up, bitches.
Let your winners ride.
Rain Man, David Sack.
And instead, we open source it to the fans,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E22: Reflecting on the Robinhood situation with Bestie Guestie Vlad Tenev</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000023/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000023/</guid>
        <description>Now wait, Vlad, you have to turn your camera off. And then I&amp;rsquo;m going to do my little bit where the
bestie guesting door knocks. Oh, no, Jason. No, that&amp;rsquo;s not silly. This is silly. Here we go.
But I can do it. It&amp;rsquo;s very easy for me. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry about it. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry about
these guys don&amp;rsquo;t want to do it. They don&amp;rsquo;t like my they don&amp;rsquo;t like my bets.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E21: Media misalignment, subjects controlling narratives &amp; more with bestie guestie Draymond Green</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000022/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000022/</guid>
        <description>We&amp;rsquo;re dropping what up?
The track I mean,
I am recording testing and testing my recording and here me
bet you know, but here we go in three two
your winners bride
raing man v insects
And it said we open source it to the fans and they&amp;rsquo;ve just gone crazy with it.
Love you insects.
Queen of quinoa.
Hey, everybody.
It&amp;rsquo;s the all in podcast.
Wet your beak.
Young Spielberg coming at you on a Friday morning afternoon.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E20 Robinhood wrap up, Insiders vs. Outsiders, California&#39;s failing report card &amp; how to fix it</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000021/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000021/</guid>
        <description>I&amp;rsquo;m going all in, where you&amp;rsquo;ll be, where you&amp;rsquo;ll be, where you&amp;rsquo;ll be, I&amp;rsquo;m going all in, don&amp;rsquo;t let your winners ride, Rain Man, David Sachs, I&amp;rsquo;m going all in, and it said, we open sourced it to the fans and they&amp;rsquo;ve just gone crazy with it, I&amp;rsquo;m going all in
Alright everybody, welcome, it is the podcast you&amp;rsquo;ve been waiting for, the all in pod emergency episode 20, the number 11 podcast in the world, number one in tech, number 11 overall, Joe Rogan, Sway, Pivot, NPR, Rachel Maddow, left in the dust, welcome to the number 11 podcast in the world, can you believe it?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E19 Breaking down Robinhood&#39;s GameStop decision Why did it happen and how can it be prevented in the future</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000020/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000020/</guid>
        <description>Hey everybody welcome to the all in podcast it
was a slow news week. So we decided we&amp;rsquo;d give you a special
episode. We&amp;rsquo;re going to go around the horn with our special
picks. We&amp;rsquo;re each going to pick three picks everybody. We&amp;rsquo;re
going to pick our favorite recipe, our favorite new hobby
and our favorite streaming guilty pleasure, because there
was no news with us today. The dictator Chamath Palihapitiya</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E18: Inauguration talk, breaking down the $1.9T stimulus, the case for recalling Gavin Newsom &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000019/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000019/</guid>
        <description>Hey everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s me, Jason Calaclinas. Welcome, welcome.
Hey everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s me, Jason.
Thank god Trump&amp;rsquo;s out.
I hate Trump and I love myself.
Hey everybody, happy days are here again. Champagne bottles popping. Happy days are here again.
Sax is so happy. Trump&amp;rsquo;s out of office.
He gave an amazing speech about how great Biden&amp;rsquo;s inauguration was.
Welcome to the All In podcast.
Oh my gosh.
With me today, in our post-inauguration afterglow, is the dictator, Chamath Palihapitiya,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E17: Big Tech bans Trump, ramifications for the First Amendment &amp; the open Internet</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000018/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000018/</guid>
        <description>Hey, everyone. Hey, everyone. Welcome to the all-in pod.
Your illustrious moderator, Jason Kalkanis, has been purged.
Canceled?
He&amp;rsquo;s been canceled. We canceled him for his constant interruptions and low IQ comments.
We decided that the minimum IQ required to be on this pod is 140, 150.
He did not make the cut. And so now, it is just me, Chamath, and Freeberg.
He is, uh, Jason is away. He is actively implementing our jerk-off-to-win strategy to solve the pandemic and free speech.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E16: Reflecting on the riots at the US Capitol, plus: Georgia runoff elections, vaccine distribution &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000017/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000017/</guid>
        <description>I&amp;rsquo;m going all in, wet your beak, wet your beak, wet your beak
I&amp;rsquo;m going all in
We&amp;rsquo;ll let your winners ride
Rain Man, David Sass
I&amp;rsquo;m going all in
And it said, we open sourced it to the fans and they&amp;rsquo;ve just gone crazy with it
Love you, Wesley
Ice Queen of Kid Wa
I&amp;rsquo;m going all in
Let your winners ride, let your winners ride
I&amp;rsquo;m going all in</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E15 “The Besties” All-In’s inaugural award show covering the best, worst &amp; most memorable of 2020</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000016/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000016/</guid>
        <description>You gotta rise up before you begin You gotta dive in before you can swim
You gotta give it all to win We&amp;rsquo;re going all in
Hey everybody, welcome back. Besties are back for the all-in podcast.
The queen of quinoa, Freeburg is here, the dictator Chamath, and of course,
rain man David Sachs. And it&amp;rsquo;s been a big week here in Silicon Valley with Airbnb
and Wish both going public for over a hundred billion dollars combined.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E14: Salesforce acquires Slack, DeepMind’s AlphaFold breakthrough, Trust Fund Socialists &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000015/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000015/</guid>
        <description>Okay, besties are back. Besties are back going around the horn. Rain Man David Sacks calling
in from an undisclosed location, suffering through two code 13s in one lifetime.
And David Friedberg is here, the queen of quinoa, spacking everything in sight,
living the life, calling in from a nondescript Ritz-Carlton room, it appears to be.
And of course, the dictator himself, Chamath Palihapitiya, cackling like a fool.
Welcome back, everybody.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E13: SPACsgiving Special! More promising vaccine news, innovation vs. regulation, reforming higher ed, morality of challenge trials &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000014/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000014/</guid>
        <description>Hey, everybody. Welcome back. Besties are back and it&amp;rsquo;s a bestie Spacksgiving. Congratulations
to the queen of quinoa. His second company, David Freeberg, announces today, hours before
the taping of this special Thanksgiving pod, that he is taking Metro Mile public through
a SPAC and that besties see. And here is the quote that as only Chamath can tweet, Buffett
had Geico. I pick Metro Mile. I would just like to say that&amp;rsquo;s how you move markets.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E12: Biden wins, Pfizer vaccine, markets rip, Trump&#39;s next act, COVID endgame scenarios &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000013/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000013/</guid>
        <description>Hey, everybody, welcome to another all in podcast.
This is an all bestie, no guestie episode of all in.
The last time you heard from the besties, it was election night
and it was a shit show, a fucking crazy shit show.
Let&amp;rsquo;s be honest.
I mean, we if we go back and look at that historical document,
we had moments where we thought Trump was going to absolutely crush.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E11: Election Night Special featuring Phil Hellmuth, Bill Gurley, Brad Gerstner &amp; more!</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000012/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000012/</guid>
        <description>Hello everybody. Welcome. Uh, we are live at the all-in headquarters
And the all-in podcast is now live. We have 63 people watching already
And bear with us while we get the besties on the line. I&amp;rsquo;ll be doing my introductions in just a moment after I tweet this
um
But it is an eventful night and we had to start early
because
uh
It&amp;rsquo;s looking like this could be another shocker</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E10 Twitter &amp; Facebook botch censorship (again), the publisher vs. distributor debate &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000011/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000011/</guid>
        <description>Hey everybody, hey everybody, welcome besties are back. Besties are back. It&amp;rsquo;s another all-in
podcast dropping it to you unexpectedly because there&amp;rsquo;s just so much news.
It&amp;rsquo;s too much surprise bestie pods but dropping a bestie. It&amp;rsquo;s not a code 13. We&amp;rsquo;re not dropping
any Snickers bars today. Just dropping a bestie. Oh no, he&amp;rsquo;s got a megaphone.
It&amp;rsquo;s a special censorship edition. Warning, warning.
We hit a new low in terms of people needing to be heard.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E9 Trump has COVID, First debate reactions, Coinbase letter response &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000010/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000010/</guid>
        <description>Hey, everybody. Hey, everybody. Welcome to another all in podcast. We just got the show notes,
and I&amp;rsquo;m ripping them up because the president has the Rona. We knew this was a possibility.
We had an incredible docket brewing, but as fate loves irony, we found out on Wednesday night,
I believe, just in a brief timeline here, Wednesday night, Hope Hicks, his personal assistant,
got the Rona. And then, of course, President Trump announced late last night that he,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E8: TikTok &#43; Oracle, how privacy loss will impact society, economy &amp; COVID outlooks for 2021 &amp; beyond, California wildfires &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000009/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000009/</guid>
        <description>Hey everybody, hey everybody, welcome to another episode of All In, the podcast episode eight.
Besties are here to talk about tech, economy, politics, the election, and our lives in Silicon
Valley. Welcome back to the pod, David Friedberg, the Queen of Kinwai is here from an undisclosed
location.
Always a joy.
Yes.
Undisclosed location somewhere in the Midwest.
You bailed on SF after the smoke. You lasted how many days into the barbecue, into the</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E7: California&#39;s collapse, how SPACs are opening the markets for growth stocks &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000008/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000008/</guid>
        <description>Hey, everybody. Welcome back to the all in podcast. Besties have reunited. It&amp;rsquo;s been
a bestie summer. Chamath, how are you doing? You&amp;rsquo;re back in America. Yes, I&amp;rsquo;m back in America.
Back in America. It feels great. Good summer. Yes. I had an incredible summer. I had seven
weeks in Italy. It was really incredible. What is the vibe in Italy post pandemic? Obviously,
they had the roughest of any nation, I think, except for China and Wuhan with COVID-19.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E6: Big Tech antitrust aftermath, potential effects of an M&amp;A clampdown on Silicon Valley &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000007/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000007/</guid>
        <description>All right, everybody, welcome back. It&amp;rsquo;s another episode of All In Podcast, the podcast that is
racing up the charts despite the fact that we record it every three or four weeks. There&amp;rsquo;s no
marketing. There&amp;rsquo;s no ads in this podcast. It&amp;rsquo;s just four friends who play poker together who&amp;rsquo;ve
decided to talk about the most important issues in the world. Welcome back to the podcast,
David Friedberg, the queen of quinoa himself.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E5: WHO&#39;s incompetence, kicking off Cold War II, China&#39;s grand plan, 100X&#39;ing America&#39;s efficiency</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000006/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000006/</guid>
        <description>Hey everybody, welcome to the All In Podcast.
This is our fifth episode.
As you know, we regularly publish this podcast,
well, every two to four weeks, something like that.
And just to give you a little idea
of how well this is going,
the podcast peaked at number 10 in tech podcasts,
even though we never publish it,
and we&amp;rsquo;re only four episodes in.
Number 10?
So tell your friends about the podcast</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E4: Politicizing the pandemic, Police reform, Biden&#39;s ideal VP, Twitter vs. Facebook on free speech &amp; more with David Sacks &amp; David Friedberg</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000005/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000005/</guid>
        <description>All right, everybody, welcome back to the All In Podcast.
We&amp;rsquo;re here with Chamath Palihapitiya, David Friedberg,
and David Sachs.
Our usual foursome as we chop up the business news
and what&amp;rsquo;s going on.
And just as a point of order, the frequency of the show
is, well, don&amp;rsquo;t ask me.
As we feel like it.
As we feel like it, correct.
So do not ask me to advertise on the podcast</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E3: Modern Cold War between US &amp; China, economic recovery, potential mass migration out of San Francisco, pandemic politicization &amp; more with David Sacks &amp; David Friedberg</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000004/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000004/</guid>
        <description>Hey, everybody, welcome to the All In Podcast
with Jason Kalacanis and Chamath Palihapitiya.
We record this podcast, well,
on a really unique schedule, Chamath.
What&amp;rsquo;s our schedule right now, whenever we feel like it?
Basically, it is whenever our significant others
get so sick of us that they kick us off
and say, don&amp;rsquo;t come back.
Yeah, we get thrown to the pool house.
We decide to pop up the podcast.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E2: Rebooting the economy, understanding corporate debt, steps to avoid a depression &amp; more with David Sacks</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000003/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000003/</guid>
        <description>All right, everybody, welcome to episode two of the All In podcast with Jason and Chamath,
some basic ground rules here. If you&amp;rsquo;re not into speculation, you don&amp;rsquo;t like to debate,
you don&amp;rsquo;t like to question authority, and you don&amp;rsquo;t like to get a shit ton of inside
information, I&amp;rsquo;m going to actually turn the podcast off right now and go download The
Daily from The New York Times or All Things Considered or some other bullshit, but we&amp;rsquo;re</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E1: US Response to COVID-19 &amp; Impact on Startups, Venture Capital &amp; Public Markets with David Friedberg</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000002/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000002/</guid>
        <description>All right, everybody, welcome to another edition of the all in podcast.
We&amp;rsquo;ll call this episode one.
We did a test and over 100,000 of you listened to the test podcast that we did in a few days,
in a few days.
Chamath is already getting addicted to his statistics, a new podcaster.
I need to focus on something going up.
Yes, exactly.
Our portfolios are getting crushed, but the podcast numbers are going up there with a</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E0: COVID-19 Political, Economic &amp; Social Ramifications featuring The Production Board&#39;s David Friedberg (frmly Founder/CEO, The Climate Corporation)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000001/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000001/</guid>
        <description>Hey everybody, welcome to the first episode of the all-in podcast with Chamath Kalyanarathia
and Jason Galkatis. That cackling voice.
Where we&amp;rsquo;re trying to save ourselves from the end of the world.
It is literally, you know, we thought we&amp;rsquo;d start this podcast on April 1st, Chamath,
and everybody thinks it&amp;rsquo;s like a big joke, that it&amp;rsquo;s an April Fool&amp;rsquo;s joke. It just happened to
be the time was perfect. We had full intentionality of starting the podcast,</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
