<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/tags/all-in-with-chamath-jason-sacks-friedberg/</link>
        <description>Recent content in All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 09:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/all-in-with-chamath-jason-sacks-friedberg/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E30: Ramifications of Biden&#39;s proposed capital gains tax hike, federal budget, India&#39;s COVID surge, founder psychology &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000031/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000031/</guid>
        <description>Shout out to a company Saxon
Despite how tired of am you I&amp;rsquo;ve woken up now now. I&amp;rsquo;m awake. You&amp;rsquo;ve awakened. I&amp;rsquo;m done. I quit
I&amp;rsquo;ll give a shout out to
You which just got acquired by
Plugs
Rain man David
Hey everybody, welcome to the all-in podcast, I&amp;rsquo;m Jason Calacanis with us today
The rain man himself calling in from an undisclosed location the queen of quinoa and of course the dictator himself Chamath</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E29: Coinbase goes public, direct listings vs. IPOs, portfolio management, unions &amp; more with Bestie Guestie Brad Gerstner</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000030/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000030/</guid>
        <description>Any word from the dictator or should we just do a I don&amp;rsquo;t know man. I got it
I I cannot spend my whole day sitting on zoom waiting for chamath
Or I could have brad gerson or come on and sitting for isn&amp;rsquo;t he richer than chamath?
He is now the largest spack in the world. Should we do that? Should I just have brad come on the pod?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E28: Public &amp; private markets update, Archegos debacle, US debt issues, wealth tax &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000029/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000029/</guid>
        <description>My name is David Sachs, and I have a broomstick in my b****.
That is why my voice is so deep. I have never had friends in my life.
Somebody be my friend who I don&amp;rsquo;t pay.
What a mood we&amp;rsquo;re in today, huh?
What a vibe.
And instead, we open source it to the fans, and they&amp;rsquo;ve just gone crazy with it.
Love you guys.
Nice.
Queen of Quinoa.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E27: The Great Inflation Debate, Amazon gets spicy on Twitter, rethinking supply chains &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000028/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000028/</guid>
        <description>Hey, everybody. Hey, everybody. Welcome to the all in podcast with us today again.
The Queen of Kinhwa, David Freeberg, David Sachs, the rain man himself.
And of course, the dictator here, Chamath. And let&amp;rsquo;s get ready. It&amp;rsquo;s time.
Chamath and Sachs. Here it comes, everybody. Sachs is ready in the red corner.
Representing Richard Nixon, Ronald Reagan, and rich people everywhere.
David, the rain man, Sachs. And in the blue corner, representing the underserved,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E26: State of Venture Capital, plus fan questions on longevity, decentralization &amp; quantum computing</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000027/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000027/</guid>
        <description>Sachs, is there something you object to here?
The poker one and net worth?
No, I mean, it&amp;rsquo;s fine.
I don&amp;rsquo;t give a shit about longevity or quantum computing.
But here&amp;rsquo;s the good news, David.
It&amp;rsquo;s not all about you.
There&amp;rsquo;s four people.
You could have two people who like the topic
and then you could just ask them a probing.
It&amp;rsquo;s fine. It&amp;rsquo;s fine.
Just just tell me when it&amp;rsquo;s over.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E25: Biden&#39;s vaccine mandate, &#39;equity&#39; in distribution, NFT speculation, impact of inflation &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000026/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000026/</guid>
        <description>Does anybody have any thoughts on this? I mean, I think it&amp;rsquo;s incredible.
So does Friedberg&amp;rsquo;s dog.
Hey, everybody. Hey, everybody. Welcome to another episode of the All In podcast.
It&amp;rsquo;s been a week. It&amp;rsquo;s been a minute with us today. Of course,
the queen of Kinwa David Friedberg and the rain man himself calling in from a nondescript
mansion in one of 17 cities, the rain man himself, David Sachs, and cackling like a dictator</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E24: Markets trend down, political manipulation via COVID “Zeroism,&#34; stimulus breakdown, biological Patriot Act</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000025/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000025/</guid>
        <description>I got a counter to the other another billion dollars. I lost. I&amp;rsquo;ve lost two
Two billion dollars in the last two days. Are you guys recording? Please record this looks like
Looks like we need a poker game tomorrow
Imagine how tilted your mouth is gonna go. Yeah
He&amp;rsquo;s gonna buy it for two million just to try and get even
Rain man David
I
Hey everybody, hey everybody, welcome to another episode of the all-in podcast.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E23 Radical DAs, breaking down FBGoogle vs. Australia, sustained fear post-vaccine &amp; fan questions!</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000024/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000024/</guid>
        <description>Jake, how are you going to do your Trump impression?
We&amp;rsquo;re going to do your your. OK. Yeah.
Everybody, I&amp;rsquo;m getting my Twitter.
Don&amp;rsquo;t get a derangement syndrome right before we start the pod.
I want to warm him up.
Ted Cruz. This doesn&amp;rsquo;t warm him up.
I get some deranged.
Get your show notes up, bitches.
Let your winners ride.
Rain Man, David Sack.
And instead, we open source it to the fans,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E22: Reflecting on the Robinhood situation with Bestie Guestie Vlad Tenev</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000023/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000023/</guid>
        <description>Now wait, Vlad, you have to turn your camera off. And then I&amp;rsquo;m going to do my little bit where the
bestie guesting door knocks. Oh, no, Jason. No, that&amp;rsquo;s not silly. This is silly. Here we go.
But I can do it. It&amp;rsquo;s very easy for me. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry about it. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry about
these guys don&amp;rsquo;t want to do it. They don&amp;rsquo;t like my they don&amp;rsquo;t like my bets.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E21: Media misalignment, subjects controlling narratives &amp; more with bestie guestie Draymond Green</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000022/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000022/</guid>
        <description>We&amp;rsquo;re dropping what up?
The track I mean,
I am recording testing and testing my recording and here me
bet you know, but here we go in three two
your winners bride
raing man v insects
And it said we open source it to the fans and they&amp;rsquo;ve just gone crazy with it.
Love you insects.
Queen of quinoa.
Hey, everybody.
It&amp;rsquo;s the all in podcast.
Wet your beak.
Young Spielberg coming at you on a Friday morning afternoon.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E20 Robinhood wrap up, Insiders vs. Outsiders, California&#39;s failing report card &amp; how to fix it</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000021/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000021/</guid>
        <description>I&amp;rsquo;m going all in, where you&amp;rsquo;ll be, where you&amp;rsquo;ll be, where you&amp;rsquo;ll be, I&amp;rsquo;m going all in, don&amp;rsquo;t let your winners ride, Rain Man, David Sachs, I&amp;rsquo;m going all in, and it said, we open sourced it to the fans and they&amp;rsquo;ve just gone crazy with it, I&amp;rsquo;m going all in
Alright everybody, welcome, it is the podcast you&amp;rsquo;ve been waiting for, the all in pod emergency episode 20, the number 11 podcast in the world, number one in tech, number 11 overall, Joe Rogan, Sway, Pivot, NPR, Rachel Maddow, left in the dust, welcome to the number 11 podcast in the world, can you believe it?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E19 Breaking down Robinhood&#39;s GameStop decision Why did it happen and how can it be prevented in the future</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000020/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000020/</guid>
        <description>Hey everybody welcome to the all in podcast it
was a slow news week. So we decided we&amp;rsquo;d give you a special
episode. We&amp;rsquo;re going to go around the horn with our special
picks. We&amp;rsquo;re each going to pick three picks everybody. We&amp;rsquo;re
going to pick our favorite recipe, our favorite new hobby
and our favorite streaming guilty pleasure, because there
was no news with us today. The dictator Chamath Palihapitiya</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E18: Inauguration talk, breaking down the $1.9T stimulus, the case for recalling Gavin Newsom &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000019/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000019/</guid>
        <description>Hey everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s me, Jason Calaclinas. Welcome, welcome.
Hey everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s me, Jason.
Thank god Trump&amp;rsquo;s out.
I hate Trump and I love myself.
Hey everybody, happy days are here again. Champagne bottles popping. Happy days are here again.
Sax is so happy. Trump&amp;rsquo;s out of office.
He gave an amazing speech about how great Biden&amp;rsquo;s inauguration was.
Welcome to the All In podcast.
Oh my gosh.
With me today, in our post-inauguration afterglow, is the dictator, Chamath Palihapitiya,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E17: Big Tech bans Trump, ramifications for the First Amendment &amp; the open Internet</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000018/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000018/</guid>
        <description>Hey, everyone. Hey, everyone. Welcome to the all-in pod.
Your illustrious moderator, Jason Kalkanis, has been purged.
Canceled?
He&amp;rsquo;s been canceled. We canceled him for his constant interruptions and low IQ comments.
We decided that the minimum IQ required to be on this pod is 140, 150.
He did not make the cut. And so now, it is just me, Chamath, and Freeberg.
He is, uh, Jason is away. He is actively implementing our jerk-off-to-win strategy to solve the pandemic and free speech.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E16: Reflecting on the riots at the US Capitol, plus: Georgia runoff elections, vaccine distribution &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000017/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000017/</guid>
        <description>I&amp;rsquo;m going all in, wet your beak, wet your beak, wet your beak
I&amp;rsquo;m going all in
We&amp;rsquo;ll let your winners ride
Rain Man, David Sass
I&amp;rsquo;m going all in
And it said, we open sourced it to the fans and they&amp;rsquo;ve just gone crazy with it
Love you, Wesley
Ice Queen of Kid Wa
I&amp;rsquo;m going all in
Let your winners ride, let your winners ride
I&amp;rsquo;m going all in</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E15 “The Besties” All-In’s inaugural award show covering the best, worst &amp; most memorable of 2020</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000016/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000016/</guid>
        <description>You gotta rise up before you begin You gotta dive in before you can swim
You gotta give it all to win We&amp;rsquo;re going all in
Hey everybody, welcome back. Besties are back for the all-in podcast.
The queen of quinoa, Freeburg is here, the dictator Chamath, and of course,
rain man David Sachs. And it&amp;rsquo;s been a big week here in Silicon Valley with Airbnb
and Wish both going public for over a hundred billion dollars combined.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E14: Salesforce acquires Slack, DeepMind’s AlphaFold breakthrough, Trust Fund Socialists &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000015/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000015/</guid>
        <description>Okay, besties are back. Besties are back going around the horn. Rain Man David Sacks calling
in from an undisclosed location, suffering through two code 13s in one lifetime.
And David Friedberg is here, the queen of quinoa, spacking everything in sight,
living the life, calling in from a nondescript Ritz-Carlton room, it appears to be.
And of course, the dictator himself, Chamath Palihapitiya, cackling like a fool.
Welcome back, everybody.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E13: SPACsgiving Special! More promising vaccine news, innovation vs. regulation, reforming higher ed, morality of challenge trials &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000014/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000014/</guid>
        <description>Hey, everybody. Welcome back. Besties are back and it&amp;rsquo;s a bestie Spacksgiving. Congratulations
to the queen of quinoa. His second company, David Freeberg, announces today, hours before
the taping of this special Thanksgiving pod, that he is taking Metro Mile public through
a SPAC and that besties see. And here is the quote that as only Chamath can tweet, Buffett
had Geico. I pick Metro Mile. I would just like to say that&amp;rsquo;s how you move markets.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E12: Biden wins, Pfizer vaccine, markets rip, Trump&#39;s next act, COVID endgame scenarios &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000013/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000013/</guid>
        <description>Hey, everybody, welcome to another all in podcast.
This is an all bestie, no guestie episode of all in.
The last time you heard from the besties, it was election night
and it was a shit show, a fucking crazy shit show.
Let&amp;rsquo;s be honest.
I mean, we if we go back and look at that historical document,
we had moments where we thought Trump was going to absolutely crush.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E11: Election Night Special featuring Phil Hellmuth, Bill Gurley, Brad Gerstner &amp; more!</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000012/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000012/</guid>
        <description>Hello everybody. Welcome. Uh, we are live at the all-in headquarters
And the all-in podcast is now live. We have 63 people watching already
And bear with us while we get the besties on the line. I&amp;rsquo;ll be doing my introductions in just a moment after I tweet this
um
But it is an eventful night and we had to start early
because
uh
It&amp;rsquo;s looking like this could be another shocker</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E10 Twitter &amp; Facebook botch censorship (again), the publisher vs. distributor debate &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000011/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000011/</guid>
        <description>Hey everybody, hey everybody, welcome besties are back. Besties are back. It&amp;rsquo;s another all-in
podcast dropping it to you unexpectedly because there&amp;rsquo;s just so much news.
It&amp;rsquo;s too much surprise bestie pods but dropping a bestie. It&amp;rsquo;s not a code 13. We&amp;rsquo;re not dropping
any Snickers bars today. Just dropping a bestie. Oh no, he&amp;rsquo;s got a megaphone.
It&amp;rsquo;s a special censorship edition. Warning, warning.
We hit a new low in terms of people needing to be heard.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E9 Trump has COVID, First debate reactions, Coinbase letter response &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000010/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000010/</guid>
        <description>Hey, everybody. Hey, everybody. Welcome to another all in podcast. We just got the show notes,
and I&amp;rsquo;m ripping them up because the president has the Rona. We knew this was a possibility.
We had an incredible docket brewing, but as fate loves irony, we found out on Wednesday night,
I believe, just in a brief timeline here, Wednesday night, Hope Hicks, his personal assistant,
got the Rona. And then, of course, President Trump announced late last night that he,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E8: TikTok &#43; Oracle, how privacy loss will impact society, economy &amp; COVID outlooks for 2021 &amp; beyond, California wildfires &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000009/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000009/</guid>
        <description>Hey everybody, hey everybody, welcome to another episode of All In, the podcast episode eight.
Besties are here to talk about tech, economy, politics, the election, and our lives in Silicon
Valley. Welcome back to the pod, David Friedberg, the Queen of Kinwai is here from an undisclosed
location.
Always a joy.
Yes.
Undisclosed location somewhere in the Midwest.
You bailed on SF after the smoke. You lasted how many days into the barbecue, into the</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E7: California&#39;s collapse, how SPACs are opening the markets for growth stocks &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000008/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000008/</guid>
        <description>Hey, everybody. Welcome back to the all in podcast. Besties have reunited. It&amp;rsquo;s been
a bestie summer. Chamath, how are you doing? You&amp;rsquo;re back in America. Yes, I&amp;rsquo;m back in America.
Back in America. It feels great. Good summer. Yes. I had an incredible summer. I had seven
weeks in Italy. It was really incredible. What is the vibe in Italy post pandemic? Obviously,
they had the roughest of any nation, I think, except for China and Wuhan with COVID-19.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E6: Big Tech antitrust aftermath, potential effects of an M&amp;A clampdown on Silicon Valley &amp; more</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000007/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000007/</guid>
        <description>All right, everybody, welcome back. It&amp;rsquo;s another episode of All In Podcast, the podcast that is
racing up the charts despite the fact that we record it every three or four weeks. There&amp;rsquo;s no
marketing. There&amp;rsquo;s no ads in this podcast. It&amp;rsquo;s just four friends who play poker together who&amp;rsquo;ve
decided to talk about the most important issues in the world. Welcome back to the podcast,
David Friedberg, the queen of quinoa himself.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E5: WHO&#39;s incompetence, kicking off Cold War II, China&#39;s grand plan, 100X&#39;ing America&#39;s efficiency</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000006/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000006/</guid>
        <description>Hey everybody, welcome to the All In Podcast.
This is our fifth episode.
As you know, we regularly publish this podcast,
well, every two to four weeks, something like that.
And just to give you a little idea
of how well this is going,
the podcast peaked at number 10 in tech podcasts,
even though we never publish it,
and we&amp;rsquo;re only four episodes in.
Number 10?
So tell your friends about the podcast</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E4: Politicizing the pandemic, Police reform, Biden&#39;s ideal VP, Twitter vs. Facebook on free speech &amp; more with David Sacks &amp; David Friedberg</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000005/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000005/</guid>
        <description>All right, everybody, welcome back to the All In Podcast.
We&amp;rsquo;re here with Chamath Palihapitiya, David Friedberg,
and David Sachs.
Our usual foursome as we chop up the business news
and what&amp;rsquo;s going on.
And just as a point of order, the frequency of the show
is, well, don&amp;rsquo;t ask me.
As we feel like it.
As we feel like it, correct.
So do not ask me to advertise on the podcast</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E3: Modern Cold War between US &amp; China, economic recovery, potential mass migration out of San Francisco, pandemic politicization &amp; more with David Sacks &amp; David Friedberg</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000004/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000004/</guid>
        <description>Hey, everybody, welcome to the All In Podcast
with Jason Kalacanis and Chamath Palihapitiya.
We record this podcast, well,
on a really unique schedule, Chamath.
What&amp;rsquo;s our schedule right now, whenever we feel like it?
Basically, it is whenever our significant others
get so sick of us that they kick us off
and say, don&amp;rsquo;t come back.
Yeah, we get thrown to the pool house.
We decide to pop up the podcast.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E2: Rebooting the economy, understanding corporate debt, steps to avoid a depression &amp; more with David Sacks</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000003/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000003/</guid>
        <description>All right, everybody, welcome to episode two of the All In podcast with Jason and Chamath,
some basic ground rules here. If you&amp;rsquo;re not into speculation, you don&amp;rsquo;t like to debate,
you don&amp;rsquo;t like to question authority, and you don&amp;rsquo;t like to get a shit ton of inside
information, I&amp;rsquo;m going to actually turn the podcast off right now and go download The
Daily from The New York Times or All Things Considered or some other bullshit, but we&amp;rsquo;re</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E1: US Response to COVID-19 &amp; Impact on Startups, Venture Capital &amp; Public Markets with David Friedberg</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000002/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000002/</guid>
        <description>All right, everybody, welcome to another edition of the all in podcast.
We&amp;rsquo;ll call this episode one.
We did a test and over 100,000 of you listened to the test podcast that we did in a few days,
in a few days.
Chamath is already getting addicted to his statistics, a new podcaster.
I need to focus on something going up.
Yes, exactly.
Our portfolios are getting crushed, but the podcast numbers are going up there with a</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>All-In with Chamath, Jason, Sacks &amp; Friedberg - E0: COVID-19 Political, Economic &amp; Social Ramifications featuring The Production Board&#39;s David Friedberg (frmly Founder/CEO, The Climate Corporation)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308000001/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308000001/</guid>
        <description>Hey everybody, welcome to the first episode of the all-in podcast with Chamath Kalyanarathia
and Jason Galkatis. That cackling voice.
Where we&amp;rsquo;re trying to save ourselves from the end of the world.
It is literally, you know, we thought we&amp;rsquo;d start this podcast on April 1st, Chamath,
and everybody thinks it&amp;rsquo;s like a big joke, that it&amp;rsquo;s an April Fool&amp;rsquo;s joke. It just happened to
be the time was perfect. We had full intentionality of starting the podcast,</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
