<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ghost Story on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/ghost-story/</link><description>Recent content in Ghost Story on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 09:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/ghost-story/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What To Listen To Next: MrBallen’s Medical Mysteries | Ghost Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4364680011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4364680011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Follow MrBallen’s Medical Mysteries wherever you get your podcasts. You can binge the first 8 episodes, early and ad-free on Amazon Music. Download the Amazon Music app today.
The human body is a miracle. But when it’s not working, it can be the stuff of nightmares. On this new series from master storyteller MrBallen, we’re sharing medical horror stories and diagnostic mysteries that are surgically calibrated to make your blood run cold.</description></item><item><title>What To Listen To Next: MrBallen’s Medical Mysteries | Ghost Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4364680009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4364680009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Follow MrBallen’s Medical Mysteries wherever you get your podcasts. You can binge the first 8 episodes, early and ad-free on Amazon Music. Download the Amazon Music app today.
The human body is a miracle. But when it’s not working, it can be the stuff of nightmares. On this new series from master storyteller MrBallen, we’re sharing medical horror stories and diagnostic mysteries that are surgically calibrated to make your blood run cold.</description></item><item><title>The Conjuring | 7 | Ghost Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4364680008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 03:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4364680008/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this final episode of Ghost Story, Tristan returns to Queens Road. With the help of Nikola, the psychic from Episode 6, Tristan makes one final attempt to figure out who killed Naomi Dancy and whether she’s the ghost from his teenage bedroom. In the end, Tristan and the Dancy family finally get to see Naomi for who she really was.
Episode Notes:
Photo of Maurice Tribe circa 1918&amp;nbsp;© Crown copyright.</description></item><item><title>The Ugly Truth | 6 | Ghost Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4364680001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 03:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4364680001/</guid><description>Podcast Description After his encounter with the ghost hunters, Tristan continues his paranormal quest by meeting with a series of psychic mediums. He doesn’t take them too seriously until he meets a strange, quiet man who seems to know more than he should about the night Naomi died. Tristan is shaken but decides it’s finally time to tell his in-laws everything that he has learned about Feyther.
Listener note: This episode contains descriptions of violence and suicide.</description></item><item><title>The Bulletins | 5 | Ghost Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4364680002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 03:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4364680002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tristan thinks he’s getting a handle on the case of Feyther and Naomi until he meets their 98-year-old daughter, Bindle. The picture she paints of her parents’ loving marriage turns everything on its head.
Follow Ghost Story on the Wondery App or wherever you get your podcasts. You can binge all episodes of Ghost Story ad-free right now by joining Wondery Plus in the Wondery App or on Apple Podcasts.</description></item><item><title>The Advantages of Believing | 4 | Ghost Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4364680003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4364680003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tristan reluctantly calls in the paranormal experts and tries to contact Naomi’s spirit — and the ghost hunters help him in ways he never expected. Then, he finds a cache of documents which reveal an unexpected side of Feyther.
Follow Ghost Story on the Wondery App or wherever you get your podcasts. You can binge all episodes of Ghost Story ad-free right now by joining Wondery Plus in the Wondery App or on Apple Podcasts.</description></item><item><title>The Locked Room | 3 | Ghost Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4364680004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4364680004/</guid><description>Podcast Description When the family haunted by the faceless apparition in Tristan’s teenage bedroom ghosts him, he's left wondering why they’re too scared to share their story. Then he finds a curious piece of evidence. Is it actually Feyther’s confession?
Listener note: This episode contains descriptions of violence and suicide. Take care while listening.
Follow Ghost Story on the Wondery App or wherever you get your podcasts. You can binge all episodes of Ghost Story ad-free right now by joining Wondery Plus in the Wondery App or on Apple Podcasts.</description></item><item><title>The Locked Room | 3 | Ghost Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4364680010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 02:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4364680010/</guid><description>Podcast Description When the family haunted by the faceless apparition in Tristan’s teenage bedroom ghosts him, he's left wondering why they’re too scared to share their story. Then he finds a curious piece of evidence. Is it actually Feyther’s confession?
Listener note: This episode contains descriptions of violence and suicide. Take care while listening.
Follow Ghost Story on the Wondery App or wherever you get your podcasts. You can binge all episodes of Ghost Story ad-free right now by joining Wondery Plus in the Wondery App or on Apple Podcasts.</description></item><item><title>The Witness | 2 | Ghost Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4364680005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 02:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4364680005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Naomi’s husband, Dr John Dancy, emerged from the murder scene a hero. He’s known in the family as “Feyther” and is still revered as a larger-than-life figure by the family. But as Tristan examines the police records, he soon finds himself where no son-in-law should ever be - questioning the family narrative about what really happened in 1937.
Listener note: This episode contains descriptions of violence and suicide. Take care while listening.</description></item><item><title>The House Next Door | 1 | Ghost Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4364680006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 02:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4364680006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tristan Redman doesn’t believe in ghosts. But weird things happened in his teenage bedroom. And when he discovers later that occupants of his family home have seen the ghost of a faceless woman, he’s intrigued. Because it just so happens that his wife’s great grandmother, Naomi Dancy, was murdered in the house next door…killed by two gunshots to the face.
Listener note: This episode contains descriptions of violence and suicide.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Ghost Story | Ghost Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4364680007/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 09:35:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4364680007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Follow&amp;nbsp;Ghost Story&amp;nbsp;on the Wondery App or wherever you get your podcasts. You can binge all episodes of&amp;nbsp;Ghost Story&amp;nbsp;ad-free right now by joining Wondery Plus in the Wondery App or on Apple Podcasts.
Wondery and Pineapple Street Studios present&amp;nbsp;Ghost Story&amp;nbsp;— a seven-part podcast series about family secrets, overwhelming coincidences and the things that come back to haunt us.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.</description></item></channel></rss>