<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Ghost Story on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/tags/ghost-story/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Ghost Story on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 07:01:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/ghost-story/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>The Advantages of Believing | 4 | Ghost Story</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/4364680006/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/4364680006/</guid>
        <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt; 0:00 / Tristan reluctantly calls in the paranormal experts and tries to contact Naomi’s spirit — and the ghost hunters help him in ways he never expected. Then, he finds a cache of documents which reveal an unexpected side of Feyther.
Follow Ghost Story on the Wondery App or wherever you get your podcasts. You can binge all episodes of Ghost Story ad-free right now by joining Wondery Plus in the Wondery App or on Apple Podcasts.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Locked Room | 3 | Ghost Story</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/4364680007/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/4364680007/</guid>
        <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt; 0:00 / When the family haunted by the faceless apparition in Tristan’s teenage bedroom ghosts him, he&#39;s left wondering why they’re too scared to share their story. Then he finds a curious piece of evidence. Is it actually Feyther’s confession?
Listener note: This episode contains descriptions of violence and suicide. Take care while listening.
Follow Ghost Story on the Wondery App or wherever you get your podcasts. You can binge all episodes of Ghost Story ad-free right now by joining Wondery Plus in the Wondery App or on Apple Podcasts.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Witness | 2 | Ghost Story</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/4364680008/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 02:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/4364680008/</guid>
        <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt; 0:00 / Naomi’s husband, Dr John Dancy, emerged from the murder scene a hero. He’s known in the family as “Feyther” and is still revered as a larger-than-life figure by the family. But as Tristan examines the police records, he soon finds himself where no son-in-law should ever be - questioning the family narrative about what really happened in 1937.
Listener note: This episode contains descriptions of violence and suicide.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The House Next Door | 1 | Ghost Story</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/4364680009/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 02:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/4364680009/</guid>
        <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt; 0:00 / Tristan Redman doesn’t believe in ghosts. But weird things happened in his teenage bedroom. And when he discovers later that occupants of his family home have seen the ghost of a faceless woman, he’s intrigued. Because it just so happens that his wife’s great grandmother, Naomi Dancy, was murdered in the house next door…killed by two gunshots to the face.
Listener note: This episode contains descriptions of violence and suicide.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Introducing: Ghost Story | Ghost Story</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/4364680010/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 09:35:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/4364680010/</guid>
        <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt; 0:00 / Follow&amp;nbsp;Ghost Story&amp;nbsp;on the Wondery App or wherever you get your podcasts. You can binge all episodes of&amp;nbsp;Ghost Story&amp;nbsp;ad-free right now by joining Wondery Plus in the Wondery App or on Apple Podcasts.
Wondery and Pineapple Street Studios present&amp;nbsp;Ghost Story&amp;nbsp;— a seven-part podcast series about family secrets, overwhelming coincidences and the things that come back to haunt us.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
