<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Breakthroughs on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/breakthroughs/</link><description>Recent content in Breakthroughs on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/breakthroughs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Innovation in cancer: Defining the future of care | Breakthroughs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8670540001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8670540001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr Ellie Cannon is joined by Jane Lyons, CEO of Cancer52 and Stefano Podesta, Oncology Lead at Pfizer UK, to discuss the big challenges and opportunities in the fight against cancer within the UK.
PP-UNP-GBR-7436 / November 2023
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Delivering a step forward for rare disease patients | Breakthroughs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8670540002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 14:11:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8670540002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr Ellie Cannon is joined by Dr. Jacqueline Barry, Chief Clinical Officer at the Cell and Gene Therapy Catapult and Owen Marks, Rare Disease Lead at Pfizer UK, to discuss the urgent need to evolve the way rare disease medicines are brought to patients, and why healthcare systems need to keep pace with scientific advancements.
PP-UNP-GBR-6142 / August 2023
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Meeting the challenge of Antimicrobial Resistance (AMR) | Breakthroughs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8670540003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8670540003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr Ellie Cannon is joined by economist Lord Jim O’Neill (who in 2014 was commissioned to chair a review into the rising increase in drug-resistant infections) and Toby Cousens, Hospital and Internal Medicines Lead at Pfizer UK, to discuss the threat of antimicrobial resistance (AMR) and the challenges it poses both to science and wider society.
PP-UNP-GBR-4716 / May 2023
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What can we learn from COVID-19 to address other healthcare challenges? | Breakthroughs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8670540004/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 16:42:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8670540004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join Dr Ellie Cannon as she talks to Susan Rienow (Country President, Pfizer UK) and Dr Richard Torbett (CEO, The Association of the British Pharmaceutical Industry) about the lessons learnt from the COVID-19 pandemic and how this could be applied to address other major healthcare challenges.
PP-UNP-GBR-2871 / December 2022
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>