<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mealtimes with Dr Kyla on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/mealtimes-with-dr-kyla/</link><description>Recent content in Mealtimes with Dr Kyla on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 05:01:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/mealtimes-with-dr-kyla/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2. Family Meals and Confident Parenting with Mandy from Raise Toddlers | Mealtimes with Dr Kyla</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1290270001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1290270001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to my very first interview episode! I’m chatting to Toddler Development Specialist and my colleague and very good friend, Mandy from Raise Toddlers. We explore her own childhood memories around food and mealtimes before we deep dive into feeding children, confidence assurance parenting, and what these look like when used together.&amp;nbsp;
Listen in to discover:
How Mandy and Dr Kyla connectedMandy’s childhood mealtime experiences and memoriesWhat family mealtimes in Mandy’s household look likeThe current favourite meal in Mandy’s houseMandy’s thoughts on meal planning&amp;nbsp;Particular foods that Mandy’s children will not eatTemptations to serve ‘easy’ mealsThe effectiveness of confidence assurance parenting</description></item><item><title>1. Dr Kyla on a Platter | Mealtimes with Dr Kyla</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1290270002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1290270002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to Mealtimes with Dr Kyla! In this podcast, we will explore and talk more about food and feeding kids, I’ll talk to experts in other fields to find out their challenges with feeding kids, and we’ll dive into some interesting topics on the side that might just change your life!
Tune into my very first episode to find out what to expect from Mealtimes with Dr Kyla and get to know me with 10 fun facts including:</description></item></channel></rss>