<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Archetypes on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/tags/archetypes/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Archetypes on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/archetypes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Archetypes - &#39;Man-ifesting A Cultural Shift&#39; with Trevor Noah, Andy Cohen and Judd Apatow</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1310200012/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1310200012/</guid>
        <description>=================================================================== COLD OPEN ===================================================================
MEGHAN: I used to love a show called Bill Nye The Science Guy.
It was a kid’s science show with experiments and some laughs. And actually, what&amp;rsquo;s funniest about all of this is when I think back to when or why I would watch that show, I… It&amp;rsquo;s bizarre to me because I wasn&amp;rsquo;t really a science kind of girl growing up. I loved cooking, gardening, writing letters.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Archetypes - &#39;Beyond the Archetype: Human, Being&#39; with Michaela Jaé Rodriguez &amp; Candace Bushnell</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1310200011/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1310200011/</guid>
        <description>MEGHAN**:** There&amp;rsquo;s a piece of art in my sitting room. It&amp;rsquo;s not fancy. It&amp;rsquo;s kind of this rectangle shape, almost plaque like that. And it just says a few words very simply across it. Human kind. Be both. My dear friend Genevieve gave it to me a couple years ago, and when I walk past it, it always makes me smile, of course, because I love her and our friendship and it reminds me of her.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Archetypes - The Audacity of the Activist with Jameela Jamil &amp; Shohreh Aghdashloo</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1310200010/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1310200010/</guid>
        <description>MEGHAN: Have you ever heard the saying if you don&amp;rsquo;t stand for something, you&amp;rsquo;ll fall for anything. I remember hearing it years ago and nodding along, thinking, mm hmm, that makes sense to me. Just stand for something. Stand for something good. But not everyone sees it that way. Especially when it comes to women. I started to notice this almost default eyeroll when someone would mention a woman fighting for a cause.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Archetypes - To ‘B’ or not to ‘B’? with Mellody Hobson &amp; Victoria Jackson</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1310200009/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1310200009/</guid>
        <description>Meghan: At this point in the series, I think we&amp;rsquo;ve established that I spent a lot of time in front of the TV growing up. I loved movies and shows. I had my favorite programs. And, as we continue to unearth – with Archetypes – many of them can be influenced by pop culture and by the media.
Growing up in the eighties and nineties, my generation, we were raised with television in the same way that this generation is raised with social media.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Archetypes - Good Wife/Bad Wife, Good Mom/Bad Mom with Sophie Grégoire Trudeau, Pamela Adlon and Sam Jay</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1310200008/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1310200008/</guid>
        <description>MEGHAN: This past summer, a friend of mine was in town with her kids for a few days. Now this to me was very exciting. Because I hadn’t seen her for a while and the idea of getting our kids together, this was a real treat. We swam, we drank wine, we splashed in the water. Then threw some pool floats in. By the way, the inflatable pizza slice proved to be a big hit.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Archetypes - Upending the &#34;Angry Black Woman&#34; Myth with Issa Rae &amp; Ziwe</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1310200007/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1310200007/</guid>
        <description>MEGHAN: About two years ago, my husband and I went to have a socially distanced dinner with another couple. Actually, it was just drinks because this was when there was still so much uncertainty with COVID. We followed all the rules and we met friends at a distance. And while it was great to just have human interaction again. An even greater moment happened as we were leaving. The wife handed me a book that she said she thought I might find interesting.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Archetypes - Breaking down &#39;The Bimbo&#39; with Paris Hilton &amp; Iliza Shlesinger</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1310200006/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1310200006/</guid>
        <description>MEGHAN: The other night, I was flipping through the channels on TV. This is a rarity with two children under the age of four. But I saw an episode of a game show called Deal or No Deal. It brought back a lot of memories.
Archival: Deal or No Deal
applause Meghan, open the case. applause
MEGHAN: Back in 2006… I had a short stint as a “briefcase girl” on the US version of the game show.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Archetypes - The Decoding of Crazy with Deepika Padukone, Jenny Slate and Constance Wu</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1310200005/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1310200005/</guid>
        <description>Content Warning: Hi, there. Before we get started, I wanted to let you know that this episode gets into some sensitive conversations.
MEGHAN: If you or someone you know is struggling, or in need of assistance, we have some resources in our show notes. And, by the way, if you find that this is too heavy for you to carry today, just tune out. It’s okay. I’ll still be here next week.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Archetypes - The Demystification of Dragon Lady with Margaret Cho &amp; Lisa Ling</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1310200004/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1310200004/</guid>
        <description>MEGHAN: Growing up in Los Angeles, these are the types of foods I would eat: tamales, ghormeh sabzi, larb, matzo ball soup, adobo… along with your usual kid fare of chicken nuggets and fries and burgers and pizza. And the types of languages I would hear? Honestly, more than you can imagine. From Armenian to Farsi, Korean, Spanish, Hebrew… Los Angeles, despite how segregated it sometimes felt, was full of culture that you could see, feel, hear and taste on a daily basis.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Archetypes - The Stigma of the Singleton with Mindy Kaling</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1310200003/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1310200003/</guid>
        <description>MEGHAN: When I was 14, I planned my wedding. Not my actual wedding. That would have been a bit harder to imagine. This wedding was an assignment for my Religion 2 class in Catholic school.
[MUSIC IN]
MEGHAN: I remember every little thing about it. I wanted it to be at The Bel-Air Hotel. And there was a swan lake, and I wanted the cake to be from Hanson’s Bakery. And the dress - oh my goodness, the dress was strapless and poofy and I’d seen it in a bridal magazine … and, and I bought it, I mean not, not the dress – I bought the bridal magazine because I took this project seriously.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Archetypes - The Duality of Diva with Mariah Carey</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1310200002/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1310200002/</guid>
        <description>MEGHAN: Way back in the fall of 1998, when I was a senior in high school, the word “diva” was having a moment. It may have had something to do with this…
[CLIP: DIVAS LIVE VH1 1998] “TONIGHT, LIVE FROM NEW YORK CITY, VH1 PRESENTS - DIVAS LIVE!”]
MEGHAN: Divas Live was a cultural touchstone. Performances from 5 legends of the music world, all sharing one stage for one night. There was Celine Dion.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Archetypes - The Misconception of Ambition with Serena Williams</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1310200001/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1310200001/</guid>
        <description>MEGHAN: When I was 11 years old, growing up in LA, I saw a commercial that would change the way I understood my place in the world. Let me be clear: it wasn’t because this ad was some kind of ingenious piece of marketing – actually, it was just the opposite.
So, here’s what happened: I was in the 6th grade, I was sitting in my classroom – and we were watching TV, when a commercial came on…</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
