<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pour Minds Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/pour-minds-podcast/</link><description>Recent content in Pour Minds Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 15:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/pour-minds-podcast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Im Warning You Now FT Mr. Jay Hill | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870274/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870274/</guid><description>Podcast Description We got a guest today ayeeee!!! Mr. Jay Hill came thru and caused a whirl wind of trouble. We discussed knowing when its time to propose, the best p*rn category, being your authentic self at all times, women carrying condoms &amp;amp; so much more. So Pour Crew, grab your drinks and Pour Up.
Upcoming Tour Dates: Atlanta 12.21.23 *GET YOUR TICKETS NOW @ https://www.pourminds.com Save this link! All items of the week will be featured here!</description></item><item><title>She On Go Cause She Po FT. OG New New | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870001/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Heyyy yall! We got another guest episode for yall today with none other than &amp;ldquo;The streets therapist&amp;rdquo; OG New New. We discussed everything from the complications that arise when dating men with baby mamas, women not meeting the prerequisites for the type of men they want to date, If dating with children is harder &amp;amp; so much more. So Pour Crew, grab your drinks and Pour Up.
Upcoming Tour Dates: Atlanta 12.</description></item><item><title>We Tellin Tha Truth &amp; Standin on business FT. Trae Tha Truth | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870002/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall! We got none other than H-Towns own&amp;hellip;Trae tha Truth on the couch this week. We discussed nothing but tha truth from, what is an acceptable first date to when its time to cheat. So Pour Crew, grab your drinks and Pour Up, cause this was a wild one full of Tha Truth. Upcoming Tour Dates: Atlanta *GET YOUR TICKETS NOW @ https://www.pourminds.com Save this link! All items of the week will be featured here!</description></item><item><title>A T-Rex named Lex | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870003/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall!! On this weeks episode, we unknowingly had an intervention/therapy session for Lex P. Lex made some shocking realizations about herself and took accountability for her actions. We discussed how having a victim mindset while dating can ruin your relationship, dating a man thats Bisexual, bending your morals/values when you&amp;rsquo;re in love and a listener even asked for advice about velveteen rubs. This was an enlightening and wild episode, so grab your drank and pour up Pour Crew.</description></item><item><title>Tell Me Later FT. Monaleo | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870004/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall!!! We been on a roll with the guest episodes lately, and todays guest DID NOT disappoint. We had none other than Monaleo on the couch today for some girl talk. We discussed everything from her musical background, the wonderful experience of first time motherhood, Whether or not a man can teach a woman how to be a woman and so much more. Lex also gave us the qualifications men HAVE to meet in order for her to eat his groceries.</description></item><item><title>Welcome To Vulture Island FT. Rob49 | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870005/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, we got a guest today ayeeee! Rob49 came thru and kicked it with us this week. We discussed him rising through the rap ranks almost over night, if rappers make love or always try to &amp;ldquo;beat it up&amp;rdquo;, if there is a right or wrong age to have kids and so much more. So grab your drank and pour up Pour Crew.
Upcoming Tour Dates: Houston &amp;amp; Atlanta *GET YOUR TICKETS NOW @ https://www.</description></item><item><title>Whoreible Minds Make Pour Decisions FT. WHOREible Decisions | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870006/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall!!! We got some guests today, long time friends of the show; Mandii B &amp;amp; Weezy of the Whoreible Decisions Pod. This is the chaotic collab yall been asking for. Drea dropped some hot tea about an interesting item in Lex P&amp;rsquo;s everyday carry bag. We discussed women knowingly competing to be the 1 and only in a mans life, anal orgasms, what does happily ever after mean to you, if washing your p*ssy before sex manditory and so much more.</description></item><item><title>Wagwan Harry Patwa | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870007/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 13:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, Thanks to Ty we were cuttin up this entire Harry Potter themed Halloween episode. We discussed things women do that scare men, parents paying more attention to your kids, if orgasms are mental or physical and so much more. So grab your goblet and pour you a drank cause its about to get spooky.
Upcoming Tour Dates: Dallas &amp;amp; New Orleans *GET YOUR TICKETS NOW @ https://www.</description></item><item><title>A Beautiful Nugget FT. Jokes On You Podcast | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870008/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Heyy Yall!! Today we were delighted to have the beautiful intuitive ladies from the Jokes On You Podcast. We had a grand ol time this whole episode. We discussed scaring the h*es &amp;amp; how it can be beneficial, first date expectations, if old dogs can be taught new tricks, having a code brown during a euphoric orgasm and so much more. So kick back, grab your drink and have a ball with ya girls.</description></item><item><title>Wett Up The Block FT. MissBNasty | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870009/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall!!! We got a very special guest today. The Beyonce of OnlyFans&amp;hellip;MissBNasty! We kept it real nasty this entire episode. We discussed MissBNasty&amp;rsquo;s start in the porn industry, stigmas placed on sex workers, the importance of showcasing your personality outside of sex work, ways to have better sex and oh so much more. So kick back and grab your drinks cause its Miss Nasty Time!
Upcoming Tour Dates: Philly &amp;amp; DC *GET YOUR TICKETS NOW @ https://www.</description></item><item><title>A Real Eater FT. Beatking | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870010/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hol upppp..Whats up Pour Crew, we got another hilarious episode for yall today. We were joined by Club Godzilla AKA Beatking and ratchet is an understatement for this episode. We discussed his start in music, If sex with younger of age people is better, rebound relationships, what makes you a lame man, and oh so much more. So grab ya drank &amp;amp; pour up Pour Crew!!!
Upcoming Tour Dates: Chicago *GET YOUR TICKETS NOW @ https://www.</description></item><item><title>Honestly...Nevermind | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870011/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, we back with a solo episode this week. Lex lost her voice this week and was giving Barry White this episode. We discussed If people truly want the gods honest truth or a lie, do men deserve hall passes, If men really get over their exes and so much more. So grab your wine and unwind with ya girls.
Catch us Live on AMP by Amazon every Wednesday @ 8PM: https://www.</description></item><item><title>High Minds FT. High Maintenance Podcast | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870012/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Heyy yall&amp;hellip;We got some guests todayyy!!! Today our friends Killah &amp;amp; Jaz from the High Maintenance Podcast joined us for an episode full of shenanigans. We discussed everything from lights on or off during sex, if smoking weed lady like, benefits to being a side chick and so much more. So grab your one weed or your wine and get elevated with your girls. Catch us Live on AMP by Amazon every Wednesday @ 8PM: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Ushy Gushy | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870013/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 14:01:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, we been coming back to back with the guest episodes, how about we drop a solo episode this week. We aint got no. guest today ayeeee. This week we discussed turn offs during sex, parenting, dealing with negative people on social media &amp;amp; so much more. Sit back relax and enjoy this episode. Upcoming Tour Dates: Chicago *GET YOUR TICKETS NOW @ https://www.pourminds.com ﻿Save this link! All items of the week will be featured here!</description></item><item><title>To Infinity and Beyond FT. Clayton English | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870014/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, We&amp;rsquo;ve been reading the comments and we invited a highly requested guest to make a return appearance. We were joined by Sabado Domingo AKA Clayton English!!!! Yall already know we were cuttin up during this entire episode. Clayton kicked things off by telling us about his sons joy when watching Family Feud. We discussed everything from stars in the universe, the writers strike, alien orgys, and oh so much more.</description></item><item><title>Big Boss Bites FT. Big Boss Vette | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall!!! We got a guest today, Our girl Big Boss Vette came to our new set and had a time with us. We caught on everything new in Big Boss Vette&amp;rsquo;s life since we last spoke. We discussed everything from other creators stealing your art, communicating with your toxic exes, car sex and so much more. Big Boss Vette &amp;amp; Drea also have an intervention with Lex P.</description></item><item><title>It Depends FT. Duke Deuce | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870016/</guid><description>Podcast Description WHAT THE F****** is up yall? We got another classic episode of Pour Minds for yall. Today we were joined by none other than Duke Deuce himself. We discussed dating virgins, do you give people thats been chasing you a chance, the influence music has on todays youth and so much more. So kick back relax and enjoy this episode of Pour Minds.
Upcoming Tour Dates: Charlotte *GET YOUR TICKETS NOW @ https://www.</description></item><item><title>Leo Szn Lex | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870017/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall!! We got a very special solo episode for yall today! Happy Birthday to The Don Lex P!!! We discussed Black media not being taken serious, why FMF threesomes are more applauded than MMF threesomes, how social media has birthed delusional relationship expectations and oh so much more. So kick back and take some shots with ya gworls.
Upcoming Tour Dates: Nashville August 19th *GET YOUR TICKETS NOW @ https://www.</description></item><item><title>Get That Envy Out Ya Heart FT. Malcolm Mays | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870018/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 14:07:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, WE GOT A GUEST TODAY!!!! Entertainer Malcolm Mays sat down on the couch with us today. We discussed his roles on SnowFall &amp;amp; Raising Kanan, dealing with envious people, when do you know you&amp;rsquo;ve made it and so much more. You dont wanna miss this great episode, so grab you a drink and relax with your girls.
Upcoming Tour Dates: Nashville *GET YOUR TICKETS NOW @ https://www.</description></item><item><title>Cracker Dust | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870019/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yalll, we got a long no guest episode for yall today thats full of mischief. Drea makes a big confession/reveal that shocks Lex P &amp;amp; Ty! Later in the episode, we discussed the causes of a dry kewchie, is your partner a reflection of your self-esteem, the never ending grief you face when you lose a parent and so much more. So grab you a drink and enjoy this hilarious episode.</description></item><item><title>ST. LUNATIC FT. NANDOSTL | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870020/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 14:07:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall!!! We got another fire episode for yall today&amp;hellip;and guess what&amp;hellip; We got a guest today ayyyyeeee!!! NandoSTL came and kicked it with the girls today. We discussed Nando&amp;rsquo;s start in music, how he got signed by T-Pain, the importance of the rapper starter kit, and eating groceries. You dont wanna miss this hilarious episode of Pour Minds. Upcoming Tour Dates: Orlando &amp;amp; Miami *GET YOUR TICKETS NOW @ https://www.</description></item><item><title>Make Dating Fun Again | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870021/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall!!! We got another fire episode for yall today&amp;hellip;and guess what&amp;hellip; We aint got a guest today ayyyyeeee!!! Today we discussed making dating fun again, Lex talks about her trip to Costa Rica &amp;amp; psychedelic is a understatement, Lex also proposed a multimillion dollar business plan to Drea. Upcoming Tour Dates: Orlando &amp;amp; Miami *GET YOUR TICKETS NOW @ https://www.pourminds.com ﻿Save this link! All items of the week will be featured here!</description></item><item><title>My Man My Man My Man FT Brii Renee | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, we got a very special guest on the couch today&amp;hellip; none other than the first lady of 85 Wayz Studios Brii Renee AKA Ms.Miller. We discussed everything from Brii&amp;rsquo;s start in the entertainment industry, how to handle disputes in a healthy relationshio, The many distractions in the strip club lifestyle, how do you know if a person got that good and oh so much more. So grab your wine and kick back with some girl talk.</description></item><item><title>Cant Knock My Confidence FT. Shan Boodram | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, we coming to yall from LA with our lovely and hospitable guest Shan Boodram. We discussed everything from having children at 30+ , not allowing your partner to destroy your confidence, your side piece might be your future husband, and so much more. So grab your wine and unwind with ya girls.
﻿Save this link! All items of the week will be featured here! https://shopmy.us/public/pourmindspod&amp;hellip; Send Fan Mail To: 1452 Chattahoochee Ave NW GA 30318 United States Wanna leave us a voicemail?</description></item><item><title>We Aint Old Bookie | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870024/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, we cutting up today. Stevens Charles stopped by to tell us all about LS Cream liqueur and announce something special. Today we discussed how old is too old to be twerking on them headlights, BV, doing relationship things, but still claiming to be single and so much more. So sit back grab you some LS Cream liqueur and kick it with ya girls.
Save this link! All items of the week will be featured here!</description></item><item><title>Chillin Wit Da Homies FT. Kodaq &amp; JoJo | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870025/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall!!! Today is a bit of a family affair, We got JoJo &amp;amp; Kodaq from The Jojo &amp;amp; Big Homie show on the couches today and we cut a fool #BLAMEITONTY. We talked about podcasting being oversaturated, Top 5 red flag characteristics, what categorizes you as a S*x Worker, and oh so much more. So sit back grab your wine and chill wit ya homies. Save this link!</description></item><item><title>Eye For An Eye | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870026/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Whats Up Yalllllll, Its just us today on this episode, so you already know we was cuttin up. We discussed, hookup dating culture, learning your lesson when god tells you a person isnt for you, lube, and so much more. So grab your wine and kick it with your girls.
Save this link! All items of the week will be featured here! https://shopmy.us/public/pourmindspod&amp;hellip; Send Fan Mail To: 1452 Chattahoochee Ave NW GA 30318 United States Wanna leave us a voicemail?</description></item><item><title>That Was A Word Sensei FT. Karlous Miller | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870027/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870027/</guid><description>Podcast Description We got a guest today ayeeee! On todays episode we have the hilarious and enlightened Karlous Miller. The sensei took the time to come drop some knowledge on us and catch up. We discussed the shortage of fine women, pop ups gone wrong, faking orgasms, and so much more. So sit back, grab your wine and enjoy this episode.
Save this link! All items of the week will be featured here!</description></item><item><title>Mommy &amp; Me | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870028/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870028/</guid><description>Podcast Description We got some guests today ayyyeeeee!!! Today we were joined by the eloquent owners of Melz Grillz, Dr. Mel &amp;amp; her daughter Ariel. Dr. Mel didnt hold back and dropped alot of gems. We discussed their dynamic mother/daughter relationship, their business relationship, alcoholism, men who are thirsty for sex out the gate and so much more. Grab your wine and kick it with ya girls.
Save this link! All items of the week will be featured here!</description></item><item><title>Praise This Pour Sista FT. Crystal Renee Hayslett | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870029/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pour Crew are yall with meeee? On todays episode we are joined by our good sis Crystal Renee Hayslett, star of the BET show sistas and new movie Praise This on Peacock. We covered her startup in the entertainment industry, her professional relationship with Tyler Perry, praise kinks and so much more. So grab your wine sit back and get your praise on Pour Sistas.
Save this link! All items of the week will be featured here!</description></item><item><title>Cream Donut | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870030/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, we aint got no guest today bookie. On this episode we discussed diversifying your friend group, being involved with men you absolutely do not like, if a virgin can learn how to have great sex &amp;amp; more. Lex P also professed her love of having her Donut creamed. So sit back , grab your wine and kick it with ya girls.
Save this link! All items of the week will be featured here!</description></item><item><title>Bring back Class FT. Kenny Burns | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870031/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall this week is a wild one, we had Kenny Burns come through and bring the energy &amp;amp; alcohol. We dove into Kenny&amp;rsquo;s career and his transition into the alcohol industry. Kenny also tells us about his time at Freaknik. We also discuss being more mysterious and chasing the inevitable.
Save this link! All items of the week will be featured here! https://shopmy.us/public/pourmindspod&amp;hellip; Send Fan Mail To: 1452 Chattahoochee Ave NW GA 30318 United States Wanna leave us a voicemail?</description></item><item><title>Mo Money No Problems FT. Earn Your Leisure | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870032/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, we got some guests today ayeee! Earn Your Leisure joined us on the couch to talk financial literacy, originality being lost in the industry, building generational wealth in todays society, how aggressive women get the man they want &amp;amp; much more. So grab your wine and wine down in your girls. Follow Us On All Social Media Platforms: @Pour_minds @Lex_P_ @Dreanicoleee Save this link! All items of the week will be featured here!</description></item><item><title>Them Brothas Starvin | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870033/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, we got no guest today ayeee. Today we&amp;rsquo;re getting back to the usual flow of the show being just us &amp;amp; with our hilarious banter. We discussed outing your sexual partners for attention, anxious attachment vs avoidant attachment, passport bros &amp;amp; much more. So grab your wine and kick it with your girls. Save this link! All items of the week will be featured here! https://shopmy.us/public/pourmindspod&amp;hellip; Send Fan Mail To: 1452 Chattahoochee Ave NW GA 30318 United States Wanna leave us a voicemail?</description></item><item><title>The Greene Machine FT. Navv Greene | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870034/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, this weeks episode is the reunion of the 3 amigos ; this week we were joined by the richest &amp;amp; busiest opener in the game, Navv Greene. Yall, already know this episode was full of shenanigans. We discussed everything from tour life, if nice guys truly finish last, gas station sexual enhancements &amp;amp; so much more. So grab your wine and kick it with ya gworls. LIVE SHOW TICKETS: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Hit Her With The Mule FT. Z-RO | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870035/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, This is the episode yall been waiting on, The P-Ro &amp;amp; Z-Ro connection. Houston Legend Z-Ro graced the presence of the couch and gave nothing but great insight. We discussed when to cut off friends, the importance of keeping your relationship lowkey, the pros &amp;amp; cons of hitting women with the mule &amp;amp; so much more. So grab your wine and roll with your girls. Save this link!</description></item><item><title>Himmi Hardaway FT. The Master Investor | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870036/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, we&amp;rsquo;re taking a break from the regularly scheduled shenanigans and are focused on generational wealth today. The Master Investor graced the presence of the couch and dropped plenty of generational wealth gems this episode. We discussed women being the true master investors, how easy it is to invest, the various ways to get over exes &amp;amp; much more. So grab your wine and invest in your girls.</description></item><item><title>Im Serious | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870037/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 13:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, we&amp;rsquo;re getting back to girl talk this week with just us girls. We discuss the double standards of dating younger adults, how relationships develop, sexorcisms, Drea also learned what a cuckhold is &amp;amp; much more. So grab your wine and kick it with ya girls. Save this link! All items of the week will be featured here! https://shopmy.us/public/pourmindspod&amp;hellip; Send Fan Mail To: 1452 Chattahoochee Ave NW GA 30318 United States Wanna leave us a voicemail?</description></item><item><title>SnowMinds FT. Gail Bean &amp; Isaiah John | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870038/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, we back with another fire episode featuring Gail Bean &amp;amp; Isaiah John of SnowFall. We discuss how they got their acting careers started, an in depth music discussion, we also get the inside scoop on how Hollywood captures those spicy sex scenes, &amp;amp; much more. So grab your wine and wind down with ya girls. Save this link! All items of the week will be featured here!</description></item><item><title>Boonk &amp; Liquor | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870039/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 14:08:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, we back with solo episode after a few weeks of great guests, its time to get back to the regularly scheduled shenanigans. We discuss living through your children, the dangers of posting everything online, The girls also find out what Boonk is, &amp;amp; much more. So grab your wine and take off with ya girls. Save this link! All items of the week will be featured here!</description></item><item><title>Kewchie Poo FT. Young Dro | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870040/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 22:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, we back with the another one of one episode with our guest, The legendary Young Dro. Dro kicked it on the couch with ya girls and had absolutely no filter. We discussed his sobriety, accepting the repercussions when apologizing, what makes good/bad kewchie &amp;amp; much more. So grab your wine and enjoy this latest installment. Save this link! All items of the week will be featured here!</description></item><item><title>Pulling A You On You FT. Funny Marco | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870041/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 19:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, we back with another classic episode full of mischief featuring rising entertainer Funny Marco AKA Marco. We discuss his start in the entertainment industry, having a plan outside of social media, Marco shares that he wants to take women shopping and ghost them, he also shows Lex P how to read efficiently &amp;amp; much more. So grab your wine and enjoy this episode with ya girls.</description></item><item><title>Think Before You Speak FT. We Talk Back Podcast | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870042/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 15:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, we back and we got some guests today. The ladies of We Talk Back Podcast joined us to discuss a flurry of topics. We discussed single women living essentials, Lex P professes her desire to sleep with a well known music mogul, if there is truly someone out there for everybody, good orgasms &amp;amp; much more. So grab your wine and unwind with ya girls. Save this link!</description></item><item><title>Mufasa Taught You Well FT. Symba | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870043/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, we back with a guest that has the tenacity of a lion; none other than music artist Symba. We discussed men still being in love with their baby mamas, how women from the bay put men on, If h*es exist &amp;amp; much more. So grab your wine and wind down with ya girls. Save this link! All items of the week will be featured here! https://shopmy.us/public/pourmindspod&amp;hellip; Send Fan Mail To: 1452 Chattahoochee Ave NW GA 30318 United States Wanna leave us a voicemail?</description></item><item><title>Where My Man At? | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870044/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Valentines Day yall!!! This week we decided to give a Valentines Day Masterclass. We discussed the best gift to get that special man in your life this Valentines Day, Do sidechicks deserve to have a special Valentines Day , The importance of being a good kisser &amp;amp; much more. So grab your wine and take some notes. Save this link! All items of the week will be featured here!</description></item><item><title>Finna Get Loose FT. DC Young Fly | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870045/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, this weeks episode is a bit of a family affair ; this week the multitalented DC Young Fly came through and sat on the couch with ya girls. We discussed everything from Social media comedians, if talking during sex can kill the vibe, everything that comes with having multiple kids &amp;amp; so much more. So grab your wine and kick it with ya girls.
Save this link!</description></item><item><title>Blame it on Ty Ft. Armani Caesar | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870046/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, we are back with another hilarious episode; this week the first lady of Griselda Records, Armani Caesar came through and sat on the couch with ya girls. We discussed everything from people projecting their insecurities, men that need reassurance, Backshots vs missionary, the women rap Mt. Rushmore &amp;amp; so much more. So grab your wine and kick it with ya girls.
Save this link! All items of the week will be featured here!</description></item><item><title>Hardcore Ft. Big Loon | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870047/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, we back with a guest that kept it 1000 with no chaser, the one and only Big Loon. We discussed why you may not be getting embraced by your peers, therapy, and women C.O.s getting some penitentiary peen &amp;amp; much more. So grab your wine and wind down with ya girls. Save this link! All items of the week will be featured here! https://shopmy.us/public/pourmindspod&amp;hellip; Send Fan Mail To: 1452 Chattahoochee Ave NW GA 30318 United States Wanna leave us a voicemail?</description></item><item><title>The Nutty Professor | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870048/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, we giving yall a break from having a guest this week, so we could get back to the regularly scheduled shenanigans. We discuss the commitment timeline, keeping your word, Drea gets in her director bag when it comes to nut videos &amp;amp; much more. So grab your wine and kick it with ya girls. Save this link! All items of the week will be featured here! https://shopmy.</description></item><item><title>We Takin Off FT. B.O.B | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870049/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, we back with the first release of the new year and this one is a classic; The legendary B.O.B came and kicked it on the couch with ya girls. We discuss dating people in the same circle in the industry, B.O.B lets us know the signs that you&amp;rsquo;ve found your forever partner, morning sex &amp;amp; much more. So grab your wine and take off with ya girls.</description></item><item><title>Pimp Talk Ft. Lewis Belt | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870050/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 15:08:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, we made it through another year; What better way to bring in the New Year with our guest Lewis Belt. We discuss dating People overcharging once your status increases, spending money in the early stages of a relationship &amp;amp; much more. So grab your wine and unwind with ya girls.
Save this link! All items of the week will be featured here! https://shopmy.us/public/pourmindspod&amp;hellip;
Send Fan Mail To: 1452 Chattahoochee Ave NW GA 30318 United States</description></item><item><title>Santa Claus Is Cummin To Town FT. Cocktales Podcast | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870051/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Holidays yall, We are spreading holiday cheer with this episode thanks to our guests Kiki &amp;amp; Medinah from Cocktales podcast. We christen our new studio space; discuss our favorite black Christmas movies, gift giving guidelines, snowballing &amp;amp; so much more. So grab your wine or cocktail &amp;amp; unwind with ya girls.
Save this link! All items of the week will be featured here! https://shopmy.us/public/pourmindspod&amp;hellip; Send Fan Mail To: 1452 Chattahoochee Ave NW GA 30318 United States Wanna leave us a voicemail?</description></item><item><title>Did It On Em | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870052/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 15:34:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, We doing it on em this week. We discuss hairstylists, divorce, doing it on em &amp;amp; so much more. So grab your wine and unwind with ya girls.
Save this link! All items of the week will be featured here! https://shopmy.us/public/pourmindspod&amp;hellip;
Send Fan Mail To: 1452 Chattahoochee Ave NW GA 30318 United States
Wanna leave us a voicemail? Call 678.827.1826
MUSE BEAUTY: www.musebeautycollection.com
This episode is brought to you by BetterHelp; BetterHelp has connected over 3 million people with licensed therapists.</description></item><item><title>Nuttin Is A Habit | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870053/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, We telling yall now; we nuttin up this episode. We discuss dating gamers, Lex P vs Mr. Peanut, if you prefer a man that can nut and put it back in, &amp;amp; much more. So grab your wine and unwind with ya girls.
Send Fan Mail To: 1452 Chattahoochee Ave NW GA 30318 United States Wanna leave us a voicemail? Call 678.827.1826
MUSE BEAUTY: www.musebeautycollection.com
Save this link!</description></item><item><title>Dats Da Homie | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870054/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, we aint got no guest today ayeeee. We are back with another solo episode full of shenanigans. We discuss unlearning behaviors, how to get rid of soul ties, &amp;amp; much more. So grab your wine and unwind with ya girls.
Send Fan Mail To: 1452 Chattahoochee Ave NW GA 30318 United States
Wanna leave us a voicemail? Call 678.827.1826
MUSE BEAUTY: www.musebeautycollection.com
This episode is brought to you by BetterHelp; BetterHelp has connected over 3 million people with licensed therapists.</description></item><item><title>Finessers Gon Finesse FT. Jonathan Dupiton AKA Finesse | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870055/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 16:01:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, this week ya girls get a lesson on the art of Finessing with special guest Jonathan Dupiton AKA Finesse. We discuss scamming vs finessing, if head can be too sloppy, and so much more. Sit back, relax, grab your wine and finesse the stress away. Send Fan Mail To: 1452 Chattahoochee Ave NW GA 30318 United States
Wanna leave us a voicemail? Call 678.827.1826
This episode is brought to you by BetterHelp; BetterHelp has connected over 3 million people with licensed therapists.</description></item><item><title>A Mukbang of Mischief | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870056/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, this week ya girls are back with a solo episode full of the usual shenanigans. We discuss hanging out with people because of their ascetics , internet panhandling, and so much more. Grab your wine and wind down with ya girls.
Send Fan Mail To: 1452 Chattahoochee Ave NW GA 30318 United States
Wanna leave us a voicemail? Call 678.827.1826
This episode is brought to you by BetterHelp; Learn more and save 10% off your first month at BetterHelp.</description></item><item><title>Unproblematic King FT. Paul Wall | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870057/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 19:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, this week ya girls are sittin sideways with Houstons Own, Paul Wall; rapper, family man, &amp;amp; slab rida. We discuss everything from knowing when you have found the one to staying unproblematic in a world full of problems. Grab your wine, sit back and enjoy the show!
Tickets to sip n paint in Houston hosted by Lex https://tastevitainc.com/collections/&amp;hellip;
Need advice? Email askpourminds@gmail.com
This episode is sponsored by BetterHelp.</description></item><item><title>New Orleans Bounce FT. Chase N. Cashe | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870058/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, this week ya girls take it down to the Big Easy with New Orleans native Jesse “Chase N. Cashe” Woodard, a grammy award winning producer and businessman. We discuss everything from business to toxic make up sex. Grab your wine, sit back and enjoy the show!
Need advice? Email askpourminds@gmail.com
This episode is sponsored by BetterHelp. Visit BetterHelp dot com/POURMINDS today to get 10% off your first month</description></item><item><title>Under Da Sea | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870059/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Halloween yall! This week ya girls are cutting up under da sea; we discuss signs of a crazy partner, sex classes, and much more. Grab your wine, sit back and laugh with us.
Need advice? Email askpourminds@gmail.com
NINETHCLOSET.COM for clothing
This episode is sponsored by BetterHelp. Visit BetterHelp dot com/POURMINDS today to get 10% off your first month Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>To Be Honest | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870060/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode is the therapy session we all needed featuring our girl Mia Jaye! We discuss, death, life, dealing with trauma, &amp;amp; black men.
Want Advice? Email Askpourminds@gmail.com
Go to HelloFresh dot com slash pourminds65 and use code pourminds65 for 65% off plus free shipping!
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lil Shirley | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870061/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode is Just Us! We discuss, Male Sex Toys, Dating men with full custody, &amp;amp; many more topics. Grab your wine and come kick it with your girls Want Advice? Email Askpourminds@gmail.com
Go to HelloFresh dot com slash pourminds65 and use code pourminds65 for 65% off plus free shipping!
Dipsea is offering an extended 30 day free trial when you go to Dipsea Stories dot com slash POURMINDS.</description></item><item><title>New York State of Mind | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870062/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode is featuring Mouse Jones! Follow @mouse_jones . We discuss, Are men single because of the type of women they like, Child support drama, and many more topics! Go to Bombas.com for 20% off your first order by using code: POURMINDS. Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rubber Meeting The Road feat. CyHi | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870063/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 18:23:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode is featuring CyHi! We discuss the real important things to bring to the table, dealing with imitation, teaching your younger self things and more! Follow CyHi on Instagram @Cyhi Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Go to https://www.HelloFresh.com/pourminds65 for 65% off meals and including free shipping!
Get cash back to your bank account, PayPal, or an E-gift card for Amazon and other brands.</description></item><item><title>Too Much Pressure ft. Dess Dior | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870064/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 13:21:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! Today we have Dess Dior and we discuss the pressure of social media, keeping your day 1’s around, initiating sex and more!
Follow Dess @1DessDior
Get tickets to the live show https://www.pourminds.com 10/4 - TAMPA 10/5 - MIAMI 10/6 - ORLANDO
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Dipsea is an app full of hundreds of short, sexy audio stories designed by women for women.</description></item><item><title>Pray Fa Jesus ft. Fabo | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870065/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 18:07:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode is featuring Fabo and we discuss being targeted in the public eye, getting your significant others name tatted on you and more!
Get tickets to the live show https://www.pourminds.com 9/18 - ARLINGTON 10/4 - TAMPA 10/5 - MIAMI 10/6 - ORLANDO
No one likes waiting on a paycheck, especially when you&amp;rsquo;ve got bills due. Get started with Chime today and get paid 2 days early!</description></item><item><title>Smile for Me Daddy feat. Scotty Atl | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870066/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 17:34:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all this episode is featuring Scotty ATL! We discuss the history of grills, your friend and your man not getting along and more! Get tickets to the live show https://www.pourminds.com Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Looking for affordable unique, one of a kind products made by real people? Etsy is the place for you! Go to https://www.Etsy.com and use code Hello10 for 10% of your first purchase up to $50!</description></item><item><title>Imposters | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870067/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 17:47:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! Today we discuss the statement “if he wanted to he would”, imposter syndrome and more!
Get tickets to the live show https://www.pourminds.com Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Factor is the perfect mealtime solution for an on-the-go lifestyle. Their fresh, never frozen meals are delivered ready to heat and eat in 2 minutes. Head to https://www.GO.FACTOR75.com/pourminds130 and use code pourminds130 to get $130 off across 6 boxes.</description></item><item><title>Put The Bottle Down ft. Pap Chanel | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870068/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 13:24:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode is featuring Pap Chanel and we discuss handling your liquor, the importance of using the bathroom after intercourse and more!
Get tickets to the live show https://www.pourminds.com Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
At https://www.Honeylove.com get 20% off a second item. PLUS, when you use code POURMINDS, you&amp;rsquo;ll get an ADDITIONAL 10% off your entire order!
Are you looking to buy or sell your car instantly online with no hassle?</description></item><item><title>You Not My Man Hun | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870069/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 17:56:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss doing relationship things but not in a relationship, do single men brag about dating married women, female erogenous zones and more!
Click the city for tickets to Pour Minds Live 8/27 -NEW YORK 9/18 - ARLINGTON 10/4 - TAMPA 10/5 - MIAMI 10/6 - ORLANDO
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Go to https://www.HelloFresh.com/pourminds16 for 16 free meals, 3 free gifts and including free shipping!</description></item><item><title>The Houston Episode feat.. Ali Siddiq | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870070/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 16:25:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode features Ali Siddiq and to be honest we did not stay on topic at all! We talked about a whole lot of Houston stuff and more! Follow him @AliSiddiq
Get tickets to the live show https://www.pourminds.com No one likes waiting on a paycheck, especially when you&amp;rsquo;ve got bills due. Get started with Chime today and get paid 2 days early! Applying for a free account takes less than 2 minutes.</description></item><item><title>You A Lil Puppeh | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870071/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 16:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss someone who checks off all your boxes, dating someone from the past, men sending nudes and more!
Get tickets to the live show https://www.pourminds.com
EDM Playlist: https://music.apple.com/us/playlist/edm/pl.u-PDb446Zs2LJ3v3
Ritual’s Essential for Women 18+ Multivitamin was formulated by exhaustive research to help fill nutrient gaps in the diets of women ages 18+. It is formulated with nutrients to help support brain health, bone health, blood health, and provide antioxidant support.</description></item><item><title>MMM MMM feat. Kali | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870072/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 17:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey Y’all! This episode is featuring Kali and we discuss women being weak in the knees, men being gold diggers, deal breakers in the bedroom and more! Follow Kali @kaliii
Get tickets to the live show https://www.pourminds.com Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Go to https://www.HelloFresh.com/pourminds16 for 16 free meals, 3 free gifts and including free shipping!
At https://www.Honeylove.com get 20% off a second item.</description></item><item><title>Pop it for Hugh | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870073/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 15:56:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss popular privilege, why men are considered bitter when they express their emotions and more!
The For Rich or For Pour Tour tickets are on sale now! https://www.pourminds.com/tour-tickets
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Spend less time shopping and cooking, and more time enjoying healthy food that you’ll actually love with Hungryroot. Get 30% off your first delivery and a free gift with every delivery.</description></item><item><title>Soul Snatchers feat. Big Boss Vette | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870074/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 18:26:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode is featuring Big Boss Vette! We discuss dating contracts, if a man can handle you, dealing with baby mamas and more!
Follow Vette @BigBossVette
Get tickets to the live show https://www.pourminds.com Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Go to https://www.HelloFresh.com/pourminds16 for 16 free meals, 3 free gifts and including free shipping!
Protect your online activity TODAY with the VPN rated #1 by Business Insider.</description></item><item><title>The Dependent Man and Independent Woman feat. 19 Keys | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870075/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 16:17:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode is featuring 19 keys and we discuss insecure men hiding behind money, the dependent man and independent woman, unlocking your 3rd eye and more!
Follow 19 Keys @19_Keys
Get tickets to the live show! https://www.pourminds.com/tour-tickets
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Dipsea is an app full of hundreds of short, sexy audio stories designed by women for women. Dipsea also has Sleep Stories, Wellness Sessions, and now they also offer written stories.</description></item><item><title>We In Phuket | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870076/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 16:57:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss the benefits of marriage, living with your significant other and more!
The For Rich or For Pour Tour tickets are on sale now! https://www.pourminds.com/tour-tickets
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Spend less time shopping and cooking, and more time enjoying healthy food that you’ll actually love with Hungryroot. Get 30% off your first delivery and a free gift with every delivery.</description></item><item><title>Clean Girl, Soft Life | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870077/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 17:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all this episode we discuss soft life aesthetic, women with money not being bosses and more! Get tickets to the live show! https://www.pourminds.com/tour-tickets
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Ritual’s Essential for Women 18+ Multivitamin was formulated by exhaustive research to help fill nutrient gaps in the diets of women ages 18+. It is formulated with nutrients to help support brain health, bone health, blood health, and provide antioxidant support.</description></item><item><title>Know Yo Lane ft. Navv Greene | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870078/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 15:13:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This week Navv is back! We discuss men doing too much to impress women, how embarrassing it is to be a girlfriend and more!
Get live show tickets below: 6/25 - ATLANTA, GA 7/9 - HOUSTON, TX 7/30 - DALLAS 8/5 - COLUMBIA, SC 8/6 - BIRMINGHAM, AL 8/12 - CHICAGO, IL 8/27 - NEW YORK, NY
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.</description></item><item><title>#PrayForJaden | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870079/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 16:27:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss the pressure to have kids, health in the black community, the documentary about Abercrombie and fitch and more! Get live show tickets! https://www.pourminds.com/tour-tickets
Protect your online activity TODAY with the VPN rated #1 by Business Insider. Visit my exclusive link https://www.ExpressVPN.com/pourminds and you can get an extra 3 months FREE on a one-year package.
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.</description></item><item><title>LA With The Vibes ft. G Perico | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870080/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 17:23:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode is featuring G Perico and we discuss life in LA, dating rappers and more! Follow him @bgperico Get tickets to the live show! https://www.pourminds.com/tour-tickets
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Spend less time shopping and cooking, and more time enjoying healthy food that you’ll actually love with Hungryroot. Get 30% off your first delivery and a free gift with every delivery.</description></item><item><title>Pour Some Moore ft. Tahir and Farren Moore | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870081/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 16:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode is featuring Tahir and Farren Moore from Moore To The Story Podcast! We discuss what makes marriage so hard, being the first man to treat a woman right, dating in LA and more! Follow Tahir and Farren @FarrenMoore @TahirMoore @MooreToTheStoryPodcast
Get your tickets to a live show! https://www.pourminds.com/tour-tickets
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
To find out where you can purchase Vizzy go to https://www.</description></item><item><title>Good Moms, Pour Choices ft. Erica and Milah | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870082/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 14:09:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all this episode is featuring Erica and Milah from Good Moms Bad Choices! We discuss parenting in the new generation, choosing your baby daddy, having a dating life with kids and more! Follow them @GoodMoms_BadChoices
Tickets on sale for live show today! Https://www.pourminds.com Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Eat clean 24/7, with fresh—never frozen—prepared meals that are so delicious! Head to https://www.go.FACTOR75.com/pourminds120 and use code pourminds120 to get $120 off.</description></item><item><title>You Either Applying Pressure or You Feeling It | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870083/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 16:04:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all this episode we discuss applying pressure to the wrong person, moving for love and more! Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Created by leading scientists in aging, genetics, and biometrics, InsideTracker analyzes your blood, DNA, and fitness tracking data to identify where you’re optimized—and where you’re not. For a limited time, get 20% off the entire InsideTracker store. Just go to https://www.insidetracker.com/POURMINDS</description></item><item><title>Gave You A Chance, Now I Hate It Here | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870084/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 15:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! In this episode we discuss letting your spouse manage your career, why giving someone who always wanted you a chance is a bad idea, we break down the movie “Deep Water” and more! Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Created by leading scientists in aging, genetics, and biometrics, InsideTracker analyzes your blood, DNA, and fitness tracking data to identify where you’re optimized—and where you’re not.</description></item><item><title>Ready to Sign Dem Papers feat. Ronnie Jordan | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870085/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 15:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode is featuring Ronnie Jordan! We discuss getting married too young, emasculating black men, role play and more! Follow Ronnie on IG @RonnieJordan Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
To find out where you can purchase Vizzy go to https://www.vizzyhardseltzer.com/POURMINDS
Created by leading scientists in aging, genetics, and biometrics, InsideTracker analyzes your blood, DNA, and fitness tracking data to identify where you’re optimized—and where you’re not.</description></item><item><title>Ain't No Competition Pooh ft. Jilly Anais | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870086/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 18:05:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode is featuring Jilly Anais! We discuss how to tell if your friend is in competition with you, the difference in men and women making money, having a dating life in the entertainment industry and more! Follow Jilly on IG @JillyAnais
Check out her EP here! https://music.apple.com/us/album/copy-paste-ep/1614041013
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Created by leading scientists in aging, genetics, and biometrics, InsideTracker analyzes your blood, DNA, and fitness tracking data to identify where you’re optimized—and where you’re not.</description></item><item><title>Don't Gas Me Up | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870087/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 14:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all this episode we discuss seeking approval from other races, gaslighting yourself, and more!
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Created by leading scientists in aging, genetics, and biometrics, InsideTracker analyzes your blood, DNA, and fitness tracking data to identify where you’re optimized—and where you’re not. For a limited time, get 20% off the entire InsideTracker store. Just go to https://www.insidetracker.com/POURMINDS
Purchase a 3-month Babbel subscription, you’ll get an additional 3 months for FREE.</description></item><item><title>Three's Company feat. Clayton English | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870088/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 16:34:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all this episode is featuring our fave Clayton English! We discuss if marriage matters, supervised cheating and more! Follow Clayton @ClaytonEnglish Become a Patreon member! https://www.patreon.com/PourMinds
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Created by leading scientists in aging, genetics, and biometrics, InsideTracker analyzes your blood, DNA, and fitness tracking data to identify where you’re optimized—and where you’re not. For a limited time, get 20% off the entire InsideTracker store.</description></item><item><title>Your Man Is My Man Too | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870089/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 19:07:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all this week we discuss dealing with men in relationships, fetish vs preference, we review the movie “American Animals” and more!
Become a Patreon member! https://www.patreon.com/PourMinds
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Get a $25 VISA gift card to our qualified listeners just for completing the quick and easy debt assessment at https://www.PDSDebt.com/pourminds To find out where you can purchase Vizzy go to https://www.</description></item><item><title>You Scaring Da Gworls | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870090/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 16:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all this episode we discuss things men do that scare the girls, why short men get disrespected and more! Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Use code WELCOME10 at checkout to get 10% off your first purchase at https://www.etsy.com
If you’re ready to buy, sell or trade-in a car visit https://www.vroom.com
Bright Cellars is a subscription wine service that introduces you to a variety of wines.</description></item><item><title>Southern Girls feat. Ken the Man | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870091/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode is featuring Ken The Man! We discuss the state of the hip hop, looking at men&amp;rsquo;s dating resume, and more! Follow her @ImKenTheMan
Check out her new videos!
https://youtu.be/JKFwrBOpTqo
https://youtu.be/BKe6Wcc8eLA
Purchase a 3-month Babbel subscription, you’ll get an additional 3 months for FREE. That’s 6 months, for the price of 3! Just go to Https://www.babbel.com and use promo code POURMINDS
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.</description></item><item><title>Trappin Ain't Dead feat. Wall Street Trapper | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870092/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 15:06:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all this episode is featuring Trap aka Wall Street Trapper. We discuss how to make a 9-5 your hustle, the importance of financial literacy, finances affecting your dating life and more!
Follow Trap on IG @wall_street_trapper Get tickets to our 2nd live show!! https://www.cltcomedyzone.com/shows/166768
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
If you’re ready to buy, sell or trade in a car visit https://www.vroom.com</description></item><item><title>Is It Luck or Fate Pooh? | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870093/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 16:24:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all this week we discuss if we believe in luck, having a real man, tinder swindler and more!
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Go to https://www.HelloFresh.com/pourminds16 for 16 free meals, 3 free gifts and including free shipping!
Use code WELCOME10 at checkout to get 10% off your first purchase at https://www.etsy.com
To find out where you can purchase Vizzy go to https://www.vizzyhardseltzer.com/POURMINDS Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Grand Rising Huns feat. Gigi Robinson | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870094/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This week we have a very special guest, astrologist Gigi Robinson! This week we discuss love in astrology, the meaning of the moon, sun, mercury signs, the true meaning of mercury retrograde and more! Follow Gigi on Instagram @Iamlivingaligned Get your reading done with her at https://www.iamlivingaligned.com/
Tickets to the live show on March 16!! https://www.cltcomedyzone.com/shows/166768
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS</description></item><item><title>You Get the Bag and Fumble It | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870095/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 18:04:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all this week we discuss your character after you fallout with someone, the biggest bag we ever fumbled, getting tested and more!
Get the perfect shape wear at https://www.Honeylove.com and get 20% off a second item. PLUS, when you use code POURMINDS, you&amp;rsquo;ll get an ADDITIONAL 10% off your entire order!
Get tickets to our 2nd live show!! https://www.cltcomedyzone.com/shows/166768
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.</description></item><item><title>The Art of Being Mysterious | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870096/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 16:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all, this week we discuss PTSD from friendships, the art of being mysterious and more!
Get tickets to our 2nd live show!! https://www.cltcomedyzone.com/shows/166768
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Get a $25 VISA gift card to our qualified listeners just for completing the quick and easy debt assessment at https://www.PDSDebt.com/pourminds If you’re ready to buy, sell or trade in a car visit https://www.vroom.com</description></item><item><title>Pushin P. Period | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870097/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 15:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This week we discuss tough love vs soft approach, dating people out of desperation and more!
Go to https://www.thepillclub.com/pourminds to get your first birth control care package. The Pill Club is offering a $10 donation to https://www.Bedsider.org for every Pour Minds listener who becomes a patient. Help women in need of affordable birth control. Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Rituals essential for women 18+ multivitamin is formulated with nutrients to help support brain health, bone health, blood health, and provide antioxidant support.</description></item><item><title>The Dating Game ft. Monet | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870098/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 18:20:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we have Monet who is a dating strategist! We discuss loyalty and labels, how to pull high caliber men, celibacy and more! Follow Monet on Instagram @UGlowGirlOfficial Become a Patreon member! https://www.patreon.com/PourMinds
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Go to https://www.HelloFresh.com/pourminds14 for 14 free meals, 3 free gifts and including free shipping!
Use code WELCOME10 at checkout to get 10% off your first purchase at https://www.</description></item><item><title>Don't Be Jealous Hun | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870099/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 17:24:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss envy vs jealousy, your body rejecting your partner and more! Become a patreon member! https://www.patreon.com/PourMinds
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Purchase a 3-month Babbel subscription, you’ll get an additional 3 months for FREE. That’s 6 months, for the price of 3! Just go to Https://www.babbel.com and use promo code POURMINDS
At https://www.Honeylove.com get 20% off a second item.</description></item><item><title>A Bug's Life w/ Mona | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870100/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 17:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all this episode is featuring Mona aka @dontcallmeewhitegirl. We discuss East Coast vs South, loyalty vs stupidity and more! Follow Mona on Instagram: @dontcallmeeewhitegirl
Become a patreon member! https://www.patreon.com/PourMinds
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Go to https://www.HelloFresh.com/pourminds14 for 14 free meals, 3 free gifts and including free shipping!
Go to https://www.thepillclub.com/pourminds to get your first birth control care package. The Pill Club is offering a $10 donation to https://www.</description></item><item><title>Y'all Too Strict | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870101/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 15:39:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all this episode we discuss transitional relationship, not taking serious things too serious and more! Become a patreon member! https://www.patreon.com/PourMinds
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Get a $25 VISA gift card to our qualified listeners just for completing the quick and easy debt assessment at https://www.PDSDebt.com/pourminds Email us to get your questions answered on the show askpourminds@gmail.com Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Is Women Empowerment a Scam? | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870102/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 14:55:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all today we discuss being the successful person in your family, are women really for each other, sex education laws and more!
Get your taste pills, toys, lingerie and more here! Use code POURMINDS for a discount https://www.tastevitainc.com/
Raise your credit score in 20 days! Visit https://www.scoremaster.com/PourMinds
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS Save fifteen dollars off your first visit with a board-certified dermatologist at https://www.</description></item><item><title>No Husband? No Problem feat. Erica Duchess | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870103/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 15:04:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all this episode is featuring comedienne Erica Duchess and we discuss how to know if a friendship/relationship is genuine, Women waiting longer to have kids, multiple marriages and more! Follow Erica @EricaDuchess
Get your taste pills, toys, lingerie and more here! Use code POURMINDS for a discount https://www.tastevitainc.com/
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Go to https://www.HelloFresh.com/pourminds12 for 12 free meals, including free shipping!</description></item><item><title>All I Want for Christmas is My Things Hun | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870104/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 18:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss levels to gifts, living in your purpose and more! Shop our new merch! https://www.bypourminds.com Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS Get a $25 VISA gift card to our qualified listeners just for completing the quick and easy debt assessment at https://www.PDSDebt.com/pourminds Go to https://www.GreenChef.com/pourminds100 and use code pourminds100 to get $100 off including free shipping! Go to https://www.storyworth.com/pourminds for $10 off your first purchase!</description></item><item><title>Wifey Material feat. Deelishis | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870105/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 16:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss “IG girls” getting married, plastic surgery, feeling sexy after kids and more! Follow Deelishis @iamsodeelishis Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS Go to https://www.thepillclub.com/pourminds to get your first birth control care package and donate to help more women in need of affordable birth control For 40% off the first 3 months of a peppermint dream subscription PLUS a free mug and frother, or 20% off a one-time purchase visit https://www.</description></item><item><title>Be Specific feat. Navv Greene | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870106/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 14:27:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss what men REALLY want, men being in women&amp;rsquo;s business, how men feel about extremely freaky women and more! Follow Navv on all social media @NavvGreene Shop our new merch! https://www.bypourminds.com
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Get a $25 VISA gift card to our qualified listeners just for completing the quick and easy debt assessment at https://www.PDSDebt.com/pourminds Sell, trade or buy your next vehicle at https://www.</description></item><item><title>I Love Both of Y'all Hun | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870107/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 18:17:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss being in love with two people, giving men money, pain kinks and more! Enjoy 20% off Pour Minds merch with code BLACK20 Shop Now: www.bypourminds.com
Get your taste pills, merch, lingerie and use code POURMINDS here! https://tastevitainc.com Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS Go to https://www.thepillclub.com/pourminds to get your first birth control care package and donate to help more women in need of affordable birth control Sell, trade or buy your next vehicle at https://www.</description></item><item><title>You A Throwback and You Old | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870108/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 14:08:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss Double standards with ageism, Section etiquette for men and more! Get your taste pills, toys, lingerie and more here! Use code POURMINDS for a discount https://tastevitainc.com/
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Get a $25 VISA gift card to our qualified listeners just for completing the quick and easy debt assessment at https://www.PDSDebt.com/pourminds Sell, trade or buy your next vehicle at https://www.</description></item><item><title>Having My Way | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870109/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 16:31:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss if there should be an age restriction on cosmetic surgery, the &amp;lsquo;having my way&amp;rsquo; movement, teaching how to scissor and more! Tickets to the live show! https://nashville.zanies.com/show/pour-minds-podcast-2/
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Go to https://www.HelloFresh.com/pourminds12 for 12 free meals, including free shipping!
Save fifteen dollars off your first visit with a board-certified dermatologist at https://www.Apostrophe.com/POURMINDS when you use our code:POURMINDS.</description></item><item><title>The Mind of a Cheater | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870110/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2021 20:39:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss the psychology behind cheating, delaying intimacy, a different love language and more! Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Go to https://www.HelloFresh.com/pourminds12 for 12 free meals, including free shipping!
Go to https://www.thepillclub.com/pourminds to get your first birth control care package and donate to help more women in need of affordable birth control Girlfriend Collective is offering first time customers $25 off purchases of $100 or more when you go to https://www.</description></item><item><title>Freaky Friday ft. Cookiiee | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870111/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 13:27:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode is featuring @EatMyCookiiee and we discuss Sex shaming sex workers, Dating in the sex industry, if the industry is over saturated and more!
Follow Cookie on Twitter @EatMyCookiiee and her onlyfans https://onlyfans.com/cookiieee
Try BlueChew FREE when you use our promo code POURMINDS at checkout&amp;ndash;just pay $5 shipping. https://www.BlueChew.com, promo code POURMINDS to receive your first month FREE!
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.</description></item><item><title>You Tannet Up! | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870112/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 13:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss dating behind your friends, People becoming classist with success, Affirmations during sex and more!
Try BlueChew FREE when you use our promo code POURMINDS at checkout&amp;ndash;just pay $5 shipping. That’s https://www.BlueChew.com, promo code POURMINDS to receive your first month FREE! Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS Get a $25 VISA gift card to our qualified listeners just for completing the quick and easy debt assessment at https://www.</description></item><item><title>In the Bible ft. Brianda | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870113/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 13:18:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! We have a guest today! This episode features @BibleBrianda (please know she’s a comedian and we had a great time!) we discuss Is our environment too hyper sexual, Being spiritual vs being religious, Practicing celibacy and why.
Follow Brianda on all platforms @BibleBrianda Get the BEST toys and the popular taste pills here! Use code POURMINDS for 15% off https://taste-vitamins-inc.myshopify.com/
Get tickets to the first live show!</description></item><item><title>Beggy Bundy | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870114/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 13:29:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss Applying pressure vs harassment, Finessing vs begging, weird turn ons and more! Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS Go to https://www.GreenChef.com/pourminds100 and use code pourminds100 to get $100 off including free shipping! Get your new headphones and save 15% off your Raycon order at https://www.buyraycon.com/POURMINDS
Save fifteen dollars off your first visit with a board-certified dermatologist at https://www.Apostrophe.com/POURMINDS when you use our code:POURMINDS.</description></item><item><title>He A Lil Baddie | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870115/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss men want to get treated like baddies too, Men being financially attracted to you, Having the best sex once you turn 30 and more! For the taste pills as seen is previous episodes visit https://taste-vitamins-inc.myshopify.com and use code POURMINDS Visit https://www.ThriveCausemetics.com/pourminds for 15% off your first order! This is an exclusive offer you can ONLY get here! Grow thicker, healthier hair by going to https://www.</description></item><item><title>Hold it down for what? Ft. LightSkin Keisha | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870116/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 15:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode features LightSkin Keisha and we discuss Holding somebody down and fighting for your relationship vs leaving, are men better friends than women, masturbating in a relationship and more!
Get tickets to the first live show!! https://nashville.zanies.com/show/pour-minds-podcast/?date=11%2F17%2F2021&amp;amp;timeId=2363616 Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Go to https://www.HelloFresh.com/pourminds12 for 12 free meals, including free shipping!
To find out where you can purchase Vizzy go to https://www.</description></item><item><title>Pocket Full of Stones | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870117/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 21:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss borrowing money from friends when you got a man, How much of an age gap is too much, Sex Tapes and more! Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Get quick and easy smoothies! Order online with the code PourMinds20 and get 20% off + free delivery right to your door. Visit https://www.evivenutrition.com and discover Evive delicious products today!</description></item><item><title>Jive Records featuring Brianna Amor | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870118/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 14:33:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all this episode features Brianna Amor and we discuss expectations being too high when dating, if it’s irresponsible to have a child when you aren’t financially stable, freaky rich men and more!
Tickets to live show !!! https://nashville.zanies.com/show/pour-minds-podcast/
Follow Brianna on all platforms @BriannaAmor
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Go to https://www.HelloFresh.com/pourminds12 for 12 free meals, including free shipping!
To find out where you can purchase Vizzy go to https://www.</description></item><item><title>It's Me or Your Mama Hun | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870119/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 12:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all this episode we discuss overstepping boundaries with your friends, needy men and Oedipus complex, how to attract a woman and more!
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Get a $25 VISA gift card to our qualified listeners just for completing the quick and easy debt assessment at https://www.PDSDebt.com/pourminds
To find out where you can purchase Vizzy go to https://www.vizzyhardseltzer.com/POURMINDS
Get 20% Off + Free Shipping, with the code POURMINDS at https://www.</description></item><item><title>Lasagna Gate ft. Jerome Trammel | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870120/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 17:25:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all this episode features Jerome Trammel and we discuss down low culture, if media effects sexuality, steps to prepare for anal and more!
Follow Jerome! @MrJeromeTrammel Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Go to https://www.HelloFresh.com/pourminds12 for 12 free meals, including free shipping!
To find out where you can purchase Vizzy go to https://www.vizzyhardseltzer.com/POURMINDS
Purchase a 3-month Babbel subscription, you’ll get an additional 3 months for FREE.</description></item><item><title>Do It Like It's My Bidet...Baybeee | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870121/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 12:22:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This is the birthday episode in honor of Lex’s birthday this week and we talking everything birthday! Birthday sex, birthday expectations, birthday dinners and more! The secret to the best taste down below!Get your taste pills https://www.TasteVitaInc.com with discount code POURMINDS for 15% off
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Get quick and easy smoothies! Order online with the code PourMinds20 and get 20% off + free delivery right to your door.</description></item><item><title>She Want A Man, Don't Need A Man | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870122/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 20:51:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all, this episode we discuss if being independent is overrated, Drinking etiquette, Making love and more! Get pour minds merch now! https://www.bypourminds.com
Get your taste pills https://www.TasteVitaInc.com with discount code POURMINDS for 15% off
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Go to https://www.HelloFresh.com/pourminds12 for 12 free meals, including free shipping!
To find out where you can purchase Vizzy go to https://www.vizzyhardseltzer.com/POURMINDS
Purchase a 3-month Babbel subscription, you’ll get an additional 3 months for FREE.</description></item><item><title>It's The Pay Pig For Me | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870123/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This week we discuss time and opportunity, is having a type when dating hurting or helping you, pay pigs and more! Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Go to https://www.GreenChef.com/pourminds100 and use code pourminds100 to get $100 off including free shipping!
Go to https://www.thepillclub.com/pourminds to get your first birth control care package and donate to help more women in need of affordable birth control</description></item><item><title>Yo Quiero Collard Greens feat. Karlous Miller | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870124/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 03:22:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss if you’re 30 and unmarried you’re ran through, Do black women need to lower our standards, using food in the bedroom and more! Get new merch! https://www.bypourminds.com
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Go to https://www.GreenChef.com/pourminds100 and use code pourminds100 to get $100 off including free shipping!
Visit https://www.ThriveCausemetics.com/pourminds for 15% off your first order!
To find out where you can purchase Vizzy go to https://www.</description></item><item><title>Groupie Love ft. Yung Joc | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870125/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 23:27:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all this episode we discuss Groupie stories, How to go from hoe to housewife, How to turn yo bdb out and more. Get pour minds merch now! https://www.bypourminds.com
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Go to https://www.HelloFresh.com/pourminds12 for 12 free meals, including free shipping!
Get a $25 VISA gift card to our qualified listeners just for completing the quick and easy debt assessment at https://www.</description></item><item><title>Baby Mama Goals | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870126/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 12:29:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all this episode we discuss Plastic surgery culture, Looking up to rapper baby mamas, Sneaky links and more!
To find out where to purchase Vizzy go to https://www.vizzyhardseltzer.com/POURMINDS.
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Go to https://www.thepillclub.com/pourminds to get your first birth control care package and donate to help more women in need of affordable birth control
You don&amp;rsquo;t have to search for coupons anymore!</description></item><item><title>The Streets Is Watching ft. RL | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870127/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 20:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss what makes a woman high value, being attracted to someone outside of your relationship (but not cheating), how to keep your relationship/marriage spicy and more!
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Go to https://www.HelloFresh.com/pourminds12 for 12 free meals, including free shipping!
Go to https://www.babbel.com and use code POURMINDS at checkout to learn a new language and receive 3 free months.</description></item><item><title>Return of the Dirty Mack | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870128/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 13:25:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss dirty macking, entitlement, starting your “engine” and more! The rap playlist is almost done so I’ll drop that in the description next week!
To find out where to purchase Vizzy go to https://www.vizzyhardseltzer.com/POURMINDS.
Get 10% off your first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Get new merch! https://bypourminds.com
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lord Farquaad Could Never | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870129/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 00:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all this episode we discuss being scared to date after a breakup, missing out on fun to save money, sex classes and more!
Get new merch! https://bypourminds.com
Sign up for Samia’s classes and use code pourminds for a discount! https://thesexualessentials.com/our-classes/
Get 10% off their first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Go to https://www.HelloFresh.com/pourminds12 for 12 free meals, including free shipping!
Check out https://www.whocherrylou.com Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>The Blacktoe Nation | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870130/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss get rich schemes, dressing how you want to be addressed, air-pulse stimulating toys and more!
https://www.betterhelp.com/PourMinds for discounted therapy sessions!
You don&amp;rsquo;t have to search for coupons anymore! Visit https://www.joinhoney.com/pourminds and add it to chrome for discounts on almost ANYTHING!
Toys from https://thesexualessentials.com/toys/
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hibachi Titties feat. Samia | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870131/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! Today’s episode is all about sex! We have a special guest, sex expert Samia and we discuss sexual compatibility, how to strengthen orgasms, how to squirt and so much more!
Get 10% off their first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Go to https://www.HelloFresh.com/pourminds12 for 12 free meals, including free shipping!
For $20 off your Buffy comforter, visit https://www.Buffy.co and enter POURMINDS
Follow Samia @sexualessentials Join her patreon https://www.</description></item><item><title>Is You Clickin' or What? | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870132/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 14:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss Is click bait worth it, Having a boy vs having a girl, Sex with different races and more! For $20 off your Buffy comforter, visit https://www.Buffy.co and enter POURMINDS
Get your pour minds merch at https://www.bypourminds.com
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Don Like That | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870133/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss if your man is cheating but you’re not leaving, incel culture, how to properly spank and more!
Get your merch at https://www.bypourminds.com
Bright Cellars is offering you 50% off your first 6 bottle box of wine by going to https://www.brightcellars.com/POURMINDS
https://www.betterhelp.com/PourMinds for discounted therapy sessions! In addition, financial aid is available! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What You Mean You Ain't Nasty? | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870134/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss Insecurities as a bad bitch, Selling pussy vs having a bdb, Vanilla sex and more!
https://www.betterhelp.com/PourMinds for discounted therapy sessions!
For $20 off your Buffy comforter, visit https://www.Buffy.co and enter POURMINDS Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Pfizer Gang | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870135/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 13:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss your man judging you off your past, uncomfortable convos with friends, things in the bedroom that are absolutely off limits and more!
Get your merch at https://www.bypourminds.com Visit https://www.GreenChef.com/90pourminds and use code 90pourminds to get $90 off including free shipping!
https://www.betterhelp.com/PourMinds for discounted therapy sessions!
You don&amp;rsquo;t have to search for coupons anymore! Visit https://www.joinhoney.com/pourminds and add it to chrome for discounts on almost ANYTHING!</description></item><item><title>I Like My Girls BBW ft. Jack Thriller | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870136/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 14:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss being loyal during talking stage, is cheating a deal breaker, if head with a BBW better and more! Follow Jack @JackThriller Get new merch on our new site! https://www.bypourminds.com Get 10% off their first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Go to https://www.HelloFresh.com/pourminds12 for 12 free meals, including free shipping! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cheat Day | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870137/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 16:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! Today we discuss not depriving yourself while trying to stand up to someone you used to date, men who argue with women, Sexually inexperienced partners, the movie Secret Society and more!
Bright Cellars is offering you 50% off your first 6 bottle box of wine and a 7th bottle FREE by going to https://www.brightcellars.com/POURMINDS
https://www.betterhelp.com/pourminds for your counseling needs
Visit https://www.pourminds.com for merch!
Lex Playlist - https://tidal.</description></item><item><title>Sex Lies | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870138/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870138/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss Mixing friend groups, Your man coming in between friendships, Sex lies and more! Get 10% off their first month of counseling at https://www.betterhelp.com/POURMINDS
Go to https://www.HelloFresh.com/pourminds12 for 12 free meals, including free shipping! Get better insurance with Gabi! Go to https://www.gabi.com/POURMINDS Get Honey for FREE and start saving money at https://www.Joinhoney.com/pourminds Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>HTown Forever | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870139/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 14:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss Doing scandalous things and not telling your friends, beginning expectations (1 month in a relationship), how do i know if my sex is good? The coochie scale and more!
Get your merch at https://www.POURMINDS.com Visit https://www.GreenChef.com/90pourminds and use code 90pourminds to get $90 off including free shipping!
https://www.betterhelp.com/PourMinds for discounted therapy sessions! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>I-N-D-E-P-E-N-D-E-N-T | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870140/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss ageism, are women becoming too independent, is anal play the gateway drug and more!
Get your merch at https://www.POURMINDS.com Visit https://www.hellofresh.com/pourminds10 for 10 free meals!
https://www.betterhelp.com/PourMinds for discounted therapy sessions!
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tarzan Returns | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870141/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 16:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss the Only Fans epidemic, men needing therapy, men moaning and more!
Bright Cellars is offering you 50% off your first 6 bottle box of wine by going to https://www.brightcellars.com/POURMINDS.
Get your merch now! https://www.POURMINDS.com
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Me and Mr. Eugene ft. KikiSaidSo | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870142/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 14:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we have Kiki from Cocktales joining us and discuss sending subliminal to your friends online, I&amp;rsquo;m in your city texts, FaceTime sex and more!
Follow Kiki on all social @kikisaidso and check out her podcast Cocktales
https://www.betterhelp.com/pourminds​ for your counseling needs
Use https://www.headspace.com/pourminds for your 1 month free trail! Start meditating and sleeping better!
Order your tushy and get 10% off plus free shipping! https://www.</description></item><item><title>Trappin Ain't Dead | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870143/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 17:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss the saying “being humble will take your far”, people being haters vs not liking you, voodoo sex and more! https://www.betterhelp.com/pourminds for your counseling needs
You don&amp;rsquo;t have to search for coupons anymore! Visit https://www.joinhoney.com/pourminds and add it to chrome for discounts on almost ANYTHING!
As promised here is Lex’s playlist! It’s on tidal, I do not have Apple Music. Hope y’all enjoy! https://tidal.</description></item><item><title>Lex P and The P Is For... | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870144/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 11:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870144/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This week we discuss hairstyles attracting certain men, praising black men, eruption videos and more! Visit www.BetterHelp.com/POURMINDS for all your therapy needs!
Use www.headspace.com/pourminds for your 1 month free trail! Start meditating and sleeping better! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Did you brush your teeth today? | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870145/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 13:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss how to turn the tables on niggas, Dating outside of your league, The importance of being a good kisser and oral hygiene and more!
https://emeraldgoddesshair.com/
Receive 50% off your first 6 wine bottle order by heading to brightcellars.com/pourminds for 50% off your first Bright Cellars box! Go to HelloFresh.com/pourminds10 and use code pourminds10 for 10 free meals, including free shipping!
Visit www.BetterHelp.com/POURMINDS for a month of discounted therapy!</description></item><item><title>She Get It From Her Mama | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870146/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 18:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall! This episode we discuss being gay for pay, mean girls, the 69 sex position and more!
betterhelp.com/pourminds for your counseling needs
You don&amp;rsquo;t have to search for coupons anymore! Visit www.joinhoney.com/pourminds and add it to chrome for discounts on almost ANYTHING! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Pootie Tang Returns | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870147/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 16:18:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall! This episode we discuss if successful men want successful women, being a content creator, getting ghosted after sex and more!
order your tushy and get 10% off plus free shipping! www.hellotushy.com/PourMinds
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Happy Valentines Day, But That Man Don't Like You | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870148/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, this is the valentines day episode! We discuss dating men that really like you, does time heal all, and the art of valentines day nudes!
betterhelp.com/pourminds for your counseling needs
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>You Fight My BDB, You Gotta Fight Me! | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870149/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 13:49:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall, this episode we discuss taking back someone after multiple tries, jumping in a fight with your man, morning sex vs night sex and more! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>That Thang Stretched Out, Hun | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870150/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 13:50:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y&amp;rsquo;all! This episode we discuss why dating is so hard, leaving the club early, stretched out vag and more!
Visit hellofresh.com/pourminds10 for 10 free meals!
betterhelp.com/PourMinds for discounted therapy
www.gooddayscents.com for all your candle needs! Use code POUR
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>R.B.N. (Ratchet B*tch Navy) | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870151/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 14:27:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall we back! This episode we discuss black business, having your friends back, first impressions, the importance of nipple play and more!
visit www.shopexul.com for cute clothes from a black owned business!
visit hellotushy.com/POURMINDS for a discount!
www.gooddayscents.com and use code POUR for 25% off candles!
pourminds.com for merch!
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Take That Rubber Off, Pooh | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870152/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall! This episode we discuss if you&amp;rsquo;re toxic, parental issues, when is it appropriate to stop using condoms and more!
Get discounted therapy sessions at www.betterhelp.com/pourminds
Get Merch www.pourminds.com
Get discounted meals www.greenchef.com/POURMINDS90 and get $90 off healthy meals! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>BDBs Get Curved Too! | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870153/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870153/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey Yall! This episode we discuss curving BDBs, men being overly sexual, finishing your food on a date, hotel sex and more!
Get your Pour Minds merch! www.pourminds.com
Get 25% off candles at www.gooddayscents.com use code POUR
Become a patreon member www.patreon.com/PourMinds
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>You Just A Temporary Placeholder, Hun | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870154/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 20:47:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall! This episode we discuss placeholders in dating, following your heart, sex on the first date and more!
Get 10 meals + free shipping with code POURMINDS10 from www.hellofresh.com
Get discounted therapy sessions at www.betterhelp.com/pourminds
Become a patreon member
www.patreon.com/PourMinds
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Merry Christmas! You can’t beat no more, but we cool right? | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870155/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2020 05:25:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall! This is the Christmas episode! We discuss being friends after sex, fate, why Lex finally enjoys high sex and more!
Get discounted therapy sessions at http://www.betterhelp.com/pourminds
Become a patreon member
http://www.patreon.com/PourMinds
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why Ebony, Why? Feat. Jessie Woo | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870156/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 15:18:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode features Jessie Woo and we discuss talking to your man about your past, getting in good with your mans parents, sex talk and more!
Follow Jessie @TheJessieWoo Visit www.tastevita.com (http://www.tastevita.com/) and use POURMINDS10 for a discount!
Get discounted therapy sessions at http://www.betterhelp.com/pourminds
Become a patreon member
http://www.patreon.com/PourMinds
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>You Got Daddy Issues, Hun | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870157/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 18:04:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870157/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall! This episode we discuss having daddy issues and growing up in a two parent household vs. one, supporting your friends business ventures, shower sex and more!
Visit www.tastevita.com and use POURMINDS10 for a discount!
Get discounted therapy sessions at www.betterhelp.com/pourminds
Become a patreon member
www.patreon.com/PourMinds
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Disturbing Tha Peace! | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870158/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870158/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dont forget the last day to purchase the Pour Minds Crewneck is 12/4/2020 so get your merch! www.pourminds.com
Hey y’all! This episode we discuss people disturbing your peace, being the bigger person, mixing business with pleasure and more!
Visit www.tastevita.com and use POURMINDS10 for a discount!
Get discounted therapy sessions at www.betterhelp.com/pourminds
Become a patreon member
www.patreon.com/PourMinds
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>You A Fun Girl, I Can't Take You Seriously | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870159/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 20:55:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey Yall we back! This episode we discuss being a fun girl ,letting that hurt go, crying during sex and more!
We got some new merch for yall! Only a limited amount of shirts available so get yours now! https://www.pourminds.com/merch Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Should I Get A House or My Body Done? | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870160/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870160/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all we back! This episode we talk about bonding over not liking a person, breaking bread with a man, if getting your body done is a good investment and good sex vs bad sex.
Get discounted therapy sessions at www.betterhelp.com/pourminds
Become a patreon member
www.patreon.com/PourMinds
Purchase Merch
teespring.com/stores/pour-minds SHOW LESS
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>When I Was A Young Warthog | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870161/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 07:11:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870161/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss asking for permission in relationships, COVID shaming, non sexual turn ons and more!
Become a patreon member
www.patreon.com/PourMinds
Purchase Merch
teespring.com/stores/pour-minds
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>You Not Ugly, You Just Broke | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870162/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 23:12:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870162/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall! This episode we discuss looking better as you get more money, cutting family off, poor pussy management and more!
Get discounted therapy sessions at www.betterhelp.com/pourminds
Become a patreon member
www.patreon.com/PourMinds
Purchase Merch
teespring.com/stores/pour-minds
SHOW LESS
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>That Dumbass Podcast | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870163/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 02:44:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all this episode we discuss unfollowing people you know over personal reasons, elitists, not accepting gifts, sex dreams and more! Your sex life just got an upgrade! Visit www.tastevitainc.com and use code POURMINDS10 to get your vitamins for your kitty at a discounted rate! Become a patreon member
www.patreon.com/PourMinds
Purchase Merch
teespring.com/stores/pour-minds
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Oh Violent Night | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870164/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 04:54:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870164/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all we’re back!! This episode we discuss dating broken men, your man hollering at your friend, the proper way to finger and more! Get your business to the next level! Contact - @the.Shopify.guy on Instagram Lex’s Hair - https://www.emeraldgoddesshair.com/
Get discounted therapy sessions at www.betterhelp.com/pourminds
Become a patreon member
www.patreon.com/PourMinds
Purchase Merch
teespring.com/stores/pour-minds
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>If that man don’t love you by now... | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870165/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 12:43:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss how long talking stages should be, taking the condom off, trolls on the internet, plan b pills and more!
Lex’s Hair - https://www.emeraldgoddesshair.com/
Become a patreon member
www.patreon.com/PourMinds
Purchase Merch
teespring.com/stores/pour-minds
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Would you like some p*ssy? | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870166/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 14:12:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870166/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all we’re back! This episode we discuss girl code, the saying “he know where home is”, sections in the club, positions for a small dick and more!
Lex’s Hair - https://www.emeraldgoddesshair.com/
Get discounted therapy sessions at www.betterhelp.com/pourminds
Become a patreon member
www.patreon.com/PourMinds
Purchase Merch
teespring.com/stores/pour-minds
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Amirite? Feat. Orlando and Diamond | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870167/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 04:14:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all this episode we discuss popping up on your ex, introducing threesomes, jealousy and more!
Follow Orlando @DearOrlandoRoye Find his podcast @hardorsoftpod
Follow Diamond @MuvaofGotti Her podcast is here - https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/girl-f-you/id1529018913
Get discounted therapy sessions at www.betterhelp.com/pourminds
Become a patreon member
www.patreon.com/PourMinds
Purchase Merch
teespring.com/stores/pour-minds
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Drippin’ Bigen | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870168/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 05:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss what makes a good man, should women say I love you first, men using bigen, sex enhancement pills and more!
Get discounted therapy sessions at www.betterhelp.com/pourminds
Become a patreon member
www.patreon.com/PourMinds
Purchase Merch
teespring.com/stores/pour-minds
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chocolate Chip Mint Hookah | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870169/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all this episode we discuss backtracking, arguing online, going to the bathroom in the club, using your imagination to masterbate and more!
Get discounted therapy sessions at www.betterhelp.com/pourminds
Become a patreon member
www.patreon.com/PourMinds
Purchase Merch
teespring.com/stores/pour-minds
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Your Honor, Ima Freak Bitch | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870170/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y&amp;rsquo;all! This week we discuss how dating is easier for men, guys just not being into you, men leading with money, double penetration and more!
Get discounted therapy sessions at www.betterhelp.com/pourminds
Become a patreon member
www.patreon.com/PourMinds
Purchase Merch
teespring.com/stores/pour-minds
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How You A Pick Me And Still Don't Get Picked? | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870171/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870171/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall! This episode we discuss the definition of a pick me, being a fun girl or a wife, rude business owners, sex for the first time with your boo and more! Get discounted therapy sessions at www.betterhelp.com/pourminds
Jewlery by https://rossiparedes.com/
Become a patreon member
www.patreon.com/PourMinds
Purchase Merch
teespring.com/stores/pour-minds
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>You a city girl, I didn't raise you like that! | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870172/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y&amp;rsquo;all! This episode we discuss being in a section with a BDB and other women, pulling the wrong friend, how our moms raised us, toys in the bedroom and more!
Get discounted therapy sessions at www.betterhelp.com/pourminds
Become a patreon member
www.patreon.com/PourMinds
Purchase Merch
teespring.com/stores/pour-minds
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>You Taste Like Battery Acid feat Skeete | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870173/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870173/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all this episode is featuring our good friend Skeete. We discuss paying for birthday parties, how long you should wait to get a gift, women having game, the taste of semen and more!
Follow Skeete on Twitter @CompareTheNames IG - @YaBoySkeete Become a patreon member
www.patreon.com/PourMinds
Purchase Merch
teespring.com/stores/pour-minds
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Pray for me, I got that WAP hun | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870174/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 13:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870174/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall! This episode we discuss WAP, the red flags in a relationship, getting a gift for your BDB, kegals and more!
Get discounted therapy sessions at www.betterhelp.com/pourminds
Become a patreon member
www.patreon.com/PourMinds
Purchase Merch
teespring.com/stores/pour-minds
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Put some clothes on, my man here! | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870175/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 08:23:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870175/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all this episode we discuss splitting vacations, wearing proper attire around your roommates man, marriage, soft dick and more! Become a patreon member https://www.patreon.com/PourMinds Purchase Merch https://teespring.com/stores/pour-minds Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What's Your Price? | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870176/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 04:07:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870176/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss internet bullying, confidence vs conceited, what’s your price to work with someone who is necessarily a good person, nipple play for men and more! Get discounted therapy sessions at www.betterhelp.com/pourminds
Become a patreon member https://www.patreon.com/PourMinds Purchase Merch https://teespring.com/stores/pour-minds Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>You can stop stalkin me, I don't want him anymore | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870177/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 04:54:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870177/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y&amp;rsquo;all! This episode we discuss crazy ex&amp;rsquo;s, being friends with your ex, men having too many baby mama&amp;rsquo;s, having a nice body, sex with skinny men and more! Become a patreon member https://www.patreon.com/PourMinds Purchase Merch https://teespring.com/stores/pour-minds Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>You got lambo truck money? | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870178/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 05:07:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870178/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This week we discuss being on time, buying expensive gifts, kitty maintenance and more! To get a month of discounted therapy sessions visit www.betterhelp.com/pourminds Email us @ askpourminds@gmail.com Become a patreon member https://www.patreon.com/PourMinds Purchase merch https://teespring.com/stores/pour-minds Drea’s Amazon Store https://www.amazon.com/shop/dreanicoleee Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We broke up, heal for what? | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870179/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 03:57:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall! We are back! This episode we discuss how much disrespect we take from people, accepting our flaws, moving on, and squirting! Item of the week is www.velvetnoirbc.com
Become a patron https://www.patreon.com/PourMinds Purchase Merch https://teespring.com/stores/pour-minds Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>True Life : I'm 30 and horny | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870180/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 03:56:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall! Drea isnt here this week so Im joined by my other bestie Diamond! This week we discuss getting dumped and moving on, what is downgrading, peeing and getting head after, and being 30 and horny! Subscribe to the patreon here Get merch here Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How She a Gold Digger If You Ain't Got No Gold? ft. Kodaq | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870181/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 04:01:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all this episode we discuss unwanted advances from men, calling women gold diggers, cheating and more! If you want your question answered on the show email us @ askpourminds@gmail.com Join our patreon for exclusive context https://www.patreon.com/PourMinds Follow Kodaq @ BigHomieKodaq Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>If The Rubber Don't Fit, You Must Acquit | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870182/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 04:31:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870182/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This week we discuss how women with money don’t deal with men, dating younger men, wearing condoms that don’t fit and we answered a few Q&amp;amp;A! If you want your question answered on the show email us @ askpourminds@gmail.com Join our patreon for exclusive context https://www.patreon.com/PourMinds Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A 9 - 5 Not My Type Hun | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870183/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 03:36:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870183/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall this episode we discuss dating a man with a 9-5 vs a business owner, celebrities taking over YouTube and only fans, moving on from friendships and accidentally letting a man beat.
Visit www.current.com and use code POURMINDS
Email us at askpourminds@gmail.com Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>White Silence Is Violence | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870184/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 04:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870184/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y&amp;rsquo;all! Due to everything going on we dedicated this episode to George Floyd, Breonnna Taylor, Ahmaud Arbrey, Trayvon Martin and all the other precious black lives that have been lost at the hands of racists. We talk about looting, protesting, and having white friends! We will be back next week with a regular episode, we just feel it was our duty to use our platform to speak on the social issues going on.</description></item><item><title>Is you flexible? | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870185/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 03:27:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870185/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall! This episode we discuss having a podcast with your friend, couple goals, your parents not liking your boo, being flexible and more!
If you want your question answered on the show email us askpourminds@gmail.com
Dreas Amazon Link - https://www.amazon.com/shop/dreanicoleee
Purchase merch https://teespring.com/stores/pour-minds
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Are you black enough? Feat. Weezy from Whoreible Decisions | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870186/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 02:57:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870186/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y&amp;rsquo;all this week we have special guest Weezy from Whoreible Decisions! This week we discuss having a podcast and being in a relationship, dating white men, being too black or not black enough and throuples.
Download the current app and use code POURMINDS - https://apps.apple.com/us/app/current-bank-for-modern-life/id1077
Dreas Amazon Link - https://www.amazon.com/shop/dreanicoleee
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Just Play Yo Part Miss Mamas | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870187/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 17:16:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870187/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This week we discuss party/BDB etiquette, playing your role, domestic violence, snitching and more!
Email us askpourminds@gmail.com to get your questions answered!
Purchase merch https://teespring.com/stores/pour-minds
Episode is brought to you by Www.betterhelp.com/pourminds
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 79 | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870188/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 16:39:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870188/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 79 by Drea and Lex Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Girl I aint ask you that, shut up | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870189/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 03:55:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870189/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y&amp;rsquo;all! This episode we discuss sexual assault, giving someone too much advice, pussy hygiene and more! If you want your question answered email us at askpourminds@gmail.com Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Let me press that booty button hun | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870190/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 10:25:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870190/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y&amp;rsquo;all this episode we discuss Georgia opening up even though Corona is still going crazy, moving on, being a hoe, fake bags and more! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 78 Why These N*ggas Hate Us So Much? | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870191/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 21:56:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870191/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y&amp;rsquo;all! This week we talked about ignorance being bliss, your man going on a trip with his baby mama, men on the internet hating on us, knowing or being cool with your ex&amp;rsquo;s new girl, sex appeal and how to ride dick. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Do bad b*tches fight? feat Kiki from Cocktales | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870192/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 04:31:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870192/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y&amp;rsquo;all this episode is featuring Kiki again! We discuss fighting over men, giving men wifey treatment, things to say during sex and more! Download the current app as the item of the week. Check out www.betterhelp.com/pourminds for a 10% discount! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Your Imitation Isn't Flattering Pooh | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870193/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 04:18:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870193/</guid><description>Podcast Description Your Imitation Isn&amp;rsquo;t Flattering Pooh by Drea and Lex Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Should You Shoot Your Shot If You Punching The Clock? ft Medinah from Cocktales | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870194/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 13:15:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870194/</guid><description>Podcast Description Should You Shoot Your Shot If You Punching The Clock? ft Medinah from Cocktales by Drea and Lex Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 74 - He Got D*ck for Sale ft Jazz | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870195/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 05:48:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870195/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y&amp;rsquo;all, this week we talk about the Coronavirus, disrespectful men, dating sex workers, broke me and anal sex/butt plugs. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 73 Running to the toilet like the tomb raider | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870196/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 04:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870196/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y&amp;rsquo;all! This week we talk about customer service and black people, not following people first on social media, rules to a fly out and the dumbest things we did for a dick appointment. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 72 B*tch you know me, Stop playing!! | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870197/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 05:01:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870197/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y&amp;rsquo;all!! This week we talk about people you&amp;rsquo;ve met before acting like they don&amp;rsquo;t know you, men spending money on you when they first meet you vs. making you wait, fake drunk gay women and period sex!
Lex&amp;rsquo;s items of the week:
@polishedextensions www.polishedextension.com
@_sharnise www.sharnise.com
www.wigsecured.com
Drea&amp;rsquo;s item of the week:
Vitafusion Prenatal Gummy Vitamins https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B003IP8BC8/ref=as_li_qf_asin_il_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;tag=andreahuelett-20&amp;amp;creative=9325&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;creativeASIN=B003IP8BC8&amp;amp;linkId=13b0abaf2ad739fec890578e355e44d9
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 71 - I’ll take your man | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870198/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 14:54:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870198/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey y’all! This episode we discuss taking someone’s man, women’s beef vs men’s beef, love is blind on Netflix, lifting your mans legs up and more! As always purchase your merch! https://teespring.com/stores/pour-minds
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 70 ft Kiki from Cocktales | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870199/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 05:07:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870199/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 70 ft Kiki from Cocktales by Drea and Lex Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 69 This Goes Out To All The Lovers | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870200/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870200/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode we talk about whether men should get gifts for Valentines day, should side chicks get a date, proposals on day and women proposing, Is that hoe shit in you? And what&amp;rsquo;s the definition of a freak? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sleep well babe, I need to go through your phone Feat. Diamond | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870201/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 13:25:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870201/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey yall! So Drea is in Miami this week so we have Diamond as a guest host today! We discuss men dating younger women, going through phones, having a little girl and more! Follow Diamond on twitter @MuvaOfGotti Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 67 Dear Kobe | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870202/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 05:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870202/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode we just reflect on the passing of Kobe Bryant and his daughter Gigi and also the importance of giving people their flowers while they can smell them and how short life is. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Greek life lame? Or nah? Ft. JCarp | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870203/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 08:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870203/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi yall, this week we talked about Greek life.. Being a business owner, titty fucking, etc. Special guest this week Jcarp! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Yeah I know you getting it but is you spending it? | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870204/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 05:00:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870204/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yeah I know you getting it but is you spending it? by Drea and Lex Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 64 He so fine he can ride my face | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870205/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 05:00:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870205/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Happy New Year Hoes | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870206/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 03:49:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870206/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 62 You put me in the friend zone, but I still want that puthy | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870207/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 16:40:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870207/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 61 Got You In A Cuckold | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870208/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 05:01:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870208/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>I think we should get back together, but I got herpes | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870209/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 01:21:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870209/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Stop cappin sis, tell him you didn't orgasm Feat Passport Cutty | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870210/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 11:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870210/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Epi 58 True Life : My potna died &amp; I want his girl | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870211/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 12:00:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870211/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>12 Years A Condom Feat. Mandii B of Whoreible Decisions | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870212/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 12:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870212/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sis Wait, Your Ex Husband Gay? ft. Carla Wilmaris | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870213/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 03:20:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870213/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>F*ck the baggage, where the bag at? | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870214/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 11:00:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870214/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Turn that Boosie on, I'm tryna make love | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870215/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 11:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870215/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hoe Life vs Wife Life | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870216/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 11:00:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870216/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Sky Is Blue &amp; This Puthy Is Pink | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870217/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 11:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870217/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>True Life - I rubbed my coochie till it broke | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870218/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 18:08:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870218/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode! Build-A-Man | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870219/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 16:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870219/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Your mom looks like Florida Evans | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870220/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 11:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870220/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Spit in my face pleathe | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870221/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 11:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870221/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 48 Swiggity swooty, I'm comin for dat booty | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870222/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 11:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870222/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is your puthy fire? Or you got that reggie? | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870223/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 11:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870223/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Shameless Minds ft. Tahoe of So Shameless | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870224/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 12:46:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870224/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Miami is not a vacation bro | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870225/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 11:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870225/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Your IG is an ad and I'm tryna hit | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870226/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 11:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870226/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 43 BBQ's and Abortions | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870227/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 11:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870227/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 42 Oh NOW you wanna use condoms? | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870228/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 11:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870228/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hi nice to meet you, can I pay your bills? feat. Karlous Miller | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870229/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 11:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870229/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode! We can only date if you plan on being my husband | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870230/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 04:08:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870230/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 40 - I need more white friends | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870231/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 11:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870231/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode: Pour Decisions w/ Mandii B of Whoreible Decisions | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870232/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 19:34:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870232/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 39 - You proud to be a hoe? | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870233/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 11:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870233/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 38 F*ck them kids Feat. Kiki from Cocktales | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870234/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 11:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870234/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 37 - You don't have to introduce us bae, we already f*cked | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870235/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 11:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870235/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 36 - Yeah you like me, but so does everybody else | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870236/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 11:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870236/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 35 - You hit a long time ago, please let it go | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870237/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 16:09:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870237/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 34 - That d**k was fire but I ain't mean what I said bro | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870238/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 11:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870238/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 33 - B*tches be cappin, it's me... I'm b*tches | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870239/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 11:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870239/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 32 - Are You A Stallion Or A Pony? Ft. KasFacts | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870240/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 11:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870240/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 31 - You don't respect your marriage, why should I? | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870241/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 13:15:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870241/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 30 - It's Time To Give That P*ssy Up Sis | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870242/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 00:34:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870242/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 29 - Your Nigga A Hoe Sis | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870243/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 23:39:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870243/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 28 - Run the red light | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870244/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 11:19:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870244/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 27 - Please don't make me f*ck you again man | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870245/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 13:03:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870245/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 26 - I accidentally gave your p*ssy away, my bad | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870246/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:38:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870246/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 25 - Lift your man legs up | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870247/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 00:38:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870247/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 24 - You need a therapist, not a girlfriend | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870248/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 01:05:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870248/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>BONUS EPISODE! Texas vs ATL women | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870249/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 00:40:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870249/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 23 - Sex with transgenders | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870250/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 23:50:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870250/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 22 - Don't order the steak sis, he ain't got enough money | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870251/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 01:44:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870251/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 21 - You're pregnant, why are you dating? | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870252/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 23:58:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870252/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 20 - Sex compatibility | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870253/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 00:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870253/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 19 - Can being fine save your life? | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870254/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 00:12:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870254/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode 2! Dating industry men! | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870255/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 02:39:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870255/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 18 - Is it a threesome or a train? | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870256/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 23:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870256/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 17 - Does oral count as a body? | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870257/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 01:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870257/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sneaky Hoe vs Honest Hoe.. Bonus episode! | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870258/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 01:17:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870258/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 16 - I'm sexing my new man and thinking about my old one | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870259/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 04:28:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870259/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 15 - Dating in ATL | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870260/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 04:08:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870260/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 14 - I flewed you out, I'm hittin.. PERIOD | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870261/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 00:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870261/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 13 - You're really pretty for a black girl | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870262/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 03:20:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870262/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 11 - Is a 9-5 a hustle? | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870263/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 04:51:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870263/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 10 - Blackfishing and Sex Stories | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870264/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 01:49:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870264/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 9 - THE CLOUT EPISODE! | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870265/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 05:39:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870265/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 8 - Sex Workers | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870266/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 02:43:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870266/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 7 - Dating Men With Girlfriends | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870267/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 02:46:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870267/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 6 - Lex's Belly Button | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870268/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 04:21:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870268/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 5 - Are Women Funny? | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870269/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 02:09:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870269/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 4 - Women cheat better | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870270/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 02:50:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870270/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 3 - Lick your man nipples queen | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870271/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 01:52:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870271/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 2 - You fine in Texas, but not in LA | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870272/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 02:25:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870272/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 1 - I want to pee on you | Pour Minds Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4327870273/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 02:39:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4327870273/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>