<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hard Feelings with Jennette McCurdy on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/hard-feelings-with-jennette-mccurdy/</link><description>Recent content in Hard Feelings with Jennette McCurdy on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 08:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/hard-feelings-with-jennette-mccurdy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>authentic connection | Hard Feelings with Jennette McCurdy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9502900011/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9502900011/</guid><description>Podcast Description i got lunch with a new friend and it was a deeply fulfilling experience. have i finally beaten social anxiety ? or was there just something specific and special about this connection ?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>burnout | Hard Feelings with Jennette McCurdy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9502900010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9502900010/</guid><description>Podcast Description i used to think work-life balance was for lazy people who couldn’t cut it. turns out, they were on to something. sorry i judged you, you balanced and healthy individuals.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>acne | Hard Feelings with Jennette McCurdy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9502900009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9502900009/</guid><description>Podcast Description once upon a time there was a girl named jennette who struggled with acne. she then became a woman named jennette who still struggled with acne. this was a confusing and frustrating journey for her. until she met a handsome prince named benzoyl peroxide. only, the story is a lot more complicated than that. listen to the episode to hear the full fairytale.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>abandonment issues | Hard Feelings with Jennette McCurdy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9502900008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9502900008/</guid><description>Podcast Description abandonment issues: we all know them, we all hate them. well, maybe we don’t all know them. but i certainly do. in a heightened way. even with, i’m embarrassed to admit, my assistant…
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>ending friendships | Hard Feelings with Jennette McCurdy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9502900007/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9502900007/</guid><description>Podcast Description i don’t think friendships are necessarily a forever thing. i think sometimes it’s beneficial to end them. in my twenties, i tried to stay in expired friendships where the dynamic was doing me a disservice. in this episode, i talk through two examples of when i ended “key” friendships in my life.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>egg freezing | Hard Feelings with Jennette McCurdy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9502900006/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9502900006/</guid><description>Podcast Description “doctor week” is a week i dread every year. it’s a week where i stuff as many doctor’s appointments in as possible because i dread them so much that i want to get them all over with as quickly as possible. this time, the appointments were a mammogram, ultrasound, pap smear, genetic testing, and an egg freezing consultation. i talk about what these appointments brought up for me emotionally, in the most i-have-zero-credentials-and-am-clearly-not-a-doctor sort of way.</description></item><item><title>loyalty | Hard Feelings with Jennette McCurdy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9502900001/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9502900001/</guid><description>Podcast Description in this episode i delve into loyalty and, more specifically, what an issue i think it presents in certain relationships. the key relationship that comes to mind for me is the one with my “dad”. to understand why i put “dad” in quotes, you’re gonna have to listen to the episode. mormon punch recipe: 1 part sprite, 1 part rainbow sherbet, 1 dollop of whipped cream, ice to taste.</description></item><item><title>pressure | Hard Feelings with Jennette McCurdy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9502900002/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 18:34:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9502900002/</guid><description>Podcast Description i used to be an “underdog”. it was a narrative that fueled me. nowadays i don’t have the external circumstances that support that narrative, so what do i do now ? no i’m actually asking. this isn’t rhetorical. i’m literally asking you, the reader, to tell me what to do now. you can send ideas to my managers, norm &amp;amp; derek, at mainstay entertainment.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>bad mood | Hard Feelings with Jennette McCurdy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9502900003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 07:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9502900003/</guid><description>Podcast Description i recorded this episode in new york city, the capital of stink. i was in a pissy mood. i kind of want to mention the hotel i stayed in so that, should you visit new york, you don’t have to subject yourself to those nasty, moldy steamers, but i can’t bring myself to. actually i can, it was called public hotel.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>shame | Hard Feelings with Jennette McCurdy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9502900004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9502900004/</guid><description>Podcast Description this past year has been crazy. with the success of my book, i thought the shame i felt about my past would finally wash away. surprise ! it didn’t. listen to the episode to hear more about it, i don’t want to spoil it all here. why are you still reading this ? please go listen now.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hard Feelings with Jennette McCurdy (Official Trailer) | Hard Feelings with Jennette McCurdy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9502900005/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 17:22:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9502900005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennette McCurdy doesn't give a f*ck. Except that she does. She gives many f*cks. So many, in fact, that she hurts constantly. "This is what it means to be human," Jennette said in an exclusive quote for this podcast description. She said it with her chin in her palm, taking herself seriously.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>