<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Science Vs on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/science-vs/</link><description>Recent content in Science Vs on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/science-vs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ayahuasca: WTF is up with DMT? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360001/</guid><description>Podcast Description DMT might be the weirdest drug in the already weird world of psychedelics. It’s the active ingredient in ayahuasca, but on its own, DMT can give you what’s nicknamed “the businessman’s trip” — a psychedelic journey that can be done and dusted inside 15 minutes. So what is this drug doing to our brains? And could it help people with depression? We catch up with Dr Chris Timmermann, Dr Graham Campbell, Michelle Baker Jones and Dr David Olson to find out.</description></item><item><title>Personality Tests: Who Are You Really? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Personality tests like the MBTI are all over the internet, the workplace, and dating apps — but some say it’s all a bunch of baloney. So are any of these tests legit? And what can science actually tell us about personality? We talk to psychologists Dr. Alexander Swan, Dr. Emorie Beck, and Dr. Ted Schwaba.
Find our transcript here: https://bit.ly/ScienceVsPersonalityTests
In this episode, we cover: (00:00) Chapter 1: Personality tests and their impact (05:49) Chapter 2: Personality and the MBTI (13:21) Chapter 3: Why personality ‘types’ flop (24:52) Chapter 4: The scientist’s personality test (30:05) Chapter 5: What personality can predict (33:24) Chapter 6: Can you change your personality?</description></item><item><title>Caffeine: How Much is Too Much? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Caffeine is a drug that tons of us take every day. But is that a bad thing? And if we get it in the form of energy drinks, is that super dangerous? We talk to Dr. Astrid Nehlig, Prof. Gregory Marcus, and Prof. Sachin Shah. Find our transcript here: https://bit.ly/ScienceVsCaffeineEnergyDrinks
In this episode, we cover: (00:00) Chapter 1: We love/hate caffeine (02:12) Chapter 2: Coffee and our guts (07:12) Chapter 3: Coffee and our brains (12:40) Chapter 4: Coffee and our zzzzzzs (17:42) Chapter 5: Coffee makes us go vroom vroom vroom!</description></item><item><title>MDMA: Can Ecstasy Cure Your Agony? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Molly, ecstasy, MDMA: whatever you call it, this drug is blowing up. Some say MDMA can be a legitimate medicine to treat conditions like PTSD. But others reckon it&amp;rsquo;s a dangerous drug that can fry your brain, and even kill you — from just one bad pill. Who&amp;rsquo;s right? That&amp;rsquo;s what we&amp;rsquo;re snorting up today. We talk to psychiatrist George Greer, public health researcher Prof. Joseph Palamar, former DEA special agent James Hunt, and neuroscientist Prof.</description></item><item><title>Pssst!! The Science of Gossip | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360005/</guid><description>Podcast Description We all know gossip can be bad — but some of us still can’t seem to get enough of it. So today we’re digging into the science of gossip to answer questions like: who really gossips? And why do we love it so much? We spill the tea with sociologist Dr. Stacy Torres and neuroscientist Professor Josep Marco-Pallarés.
Find our transcript here: https://bit.ly/ScienceVsGossip
In this episode, we cover: (00:00) Gossip has a bad rap (06:21) Who gossips?</description></item><item><title>When Your Eyes See Lies | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360006/</guid><description>Podcast Description A dead man with a bitten penis and perplexing DNA, a terrifying syndrome where everything around you appears in miniature, and the big lie we all believe about lemmings: Wendy and Joel tell three science stories about times when things were not what they seemed, recorded live at the Beaker Street Festival in Tasmania. Find our transcript here: https://bit.ly/ScienceVsLIVE Chapters: (00:00) Welcome to Science Vs LIVE! (02:08) The Case of the Missing Penis (17:55) Alice In Wonderland Syndrome (31:35) The Big Lemming Lie</description></item><item><title>Sleep: How Do We Get More? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Not sleeping enough turning you into a monster? In one of our most popular episodes, we bring you the cutting-edge science that helps us understand why. And we sort through the fads to find out, what really works to get more ZZZs. We speak with lab coordinator Pam DeYoung, sleep researcher Dr. Brady Riedner, and circadian scientist Prof. Russell Foster. Find our transcript here: https://bit.ly/ScienceVsSleep2023
In this episode, we cover: (00:00) Not sleeping sucks (03:00) What does lack of sleep do to us?</description></item><item><title>Seed Oils: Is Your Canola Oil Killing You? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360008/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’ve been told that foods like butter and bacon are bad for us — because they&amp;rsquo;re packed with saturated fats. And top dogs in nutrition say that a better option is vegetable oil, like canola oil. But there’s a trend popping off claiming that these top dogs are barking up the wrong tree. They say that butter is better and that those vegetable oils, aka “seed oils,” are incredibly dangerous.</description></item><item><title>UFOs: The Truth Is Right Here | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360009/</guid><description>Podcast Description A whistleblower claims that the U.S. government is covering up what it knows about aliens on Earth, and several military pilots recently testified to seeing strange objects in the sky. It kinda feels like the tide is turning on UFOs — even NASA is taking these sightings seriously. So what’s going on here? Have aliens visited? And will we ever find alien life somewhere … out there? We speak to astrophysicists Prof.</description></item><item><title>Andrew Huberman on Supplements, the Covid Lab Leak Theory and more | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrew Huberman is a skate punk turned neuroscientist, and he hosts one of the most popular podcasts in the U.S.: The Huberman Lab. Today, we talk to him about his unlikely path to becoming a scientist, his fascinating research into regrowing neurons, the Covid-19 lab leak theory, and some of the criticism he&amp;rsquo;s gotten for promoting certain supplements.
Coronavirus: Was It Made In a Lab? https://gimletmedia.com/shows/science-vs/dvheexn Find our transcript here: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>Self-Care: Can You Hack Your Mood? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can plunging into an ice bath make us feel happier? What about gratitude journaling? We’re digging into some of the quirkiest self-care hacks around the internet to find out what the science says — and whether you should add them to your routine. We talk to environmental physiologist Dr. Heather Massey, counseling psychologist Prof. Joel Wong, and social psychologist Dr. Juliana Schroeder. This episode does mention depression. Here are some crisis hotlines: United States: US National Suicide Prevention Lifeline 988 (Online chat available); US Crisis Text Line Text “GO” to 741741</description></item><item><title>Why Fossil Nerds Are Pissed Right Now | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360012/</guid><description>Podcast Description The smash hit Netflix documentary “Unknown: Cave of Bones” has kicked off an all-out science brawl. The film makes extraordinary claims about a strange ape-like creature that lived hundreds of thousands of years ago — claims that rewrite what it means to be human. But some scientists are pushing back, saying that at this point, these extraordinary claims aren’t backed up by extraordinary evidence. So, what’s going on? Is “Cave of Bones” a Cave of Lies?</description></item><item><title>Vaping: Is It Really That Bad? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360013/</guid><description>Podcast Description More and more people are puffing on vapes — but some governments are making moves to ban them. So how dangerous is vaping, really? And as we inhale that sweet cherry flavor into our lungs, could we also be changing our brains? To find out, we talk to tobacco researcher Dr. Michael Chaiton, inhalation toxicologist Professor Ilona Jaspers, and pharmacology researcher Melissa Herman.
Find our transcript here: https://bit.ly/ScienceVsVaping In this episode, we cover: (00:00) The fears around vaping (03:41) Could vaping make you sick?</description></item><item><title>Breathwork: A Bunch of Hot Air? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360014/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360014/</guid><description>Podcast Description The latest hot new trend is: breathing. Yeah, that’s right — there are claims that so-called breathwork can cure depression and supercharge your brain. Breathfluencers reckon that we&amp;rsquo;re breathing all wrong but that with the right kind of breathing, you could be living a happier, healthier life. So what&amp;rsquo;s the deal here? Are you really breathing badly? And if you learned the right way to breathe, could you become a better you?</description></item><item><title>We're Back! And Boldly Going Where We've Never Gone Before | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brand-new episodes will drop starting next week! Stay tuned for science deep dives on breathing and breathwork, seed oils (what SHOULD we cook with??), UFOs, self-care, energy drinks, personality tests and much much MUCH more.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Best Ever Episode of Science Vs | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360016/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week – our episode that you voted as our BEST wild card episode!! You’ll have to listen to find out what it is. Find our transcript here: https://bit.ly/SVBestEverEp
In this episode talk to Brie Smith, Micah Truman, Katrina Spade and Thomas Bass. This episode was produced by Blythe Terrell and Wendy Zukerman, with help from Meryl Horn, Michelle Dang, Rose Rimler, Courtney Gilbert and Disha Bhagat. Were edited by Blythe Terrell and Caitlin Kenney.</description></item><item><title>Orgasms: Your Favorite Sex Episode! | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here’s the episode you picked as our best sex and sexual health episode: Orgasms! There’s this idea that the female orgasm is a complicated riddle, but for a man with a penis, getting off is easy peasy. Is there really an orgasm gap? And if so — can science explain it? To learn more, we talk to neuroscientist Dr. Nan Wise, neuroscientist Dr. Nicole Prause and psychologist Dr. Candice Hargons.</description></item><item><title>Exercise: Your Favorite Wellness Episode! | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360018/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here’s the episode you voted as our best wellness episode: Exercise! Lots of people hit the gym to shed unwanted pounds, but they don’t always see results on the scale. We tackle the power of exercise and why you should bother. We speak with obesity expert Dr. Yoni Freedhoff, psychiatrist Dr. Gary Cooney, neuroscientist Prof. Wendy Suzuki and urologist Dr. Stacey Kenfield.
Find our transcript here: https://bit.ly/SVFavWellnessEp
This episode was produced by Wendy Zukerman, with help from Meryl Horn, Rose Rimler and Lexi Krupp.</description></item><item><title>Magic Mushrooms: Your Favorite Drugs Episode! | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here’s the episode you voted as our best drug episode: Magic Mushrooms! People are saying that shrooms cured their depression and anxiety. But is this for real? How could taking a trip on psychedelics fix your brain? Today, magic mushrooms ditch their tie dye for a lab coat as we go on a magical journey into the science. We talk to clinical psychologists Dr. Alan Davis and Dr. Albert Garcia-Romeu, and neuropsychologist Dr.</description></item><item><title>Behind the Scenes of ‘Oppenheimer’ | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 18:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we&amp;rsquo;re going behind the scenes of Christopher Nolan&amp;rsquo;s blockbuster film “Oppenheimer.” Professor David Saltzberg, one of the scientists who consulted on the movie (also “The Big Bang Theory”), joins us to chat about the science behind the movie. We also giggle about working with actors like Cillian Murphy to explain complicated science, and what the film got … maybe a little … wrong.
Find our transcript here: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>How Bats Break Science | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 15:06:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Many bats can live a bizarrely long time, and brush off viruses that kill people. How do they do it and what can we learn from them? Zoology Professor Emma Teeling and bat researcher and clinician Matae Ahn fly through the science. Find our transcript here: https://bit.ly/ScienceVsBats This episode was produced by Flora Lichtman with help from Wendy Zukerman, Joel Werner, R.E. Natowicz, and Michelle Dang, Rose Rimler. Editing by Jorge Just, Annette Heist and Blythe Terrell.</description></item><item><title>Sex Drive: The Dirrrrrrty Science | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tons of people struggle to get revved up about sex. It can mess with their relationships and how they feel about themselves. So enter the multimillion-dollar supplement industry with miracle solutions. Even Big Pharma has joined the battle for our libido, with drugs that claim to work wonders. But what if our ideas about sex drive are completely wrong? What if a pill (or testosterone injection) isn&amp;rsquo;t the answer?</description></item><item><title>Who Killed Affordable Housing? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 17:36:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Housing has gotten SO expensive — for many of us, buying something seems totally out of reach. And even renting a decent apartment is a struggle these days. Who, or what, is to blame for these high prices? We track down the culprit with urban planner Prof. Nicole Gurran and attorney Prof. Sara Bronin. Find our transcript here: https://bit.ly/ScienceVsAffordableHousing
In this episode, we cover: (00:00) The Crime (03:48) Suspect 1: Greedy developers (07:20) Suspect 2: AirBnB (14:20) Suspect 3: Zoning (24:00) The Twist!</description></item><item><title>Gluten: Should You Give It Up? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360024/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Going gluten-free is all the rage — we hear it’s the secret hack to being more healthy, even if you don’t have celiac disease. But is gluten actually bad for all of us? And what’s the deal with gluten sensitivity? We talk to immunologist Dr. Armin Alaedini, gastroenterologist Dr. Carolyn Newberry, and nutrition epidemiologist Dr. Natalie Riediger. Find our transcript here: https://bit.ly/ScienceVsGluten
In this episode, we cover: (00:00) Chapter 1: Why the internet hates gluten (02:17) Chapter 2: How gluten can hurt some people (05:21) Chapter 3: What’s up with gluten sensitivity (11:35) Chapter 4: Gluten and the placebo effect (15:27) Chapter 5: Other stuff besides gluten could be to blame (22:05) Chapter 6: Can a gluten-free diet help you lose weight?</description></item><item><title>AI: Is It Out Of Control? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360025/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Artificial Intelligence seems more human-like and capable than ever before — but how did it get so good so quickly? Today, we’re pulling back the curtain to find out exactly how AI works. And we&amp;rsquo;ll dig into one of the biggest problems that scientists are worried about here: The ability of AI to trick us. We talk to Dr. Sasha Luccioni and Professor Seth Lazar about the science.</description></item><item><title>Blue Balls: A Ball-Faced Lie? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360026/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360026/</guid><description>Podcast Description We join forces with Sarah Marshall from You’re Wrong About to dive into a question for the ages: Blue balls — are they real? And we’ve got some BIG blue balls news in this episode! The survey we did when it originally aired has been turned into a peer-reviewed paper led by scientists at Queen’s University! WE MADE SCIENCE! And if you took our survey, you helped!
So join us as we revisit this romp where we ask if blue balls are a ball-faced lie, something that men make up to pressure women to have sex with them.</description></item><item><title>The Dentist: Toss the Floss? Flush the Brush? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360027/</guid><description>Podcast Description The dentist tells us to floss, brush, avoid certain food and drinks &amp;hellip; but what actually matters when it comes to having healthy teeth? We&amp;rsquo;re drilling into the science on all of it. Plus, we go undercover to find out how many dentists are trying to upsell you when you go in for a checkup. We talk to epidemiologist and dentist Professor Philippe Hujoel, dentist Dr. Alisha Virmani, and economist Dr.</description></item><item><title>Skin Care: Is Anti-Aging a Scam? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360028/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360028/</guid><description>Podcast Description When it comes to keeping our skin looking younger, what works? Retinol, hyaluronic acid, vitamin C? This simple question has become confused by the billion-dollar skin-care industry, which floods us with scientific-sounding claims about the chemicals they say we should put on our face. We find out the real science on what you need for healthy skin with Dr Natalia Spierings, Dr Szu Wong and Kirsten Drysdale. Find our transcript here: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>Did We Predict the Pandemic? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360029/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Just two months before Covid-19 broke out, we made a fictional pandemic episode that was like “Contagion” but with citations. And we played it for Dr. Anthony Fauci. Today, we’re looking back at that episode and asking — how much of the pandemic did we predict? This episode has some unbleeped curse words. Find our transcript here: https://bit.ly/ScienceVsPandemic
In this episode, we cover: (00:00) Chapter One: Why we’re sharing this episode (03:42) Chapter Two: Meet Dr.</description></item><item><title>I’ll Be Dammed: Beavers Fighting Climate Change | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360030/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we give a dam about beavers. These busy rodents don’t just chill and go with the flow — it turns out their grabby paws are actually helping hands in the fight against climate change. We dive into how this works with ecologists Dr. Emily Fairfax and Dr. Ben Dittbrenner. Find our transcript here: https://bit.ly/ScienceVsBeavers
In this episode, we cover:
(00:00) Intro: How beavers “beaver away” (02:22) Chapter One: How beavers can help (06:18) Chapter Two: Can we move beavers for the better?</description></item><item><title>Ketamine: How Special is Special K? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360031/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360031/</guid><description>Podcast Description For years, ketamine has been thought of mostly as a horse tranquilizer — or a street drug that puts you in a scary-sounding K-hole. But now, we’re hearing reports that it could be almost a miracle medicine, treating stubborn depression and other mental illnesses. So how good is it, really? And could using a drug like this for depression actually be dangerous? We talk to researchers Dr. Rebecca Price, Prof.</description></item><item><title>Pit Bulls: Bad to the Bone? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360032/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pit bulls have a dark reputation. And some people say the science backs this up: that they bite people more often and do more damage when they chomp down. But other people say, no way — these dogs don’t deserve their bad rap. And if a dog has a problem, it’s really the owner’s fault. So who’s right? To find out, we talk to animal behavior expert Anna MacNeil, statistician Dr.</description></item><item><title>Superbugs: Apocalypse … Now? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360033/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Imagine getting an infection, going to the doctor, and having no little pill to make you better. Welcome to a world of SUPERBUGS. For years we&amp;rsquo;ve been hearing that our antibiotics aren&amp;rsquo;t working as well as they used to. But recently, it feels like things have really gotten out of hand — we’re told that these super scary antibiotic-resistant bugs are EVERYWHERE. In today’s episode, Wendy visits a freezer filled with superbugs to find out how worried we need to be, and what scientists are doing about this.</description></item><item><title>Hangovers: What Really Helps? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360034/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360034/</guid><description>Podcast Description What actually cures a hangover? Water? Crushed up Advil? Maybe a burger, fries and a Diet Coke? We wanted to know what the science says about how to bounce back when we’ve had a few too many. We talk to psychopharmacologist Andrew Scholey to find out.
Find our transcript here: https://bit.ly/ScienceVsHangovers In this episode, we cover: (00:00) Party on Bourbon Street (02:11) Does water cure a hangover? What about electrolytes?</description></item><item><title>Alcohol: Time to Put a Cork in It? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360035/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360035/</guid><description>Podcast Description For decades we’ve been yanked around over alcohol: one day it’s actually good for us, the next day it’s a killer. And recently there’ve been reports that even a little bit of booze is bad for you overall. We first looked into this back in 2019, and since then the research has evolved faster than a nanobrewery’s tap list. So today we’re diving back into the science to find out: is just a bit of alcohol dangerous?</description></item><item><title>Weight Loss Meds: Is Ozempic a Miracle Drug? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360036/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360036/</guid><description>Podcast Description People say drugs like Ozempic are helping them lose tons of weight. But are these drugs really all they’re cracked up to be? Or could this be yet another dangerous weight loss fad? We talk to endocrinologists Prof. Tricia Tan and Dr. Daniela Hurtado.
Note: In this episode we discuss weight and weight loss. Please take care when listening, and here are some resources:
U.S. helpline for the National Eating Disorders Association: 800-931-2237 SAMHSA&amp;rsquo;s National Helpline US: 800-662-HELP (4357) National Suicide Prevention Lifeline: 800-273-TALK (8255), or text the Crisis Text Line (text HELLO to 741741).</description></item><item><title>Nerds, Assemble! Science Vs Is Back | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360037/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360037/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’ve got the goods on weight loss drugs, ketamine, pit bulls, skincare and more! Come for the science, stay for the jokes. Or vice versa. In your feeds March 23. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Listen to Science Vs in Spanish! | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360038/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Science Vs has gone bilingual! La Ciencia Vs is the Spanish-language version of the show, and today we’re introducing the amazing hosts, Dr. Leonora Milán and Dr. Alejandra Ortíz, and sharing the Serial Killers episode: Asesinos Seriales. Find more episodes — like Veganos, Placebo, ASMR, Ejercicio — on the La Ciencia Vs feed on Spotify.
This episode was produced by Michelle Dang and Wendy Zukerman. Mix and sound design by Bobby Lord.</description></item><item><title>Adderall: What's It Doing to Your Brain? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360039/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 00:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360039/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s an Adderall shortage across the U.S., and it’s causing huge problems for people with ADHD. But on the flip side, we hear people saying that we shouldn’t be giving this drug out anyway. So we wanted to know: What is Adderall, exactly? What is it doing in people’s brains? And is there any truth to this idea that Adderall is like meth — could it be dangerous? We talk to psychiatrist Prof.</description></item><item><title>When Science and Superstitions Collide | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360040/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 00:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360040/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the THIRTEENTH season of the show! So we’re diving into stories about superstitions and luck. We’ll share the eerie tale of a 13-legged sea creature. We’ll talk about a hot new telescope that’s trying to look back 13 billion years ago to uncover the secrets of the universe. And we’ll talk about a squeaky superstition that involves a rat — as the tooth fairy. We speak to marine biologist Dr.</description></item><item><title>Hypnosis: Does It Really Work? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360041/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360041/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is hypnosis? Is it mind control? Are some people just faking? We’re revisiting this episode in which we explore the science of hypnosis and take Science Vs to the edge of consciousness. In the service of journalism, Wendy tries to get hypnotized at a comedy club and in a doctor’s office. We talk to comedian Jim Spinnato, Prof. Philip Muskin, Prof. Amanda Barnier, and Prof. Amir Raz. Find our transcript here: bit.</description></item><item><title>Deodorant: Is It Dangerous? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360042/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 20:23:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we’re diving into your armpits! We’ll find out why some of us are so freaking smelly. And then we’re asking: Are deodorants and antiperspirants safe, or should we ditch our sticks? We’ll talk to microbiologist Professor Gavin H Thomas, microbiologist Research Associate Professor Julie Horvath, epidemiologist Associate Professor Hanno Ulmer, and epidemiologist Professor Julia Knight. Here’s a link to our transcript: https://bit.ly/sciencevsdeodorant This episode was produced by Meryl Horn, with help from Michelle Dang, Disha Bhagat, Rose Rimler, Courtney Gilbert, and Wendy Zukerman.</description></item><item><title>The Male Pill: When Is It Coming? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360043/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360043/</guid><description>Podcast Description A male birth control pill has been this big tease for decades. And today, with the overturning of Roe v. Wade … a male pill might matter more than ever. So we’re grabbing science by the balls to find out – where is it? Will it ever get to the shelves? We talk to physicians Prof. John Amory and Dr. Brian Nguyen. Find our transcript here: https://bit.ly/3zq9dcq
This episode was produced by Michelle Dang, with help from Disha Bhagat, Rose Rimler and Meryl Horn.</description></item><item><title>The Mystery of the Man Who Died Twice | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360044/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360044/</guid><description>Podcast Description A dead body turns up with a stolen identity. We tell the story of how a grandmother tracked down the truth — and helped create a whole new and controversial world of crime fighting. To tell this story, we talk to U.S. Marshal Peter Elliott, Dr. Margaret Press, and Phil Nichols. [REBROADCAST]
CN: This episode discusses suicide. If you or someone you know is experiencing a mental health crisis, in the U.</description></item><item><title>Mass Shootings: How Do We Stop Them? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360045/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 22:48:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Buffalo. Uvalde. Highland Park. These mass shootings keep happening. One side says the problem is the guns, and the other side says the problem is the people. Who’s right? And what policies might actually work to stop mass shootings? We talk to NSSF spokesperson Mark Oliva, gun control researcher Prof. Mark Gius, criminologist Dr. Jillian Peterson, and epidemiologist Dr. Veronica Pear. CN: This episode discusses suicide. If you or someone you know is experiencing a mental health crisis, in the U.</description></item><item><title>Should We Compost Human Bodies? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360046/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360046/</guid><description>Podcast Description What&amp;rsquo;s the greenest way to die? Some nerds are saying that our bodies should go the way of our veggie scraps — and become compost. But will people get on board with spreading Grandpa in the garden? To find out, we talk to Brie Smith, Micah Truman, Katrina Spade and Thomas Bass.
Link to our transcript: https://bit.ly/svhumancomposting This episode was produced by Blythe Terrell and Wendy Zukerman, with help from Meryl Horn, Michelle Dang, Rose Rimler, Courtney Gilbert and Disha Bhagat.</description></item><item><title>The Fight to Fix a Racist Medical Gadget | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360047/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 17:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360047/</guid><description>Podcast Description The EEG is an incredibly important medical tool — and it’s been failing Black patients for decades. So today we’ll hear from two young, Black scientists who teamed up with hairdressers to do something about it. We speak to neurologist Dr. Jessie Baity, engineer Arnelle Etienne, biomedical scientist Lietsel Jones, and hairstylist Nina Woodley. Link to our transcript: https://bit.ly/sciencevsEEG This episode was produced by Taylor White, Meryl Horn and Wendy Zukerman, with help from Rose Rimler, Michelle Dang, Ekedi Fausther-Keeys, Courtney Gilbert, and Disha Bhagat.</description></item><item><title>Vegans: Are They Right? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360048/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do vegans have a right to be so smug? We’re finding out whether it really is better for the environment, and our bodies, to go vegan. We speak to environmental researcher Joseph Poore, historian Prof. Connie Hilliard, anthropologist Prof. Katharine Milton, and nutrition researcher Prof. Roman Pawlak.
A version of this episode originally ran in 2018; today’s episode contains updated science.
Check out the transcript here: https://bit.ly/vegansupdated The episode was produced by Rose Rimler and Wendy Zukerman, along with Meryl Horn, Odelia Rubin and Kaitlyn Sawrey.</description></item><item><title>Hydration: Are You Drinking Enough Water? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360049/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Celebs and wellness blogs treat water like a magic elixir that will make us the most attractive and healthiest version of ourselves. But do these claims hold water? And how much do we really need to be drinking to stay healthy? We speak to Professor Hollie Raynor, Professor Stavros Kavouras and Dr. Tamara Hew-Butler to find out.
Find our transcript here: https://bit.ly/3AEtH0W
This episode was produced by Wendy Zukerman, with help from Nick DelRose, Michelle Dang, Meryl Horn, Courtney Gilbert, Rose Rimler and Disha Bhagat.</description></item><item><title>We're Back for Season THIRTEEN | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360050/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 18:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360050/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s tons of misinformation, fads and strong opinions floating around out there — but then there’s SCIENCE. Season 13 starts on September 8! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Fauci on Monkeypox: What Went Wrong | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360051/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 18:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360051/</guid><description>Podcast Description We called up Dr. Anthony Fauci to talk about monkeypox. We wanted to know — what’s the deal with the slow response here? And why haven’t we gotten this virus under control?
Here’s a link to our transcript: https://bit.ly/3BB7WBi This episode was produced by Wendy Zukerman, Michelle Dang, Meryl Horn, Courtney Gilbert, Rose Rimler, Nick DelRose and Disha Bhagat. We’re edited by Blythe Terrell. Mix and sound design by Sam Bair.</description></item><item><title>Monkeypox: What's Going On? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360052/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 20:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Monkeypox has been spreading around the world. So … what exactly is this disease? How worried should we be, and how can people stay safe? We talk to Dr. Carlton Thomas, Professor Chloe Orkin and Professor Yan Xiang.
Check out our transcript (with 147 citations!): https://bit.ly/sciencevsmonkeypox And if you are looking for another great podcast on this, check out A Bumpy Ride. It’s by Leo Herrera, and it’s really beautiful.</description></item><item><title>Abortion: The Science and the Supreme Court | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360053/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 22:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last week, the U.S. Supreme Court overturned Roe v. Wade. And in their opinion, we found a lot of scientific-sounding statements. So we wanted to find out whether these statements are true. We’ll tell you what actually happens in an abortion, whether a fetus can feel pain, and what the risks are for a pregnant person. We visit an abortion clinic in Texas and talk to Dr. Amita Murthy, Dr.</description></item><item><title>Nightmare on Science Street | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360054/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 23:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we’re sharing a collection of spooky science stories. You’ll hear about a nightmare in the ocean, a nightmare on land, and even a nightmare … IN YOUR MIND. We talk to scientists including marine biologist, Dr. Olga Shpak and malacologist Jaynee Kim.
Find our transcript here: https://bit.ly/3O4Ag22 See the video Olga’s team shot of killer whales attacking a bowhead here: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OskmkWV0Ypk This episode was produced by Wendy Zukerman, Michelle Dang, Meryl Horn, Ilya Kolmanovsky, and Rose Rimler.</description></item><item><title>Placebo: Can the Mind Cure You? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360055/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 20:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360055/</guid><description>Podcast Description [REBROADCAST] Could fake medicine actually take away your pain or treat a disease? We dig into the science of placebos to find out more about the power of the mind to heal. We speak to medical researcher Prof. Ted Kaptchuk, neuroscientist Prof. Fabrizio Benedetti and medical psychologist Prof. Manfred Schedlowski. Check out the full transcript here: https://bit.ly/3xaPKM3 This episode was produced by Wendy Zukerman, with help from Rose Rimler, Meryl Horn, Kaitlyn Sawrey and Michelle Dang.</description></item><item><title>A Mystery in the Air | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360056/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 22:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360056/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a little girl, Ella Kissi-Debrah, suddenly got sick and landed in the hospital, doctors were stumped. In this episode, her mom, Rosamund, takes on the fight to find out what exactly happened to Ella. And the answer has BIG implications — for us all. We’ll hear from Rosamund Adoo-Kissi-Debrah and Professor Stephen Holgate.
Find our transcript here: https://bit.ly/3z17Gdv
This episode was produced by Ekedi Fausther-Keeys with help from Rose Rimler, Wendy Zukerman, Michelle Dang, Meryl Horn, and Courtney Gilbert.</description></item><item><title>ASMR: How Whispering Hijacks the Brain | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360057/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 23:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360057/</guid><description>Podcast Description ASMR is huge. People say these videos of someone whispering or making soft sounds can make them feel all tingly inside, and even help them feel calm and less anxious. So, what’s going on here? We talk to scientists who have looked into what’s happening in our bodies and brains when we experience an “autonomous sensory meridian response.” You’ll hear from Dr. Giulia Poerio, Dr. Bryson Lochte and Professor Craig Richard — as well as ASMR artist Mike Bryant - aka The Velvet Whisperer.</description></item><item><title>Serial Killers: The Mind of a Murderer | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360058/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 19:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360058/</guid><description>Podcast Description [REBROADCAST] What makes a serial killer? What drives them to kill again and again? To find out the truth about this ghastly lot, we talked to forensic psychologist Prof. Eric Hickey, criminologist Ass. Prof. Wayne Petherick, and psychiatrist Prof. Gwen Adshead.
Find our transcript here: https://bit.ly/39HcSsv
Note: in this episode we discuss homicide, and sexual violence. Please take care when listening to the show, and here are some resources:</description></item><item><title>Processed Food: A Load of Baloney? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360059/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 22:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360059/</guid><description>Podcast Description We hear over and over that processed food is bad for us. But is there actually something funky going on here — or is it just junk food? We dig into what these foods are doing to our bodies. You’ll hear from Dr. Kevin Hall, Prof. Carlos Monteiro, Dr. Cathrina Edwards, and Dr. Sheela Sathyanarayana. Find our transcript here: https://bit.ly/3xYhHHZ This episode was produced by Rose Rimler with help from Michelle Dang, Meryl Horn, Ekedi Fausther-Keeys, and Rasha Aridi.</description></item><item><title>Ivermectin: The Story of a Wonder Drug | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360060/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 23:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we’re digging into the weird and wooly world of ivermectin. When promising papers came out early in the pandemic, a lot of scientists got excited about the drug, but then … cracks started to show. We went down the rabbit hole and realized that there&amp;rsquo;s way more to this story than the headlines. We’ll hear from Dr. Pierre Kory, as well as Jack Lawrence, Dr. Kyle Sheldrick, and Professor Roy Gulick.</description></item><item><title>Spotify and Misinformation: An Update! | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360061/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 20:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today on the show an update about our push to get Spotify to do more to stop misinformation spreading on the platform.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Abortion Underground | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360062/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 18:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360062/</guid><description>Podcast Description REBROADCAST. The Supreme Court is set to rule on a major abortion case this year, and the court could decide to overturn Roe v. Wade. Already, places like Oklahoma, Texas and Idaho are rolling out major abortion restrictions. So today, we’re going back to the pre-Roe years, when one group of women got fed up and decided to take their health into their own hands. We talk to “self-helpers” Carol Downer and Francie Hornstein, who led a movement for safe abortions and education for women by women.</description></item><item><title>Ukrainian War: Fighting Russia's Propaganda Machine | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360063/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Russia attacked Ukraine more than a month ago — and the war has raged ever since. From the beginning, Russia has been pushing out propaganda and disinformation about what’s actually going on. So this week, we’re sharing parts of a podcast from independent journalists Pyotr Ruzavin and Natalka Gumenyuk, who have been covering what’s happening in Ukraine and what the people who live there are experiencing. Their show is called Fuck War.</description></item><item><title>Ancient Aliens: Who Really Built the Pyramids? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360064/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 17:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360064/</guid><description>Podcast Description [REBROADCAST] Is it possible that the pyramids were built with a helping hand &amp;hellip; from aliens? If not, how did the ancient Egyptians build them without modern technology? To get to the bottom of this, we speak to author Erich von Däniken, paleoanthropologist Dr. Shelby Putt, Egyptologist Dr. Mark Lehner, and archaeologist Prof. David S. Anderson.
Check out the transcript here: https://bit.ly/3LbPnoJ
This episode was produced by Rose Rimler with help from Wendy Zukerman, along with Meryl Horn, Kaitlyn Sawrey, Michelle Dang and Odelia Rubin.</description></item><item><title>Trans Kids: The Misinformation Battle | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360065/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 01:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360065/</guid><description>Podcast Description U.S. politicians are trying to keep trans kids from getting the medical care they need to transition — and states are banning them from playing on the sports teams that match their gender. So we’re looking at the science here, and asking: are the medical treatments for trans kids dangerous? And do trans folks have an advantage when it comes to sports? We talk to Florence Ashley, Dr. Jack Turban, and Joanna Harper to find out.</description></item><item><title>Here’s What’s Coming Up! | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360066/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 23:18:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360066/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s tons of misinformation, fads and strong opinions floating around out there — but then there’s SCIENCE. Find it here! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Misinformation: What Should Our Tech Overlords Do? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360067/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 02:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360067/</guid><description>Podcast Description After Joe Rogan was accused of spreading Covid-19 vaccine misinformation on his podcast, Spotify landed in the hot seat. People (including us!) wanted to know what the platform was doing to stop it. In this episode, we look into how tech platforms are fighting misinformation — and find out what actually works. To find out we speak to Professor David Rand, Professor Hany Farid, Laura Edelson and evelyn duoek.</description></item><item><title>Joe Rogan: The Malone Interview | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360068/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Recently, Joe Rogan aired an interview that scientists are up in arms about — with Dr. Robert Malone. Malone talked smack about the Covid-19 vaccines, talking about scary side effects and implying that the vaccines are a risk to our fertility. Enter Science Vs. We fact check the bejesus out of it and zoom out to talk about the bigger picture: what to watch for if you’re worried about getting sucked in by misinformation online.</description></item><item><title>The Moon: Why Are We Really Going Back? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360069/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 02:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360069/</guid><description>Podcast Description The moon race is back! Countries — and billionaires — are lining up to take a crack at returning to the moon. But why are we really going? Some say this is a lunar gold rush, that countries want to mine the moon for resources. Others are saying the real reason to go to the moon today is that it’ll help us get to Mars. To find out, we talk to engineer Dr.</description></item><item><title>Fauci on How This Ends | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360070/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 00:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Anthony Fauci sits down with us to talk about omicron, how this pandemic actually ends — and how he’s fighting back against the haters. Find our transcript here: https://bit.ly/3Djq9jX
Science Vs is produced by Wendy Zukerman, Rose Rimler, Meryl Horn, Michelle Dang, and Ekedi Fausther-Keeys. We’re edited by Blythe Terrell. Mix and sound design by Daniel Ramirez. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Omicron: Do You Need to Freak Out? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360071/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 03:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welp, the pandemic has served up yet another poop sandwich, and it’s called omicron. This variant is popping up in dozens of countries across the world, and scientists are racing to get a handle on it. So how bad could this be? And could it sneak past our vaccines? To find out, we talk to virologist and immunologist Professor Ann Sheehy, Prof. Art Wallace, epidemiologist Dr. Barbara Cohn, immunologist Dr.</description></item><item><title>Presenting Gastropod: How Chilis Conquered the World | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360072/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360072/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’ve got a spicy treat for you: a show called Gastropod. Hosts Nicola Twilley and Cynthia Graber dig into the world of food and serve up a forkful of science, plus a dash of history. In this episode: chili peppers! Why do we love spicy things when they set our mouths on fire? Plus, where did chilis come from — and how did they take over the world?</description></item><item><title>Jurassic Park: Hold On to Your Butts | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360073/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 23:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Could our dreams for a real Jurassic Park come true? Headlines say scientists are closer than ever to resurrecting prehistoric animals like the woolly mammoth. But is this for real!? Can we really bring back long-gone animals from the dead … maybe even the dinosaurs? We speak to paleontologists Professor Jack Horner and Professor Mary Schweitzer, and biologists Professor Beth Shapiro and Robyn Bortner. Here’s a link to our transcript: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>Killer Asteroids: NASA Strikes Back | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360074/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360074/</guid><description>Podcast Description [REBROADCAST] Asteroids! In just two weeks, NASA plans to launch a first-of-its-kind mission to try to move an asteroid off its path. If it works, this could be a huge breakthrough in protecting us from runaway space rocks. So we’ve updated this episode from a few years ago, where we talked about how serious this asteroid threat is — and some of the other ways we might fight back.</description></item><item><title>Monkey Say What? LEOPARD!! | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360075/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Science isn’t always dressed up in fancy lab coats and goggles — sometimes it goes undercover! In this episode, we go behind the scenes in the Congolese rainforest to show you just how down and dirty scientists are willing to get to answer their questions. We find out how the putty-nosed monkey might be chattier than we thought — and what all that monkey gab could mean. Researcher Frederic Gnepa Mehon gives us the scoop.</description></item><item><title>Chronic Pain: Can Our Brains Fix It? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360076/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 23:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360076/</guid><description>Podcast Description People with chronic pain often struggle with it for years while doctors scour their bodies for the cause. But are we looking in the wrong spot? For some of us, could an answer — and the solution — actually be in our brains? To find out, we talked with Professor Lorimer Moseley, Dr. Javeria Hashmi, and psychologist Alan Gordon.
Here’s a link to our transcript: https://bit.ly/3jHBvYb
To learn more about Alan’s therapy, check out his new book, “The Way Out.</description></item><item><title>The Legendary Condom Queen | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360077/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 21:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Joycelyn Elders is a total badass. She grew up in poverty in rural Arkansas, but in 1993 she rose to become the surgeon general of the United States — appointed by President Bill Clinton. Joycelyn wanted to put sex education front and center, to help teenage girls avoid getting pregnant. Decades ago, she was saying things that could be ripped out of the headlines today. But America wasn’t ready for this, and after just over a year, she was fired.</description></item><item><title>Burnout: Can We Fix Work? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360078/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 23:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Work can really suck. And for lots of us, burnout has been feeling especially terrible. This week, we dive into how burnout messes with our brains and bodies, and we find out whether working from home is making things worse. Plus: Could the four-day workweek be the key to fixing our jobs? We speak to neuroscientist Professor Wendy Suzuki, economist Professor Nick Bloom, and Dr. Alex Pang.
Here’s a link to our transcript: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>Blue Balls: You're Wrong About Them | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360079/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 16:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360079/</guid><description>Podcast Description We join forces with Sarah Marshall from You’re Wrong About to dive into a question for the ages: Blue balls — are they real? We’ve heard that for people with balls, if you get aroused but don’t ejaculate, it can be incredibly painful. But is that true? Or is it a ball-faced lie, something that men make up to pressure women to have sex with them? Join us for a ball-busting episode that puts blue balls to the ultimate test-es, reaching a gripping conclusion as we ask: If blue balls is in fact real — can people with vaginas get it too?</description></item><item><title>True Love: Is Monogamy Unnatural? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360080/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 19:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360080/</guid><description>Podcast Description [REBROADCAST] Are humans built for monogamy? Or is the idea of having one partner forever just a myth forced on us by tired old love songs? We revisit the science of love in one of our favorite episodes, hearing from Dr. Helen Fisher, Professor Larry Young and Dr. Dieter Lukas.
Find the transcript here: https://bit.ly/3meWcuN This episode was produced by Wendy Zukerman with Heather Rogers, Kaitlyn Sawrey, Ben Kuebrich, Shruti Ravindran and Rose Reid.</description></item><item><title>The Secret World of Plants | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360081/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 18:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Plants aren’t just sitting around looking cute; they’re doing all sorts of stuff, like defending themselves, and even warning other plants about danger. Today, we’re talking all about the weird and wily world of plants with Professor Beronda Montgomery from Michigan State University. She has a new book out called “Lessons From Plants.” Transcript: https://bit.ly/3kQ2bHg This episode was produced by Taylor White, with help from Wendy Zukerman, Nick DelRose, Rose Rimler, Meryl Horn and Michelle Dang.</description></item><item><title>Childbirth: Are Doctors Messing It Up? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360082/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 15:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Childbirth seems to be getting more and more medicalized, with C-sections and other interventions out the wazoo. But childbirth isn’t a disease! So is all this medical meddling really necessary, or are doctors too trigger-happy with the scalpel? To find out, we talked to obstetrician and gynecologist Dr. Sarah Osmundson, doula Shala Konomi, clinical scientist Dr. Sarah Stock, and obstetrician and gynecologist Dr. Crystal Berry-Roberts.
Here’s a link to our transcript: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>Weight: Is Fat Unhealthy? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360083/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 23:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360083/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re hearing nonstop chatter about the “quarantine 15.” But should we really care if we put on weight? Is fat bad for us? We talk to Prof. Henry Blackburn, Assoc. Prof. Laura den Hartigh, and Assoc. Prof. A. Janet Tomiyama. Here’s a link to our transcript: https://bit.ly/2XxewHo
Note: In this episode we discuss weight, weight loss, and weight stigma. Please take care when listening, and here are some resources:</description></item><item><title>Therapy: Does It Work? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360084/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 14:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our mental health has taken a turn for the worse the past couple of years. We keep hearing that therapy can help, but it can be a big investment of time and money. So is it worth it? How often does therapy really help people? To find out, we talked to Jacquelyn Revere and psychologists Dr. Jonathan Shedler, Professor Bunmi Olatunji and Dr. Nancy McWilliams.
Here’s a link to our transcript: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>Let’s Do Science Again!! | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360085/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 18:08:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360085/</guid><description>Podcast Description There are a lot of fads, blogs and strong opinions, but then there’s SCIENCE. Season 11 starts Sept. 9! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Presenting Not Past It: The Vax That Got Axed | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360086/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we’re sharing an episode of a show we love: Not Past It. ​​Did you know there was almost an AIDS vaccine? On June 3, 1998, AIDSVAX VAX004 reached the final stage of trials before widespread approval. Not Past It host Simone Polanen gets the facts on the vax and why it never made it to the masses. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Delta Variant: How Bad Is It? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360087/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 21:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360087/</guid><description>Podcast Description This delta variant of the coronavirus seems to really be screwing us over. Cases are spiking in the U.S., and we keep hearing about vaccinated people getting Covid. So how worried should we be? And what is it about delta that makes it so sneaky? We talk to public health supervisor Katarina Grande and virologist and immunologist Professor Ann Sheehy to find out.
Here’s a link to our transcript: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>Pet Food: How Fancy Should They Feast? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360088/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360088/</guid><description>Podcast Description There are soooo many options for what to feed your dog or cat, from the cheap stuff at the supermarket to fresh food delivered straight to your door. So what’s the best option? And just how fancy do we need to get to be good pet parents? We ask Prof. Maja Louise Arendt, Dr. Paul Pion and Prof. Marion Nestle. UPDATE 6/1/21: We adjusted the episode to better reflect Paul&amp;rsquo;s opinion about the link between grain-free food, taurine, and heart problems in dogs.</description></item><item><title>The G Spot: Come Again? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360089/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360089/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re heading into a big summer, with more places and — ahem — people opening up. So we’re revisiting one of our favorite episodes about feeling good. Maybe you’ve heard about this magic button in the vagina that can cause amazing orgasms. What’s going on with it? Join us on a hunt for the elusive G spot. Our guides: Prof. Beverly Whipple, who introduced America to the G spot in the 1980s, and Prof.</description></item><item><title>Back From the Dead | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360090/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 01:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we&amp;rsquo;re telling tales that push life to the ultimate limit. We&amp;rsquo;re bringing things back from the dead, diving into the mysteries of immortality and asking just how much can the human body take? We talk to Rohan Schoeman, Dr. Eduard Argudo, Audrey Mash, Prof. Ferdinando Boero, Prof. Shin Kubota, Dr. Moiya McTier, and Prof. David Howard.
UPDATE 5/17/21: An earlier version of this episode said that Nesyamun was scanned using MRI.</description></item><item><title>A Seedy, Late-Night Adventure | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360091/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, under cover of darkness, we&amp;rsquo;re hunting buried treasure. This is a wild romp through one of the oldest science experiments in the world. And at first, everything was going to plan. Scientists had a secret map, headlamps, shovels … but then — out of nowhere — something got in the way. We go on this journey with plant biologists Professor Frank Telewski, Dr. Marjorie Weber, and Dr. David Lowry.</description></item><item><title>Screens: Are They Ruining Our Brains and Mental Health and Eyes and | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360092/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 22:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tons of us are spending waaaayyy more time using screens these days — and it’s freaking us out. We’ve got all kinds of worries. Like, is all this screen time rotting kids’ brains? Is social media destroying our mental health? And then there’s our eyes. Our eyes!! Are all these screens ruining them too?! To find out, we speak to psychologist Dr. Brenna Hassinger-Das, communication studies researcher Dr. Natalie Pennington and optical physicist Dr.</description></item><item><title>Havana Syndrome: Did a Secret Weapon Fry Diplomats' Brains? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360093/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Back in 2016, U.S. Embassy workers in Cuba were struck by a mysterious noise, followed by symptoms like headaches, dizziness and memory problems. This sent the U.S. scrambling to try to find the culprit. Could it have been an ear-piercing sonic weapon? Or something even sneakier — a device that could beam microwaves into your brain?? We speak to journalist Tim Golden, Prof. Douglas Smith, Prof. Fernando Montealegre-Zapata, Dr.</description></item><item><title>How Science Created Morons | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360094/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360094/</guid><description>Podcast Description REBROADCAST: This episode looks at how one of the worst ideas in science got a big push from a bad study… and intellectuals of the day lapped it up. We speak to science writer Carl Zimmer and Prof. J. David Smith, whose research helped get to the bottom of this messed-up story. Check out the full transcript here: https://bit.ly/3sZ3m8P This episode was produced by Kaitlyn Sawrey, Wendy Zukerman, and Romilla Karnick with help from Meryl Horn, Rose Rimler, Shruti Ravindran and Nick DelRose.</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus: How Scary Are the Variants? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360095/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 01:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360095/</guid><description>Podcast Description UPDATE 4/13/21: Since this episode published, there has been some evidence linking the Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson coronavirus vaccine to rare blood clots. As of April 13, there were six cases in the U.S. out of more than 6.8 million doses, and one person had died. The CDC and FDA have recommended pausing the vaccine while they learn more.
Details are here: https://www.cdc.gov/media/releases/2021/s0413-JJ-vaccine.html Just as coronavirus vaccinations are ramping up, a bunch of new variants are here, threatening to muck everything up.</description></item><item><title>Snake Bite Cures: Weasels, Pigeons, Pee | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360096/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 20:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Venomous snakes entranced medieval Europe. And although bites were rare, this didn’t stop 14th century doctors from using everything but the kitchen sink to make snake bite treatments. We’re talking weasels, birds — even the pee of a young man. So was it all for snakes and giggles? Or is there something we’re missing in our treatments today? We speak to medieval animal expert Dr. Kathleen Walker-Meikle. Check out the transcript here: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>SNAKES!!! | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360097/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 23:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Snake venom is a wily beast. It&amp;rsquo;s packed with hundreds of toxins that can attack our blood vessels, muscles and nerves. That&amp;rsquo;s why snake bites kill some 100,000 people each year. On today&amp;rsquo;s show — dangerous snake bites and the bizarre way we make the only thing that can save you from them: antivenom. (Spoiler alert: it takes snake milkers and stables filled with horses.) We&amp;rsquo;ll also look at the groundbreaking research that could eventually revolutionise all this.</description></item><item><title>UFOs: Through the Wormhole Again | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360098/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 18:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360098/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2017, a weird-looking space object called ʻOumuamua whipped past our sun. Now a Harvard scientist is suggesting it miiiight be an alien probe! So we’re revisiting this episode from a few years ago, where we ask: could aliens actually exist? Is there any chance they’ve visited Earth already? We talked to astronomers Dr. Jill Tarter, Dr. Seth Shostak, investigative journalist David Clarke, and physicist Prof. Jim Al Khalili.</description></item><item><title>Brood X: A Drug-fueled Cicada Orgy | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360099/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 03:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Parts of the U.S. are about to see a surge of cicadas — masses of flying bugs, popping up all over the place. After 17 years underground, a crap ton of Brood X cicadas will emerge for a giant chorusing orgy — and it’s all for sex and drugs. So what does this cicada storm mean for us? Should we be bugging out? We speak to biologist Dr. John Cooley, ecologist Dr.</description></item><item><title>Immune Boosting: Is It a Bust? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360100/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Internet influencers have been pushing “immune boosters” during the pandemic — claiming they’ve got just the pill, berry or brew to rev up our body’s defenses. But is there really a way to boost our immune system? We’re finding out whether these vitamins and supplements truly work as a shield against colds and viruses. We speak to public health Prof. Tim Caulfield, nutrition Prof. Carol Johnston, immunologist Shiv Pillai, and immune aging researcher Niharika Duggal.</description></item><item><title>Bringing the Science Back, Baby! | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360101/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 19:31:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360101/</guid><description>Podcast Description There are a lot of fads, blogs and strong opinions, but then there’s SCIENCE. Season 10 starts March 4! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Butterflies Are Secret Monsters | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360102/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 22:39:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Butterflies flit through life as the pride and joy of the insect world. But when we saw photos of butterflies swarming the eyes of turtles, we wondered if there was a dark side lurking behind all those flashy colors. Assistant Professor of Biology Chandreyee Mitra lets us in on these butterfly secrets.
Here’s a link to our transcript: https://bit.ly/36osuwx This episode was produced by Nick DelRose with help from Wendy Zukerman, Meryl Horn, Michelle Dang, Rose Rimler, and Taylor White.</description></item><item><title>Presenting Coronavirus: Fact Vs. Fiction | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360103/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 15:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360103/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, we’re sharing an episode of Coronavirus: Fact Vs. Fiction, a podcast from CNN. This episode is The Hunt for Disease X: As human activity ventures further into the wilderness, scientists believe more diseases will emerge. CNN Senior International Correspondent Sam Kiley takes Dr. Sanjay Gupta on a journey deep into the rainforests of the Democratic Republic of the Congo, where the hunt for the next pandemic pathogen continues.</description></item><item><title>Magic Mushrooms: Trip Through the Science | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360104/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 23:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Magic mushrooms have hit the headlines, with people saying that shrooms cured their depression and anxiety. But is this for real? How can taking a trip on psychedelics fix your brain? Today, magic mushrooms ditch their tie dye for a lab coat as we go on a magical journey into the science. We talk to clinical psychologists Dr. Alan Davis and Dr. Albert Garcia-Romeu, and neuropsychologist Dr. Katrin Preller.</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus: More Scared or Less Scared? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360105/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 23:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360105/</guid><description>Podcast Description MINI EPISODE! Tons of new science means fresh answers on a few things that really freaked us out at the start of the pandemic: coronavirus on surfaces; ibuprofen and Covid-19; and getting Covid twice. Link to transcript: https://bit.ly/3lXu6Ca
This episode was produced by Rose Rimler, Nick DelRose, and Wendy Zukerman with help from Michelle Dang and Hannah Harris Green. We’re edited by Blythe Terrell with help from Caitlin Kenney.</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus: Shots! Shots! Shots! | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360106/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 22:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360106/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s a ton of hoopla over these new coronavirus vaccines. But given that they’ve been produced at warp speed — can we trust them? We also find out what’s going on with “long haulers.” How common is it to be sick for months from Covid-19? Plus, fresh new science about why some young people land in the hospital. We talk to Dr. Katy Stephenson, Dr. Alexander Hoischen, Dr. Jeffrey Siegelman, and Prof.</description></item><item><title>Did the CIA do it? Part II | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360107/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360107/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a deadly pig virus hit Cuba in 1971, some claimed the CIA was behind it all. But could it be true? In part two of our investigation into the outbreak, we finally hear directly from the CIA — and get to the bottom of what happened. In this episode: ex-CIA Brian Latell, journalist Drew Fetherston, Professor Mary-Louise Penrith and Professor José Manuel Sánchez-Vizcaíno. Please fill out our Science Vs survey!</description></item><item><title>Did the CIA Plant a Virus in Cuba? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360108/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 01:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360108/</guid><description>Podcast Description When the Cuban government rounded up and killed thousands of pigs in 1971, people were angry and confused. Castro claimed they were trying to stop an outbreak. But then rumours started spreading that something much bigger was behind it all. The CIA. To find out more, we speak to Professor Virgil Suarez, journalist Drew Fetherston, Professor Mary Louise Penrith, ex-CIA Carol &amp;ldquo;Rollie&amp;rdquo; Flynn and Professor Loch Johnson.
Here’s a link to our transcript: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>Platypuses Get a Glow Up | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360109/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 19:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360109/</guid><description>Podcast Description The eccentric platypus has always turned heads, and now it’s got something else up its sleeve. We talked with mammalogist Dr. Paula Anich to get the scoop.
Here’s a link to our transcript: https://bit.ly/34YfHR4
This episode was produced by Nick DelRose with help from Wendy Zukerman, Rose Rimler, Michelle Dang, and Hannah Harris Green. We’re edited by Blythe Terrell. Mix and sound design by Bumi Hidaka. Music written by Peter Leonard.</description></item><item><title>Reparations: How Could It Work? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360110/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 21:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360110/</guid><description>Podcast Description The idea of paying Black Americans reparations for slavery has been around for a long time, but it’s starting to get more support than ever. So we ask: If the country does agree to pay up, how do you calculate the bill? And how could the U.S. come up with that kind of cash? To find out, we talk to historian and farmer Leah Penniman, economist Prof. William Darity Jr.</description></item><item><title>Supervolcanoes: Is Yellowstone Gonna Blow? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360111/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360111/</guid><description>Podcast Description We keep hearing that a Yellowstone supervolcano could blow at any moment — and possibly wipe us all out. So is Yellowstone overdue for the BIG ONE, and if it happens, how bad could it be? To find out, we talk to paleoecologist Dr. Gill Plunkett, Yellowstone Volcano Observatory Scientist-in-Charge Dr. Mike Poland and Washington resident Christian Jacobsen. Here’s a link to our transcript: https://bit.ly/3kliFV6
Check out Yellowstone Volcano Observatory’s weekly blog the “Caldera Chronicles”: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Science Vs Presents: How to Save a Planet | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360112/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 23:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360112/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re sharing another great Gimlet show, How to Save a Planet. On this episode: It started with students walking out of school to demand more action on climate change, built into an international movement – and then was propelled forward by a pandemic. This is the surprising story behind Europe’s climate plan, and what the rest of us can learn from it. Find more episodes here: https://open.spotify.com/show/1KzrasExlM5dgMYwgFHns6 How to Save a Planet is hosted by Alex Blumberg and Dr.</description></item><item><title>Lab-Grown Meat: We Grill It | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360113/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 23:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Silicon Valley seems to be constantly pumping out &amp;ldquo;solutions&amp;rdquo; to fix our broken food system. The latest and greatest: cell-cultured meat — meat that&amp;rsquo;s grown in vats, without needing to kill animals. Companies say their new techy meat will be safe and better for the planet than what we have now. We join forces with Chase Purdy, author of “Billion Dollar Burger,” to find out if this stuff is all it’s cracked up to be.</description></item><item><title>Hunting an Invisible Killer | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360114/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 01:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360114/</guid><description>Podcast Description An adventuring Swedish doctor takes on a decades-long medical mystery: What exactly was the 1918 flu? We talk to Dr. Johan Hultin, Eileen Hultin, Dr. Jeffery Taubenberger, Ann Reid, Rita Olanna and Annie Conger. Here’s a link to our transcript: https://bit.ly/30mnvt6
Check out Radiolab’s episode on the 1918 flu here: https://bit.ly/3n9cxkm
And the book Flu: The Story of the Great Influenza Pandemic of 1918 and the Search for the Virus That Caused it by Gina Kolata: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>Orgasms: Come for the Science | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360115/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 00:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360115/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s this idea that the female orgasm is a complicated riddle, but for a man with a penis, getting off is easy peasy. Is there really an orgasm gap? And if so — can science explain it? To learn more, we talk to neuroscientist Dr. Nan Wise, neuroscientist Dr. Nicole Prause and psychologist Dr. Candice Hargons. Here’s a link to our transcript: https://bit.ly/340vQDV
Learn more about Dr. Nicole Prause’s’s lab, the Liberos Center: https://www.</description></item><item><title>SHARKS!!! Sink Your Teeth in Again | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360116/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 16:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360116/</guid><description>Podcast Description NOTE: This episode first published 6/13/19. Are sharks the super-predators we think they are? Or have we been baited with great white lies? To find out, we interviewed shark researchers Dr. Taylor Chapple, Dr. Tricia Meredith and Dr. Chris Pepin-Neff, along with surfer Mike Wells. We’re doing a survey for our episode on orgasms! We’d love for you to take it: https://blythet.typeform.com/to/qhESeova
Check out the full episode transcript here: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>Astrology: Are Geminis the Worst? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360117/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 17:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360117/</guid><description>Podcast Description For centuries, people have been looking to the stars to tell us all kinds of things — what our future holds, who we should date. So what does the science say about astrology? It turns out, there’s some surprising stuff here. We speak to astronomer Prof. Caty Pilachowski, Prof. Dave Henningsen and astrology lover Natalie Norman. Here’s a link to the transcript: https://bit.ly/31VTDoM This episode was produced by Meryl Horn and Rose Rimler, with help from Wendy Zukerman, Michelle Dang, Hannah Harris Green and Nick DelRose.</description></item><item><title>Mini Mask Update | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360118/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 17:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360118/</guid><description>Podcast Description MASKS. Since the early days of the pandemic, it’s been tough to nail down how much they can really do to slow down the spread of the virus. We speak to industrial hygienist Dr. Rachael Jones and share some new science that puts the final nail in the coffin of this debate (hint yes, you should wear a mask — your friends, family and neighbors too). Here’s a link to our transcript: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>Probiotics: Scam or Superfood? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360119/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 22:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kombucha, kefir and other probiotic-crammed foods are marketed as charmers of the human microbiome — and the key to immune, gut and brain health. But how much does the microbiome actually matter, and do probiotics live up to the hype? To learn more we talked with biomedical engineering professor Ilana Brito, immunologist Dr. Yasmine Belkaid, psychiatry professor Ted Dinan, and microbiologist Dr. Namrata Iyer.
UPDATE 8/28/20: An earlier version of this episode said there was a little bit of evidence that specific microbes can help with irritable bowel disease.</description></item><item><title>New Season! Time for Non-Coronavirus Content | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360120/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 22:24:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Science Vs is back August 27th. Fact you next week! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus: Are We Back Where We Started? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360121/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 03:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360121/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re six months into this coronavirus pandemic, which has shaken the world and stunned scientists. What have we learned? Where are we headed? To find out, we talk to virologist Professor John Dennehy, virologist and immunologist Professor Ann Sheehy, and hospital epidemiologist Dr. Cassandra Pierre. We also check back in with Dani Schuchman, who is now three months into his recovery from Covid-19. Also: MEAT-EATING SPONGES!!
Here’s a link to our transcript: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>Fauci! He’s Back! | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360122/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 23:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Anthony Fauci, director of the National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases, member of the White House Coronavirus Task Force and America&amp;rsquo;s favorite nerd joins Science Vs again. Wendy chats with Dr. Fauci about the pandemic’s past, present and future. Here’s a link to our transcript: https://bit.ly/2V82uQg
This episode was produced by Wendy Zukerman, Meryl Horn, Rose Rimler, Michelle Dang, Mathilde Urfalino and Sinduja Srinivasan. We’re edited by Blythe Terrell and Caitlin Kenney.</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus: Dude, Where's My Vaccine? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360123/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360123/</guid><description>Podcast Description All through the pandemic, we’ve been waiting for a possible silver bullet: a vaccine. How soon could we actually get one? To find out, we talk to microbiologist and immunologist Professor Karla Satchell, immunologist Dr. Kathryn Stephenson, Pfizer executive Mike McDermott, and Ian Haydon, who’s participating in a vaccine clinical trial.
Here’s a link to our transcript: https://bit.ly/3egWFrc
This episode was produced by Wendy Zukerman, with help from Michelle Dang, Sinduja Srinivasan, Laura Morris, Meg Driscoll, Rose Rimler, Meryl Horn, and Mathilde Urfalino.</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus: Weirdest Virus Ever? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360124/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 01:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360124/</guid><description>Podcast Description The coronavirus seems to cause symptoms all over our body, from nose to toes. So how can one virus do so many strange things? To find out, we talk to gastroenterologist Dr. Anthony DeBenedet, virologist and immunologist Professor Ann Sheehy, otorhinolaryngologist Professor Thomas Hummel, and dermatologist Professor Amy Paller. Here’s a link to our transcript: https://bit.ly/2zqehBZ This episode was produced by Rose Rimler and Meryl Horn with help from Wendy Zukerman, Sinduja Srinivasan, Michelle Dang and Mathilde Urfalino.</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus: Protesting in a Pandemic | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360125/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 04:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hundreds of thousands of people have joined the global protest movement sparked by the death of George Floyd. And a lot of doctors and public health experts are on board, despite concerns about the pandemic. So how can protesters stay safe — from coronavirus, and from police weapons like tear gas? To find out, we talk to epidemiologist Dr. Cassandra Pierre, Dr. Rohini Haar, and a protester who’s been tear gassed.</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus: Labs Go Dark | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360126/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Life is on pause for many of us right now. But scientists don’t want to stop! Researchers have had to figure out how to keep experiments going and keep lab animals alive — all while keeping themselves safe. To find out how they’re managing it, we talk to evolutionary biologist Dr. Ximena Bernal, plant biologist Professor Frank Telewski, marine conservation biologist Christine Figgener, and station manager Erin Heard.</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus: Sweden Goes Rogue | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360127/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 05:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360127/</guid><description>Podcast Description While a lot of countries have put in strict measures, like lockdowns, to stop the coronavirus, there’s been a conspicuous outlier: Sweden. The country has carved a different path, trying to keep its hospitals from being overrun while allowing society to function as normally as possible. So, is the Swedish model working? To find out, we talk to medical epidemiologist Dr. Emma Frans, Professor Annelies Wilder-Smith, Dr. Gary Weissman, and Dr.</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus: The Mask Wars | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360128/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 03:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360128/</guid><description>Podcast Description When the pandemic started, we were told not to bother with masks. But now it looks like experts have done a 180 here, and a lot of us are being told to cover our mugs when we leave the house. So which is it? Should we mask up or not? To find out, we talk to epidemiologist Professor Benjamin Cowling, microbiologist Dr. Anna Davies, and clinical psychologist Dr. Olga Perski.</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus: Pregnant in a Pandemic | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360129/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 19:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360129/</guid><description>Podcast Description How bad is the coronavirus for pregnant people and babies? Producer Meryl Horn is digging into this question for today’s episode. And it’s personal, because Meryl is pregnant and living in the pandemic hot spot that is New York City. We talk to Professor Emily Oster, pathologist Dr. David Schwartz, and obstetrician Dr. Suzanne LaJoie. Also: SWIMMING DINOSAURS!?
Here’s a link to our transcript: bit.ly/2YKzD7e This episode was produced by Meryl Horn with help from me Wendy Zukerman, Rose Rimler, Laura Morris, Michelle Dang and Sinduja Srinivasan.</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus: Was It Made In a Lab? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360130/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 05:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Since the outbreak started, we’ve been hearing that this coronavirus came from bats before jumping to humans. But recently, claims that the virus escaped from a lab have been getting a lot of attention. So did it? Is there an evil scientist behind all of this? To find out, we talk to microbiologist Professor Benhur Lee, Christian Stevens, and virologist Dr. Oscar MacLean. Also: FROGS!! UPDATE 4/27/20: An earlier version of this episode played a quote from a politician saying that China has only one biosafety level 4 lab.</description></item><item><title>Working Out From Home — in 7 Minutes? [Rebroadcast] | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360131/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 20:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Social distancing has made it harder for a lot of us to get exercise. So we’re revisiting our episode on the seven-minute workout. Can this bite-size routine really keep us fit? Back in 2018, we asked exercise scientist Prof. Jeff Coombes — and Wendy gave it a go. Check out the transcript here: https://bit.ly/2RQarYz We also looked into the broader science of exercise in this episode: https://open.spotify.com/episode/3iMLOaNVAy0s6RsdecUySj And find the original study on the seven-minute workout here: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus: Can You Get It Twice? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360132/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 04:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360132/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re hearing stories of people getting this coronavirus, recovering, and then getting it again. So what’s going on: Does getting this virus give you immunity or not? To find out, we talk to virologist Dr. Kirsty Short of the University of Queensland and Dr. Robin Berzin of Parsley Health.
Here’s a link to our transcript: https://bit.ly/3ajK5om
This episode was produced by Meryl Horn, Wendy Zukerman, Michelle Dang, Rose Rimler, Sinduja Srinivasan and Laura Morris.</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus: When Will It End? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360133/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 03:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360133/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the U.S. we&amp;rsquo;ve been social distancing for a few weeks now, and the question on everyone’s mind is: When can we go back to “normal”? And what’s happening in China, where they’ve already lifted the lockdown? To find out, we talk to Dr. Swapnil Mishra, part of the Imperial College Covid-19 Response Team, and Dr. Franz-Josef Schmitt. Here’s a link to our transcript: https://bit.ly/2y5nJtc You can listen to The Journal’s full interview with Dr.</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus: Should I Disinfect EVERYTHING? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360134/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 04:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360134/</guid><description>Podcast Description There are reports that the coronavirus can survive on surfaces for days. So how careful should we be about cleaning the stuff we touch? And do we need to be disinfecting our groceries? To find out, we talk to pathologist and microbiologist Dr. Josh Santarpia and toxicologist Dr. Joshua King. UPDATE 4/7/20: An earlier version of this episode suggested that Alex was wiping down his groceries with bleach, but the wipes he was using didn&amp;rsquo;t contain bleach.</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus: Is It Airborne? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360135/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 05:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360135/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re hearing conflicting things about how the coronavirus spreads — is it through coughs and sneezes only? Or could it be floating in the air, infecting us as we walk down the street or go grocery shopping? We ask Dr. Rachael Jones, an industrial hygienist, and Dr. Zhi Ning, an environmental engineer. Here’s a link to our transcript: https://bit.ly/3aI1kAE
This episode was produced by Rose Rimler, Wendy Zukerman, Michelle Dang, Meryl Horn, Sinduja Srinivasan, Laura Morris, and Meg Driscoll.</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus: Are Young People Safe? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360136/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 04:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360136/</guid><description>Podcast Description From the early days of this coronavirus outbreak, it’s looked like the disease is way worse for older people. But now we’re hearing more stories of younger folks getting really sick. What’s going on? Is this virus scarier for younger people than we thought? We hear from a Gen-Xer who landed in the hospital with Covid-19, and we talk to immunologist Professor Vincent Racaniello. Also: THE HIGHEST MOUSE! We’ve set up a voicemail to collect all of your questions about coronavirus.</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus: Will Chloroquine Save Us? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360137/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 02:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360137/</guid><description>Podcast Description President Trump says an anti-malarial drug could be a “gift from god” for treating Covid-19. Does it really work? And is it dangerous? We talk to toxicologist Professor Daniel Brooks, infectious disease specialist Dr. Matthew Pullen, and microbiologist Professor Karla Satchell. Also: VAMPIRE BATS!
We’ve set up a voicemail to collect all of your questions about Coronavirus. Or if you’re a healthcare worker with a personal story you want to share, please call ‪(774) 481-1238‬ and leave us a message.</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus: Unmasking the Facts and Ibuprofen Scares | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360138/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 03:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360138/</guid><description>Podcast Description Healthcare workers across the U.S. are saying they don’t have enough protective gear to keep them safe against the coronavirus. They’re having to reuse masks, and they’re worried that they may have to resort to homemade cloth masks. Is all this safe? Plus, reports are saying that ibuprofen, the stuff in Advil, is making people with coronavirus sicker. But what does the science say? To find out we spoke to infectious disease expert Professor Raina MacIntyre, industrial hygienist Dr.</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus: A Story From the Front Lines | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360139/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 23:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360139/</guid><description>Podcast Description As Covid-19 cases rise in the U.S., healthcare workers are already struggling to keep up. In a different kind of episode, we bring you an interview with Dr. Antoinette Ward, who is leading Covid-19 testing at a major hospital in Atlanta — and finding ways to treat the rapidly increasing number of patients. This interview comes from iHeartRadio’s The Women. For more stories from those on the front lines, listen here: http://bit.</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus: What Should You Do Now? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360140/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 22:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360140/</guid><description>Podcast Description The coronavirus pandemic is here, and in the U.S., this is starting to get very real. We talk to people in South Korea and Italy to see what life has been like for them. And we find out what the problem was with America’s tests — are they fixed now? And now that social distancing is on everyone’s mind, do we have evidence that it will really “flatten the curve”?</description></item><item><title>More Science Vs Coming Right Up | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360141/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 14:34:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Science Vs is back March 19th. Fact you next week. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus: Fears and Facts | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360142/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360142/</guid><description>Podcast Description The new coronavirus continues to spread around the world, and it’s already killed several people in the U.S. People are starting to worry that this will turn into a full-blown pandemic. So how many of us could ultimately get infected — and is it time to prepare for the worst? To find out, we talk to epidemiologists Dr. Cécile Viboud and Prof. Marc Lipsitch.
Here’s a link to our transcript: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus Outbreak: How Scared Should You Be? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360143/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 04:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360143/</guid><description>Podcast Description A new virus showed up in China late last year, and it’s making its way to other countries too. So what do scientists know about the virus so far? And how worried should we be? To find out we talk to infectious disease researchers Dr. Kristian Andersen and Dr. Catharine Paules, physician Dr. Hui, and director of the National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases Dr. Anthony Fauci.</description></item><item><title>How to Stop A Killer Asteroid | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360144/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 02:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360144/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week — asteroids. Could a space rock really slam into us and destroy the world? And if we did spot one heading straight for us, is there anything we could do to stop it? We speak with asteroid researcher Dr. Alan Harris, astrophysicist Dr. Sergey Zamozdra, computational physicist Dr. Cathy Plesko, and physicist Dr. Andy Cheng. Check out the full transcript here: http://bit.ly/2MrW1vp Selected references: Overview of Chelyabinsk impact and risk from asteroids: http://bit.</description></item><item><title>Healthcare: How Do We Fix It? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360145/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360145/</guid><description>Podcast Description American healthcare has big problems. Some say the solution is Medicare For All: one government plan for everybody. But others say government healthcare would be worse than what we already have. Who’s right? And how did things get this bad? We talk to health policy researchers Prof. Harold Pollack and Robin Osborn. Check out the full transcript here: https://bit.ly/38ye0cY Selected references: Paper from last year on why American healthcare spending is so high: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>Ants: Tales from the Underground | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360146/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 23:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360146/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s show, three f-ant-astic stories of survival, friendship and courage about some of the most underrated creatures in the animal queendom. Produced with our friends at Every Little Thing, another Gimlet podcast. We spoke with behavioral ecologist Dr. István Maák, biologist Dr. Erik Frank, entomologist Dr. Christina Kwapich, and biologist Prof Derrick Brazill. Check out the full transcript here: http://bit.ly/38cDgoU Selected references: István’s study on ants surviving in a nuclear bunker: http://bit.</description></item><item><title>Police Shootings: The Data and the Damage Done | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360147/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 02:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360147/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been five years since the high profile shootings of several unarmed black teenagers and men launched the Black Lives Matter movement. Since then, police departments have been doing all kinds of things to respond to the deaths and protests. But do any of them work? To find out we speak with social psychologist Prof. Jennifer Eberhardt, psychologist Prof. Phillip Atiba Goff, public policy expert Dr. David Yokum, criminologists Dr.</description></item><item><title>When a Hospital becomes The Butcher Shop | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360148/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 02:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360148/</guid><description>Podcast Description A group of teenagers and college kids were fed up with the lousy healthcare in their neighborhood. So they decided to fight the system head on—a fight that still resonates today. Sid Davidoff, Mickey Melendez, and Cleo Silvers share their story. Check out the full transcript here: http://bit.ly/33QhYKX Selected references: Mickey Melendez&amp;rsquo;s Book: http://bit.ly/34Ww1ik Interview with Cleo Silvers: http://bit.ly/2Xcg58S Article about lead testing in the 1970s: http://bit.ly/2qTJSqN To hear more on lead poisoning prevention today: http://bit.</description></item><item><title>Sleep: All Aboard the Snooze Cruise! | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360149/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 01:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Not sleeping enough turning you into a monster? Cutting-edge science helps us understand why. And we sort through the fads to find out, what really works to get more ZZZs. We speak with lab coordinator Pam De Young, sleep researcher Dr. Brady Riedner, and circadian scientist Prof. Russell Foster. Check out the full transcript here: http://bit.ly/2Ns26Zt Selected references: Consensus on the optimal amount of sleep: http://bit.ly/2Nu33Rc Local sleep review: http://bit.</description></item><item><title>5G: Welcome to the Revolution? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360150/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 23:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360150/</guid><description>Podcast Description How should we feel about 5G? Is it a breakthrough technology that will revolutionize our world, or in a bid to get new gadgets, are we risking our health? To find out, we spoke with electrical engineer Prof. Jeff Andrews, biologist Prof. Henrik Mouritsen, radiology safety expert Prof. Chris Collins, and psychologist Prof. Rodney Croft. Check out the full transcript here: http://bit.ly/2qd2MIR Selected references: Jeff’s paper on the future of 5G: http://bit.</description></item><item><title>Vaping: What the Hell is Going On?! | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360151/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 02:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vaping is all the rage in the U.S., but young people are turning up at hospitals barely able to breathe. Over a thousand vapers have gotten sick⁠—34 are dead⁠—and no one knows why. We investigated the case of the mysterious vaping disease with help from Geri Sullivan, pulmonologist Dr. Louella Amos, lab director Iniobong Afia, inhalation toxicologist Prof. Ilona Jaspers and researcher Dr. Jamie Hartmann-Boyce. Check out the full transcript here: http://bit.</description></item><item><title>PANDEMIC!!! | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360152/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 16:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360152/</guid><description>Podcast Description If a pandemic ripped across the world, how bad would it really get? You’ve heard the horror stories, but you’ve never heard one like this. Dr. Anthony Fauci, who advises the President on emerging infectious diseases, helps us out. Check out the full transcript here: http://bit.ly/2M4Tlnt Selected references: The CDC’s history of the 1918 Pandemic: http://bit.ly/2AXiGJP Time-lapse tracking the transmission and evolution of H7N9: http://bit.ly/2B1nYnG CDC’s Pandemic Influenza Plan: http://bit.</description></item><item><title>Heartbreak: Why does it hurt so bad? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360153/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360153/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’ve all been dumped, but some of us have felt physically sick from a heartbreak &amp;ndash; sometimes really sick. Neuroscientist Prof. Lucy Brown explains how pangs from a heartache might not just be in our heads. Check out the full transcript here: http://bit.ly/2OhEIi9 Selected references: Lucy’s FMRI study of the rejected in-love college students: http://bit.ly/355Xz5B The social/physical pain overlap in the brain: https://bit.ly/2IkRQiVHow psychological stress affects the immune system: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>Football: Should We Cancel It? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360154/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 00:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360154/</guid><description>Podcast Description America’s favorite pastime seems to be plagued by tragedy. Former NFL players have come forward to say they’re suffering from a serious brain disease. Others have ended their lives. So we wanted to know: how risky is playing football? Cornerback Isiah Swann, neuroscientist Dr. Kevin Bieniek, neurosurgeon Prof. Bob Cantu, and neurologist Dr. Ira Casson weigh in. Check out the full transcript here: http://bit.ly/2mWkuyR Note: In this episode we discuss depression and suicide.</description></item><item><title>Exercise: Fat Buster or Belly Flop? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360155/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lots of people hit the gym to shed unwanted pounds, but they don’t always see results on the scale. This week, we tackle the power of exercise and why you should bother. We speak with obesity expert Dr. Yoni Freedhoff, psychiatrist Dr. Gary Cooney, neuroscientist Prof. Wendy Suzuki and urologist Dr. Stacey Kenfield. Check out the full transcript here: http://bit.ly/2kqreUR UPDATE 10/31/19: An earlier version of this episode said that exercise isn’t a reliable treatment for depression.</description></item><item><title>Let's...science...AGAIN! | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360156/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 16:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Science Vs is back September 19th. Fact you next week. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Dinosaur Explosion | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360157/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 21:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360157/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why are there so many new, weird dinosaurs? Friend of the show Joel Werner goes down the rabbit hole, and finds a surprising answer. He speaks to paleontologists Dr. Steve Brusatte and Dr. Jonathan Tennant. Listen to Joel’s podcast The Sum Of All Parts here: https://ab.co/2YujtzU. Check out the transcript here: http://bit.ly/2Ts169i Science Vs will be back in September with a brand new season! UPDATE 8/13/19: We removed some lines suggesting that the reason that Joel and other people growing up in the 80s don&amp;rsquo;t know about some dinosaurs, such as Spinosaurus and Edmontosaurus is because of the &amp;ldquo;Dino Explosion&amp;rdquo; in the 1990s.</description></item><item><title>How Bad Science Killed A President | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360158/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 21:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360158/</guid><description>Podcast Description When President Garfield was shot by an assassin in 1881, the best and brightest in medicine and science did everything they could to save him - and turned the President into a human guinea pig. But they missed something big, that could have saved him. To find out what it was, we spoke to surgeon and medical historian Dr Ira Rutkow, and Sara Murphy - collections manager at the National Museum of American History.</description></item><item><title>Peanuts: Public Enemy No. 1? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360159/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 22:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Peanut allergy in children has been on the rise since the 1990s. What’s to blame? We find a clue in a very unexpected place, and talk to pediatric allergist Prof. Gideon Lack. Check out the full transcript here: http://bit.ly/2rkEcqL Selected References: Gideon’s landmark 2015 study: https://bit.ly/2QsvOMvThe mouse rash study: https://bit.ly/2Mf6hZVCDC’s report on rising skin and food allergies (1997-2011): https://bit.ly/2XgjGlJ This episode was produced by Rose Rimler with help from Wendy Zukerman, along with Meryl Horn and Michelle Dang.</description></item><item><title>The Abortion Underground | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360160/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 23:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360160/</guid><description>Podcast Description Before Roe v. Wade, there were thousands of illegal abortions in the U.S. every year. Some of these were incredibly dangerous; women would use knitting needles or coat hangers to end pregnancies. This, and other illegal methods, could lead to injury or death. In the 1970s, one group of women got fed up and decided to take women&amp;rsquo;s health into their own hands. We talk to “self-helpers” Carol Downer and Francie Hornstein, who led a movement for safe abortions and education for women by women.</description></item><item><title>Placebo: Can the Mind Cure You? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360161/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 23:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360161/</guid><description>Podcast Description Could fake medicine actually take away your pain or treat a disease? We dig into the science of placebos to find out more about the power of the mind to heal. We speak to medical researcher Prof. Ted Kaptchuk, neuroscientist Prof. Fabrizio Benedetti and medical psychologist Prof. Manfred Schedlowski. UPDATE 5/13/19: We changed a few things in this episode to clarify facts. An earlier version of this episode implied that the placebo surgery for knee and back pain was really effective in itself.</description></item><item><title>Vaccines: Time for a Booster Shot [Rebroadcast] | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360162/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360162/</guid><description>Podcast Description Autism, seizures, and overloaded immune systems - could these really be side effects of vaccines? From the archives, we bring back our dive into the science to find out how safe vaccines really are. We spoke to public health researchers Prof. Dan Salmon and Prof. Amy Kalkbrenner and neurologist Prof. Ingrid Scheffer. Check out the full transcript here: http://bit.ly/2IVgabd Selected References: The National Academies (aka Institute of Medicine) report on vaccine safety A report on the genetic underpinnings of epilepsyThis study looked for neurologic disorders after the MMR shot in half a million kidsThis one looked at all children born in Denmark between 1991 and 1998 Credits: This episode has been produced by Heather Rogers, Wendy Zukerman, and Shruti Ravindran.</description></item><item><title>Fertility Cliff: Is It Real? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360163/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 15:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360163/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re often told to have kids quickly, before our biological clock strikes and we fall off the fertility cliff. This week we find out if that’s true for women or men. And if the cliff is real, can you do anything about it, like freezing your eggs? Plus, the sperm-aggedon! We speak to epidemiologist Prof. Lauren Wise, reproductive endocrinologist Dr. Mary Sabatini, and andrologist Prof. Allan Pacey. UPDATE 7/10/19: A previous version of this episode incorrectly identified the nationality of a character in Indiana Jones.</description></item><item><title>Race: Can We See It In Our DNA? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360164/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 05:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360164/</guid><description>Podcast Description For decades, we&amp;rsquo;ve heard that race is a social and cultural idea — not scientific. But with the changing world of genetics, is race science back? We speak to sociologist Prof. Dorothy Roberts, evolutionary biologist Prof. Joseph L. Graves Jr. and psychological methodologist Prof. Jelte Wicherts. Check out the full transcript here: http://bit.ly/2nTDU8w Selected references: Dorothy’s book on the history of scientific racism One of Joseph’s books unpacking raceThe 2005 paper on population structureA handy FAQ from a population geneticistA paper on the knowns and unknowns about genes and the environment on IQ Credits: This episode was produced by Rose Rimler, with help from Wendy Zukerman, as well as Meryl Horn and Michelle Dang.</description></item><item><title>DNA Kits: Can You Trust Them? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360165/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 01:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Millions of people are sending off their DNA to companies like Ancestry.com and 23andme to find out where they come from, and what diseases they might get. But how much can you trust these DNA kits? To find out, we speak to anthropologist Prof. Jonathan Marks and geneticist Dr Adam Rutherford. Check out the full transcript here: http://bit.ly/2OSICOD Selected references: This academic paper on genetic ancestry testingAncestry.com’s white paper The genetics of Alzheimer DiseaseA perspective piece on genetic privacy Credits: This episode was produced by Rose Rimler, with senior producer Kaitlyn Sawrey… with help from Wendy Zukerman, Meryl Horn and Michelle Dang.</description></item><item><title>Pets on Planes: Are Emotional Support Animals Legit? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360166/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360166/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can petting Fluffy or Fido help with anxiety on planes? Or are emotional support animals a load of croc? We talk to psychologist Prof. Hal Herzog to find out if science has anything to say on whether these pets should fly high or be grounded. Check out the full transcript here: http://bit.ly/2MD2lPC Selected references: Hal’s critical review on whether pets can improve mental health Study showing that blankets worked just as well as dogs to reduce anxiety in childrenHere’s a good article describing the differences between emotional support animals and service animals A couple reviews on the evidence that animal-assisted therapy can help with psychiatric illnesses Credits: This episode was produced by Meryl Horn, with help from Wendy Zukerman, Rose Rimler, and Michelle Dang.</description></item><item><title>Fasting Diets: What's the Skinny? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360167/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 01:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fasting diets are all the rage right now and health-fluencers claim it can help you lose weight, live longer and even fight cancer. So what does the science say? We speak to nutrition researchers Dr Krista Varady and Dr Courtney Peterson, as well as cancer researcher Professor Valter Longo. Check out the full transcript here: http://bit.ly/35FYJoP Selected references: Krista’s study comparing alternate day fasting with regular dieting, which found they had similar weight loss after one year.</description></item><item><title>Science's Rotten Underbelly | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360168/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 00:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360168/</guid><description>Podcast Description During a golden age for scientific progress, a group of scientists were given free rein to do whatever they wanted to their human lab rats. We got new drugs, and learnt exciting new things. But some researchers took it too far&amp;hellip; And what seemed like a scientific fantasy turned into one of the largest American science scandals. Check out the full transcript here: http://bit.ly/2MLBX6u Selected references: The 1976 report from the National Commission for the Protection of Human Subjects of Biomedical and Behavioral Research Allen Hornblum’s book Acres of Skin (1998)2007 report from the Institute of Medicine Committee on Ethical Considerations for Research The Experimental Scurvy in Man 1969 study Credits: This episode was produced by Wendy Zukerman with help from Rose Rimler, Meryl Horn and Michelle Dang.</description></item><item><title>Alcohol: A Pour Decision? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360169/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 00:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360169/</guid><description>Podcast Description For decades we’ve been told that having a glass or two of wine is good for you. But recently there’ve been reports that even a little bit of booze is bad for you. So what is going on? Is just a bit of alcohol dangerous? To find out we talk to epidemiologist and nutritionist Prof. Eric Rimm, psychologist Prof. Tim Stockwell, and cancer researcher Dr. Susan Gapstur. Check out the full transcript here: http://bit.</description></item><item><title>We're back next week! | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360170/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 18:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 6 is on it&amp;rsquo;s way, fellow nerds! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Mystery of the Man Who Died Twice | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360171/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 23:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360171/</guid><description>Podcast Description A dead body turns up with a stolen identity. This week, we tell the story of how a grandmother tracked down the truth — and helped create a whole new and controversial world of crime fighting. To tell this story, we talk to U.S. Marshal Peter Elliott, Dr. Margaret Press, and Phil Nichols. Check out the transcript here; http://bit.ly/33CNj3i Note: in this episode we discuss suicide and homicide. Please take care when listening to the show, and here are some resources: National Mental Health Helpline: 1-800-662-HELP (4357).</description></item><item><title>The Science Of Being Transgender | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360172/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 23:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Recently we’ve been hearing a lot about transgender identity. That made us wonder… what makes us the gender that we are? And what should you do if your kid doesn’t fit the mold? To find out, we talked with endocrinologist Dr. Joshua Safer, psychologist Dr. Laura Edwards-Leeper, and psychologist Dr. Colt Keo-Meier. Check out the transcript: http://bit.ly/31k0oNk UPDATE 3/29/19 : An earlier version of this episode misinterpreted a study regarding the question of how many children who visited a gender identity clinic grow up to be trans.</description></item><item><title>The Wank Worm: How NASA Got Hacked | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360173/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 20:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360173/</guid><description>Podcast Description Before WikiLeaks, there was the Wank Worm. In this week’s episode, we tell you the story of how Australian hackers infiltrated NASA, just months after the country was hooked up to the internet in 1989. Joel Werner, host of Sum of All Parts, helps us tell this story, along with cybersecurity researcher Dr. Suelette Dreyfus. Check out the transcript here: http://bit.ly/35EkMw5 UPDATE 12/07/18: An earlier version of this episode stated that Galileo&amp;rsquo;s engines ran on nuclear power.</description></item><item><title>Ancient Aliens: Who Really Built the Pyramids? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360174/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 23:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360174/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is it possible that the pyramids were built with a helping hand&amp;hellip; from aliens? If not, how on Earth did the Egyptians built them without modern technology? To get to the bottom of this, we speak to author Erich von Däniken, paleoanthropologist Dr. Shelby Putt, Egyptologist Dr. Mark Lehner, and archaeologist Prof. David S. Anderson. Check out the transcript here: http://bit.ly/2P6tvl9 Selected references: This paper about the evolution of intelligence.</description></item><item><title>7 Minute Workout: Fit or Fad? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360175/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 19:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360175/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 7 Minute Workout is all the rage, but can working out for just 7 minutes really do anything? To figure out whether this fitness trend is a load of crock, we speak to exercise scientist Prof. Jeff Coombes. Plus, Wendy gives it a go. Check out the transcript right here: http://bit.ly/32qS7IO Selected references: The original 7 minute workout Jeff’s review paper on short intense workouts and weight lossOther reviews about heart health, diabetes, and fitness in healthy peopleThe study on really, really, really short workouts Credits: This episode was produced by Rose Rimler with help from Wendy Zukerman, along with Meryl Horn and Odelia Rubin.</description></item><item><title>CBD: Weed Wonder Drug? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360176/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360176/</guid><description>Podcast Description CBD mania is in full swing and people are using it for just about anything, but what is this chemical in cannabis? In this week’s episode, we tell you unlikely origin story of CBD and if the science backs up the hype. We speak to Paige Figi, neuroscientist Prof. Kent Hutchison, clinical researcher Dr. Mallory Loflin, and Josh and Joel Stanley. Check out the transcript right here: http://bit.ly/2OVCfub Selected references: Mallory’s study showing most CBD products are labeled inaccurately and 1 out of 5 has some THCReview discussing all the possible things CBD is binding to in the brainNational Academy of Sciences report on cannabis and cannabinoids Clinical trial showing CBD reduces seizures for treatment-resistant epilepsy Credits: This episode was produced by Kaitlyn Sawrey with help from Wendy Zukerman, along with Rose Rimler, Meryl Horn and Odelia Rubin.</description></item><item><title>Election Special: Immigration | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360177/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360177/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the final installment of our election series, we tackle immigration: the #1 concern of Americans as they head to the polls. It&amp;rsquo;s been a huge focus for President Trump&amp;hellip; and people say immigrants are stealing jobs and driving up the crime rate. But what does the research say? There have been a bunch of new studies since we published our episode on immigration, so we&amp;rsquo;ve updated this to reflect what&amp;rsquo;s new.</description></item><item><title>Election Special: Climate Change | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360178/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360178/</guid><description>Podcast Description Recently we&amp;rsquo;ve been warned that climate change is scarier than ever &amp;ndash; and that we are to blame. Yet surveys find around half of Americans don&amp;rsquo;t think climate change is caused by humans. So how does science know that? And how bad will climate change get? Science Vs has brought this episode up to date so you have the facts for next week&amp;rsquo;s midterm elections. Check out the transcript with all the citations, right here: http://bit.</description></item><item><title>Election Special: Abortion | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360179/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360179/</guid><description>Podcast Description The battle over abortion is fast becoming one of the key issues of the midterm election. And in this battle you’ll hear many things about abortion: that it’s painful for the fetus, and that late-term abortions are a huge issue. But what does the science say? If you want to read our transcript, with all the citations - check it out right here: http://bit.ly/2Bn9u1i Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Election Special: Gun Violence | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360180/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360180/</guid><description>Podcast Description After 11 people were shot and killed in a Pittsburgh synagogue over the weekend, mass shootings are back in the news. With the midterm elections happening next week, we&amp;rsquo;ve updated our episode on guns and are re-releasing it to give you the facts ahead of polling day. Heads up: this episode contains the sound of guns - and we’ll be discussing homicide, suicide and domestic violence. Please take care when listening to the show.</description></item><item><title>Online Dating: Can Science Find You Love? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360181/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 19:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Online dating can feel like drudgery… can science help you game the system? And do those matching algorithms actually work? To find out, we talked to psychologist Asst. Prof. Paul Eastwick, social psychologist Prof. Viren Swami, mathematician Asst. Prof. Hannah Fry, and Rose Reid. Check out the transcript right here: http://bit.ly/2E73qLH Selected references: Paul’s primer on speed dating experiments, and the Machine Learning studyThe study with the archaeology students on physical attractivenessHannah’s book, which includes more detailed Optimal Stopping Theory mathsA thorough review paper on online dating Credits: This episode was produced by Odelia Rubin, with help from Wendy Zukerman along with Rose Rimler, and Meryl Horn.</description></item><item><title>Murder Mystery: An 1850s Whodunnit | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360182/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 22:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360182/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s 1849, and a gruesome murder has just happened at Harvard. As body parts turn up, the science of the day is put to the ultimate test… to find out: who did it? We speak to Prof. Paul Collins, who tells us how this morbid mystery unfolds. Check out the transcript right here: http://bit.ly/2BntpNU Selected references: Paul Collins’ book, Blood And Ivy: The 1849 Murder That Scandalized Harvard The transcripts from the trial against John Webster Also check out our previous episodes on Forensic Science and DNA and the Smell of Death.</description></item><item><title>Gentrification: What's Really Happening? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360183/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360183/</guid><description>Podcast Description You’ve probably heard that gentrification changes neighborhoods for the worse: first come the hipsters and then the bankers. Soon, the neighborhood is overrun with dog spas and wine bars, and the original residents are nowhere in sight. But what does the science say? And, is there anything good about gentrification? We speak to Prof. Lance Freeman, Asst. Prof. Rachel Meltzer and Nicole Mader to find out. Check out the transcript right here: http://bit.</description></item><item><title>Soy, Almond, Oat Milks: Are They Udder Bull? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360184/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 16:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360184/</guid><description>Podcast Description Moooove over, dairy milk: the alternative milk craze is here. But are they more than just a frothy fad? To find out which is best for the planet, we speak to environmental researcher Joseph Poore. Check out the transcript right here: http://bit.ly/2P3H6c9 Selected references: Joseph’s study which has a comparison of soy and dairy milk, and his database which includes all his raw data and references Systematic review of greenhouse gases for different foods and drinks (see table 9 for milks)Lots of studies here on the water footprint of different crops and animal productsA report comparing the environmental impacts of almond, oat, rice, soy and dairy milksCredits: This episode was produced by Meryl Horn with help from Wendy Zukerman, along with Rose Rimler and Odelia Rubin.</description></item><item><title>Vegans: Are They Right? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360185/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 22:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360185/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do vegans have a right to be so smug? This week we find out whether it really is better for the environment, and our bodies, to go vegan. We speak to environmental researcher Joseph Poore, historian Prof. Connie Hilliard, anthropologist Prof. Katharine Milton, and nutrition researcher Prof. Roman Pawlak. Check out the transcript right here: http://bit.ly/2OeFye7 Selected references: Joseph’s study comparing 40,000 different farmsConnie’s paper comparing countries that consume more or less dairyA big review of calcium intake and fracture riskThis report on the influence of the dairy industryKatie’s paper on the evolution of meat-eatingRoman’s work rounding up studies on a vitamin deficiency Credits: This episode was produced by Rose Rimler with help from Wendy Zukerman, along with Meryl Horn and Odelia Rubin.</description></item><item><title>Essential Oils: Science or Snake Oil? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360186/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 22:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360186/</guid><description>Podcast Description Essential Oils - and their claims - are huge right now. But is it all hype, or is there something special about these little brown bottles? To get to the bottom of it, we dig through the studies and speak to cognitive neuroscientist Dr. Rachel Herz and psychologist Prof. Mark Moss. Check out the full transcript here: http://bit.ly/2PyEsKy Selected references: Rachel Herz’s books: Why You Eat What You Eat &amp;amp; The Scent of DesireA review of the benefits of peppermint tea and oil A critical review of the clinical trials Mark’s two studies showing that rosemary can enhance memoryThe experiment where lavender had different effects depending on what the people expected it to do Credits: This episode was produced by Meryl Horn, with help from Wendy Zukerman, Rose Rimler and Odelia Rubin.</description></item><item><title>Plastics: The Final Straw? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360187/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 21:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360187/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re back! This week we tackle the War on Straws and how worried we should be about all the plastic filling our oceans. We speak to marine biologist Christine Figgener, environmental educator Carrie Roble, physiology Prof. John Weinstein, and ecology Prof. David Barnes. Check out the full transcript here. Selected readings: The infamous turtle videoAn ambitious project that mapped the Great Pacific Garbage PatchThis paper that breaks down the sources and amount of plastic getting in the ocean John’s study on how fast microplastics formThis meta-analysis on microplastics, fish, and invertebratesA review of some of the chemicals in plastic and child health Credits: This episode was produced by Wendy Zukerman along with Rose Rimler, Meryl Horn and Odelia Rubin.</description></item><item><title>We Return... With A Twist. | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360188/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 17:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360188/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season Five of Science Vs will be in your ears next Thursday. This season we&amp;rsquo;re covering plastic straws, essential oils, veganism, ancient aliens and a lot of other topics that have got the internet hot and bothered. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Welcome, New Listeners! | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360189/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 20:34:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360189/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;ll be back in your ears with season 5 of Science Vs in the Fall&amp;hellip; but in the meantime, new listeners, here&amp;rsquo;s some episode recommendations to get you started. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Serial Killers: Science of the Lambs | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360190/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 21:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360190/</guid><description>Podcast Description What makes a serial killer? What drives them to kill again and again? To find out the truth about this ghastly lot, we talked to forensic psychologist Prof. Eric Hickey, criminologist Ass. Prof. Wayne Petherick, and psychiatrist Prof. Gwen Adshead. Check out the full transcript here: http://bit.ly/34aoJXG Note: in this episode we discuss homicide, and sexual violence. Please take care when listening to the show, and here are some resources: National Mental Health Helpline: 1-800-662-HELP (4357).</description></item><item><title>UFOs: What the Government Covered Up | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360191/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 23:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360191/</guid><description>Podcast Description Could aliens actually exist? Is there any chance they’ve visited Earth already? What really happened at Roswell? The truth&amp;hellip; is right here. We talked to astronomers Dr. Jill Tarter, Dr. Seth Shostak, investigative journalist David Clarke, and physicist Prof. Jim Al Khalili. Check out the full transcript here: http://bit.ly/2PqOHRj Selected readings: Seth’s account of that day in 1997The “Condon report”&amp;ndash; a 1968 effort to go through and identify all UFO sightingsThe Roswell ReportThis paper estimating how many planets are in the “Goldilocks” zoneA good read on wormholes and their history; a tough read on how we might use them to teleport Credits: This episode has been produced by our senior producer Kaitlyn Sawrey, as well as Wendy Zukerman and Rose Rimler, with help from Shruti Ravindran and Meryl Horn.</description></item><item><title>Lyme Disease: How Scary Is It? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360192/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 01:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360192/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, we’re entering the Lyme Wars. We’re asking: what is Lyme disease? How do you get it? How do you know you have it? And if you get infected, are you stuck with it forever? To find out we talk to neurologist Dr John Halperin, neuropsychology researcher Dr Kathleen Bechtold, and a Lyme patient we’re calling Emily. Check out the full transcript here: http://bit.ly/2DZhQxo Selected readings: About the culprits behind Lyme Disease The best summary on how well the Lyme tests workKathleen&amp;rsquo;s study about patients suffering from Post-Treatment Lyme Disease SyndromeA most helpful primer on Chronic LymeTwo controlled trials showing that long-term antibiotics use doesn’t help zap out lingering Lyme symptoms Credits: This episode has been produced by Shruti Ravindran, with help from Wendy Zukerman, along with Rose Rimler and Meryl Horn.</description></item><item><title>Circumcision: Why Are We Doing This? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360193/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 21:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360193/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, we’re entering the foreskin firestorm. We’re asking: what are the risks of circumcision? And are there any medical benefits? To find out we talk to pediatric urologist Andrew Freedman, HIV researcher Godfrey Kigozi, and sex researcher Caroline Pukall. Check out the full transcript here: http://bit.ly/38leLWD Selected readings: The American Academy of Pediatrics technical report, which Andrew helped writeA thoughtful opinion piece from AndrewThe trial in Uganda that Godfrey co-authoredCaroline’s team’s penis-poking studyAnother paper from Caroline’s team on how men feel about their circumcisions Credits: This episode has been produced by Rose Rimler, with help from Wendy Zukerman, along with Shruti Ravindran and Meryl Horn.</description></item><item><title>How Science Created Morons | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360194/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 21:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360194/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, how one of the worst ideas in science got a big push from a bad study… and intellectuals of the day lapped it up. We speak to science writer Carl Zimmer and Prof. J. David Smith, whose research helped get to the bottom of this disturbing story. UPDATE 05/25/18: This episode has been updated. A previous version said that the &amp;lsquo;good&amp;rsquo; side of the Kallikak family included someone who had signed the Declaration of Independence.</description></item><item><title>Polar Bears: A Surprising Tail | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360195/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 21:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360195/</guid><description>Podcast Description We have this idea that polar bears are teetering on the brink of extinction. But the story isn’t that simple. To find out why, we talk to environmental lawyer Kassie Siegel, wildlife biologist Dr. Karyn Rode, and sea ice expert Dr. Ignatius Rigor. With a little help from Payton, a polar bear at the Memphis Zoo. Check out the full transcript here: http://bit.ly/2qv9n1t Selected readings: This map of polar bear populations around the ArcticOn the Endangered Species Act and global warmingKaryn’s tale of two bear populationsThis paper on Arctic sea ice This episode was produced by Wendy Zukerman, senior producer Kaitlyn Sawrey, and Heather Rogers, will help from Rose Rimler, Shruti Ravindran, and Meryl Horn.</description></item><item><title>Scott Kelly: How A Year in Space Changes You | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360196/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 22:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360196/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, something different. We speak to astronaut Scott Kelly, who went up to space a man and came back a Rhesus monkey. Just kidding, that didn’t happen at all. Listen to find out the real story. PLUS: We talk to Lynn Levy, star producer of the Gimlet show The Habitat. Check out the full transcript here: http://bit.ly/2LEvaf7 Selected readings:NASA’s updated press release about Scott and MarkMore information about its Twins StudyA paper about what space does to your eyeballs This episode has been produced by Romilla Karnick, Wendy Zukerman, and senior producer Kaitlyn Sawrey, with help from Rose Rimler and Shruti Ravindran.</description></item><item><title>Ketogenic Diet... Is Fat Good For You? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360197/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 22:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360197/</guid><description>Podcast Description People who love the ketogenic diet swear it boosts their brainpower, melts their fat, and makes them better athletes. Is it true? To find out, we go keto. And, we talk to some scientists: neuroscientist Dom D’Agostino, medical researcher Eric Verdin, and nutritionist Louise Bourke. Also, Wendy’s mum drops in. Check out our full transcript here: http://bit.ly/355sUF7 Selected readings:This history of the ketogenic dietA pretty comprehensive reviewEric’s exploration of keto on the memories of miceLouise’s paper on keto and sports This episode has been produced by senior producer Kaitlyn Sawrey with help from Wendy Zukerman along with Rose Rimler, Shruti Ravindran and Romilla Karnick.</description></item><item><title>Nuclear War... Total Annihilation? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360198/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 23:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360198/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nine countries, including North Korea, have nuclear weapons. What would happen if a nuclear bomb was dropped&amp;ndash; say, in New York City? We talk to nuclear historian Dr. Alex Wellerstein, nuclear engineer Dr. Tetsuji Imanaka, and epidemiologist Dr. Eric Grant. UPDATE 04/27: We&amp;rsquo;ve adjusted this episode to correct the elevated risk of cancer in survivors of the Hiroshima and Nagasaki nuclear bombs. If you survived the atomic bombs your risk of cancer is 10% higher than someone who is the same age as you.</description></item><item><title>Sex Addiction: Are They Faking It? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360199/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 21:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360199/</guid><description>Podcast Description Harvey Weinstein and Kevin Spacey are said to have it. You probably have a friend who says they have it too. But is sex addiction the refuge of scoundrels? Or is it a real psychological problem? We speak to sex therapist Dr. David Ley, clinical psychologist Dr Shane Kraus, neuroscientist Dr. Nicole Prause, and someone we call Jeff. If you are experiencing troubles related to sex, you can look for support here.</description></item><item><title>Opioids: Kicking America's Addiction | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360200/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 22:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360200/</guid><description>Podcast Description America’s got an opioid problem. So where do we go from here? What can actually help people struggling with opioid addiction? We speak to Dr. Anna Lembke, Dr. Marvin Seppala, and a patient we call Mischa. UPDATE 04/17: We’ve adjusted a couple of lines of script in this episode to clarify the role of religion in Alcoholics Anonymous and Narcotics Anonymous. A previous version of this episode incorrectly implied that the 12 step philosophy considers addiction a sin and a “defect of character”.</description></item><item><title>Opioids: How America Got Hooked | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360201/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 00:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360201/</guid><description>Podcast Description More people in the U.S. died from opioids in 2016 than the peak year of the AIDS epidemic. So how did we get here? We speak to Prof. June Dahl, pain specialist Dr. David Tauben, and emergency physician Dr. Jeanmarie Perrone. If you or someone you love is struggling with an opioid addiction, in the US you can call the Substance Abuse and Mental Health Services Administration&amp;rsquo;s National Helpline: 1-800-662-HELP or visit their website.</description></item><item><title>Brand New Science Vs! | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360202/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 21:08:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360202/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;ll be in your ears with new episodes next week - Thursday March 22nd. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Obesity - Is It Your Fault? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360203/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 18:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360203/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’ve always been told to get off the couch and stop eating junk food if you want to lose weight - but is the obesity epidemic that simple? (Spoiler alert: it’s not.) We speak to geneticist Dr Giles Yeo, exercise physiology researcher Dr Lara Dugas, gastroenterologist Dr Jessica Allegretti, nutrition researcher Dr Pablo Monsivais and Italian radio maker Jonathan Zenti, Check out Jonathan’s podcast MEAT here. Check out the full transcript here: http://bit.</description></item><item><title>Chiropractors | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360204/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 18:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360204/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can they help with back pain or anything else? We talk to chiropractor Carl Cleveland III, physical therapist Anita Gross, neurophysiologist Dr. Marcello Costa&amp;hellip;and Kaity Sawrey’s parents. Check out our full transcript here: http://bit.ly/2P3g7NW By the way… Gimlet’s doing a holiday pop up shop selling t-shirts and stickers. So show your support by getting your very own Science Vs tee shirt! Check it out at sciencevs.show/shirt. Credits: This episode has been produced by Rose Rimler, Wendy Zukerman, with help from Shruti Ravindran and Heather Rogers.</description></item><item><title>Birth Control - The Biggest Myths | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360205/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 15:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360205/</guid><description>Podcast Description Everyone’s got a myth or two about birth control they want cleared up. Like&amp;hellip; is &amp;lsquo;pulling out&amp;rsquo; AKA withdrawal really such a bad idea? Does the pill change your brain? Are IUDs safe? And why isn’t there a pill for men, already?! We ask gynecologist Dr. Amita Murthy, neuroendocrinologist Dr. Nicole Petersen, men’s health researcher Prof. Robert McLachlan and a whole roomful of experts on sex &amp;ndash; teenagers. UPDATE 05/12/17: We have updated this episode to further emphasize that the pre-cum studies are only very small.</description></item><item><title>Molly - Scary Drug or Promising Therapy? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360206/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 16:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360206/</guid><description>Podcast Description Molly, Ecstasy, MDMA&amp;hellip; whatever you want to call it, it&amp;rsquo;s all the same thing. This week, we’re turning up the bass and checking out what does it do to your brain. Is it bad for you? Could it be a potential medicine? To find out, we talk to public health researcher Prof. Joseph Palamar, DEA special agent James Hunt, and neuroscientist Prof. Harriet de Witt. Check out the full transcript here: http://bit.</description></item><item><title>Balding - What Actually Works? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360207/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 17:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360207/</guid><description>Podcast Description So&amp;hellip; you’re losing your hair. Is there anything that can be done about it? And are the treatments dangerous &amp;ndash; for your or your penis? We talk to geneticist Prof. Stefanie Heilmann-Heimbach and dermatologists Dr. Wilma Bergfeld and Dr. Robert Bernstein. Check out the full transcript here: http://bit.ly/2Yvcrrm Extra reading:A review of balding treatmentsStefanie’s paper on balding geneticsThis research on the intersex population of the Dominican Republic Notes on hair transplants Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>The Bee-pocalypse | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360208/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 15:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360208/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is killing the bees? And will we have enough food to eat if the bee-pocalypse becomes worse? We speak to Dave Goulson, Professor of Biology and Bumblebee ecologist at the University of Sussex, Judy Wu-Smart, Research Entomologist at the University of Nebraska-Lincoln, and Steve Ellis, a beekeeper in Barrett, Minnesota. Check out the full transcript here: http://bit.ly/2YEm0oc Extra reading Judy Wu-Smart’s study on how neonicotinoid pesticides affect queen beesDave Goulson’s round-up of the parasites that plague beesA comprehensive laundry list of all the factors that make the world inhospitable to bees Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Vitamins &amp; Supplements - Are They Worth It? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360209/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 15:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360209/</guid><description>Podcast Description Americans spend billions of dollars on vitamins and supplements, but are they worth it? We look at the science behind some of the most popular supplements with nutritional epidemiologist Prof. Katherine Tucker, neuroscientist Dr. Simon Dyall, and medical researcher Dr. Mark Bolland. Our Sponsors: G Suite | WP Engine Credits: This episode has been produced by Wendy Zukerman, Heather Rogers, and Shruti Ravindran. Production assistance from Rose Rimler. Our senior producer is Kaitlyn Sawrey.</description></item><item><title>Bigfoot | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360210/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 15:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360210/</guid><description>Podcast Description All over the world people report sightings of big, hairy, human-like beasts, so could Bigfoot really be out there&amp;hellip; somewhere? We ask Dr. Jeff Meldrum, Prof. Bryan Sykes, Prof. Todd Disotell, and the Round Rock, Texas, Department of Parks and Recreation. CORRECTION: In a previous version of this podcast we said Dr Meldrum works at the University of Idaho. He actually works at Idaho State University. We&amp;rsquo;ve updated this episode with his correct title.</description></item><item><title>100% Renewable Energy - Can We Do It? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360211/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 20:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360211/</guid><description>Podcast Description We need to ditch fossil fuels. Can America go 100% renewable by 2050? Does the technology already exist? We speak to Prof. Mark Delucchi, Prof. Christopher Clack, and Prof. David Connolly. UPDATE: Since this episode was published, Tesla have unveiled a prototype of a electric semi truck. Check out the full transcript here: http://bit.ly/38ku2a4 Our Sponsors: Tushy | Wordpress.com | TuneIn Credits: This episode has been produced by Wendy Zukerman, Heather Rogers and Shruti Ravindran.</description></item><item><title>The Rise of Anti-Vaxxers | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360212/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 15:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360212/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last week we explored the science behind vaccine safety. This week we try to understand where these fears came from, and why they persist. We speak to three historians: Prof. Nadja Durbach, Prof. Elena Conis, and Prof. Robert Johnston. And a concerned mom named Noelle. Check out our full transcript here: http://bit.ly/355DlZz Our Sponsors: Cotton Inc + Madewell | Spotify | Sundance Now&amp;rsquo;s Riviera | Wordpress.com Credits: This episode has been produced by Heather Rogers, Wendy Zukerman, and Shruti Ravindran.</description></item><item><title>Vaccines - Are They Safe? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360213/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 15:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360213/</guid><description>Podcast Description Autism, seizures, and overloaded immune systems. Could these really be side effects of vaccines? This week, we dive into the science to find out how safe vaccines really are. We also talk to public health researchers Prof. Dan Salmon and Prof. Amy Kalkbrenner and neurologist Prof. Ingrid Scheffer. Check out our full transcript: http://bit.ly/2PrqtX3
Our Sponsors:Cole Haan | Google Cloud, Maker of GSuite | Ziprecruiter | WPEngine
Credits: This episode has been produced by Heather Rogers, Wendy Zukerman, and Shruti Ravindran.</description></item><item><title>Detoxing &amp; Cleanses - Do They Work? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360214/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 14:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360214/</guid><description>Podcast Description Juice cleanses, fancy foods, sweat, charcoal, and colonics&amp;ndash; is there a scientifically proven way to ‘clean out’ your system? This week, we dig in deep to the science of detox and turn ourselves into guinea pigs for a juicing experiment. We talk to a passionate proctologist named Prof. Graham Newstead, as well as nutrition researcher Prof. Stella Volpe and toxicologist Dr. Susanne Ramm. Check out the full transcript here: http://bit.</description></item><item><title>New Season... Coming Soon! | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360215/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360215/</guid><description>Podcast Description Science Vs is back in your ears next week! This season we&amp;rsquo;re going to dissect the science behind detox diets, the safety of vaccines and whether America can run on 100% renewable energy. We also figure out whether vitamins and supplements are a waste of your money, why the bees are dying and where the heck the Male Pill is at?! Go to sciencevs.show/fall to check out Wendy&amp;rsquo;s favourite episodes of other Gimlet shows coming back this Fall.</description></item><item><title>Artificial Sweeteners - not so sweet? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360216/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2017 21:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360216/</guid><description>Podcast Description Low calorie, no calorie and so sweet. Artificial sweeteners just seem too good to be true. Is there a catch? We dig into two big questions: Do artificial sweeteners cause cancer, and are they making us fat? We talk to Prof. John Glendinning, Prof. Susie Swithers, Dr. Kieron Rooney, and PhD student Jotham Suez about the latest research. Plus we do a fun experiment with PJ Vogt and Alex Goldman from Reply All!</description></item><item><title>Nuclear Power - what are the Risks? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360217/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360217/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fukushima. Chernobyl. Three Mile Island. There’s been some big nuclear accidents over the past few decades, but how dangerous is nuclear power really? We take you inside the core of America’s biggest nuclear power plant and trace what went wrong at Fukushima to try to figure out: when will the next meltdown happen? And what our chances are of getting cancer from it? This week we talk to Dr.</description></item><item><title>Meditation | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360218/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 15:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360218/</guid><description>Podcast Description Silicon Valley CEOs, Tibetan monks, and crunchy hippies alike describe meditation as blissful and life-changing, but what does the science say? Can it reduce stress, increase your attention, and improve mental health &amp;ndash; or is all this focus on breathing just a bunch of hot air? Sit back, get comfortable, and focus your mind as we talk to Tim Ferriss, Professor Gaelle Desbordes, Dr. Clifford Saron, and Dr. Britta Hölzel.</description></item><item><title>True Love | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360219/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2017 15:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360219/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is love? With half of first time American marriages ending in divorce by the 20th anniversary, and infidelity being widespread, Science Vs asks: have we been lied to by our love songs? On today’s episode we explore: What happens to the brain when we fall in love? Is the compulsion to stay together biological? And, is monogamy really unnatural? We talk to Dr. Helen Fisher, Professor Larry Young, and Dr.</description></item><item><title>Antioxidants | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360220/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360220/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are chocolate, coffee and red wine actually good for us? Reading the news it seems that one day they are helping us live longer, and the next day they are giving us heart attacks. So what’s going on here? Host Wendy Zukerman and DJ/senior producer Kaitlyn Sawrey explore the science live on stage, with interview clips from Prof. Bruce Ames, Prof. David Sinclair and author Aidan Goggins. This show was recorded live at The Bell House on Thursday, March 23rd, 2017.</description></item><item><title>Abortion: What You Need To Know | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360221/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 15:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360221/</guid><description>Podcast Description Abortion is so taboo. People don’t talk about abortions they’ve had. Doctors don’t talk about abortions they’ve given. But it&amp;rsquo;s happening a lot. Almost a million abortions happened in the US in 2014. So, what actually happens in an abortion, can the fetus feel pain and what are the risks? To find out we visit an abortion clinic in Texas and talk to Dr. Amita Murthy, Dr. Lisa Harris, Dr.</description></item><item><title>GMO... OMG? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360222/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 21:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360222/</guid><description>Podcast Description Science Vs peels back the label on GM foods to find out whether they’re safe to eat and what impact they can have on the environment. Both sides of the debate have written impassioned songs, but what does the science say? We talk to Prof. Fred Gould, Dr. Janet Cotter, and Prof. David Douches to find out. Please note this episode has been updated. In the original version we suggested that the Bt corn that killed monarch caterpillars was taken off the market as a direct result of studies demonstrating its harm.</description></item><item><title>Lemmings | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360223/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2017 15:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360223/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why do four out of five dentists recommend Colgate? How many Americans really approve of Trump? This special episode is a two-parter: First, we talk to Prof. Dan Levitin, author of ‘Weaponized Lies: How to Think Critically in the Post-Truth Era’, about some recent news stories and how to be skeptical of the statistics you see. Then, we bring you a surprise you won’t want to miss. It’s about deception, murder, and of course, ~science~.</description></item><item><title>Ghosts | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360224/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2017 15:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360224/</guid><description>Podcast Description One third of Americans believe in ghosts, and one fifth have had a personal encounter. We go to a haunted house with some paranormal investigators and things get spooky. But, scientists aren’t scared - they have a range of explanations for why so many people encounter ghosts. We speak to Dr. Katie Mack, Baland Jalal, Dr. Shane Rogers, and Prof. Chris French and find out what ghosts are all about.</description></item><item><title>Climate Change... the Apocalypse? | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360225/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2017 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360225/</guid><description>Podcast Description Less than half of Americans think climate change is caused by humans, but scientists are sure about it. So, how do they know that humans are to blame? We also look into the climate change crystal ball to figure out are we doomed? Is the apocalypse nigh? We speak to Prof. Ralph Keeling, Prof. Chris Field, and Dr. David Pierce to find out. UPDATE 12/10/20: An earlier version of this episode incorrectly said that Svante Arrhenius came up with the idea that rising carbon dioxide levels could warm the planet.</description></item><item><title>Acne | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360226/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360226/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trying to get rid of acne can feel like a science experiment with your face &amp;ndash; so we get to the bottom of what works and what doesn’t. We investigate the role of diet, stress and hygiene, and meet internet celebrity Dr Sandra Lee aka Dr Pimple Popper. We also speak to dermatologist Dr. Jonathan Weiss, MD and Prof. Huiying Li, PhD. Science Vs Live! Come see our live show on the science behind red wine, coffee and chocolate - could our favorite treats actually be good for us?</description></item><item><title>Immigration | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360227/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360227/</guid><description>Podcast Description We head to a farm in Alabama to find out what happened after thousands of immigrants left the state. Did it create more jobs for Americans and what happened to the crime rate? We speak to economists Prof. Samuel Addy, Prof. Jennifer Hunt, and Prof. Brian Bell to find out. Science Vs Live! Come see our live show on the science behind red wine, coffee and chocolate - could our favorite treats actually be good for us?</description></item><item><title>New season... coming soon! | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360228/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 17:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360228/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’ve read the studies. We’ve spoken to the experts. And now it’s time for facts. There is no alternative. The new season of Science Vs will be out March 9th. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Antidepressants | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360229/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 05:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360229/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s an intriguing body of research that suggests the power of antidepressants doesn’t come from chemicals in the drugs, but from the power of placebo. Not everyone agrees, though. We speak to researchers and medical professionals on either side of the debate, and some wedged in-between &amp;ndash; Prof. Peter Kramer, psychiatrist and author of Ordinarily Well: the Case for Antidepressants; Prof. Irving Kirsch, psychologist and author of The Emperor’s New Drugs: Exploding the Antidepressant Myth; psychiatrist and radiologist Prof.</description></item><item><title>DNA and the Smell of Death | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360230/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 02:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360230/</guid><description>Podcast Description In these cases, emerging DNA evidence and the smell of death (yes, really) pushed the boundaries of what was technologically possible. But how reliable are they? To find out, we go to a body farm and talk to Assoc. Prof. Joan Bytheway, Asst. Prof. Sheree Hughes-Stamm, Matt Young, Dr. Arpad Vass, and Asst. Prof. Donovan Haines. Our Sponsors Lenovo – See how Lenovo is revolutionizing data center technology. Modcloth - Enter promo code SCIENCEVS at checkout to get $20 off an order of $100 or more!</description></item><item><title>Forensic Science | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360231/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 06:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360231/</guid><description>Podcast Description There are a slew of scientific techniques that forensic experts use to solve crimes. But how reliable are they? We’re putting forensic evidence under the microscope. To help us crack the case, we talk to Assoc. Prof. Sibyl Bucheli, attorney Chris Fabricant, former crime lab director Barry Fisher, Dr. Itiel Dror, and Assoc. Prof. Patrick Buzzini. Our Sponsors Hello Fresh – To get $35 off your first week of deliveries visit hellofresh.</description></item><item><title>Zika | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360232/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 05:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360232/</guid><description>Podcast Description Since 2015 there have been Zika outbreaks reported in sixty countries. So, where did Zika come from? What happens when you get infected? How worried should you be?And why has Zika has become such a problem recently? To find out, we speak to Assoc. Prof. Desiree LaBeaud, Dr Cathy Spong, Dr Andrew Haddow, and New York Times health reporter Donald McNeil Jr. Credits This episode has been produced by Diane Wu, Wendy Zukerman, Heather Rogers, Caitlin Kenney, and Shruti Ravindran.</description></item><item><title>Hypnosis | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360233/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 02:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360233/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, we explore the science of hypnosis, and take Science Vs to the edge of consciousness. In the service of journalism, Wendy tries to get hypnotized at a comedy club and in a doctor’s office. We talk to comedian Jim Spinnato, Prof. Philip Muskin, Prof. Amanda Barnier, and Prof. Amir Raz. Credits: This episode has been produced by Heather Rogers, Wendy Zukerman, Caitlin Kenney, Austin Mitchell, Dr. Diane Wu, and Shruti Ravindran.</description></item><item><title>The G-spot | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360234/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2016 02:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360234/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join us on a hunt for the elusive G-spot. Our guides: Prof. Beverly Whipple, who introduced America to the G-spot in the 1980s, and Prof. Helen O’Connell, a urologist and expert on female sexual anatomy. CreditsThis episode has been produced by Wendy Zukerman, Heather Rogers, Caitlin Kenney, Austin Mitchell, and Kaitlyn Sawrey. Edited by Annie-Rose Strasser and Alex Blumberg. Fact Checking by Michelle Harris.Production Assistance by Dr Diane Wu &amp;amp; Shruti Ravindran.</description></item><item><title>Organic Food | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360235/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 00:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360235/</guid><description>Podcast Description People are going bonkers for organic, but what are you really getting when you buy them? Better taste? Fewer toxic chemicals? A cleaner environment? Farmers Mark, Andy, and Brian Reeves, nutritional epidemiologist Dr. Kathryn Bradbury, Ass. Prof. Cynthia Curl, and Prof. Navin Ramankutty help us sort it all out. Credits: This episode has been produced by Wendy Zukerman, Heather Rogers, Lynn Levy, Caitlin Kenney, Austin Mitchell, and Kaitlyn Sawrey.</description></item><item><title>Gun Control (Pt 2) | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360236/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2016 01:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360236/</guid><description>Podcast Description In last week’s episode, we learned that around 30,000 Americans die each year from guns. This week, we examine possible solutions. Do better background checks, buybacks, and gun registration lead to fewer shooting deaths? What happened in Australia after they got rid of all the guns? To find out, we talk to gun shop owner Bob Kostaras, former ATF special agent Mark Jones, Prof. Philip Alpers, and Prof. Peter Squires.</description></item><item><title>Guns | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360237/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2016 20:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360237/</guid><description>Podcast Description We find out how many times a year guns are used in self-defense, how many times they’re used to murder someone, and what impact guns have on the crime rate. In this episode we speak with Prof. David Hemenway, Prof. Helen Christensen, Prof. Gary Kleck and New Jersey gun-range owner Anthony Colandro. Credits: This episode has been produced by Wendy Zukerman, Caitlin Kenney, Heather Rogers and Kaitlyn Sawrey. Edited by Annie Rose Strasser and Alex Blumberg.</description></item><item><title>Attachment Parenting | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360238/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2016 02:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360238/</guid><description>Podcast Description Judy, a mother of two young kids, practices a demanding style of child-rearing. It’s called attachment parenting, and it says you should keep your baby close at all times, breastfeed on demand, share your bed, and avoid strollers. Like many attachment parents, Judy believes the sacrifices she makes will ensure her kids will become well-adjusted, successful, happy adults. But, what does the science say? To find out, Science Vs speaks to Prof.</description></item><item><title>Fracking | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360239/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2016 22:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360239/</guid><description>Podcast Description We often hear stories about fracking that go like this: a gas company comes to a small town, starts drilling wells, and then terrible things start to happen. People get sick. Water burns from taps. Earthquakes ruin houses. And the climate will soon be destroyed. But, is fracking really a disaster unfolding? To find out, Science Vs speaks to Prof. Robert Jackson, Asst. Prof. Peter Rabinowitz and Prof. Bob Howarth.</description></item><item><title>Sneak Peek | Science Vs</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3349360240/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 16:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3349360240/</guid><description>Podcast Description There are a lot of fads, a lot of strong opinions and a lot of blogs, but then there’s SCIENCE. Science Vs is the new show from Gimlet Media that finds out what’s fact, what’s not, and what’s somewhere in between. We do the hard work of sifting through all the science so you don&amp;rsquo;t have to. This season we&amp;rsquo;ll be tackling organic food, fracking, gun control, and the G spot.</description></item></channel></rss>