<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Call Her Daddy on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/call-her-daddy/</link><description>Recent content in Call Her Daddy on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/call-her-daddy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Lautners: Team Taylor [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490317/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490317/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Join Alex in the studio for a cozy interview with Tay and Taylor Lautner. The couple discusses what it’s like to share the same name and reveals that we’ve actually been pronouncing ‘Lautner’ wrong this whole time. Taylor reminisces on his Twilight years and how overnight fame totally changed his life. He gets real about body image issues, the impact of the Team Jacob v Team Edward rivalry, and how he almost wasn’t even in the movies at all!</description></item><item><title>Am I Lame if I Don’t Want to Go Out Anymore? [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490316/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490316/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Join Father Cooper for a much needed Sunday catch-up ahead of the holidays. Alex recaps her Thanksgiving, how she got subtle baby fever, and why stuffing should be a year-round dish. She also reminds everyone that the holidays can be tough and gives her advice on how to handle complicated family dynamics. Alex then talks about her current work grind and mission to lock down a consistent work-out routine before answering some questions of the week!</description></item><item><title>Paris Hilton: Sex Symbol, Slut Shaming &amp; Sliving [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490312/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490312/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Paris Hilton on Call Her Daddy? That’s hot. Join Alex as she goes to Paris Hilton’s house for a sit-down interview. Paris reminisces on some of her most memorable 2000’s moments and what dating was like in her early twenties (hint: you were probably ghosted or blacklisted from every club). She also tells the story behind that iconic photo of her, Lindsay Lohan, and Britney Spears and talks about her long-term friendship with Kim Kardashian.</description></item><item><title>Kelsea Ballerini: Love Yourself Enough to Start Over [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490313/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490313/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Join Alex in Nashville as she reunites with Kelsea Ballerini for an overdue catch up. From opening up about struggling to break through in a male dominated industry, to rediscovering herself and her happiness post divorce, Kelsea is here to show what it truly means to choose yourself. She shares cute insights from her relationship with boyfriend Chase Stokes and dispels any rumors of jealousy. Get ready to spend a day in Nashville with Alex and Kelsea.</description></item><item><title>Jack Harlow: I’m *Not* Vanilla Baby [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490314/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490314/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Join Alex in the studio for a sit-down interview with Jack Harlow. Jack reminisces on his childhood in Louisville and why his hometown is so important to him. He also tells some hilarious stories from his teenage years like relying on girls to pass exams, how the Harry Potter books turned him on, and how he lost his virginity. Jack clarifies what he thinks “vanilla sex” is and even gives some insight into what he personally likes in the bedroom.</description></item><item><title>My Mom Found My Nudes [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490315/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490315/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Join Father Cooper for a solo vlog style episode this week. Alex sits down to give the Daddy Gang a much needed life update as she’s been out on the road traveling for the Unwell Tour and was on a guest on The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon. She shares the hilarious story behind her absolutely tragic passport photo and the great lengths she’s gone to hide it from every man in her life.</description></item><item><title>Holly &amp; Bridget: Controlling Men 101 [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490001/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Join Alex in the studio for a sit-down interview with former Girls Next Door stars, Holly Madison and Bridget Marquardt. Holly and Bridget shine a light on the darker side of Playboy and detail some of the most shocking experiences they had during their time in the Mansion. They talk about reclaiming their voices and autonomy after years of being controlled by Hugh Hefner. Holly and Bridget get real and tell the Daddy Gang what signs to look out for and how to know when a relationship has turned toxic and controlling.</description></item><item><title>How to Deal with Mean Girls [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490002/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490002/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Join Father Cooper for a Sunday Session where she answers all kinds of questions from the Daddy Gang. Alex breaks down whether or not you should ask your fiance if they cheated on you before the engagement or let it ride. She also gives her honest take on “once a cheater, always a cheater” and begs the Daddy Gang to stop romanticizing unhealthy relationships. In this episode, Alex also talks about friendships - when to cut out surface level friends, how she has personally seen her own friendships evolve over the years, how to handle when your partner’s friends have an attitude, and how to deal with a mean girl.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Hale: Sober Doesn't Mean Boring [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490003/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Join Alex in the studio for a powerful sit-down interview with Lucy Hale. Lucy opens up about the struggles she was facing behind the scenes and reveals the absolute rock bottom moment that led to her getting sober. She reflects on how drinking negatively impacted both her friendships and romantic relationships. Lucy tells Alex about what life looks like sober and how she’s been navigating dating and sex without alcohol.</description></item><item><title>Prepare for Tour with Me [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490004/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490004/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Join Father Cooper for a Sunday session as she prepares for her first ever live tour. Alex shares some life updates, takes you behind the scenes on the rehearsal process and laughs about her current mental state (she&amp;rsquo;s a little unwell). Enjoy! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Toxic Bootcamp [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490005/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Join Alex for a solo episode as she takes us all to Toxic Bootcamp. Alex gives the hard truth about why we stay in relationships that no longer serve us and hits us with the wake up call we need to get out of them! She reflects on why she was attracted to toxic in college and why she doesn’t regret going hard in the games. Alex also debunks all the common excuses we make for staying in relationships.</description></item><item><title>The Making Of The Offset Episode [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490006/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490006/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) We’re so glad you’re loving the Offset interview! And now we’re bringing you behind the scenes. Daddy Gang, get ready for a chaotic morning in the dadpad full of pizza, baby powder, jealousy, and… Alex getting high? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Offset: Blowjobs, Marriage &amp; Music [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490007/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Join Alex in the studio for a sit-down interview with Offset. Offset opens up about his childhood, his rise to fame with Migos, and tells Alex all about his career “I made it” moment that happened from jail. He shares a hilarious story about a crazy experience with an ex and gets deep about his relationship and love for his wife, Cardi B. Offset also brings the advice we didn’t know we needed!</description></item><item><title>Bella Poarch: My Secret Marriage &amp; Divorce [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490008/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Join Alex in the studio for a powerful sit-down interview with Bella Poarch. In this episode, Bella opens up about her difficult childhood and for the first time ever, she speaks about the traumatic event that happened to her during her time in the Navy. She finally opens about her secret marriage and gets real about why the marriage ultimately had to end. Daddy Gang, this episode is an inspiring story of strength and resilience.</description></item><item><title>The 5 Year Anniversary of CHD [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490009/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490009/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Join Father Cooper to celebrate the 5 year anniversary of Call Her Daddy. Alex takes us back to the moment she first decided to create Call Her Daddy and reflects on the business lessons she learned early on in her career. She speaks about her relationship with the Daddy Gang and her first ever Daddy Gang interaction. She reminisces on the trouble exploiting her dating life would sometimes cause and tells a hilarious story involving the podcast, Slim Shady and The Canadian.</description></item><item><title>Ciara: Don’t Let Him Waste Your Time [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490010/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Join Alex in the studio for a chat with Grammy-award winner, Ciara! Ciara reflects on some of her most iconic moments throughout her career and discusses hard lessons learned after nearly two decades in the industry. In this episode, Alex and Ciara discuss what it takes to leave a toxic relationship, what she now recognizes as red flags, and why you should always choose yourself first. Ciara gushes over her husband, Russell Wilson, and reminisces on their love story.</description></item><item><title>Madeline Argy Debrief: Toxic Relationships [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490011/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490011/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Come join Father Cooper for a debrief of the Madeline Argy episode. She discusses the behind the scenes process of creating this episode with Madeline and reveals this was actually not their first time podcasting together. Alex shares footage from their original sit-down interview that includes a cheating story from one of Madeline’s toxic exes, a boundary crossing ex best friend and a more serious chat about anxiety.</description></item><item><title>Madeline Argy: My Breakup Story [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490012/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Join Alex and Madeline Argy in NYC for a hilarious and chaotic 48-hour adventure. For the first time ever, Madeline opens up about her recent break-up with a very well-known ex and reveals why she had no choice but to end the relationship. Madeline also discusses her childhood: repairing broken family relationships, navigating her mother’s disability, and overcoming years of bullying. And of course, it wouldn’t be Madeline Argy without some insane stories.</description></item><item><title>The Making of the Alix Earle Episode [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490013/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490013/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Join Father Cooper on an exclusive behind-the-scenes journey into the making of the season four premiere. In this Sunday Session, Alex reveals all of the hilarious mishaps that took place during recording. She talks about the week-long process of shooting this episode while also helping Alix prepare for the launch of her own podcast, Hot Mess. This Sunday Session has it all… unreleased footage, outtakes, and even a few mental breakdowns.</description></item><item><title>Alix Earle: Secrets, Sex &amp; Scandals [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490014/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Daddy gang, get ready for the season 4 premiere of Call Her Daddy with the Internet’s biggest “It Girl,” Alix Earle. Travel to New Jersey to meet Alix’s entire family and step inside her home to experience the chaos up close. For the first time, Alix opens up about the years of embarrassment and bullying after a public scandal tore her family apart. She addresses the rumors head-on regarding a certain NFL player and her alleged role as a homewrecker.</description></item><item><title>Adam Devine: Medium Dick Energy (Revisit) [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490015/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Adam Devine is here to set the record straight - he and his wife are doing amazing. He is categorically not the Adam who cheated with women he met on instagram. Adam joins Call Her Daddy to serve the Medium Dick Energy we all need, giving us a hilarious take on what it was like to grow up in Nebraska. He performs the song he used in his Pitch Perfect audition, and it’s not what you would expect.</description></item><item><title>Birthday Sex &amp; Strip Clubs [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490016/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Daddy Gang, get comfy as we wrap up Season 3 with a solo episode featuring Father Cooper. Big Al spills the tea on her extravagant week-long birthday celebration in Miami, complete with all of the stories from her trip to the strip club. But that&amp;rsquo;s not all—she gives all the details of how her birthday sex took an unexpected turn, involving acrobatics and concussions. Despite her own chaotic life, Alex is here with some fatherly advice.</description></item><item><title>Kristin Cavallari: So You Want to Date an Athlete? (Revisit) [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490017/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) This week, Call Her Daddy is on a break, so we&amp;rsquo;re revisiting a classic episode - Father Cooper&amp;rsquo;s sit down with Kristin Cavallari. Can you imagine being in high school and having grown men with cameras following you around to stir up drama? Kristin can - and she reflects on those Laguna Beach days and explains why MTV should now be paying for the entire cast’s therapy.</description></item><item><title>My Wedding Planning Disaster [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490018/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Step into the chaos that is Alex&amp;rsquo;s wedding planning saga. She fully details her struggle to lock down a wedding location (hint: So far it has changed 7 times). Daddy Gang, you’ve asked and Alex is answering. Bridesmaids or no bridesmaids? Is she going big or keeping it low-key? Alex is taking a very non-traditional approach to her wedding and has the shocking revelation that she will be walking herself down the aisle, and her reasoning may not be what you&amp;rsquo;d expect.</description></item><item><title>"Your Fiancé Should Be Ashamed" [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490019/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490019/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) The most recent episode of Call Her Daddy sparked some controversy and Alex is here to address it. Is it disrespectful to your partner to speak about previous hookups and sexual experiences? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Exposing My Athlete Roster (Boston Edition) [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490020/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Join Alex as she returns to her college town of Boston and enters a full state of regression as the memories from her athletes past flood in. A failed date with a Patriots player? An NHL player with the largest curved penis known to man? Alex is here with her BFF Laren to spill all of the hilarious stories from her college days in Boston. These two don&amp;rsquo;t hold back – they share their own Boston shenanigans, including a trip to Planned Parenthood and Alex&amp;rsquo;s not-so-fun encounter with chlamydia.</description></item><item><title>Janelle Monáe: We Should Thank Our Exes [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490021/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Janelle Monáe joins Call Her Daddy to discuss her personal evolution and the work required to reach her own age of pleasure. Addressing past rejection and trauma from her father&amp;rsquo;s instability, she opens up about how these struggles impacted her personal relationships and how she found herself closed off to love. Janelle and Alex reflect on lessons learned from failed relationships and share why we should actually be going back and thanking our exes.</description></item><item><title>Confronting a Controlling Boyfriend | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490022/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Sunday Session, Big Al comes at you a little hungover after celebrating her anniversary with her fiancé. She takes you on a journey through the hilarious confusion of not knowing when their actual anniversary is and how they finally settled on a day to celebrate. Opening up, Alex gets personal about some difficult challenges she&amp;rsquo;s been going through in her life recently. Responding to a listener question, she discusses the importance of letting go of shame associated with having a high body count, encouraging Daddy Gang to accept and embrace their past without judgment.</description></item><item><title>The Post Malone Experience [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490023/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Join Alex as she travels to Boston to attend the Post Malone concert, sit down for an interview and get her ass kicked in beer pong. Post opens up about his childhood and how the bullying he endured has shaped his commitment to living a life of kindness. He offers a glimpse into his notoriously private life and opens up about his biggest insecurities and his fears when it comes to parenting.</description></item><item><title>Stuck in a Situationship | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490024/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Father Cooper is here with a Sunday session. Alex kicks things off with a much-awaited life update, sharing stories from her summer travels and dishing on the behind the scenes of the Zayn Malik interview. Big Al is dishing out advice, tackling the topic of &amp;ldquo;situationships&amp;rdquo; and how to break free from their grip. She also discusses what it means when someone lies about deleting your nudes and how you may unknowingly take on toxic habits when in an unhealthy relationship.</description></item><item><title>Coi Leray: Girls Is Players Too [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490025/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Coi Leray joins Call Her Daddy and opens up about her journey in the music industry, overcoming body shaming, and defying stereotypes in hip hop. She shares how she embraces self love (through some masturbation) and channels her sex appeal unapologetically. Coi talks about dating with a straightforward attitude and hilariously walks us through when someone deserves to be blocked. Alex and Coi discuss why they both believe in not taking back a cheater and point out that once someone has shown you their true colors, there’s no going back.</description></item><item><title>Harry Jowsey: From Fuckboy to Marriage Material [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490026/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Harry Jowsey makes his return to Call Her Daddy and he doesn&amp;rsquo;t hold back. He spills the tea on his dating life and reveals that his previous relationship ended due to cheating. He shares his new approach to dating aka Harry is hunting for a wife. Harry proudly declares that he&amp;rsquo;s currently in his &amp;ldquo;dad era,&amp;rdquo; which includes eating ass, sucking toes and many other wild sexual adventures.</description></item><item><title>Zayn: For the First Time in 6 Years [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490027/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490027/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Multi-platinum recording artist Zayn joins Call Her Daddy for his first sit-down interview in nearly 6 years. From Alex&amp;rsquo;s childhood home in Pennsylvania, he opens up about his surprisingly quiet life in PA, his pre-fame days, his X Factor audition, his reflections on his time with One Direction, and his decision to leave the group. Zayn also discusses the impact of fame on his mental health, proudly sharing his experiences as a father and how it has shifted his priorities.</description></item><item><title>Kim Petras: The Throat Goat [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490028/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Kim Petras joins Call Her Daddy for a completely unfiltered interview. Kim speaks about her career&amp;rsquo;s evolution, starting from her wild days in the gay clubs to her recent Grammy win. She reflects on how music became an outlet for her and shares her experiences navigating her identity as a transgender artist. Kim opens up about her dating life and the two burst into laughter when they realize they have the same celebrity crush.</description></item><item><title>How Does Patriarchy Affect Me? | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490029/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Naomi Snider joins Call Her Daddy to break down the never-ending question: Why does patriarchy still exist? Naomi and Alex dive into what patriarchy actually means and give examples of how it affects our everyday lives and relationships. Naomi explains why women are constantly pitted against each other and how we&amp;rsquo;re taught to blame each other instead of the messed-up system as a whole. Naomi and Alex talk about how beauty standards have changed over time and why we need to stop blaming individual women for playing the game.</description></item><item><title>Navigating Finances in a Relationship | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490030/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490030/</guid><description>Podcast Description What’s one of the most uncomfortable topics to discuss in a relationship? Money. Thankfully Mrs. Dow Jones is here to give us the tools to better discuss finances in our romantic relationships and to overall make smarter decisions with our money. She talks about joint bank accounts, moving in together, splitting expenses, differing spending habits, and more.If you&amp;rsquo;re struggling to bring up money with your partner or feeling like you&amp;rsquo;re not on the same page financially, Mrs.</description></item><item><title>Stassi Schroeder: A Proud Basic Bitch [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490031/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490031/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Get ready for an outrageously good time as Stassi Schroeder joins Call Her Daddy. Once Alex and Stassi start talking, there&amp;rsquo;s no shutting them up. When discussing her outfit of the day for the interview, she confesses to once splurging 40k on a national OOTD holiday. Settling some debates, Stassi shares her take on various trends, determining whether they are basic or not. Aperol Spritzes? GRWM videos?</description></item><item><title>Understanding the Baggage I Bring to My Relationship [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490032/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490032/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Join Alex and Lauren as they dive deep into their personal journeys and unpack the emotional baggage they brought into their current romantic relationships. Alex opens up about how her desire for independence unintentionally created distance between her and her partner, while Lauren discusses her previous approach to conflict and how it hindered her relationship. They explore the importance of compromise and the ongoing effort required for a healthy partnership.</description></item><item><title>Stop Having Average Sex (ft. Laren &amp; John Mayer) [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490033/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490033/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Join Alex as she travels to Chicago to attend the John Mayer concert with her BFF Laren. The girls sit down to podcast and Laren spills the tea on her new boyfriend. Things take a wild turn as Alex leads the Daddy Gang on a bar crawl through Chicago, making some questionable choices along the way. Alex and Laren share some hilarious moments like relationship fights in bed and Alex&amp;rsquo;s current sexual fantasy.</description></item><item><title>It’s Time to Manage Your Finances | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490034/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you the person who never checks their bank account and prefers to live in the dark? Do you Uber everywhere and order Postmates for every meal? Haley Sacks (aka Mrs. Dow Jones) is the zillenial finance queen and she’s here to give us the basic tips we all should know but were never taught. Dow Jones breaks down how you should be spending each paycheck and thankfully it does not involve budgeting item by item.</description></item><item><title>Shay Mitchell: Let Him Go, You Deserve Better [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490035/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490035/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Shay Mitchell joins Call Her Daddy to discuss her journey to loving herself and knowing her worth. Reminisce with her on the Single Shay era as she spills the tea on her dating life and the valuable lessons she learned along the way. Shay’s insight will have you wanting to leave all of your toxic relationships in the past. Shay opens up about her relationship with her partner Matte, the dynamic of their relationship and how they establish trust while he’s on the road touring with Drake.</description></item><item><title>The Making of the Ariana Madix Episode [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490036/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490036/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Join Alex on an exclusive behind-the-scenes journey into the making of the Ariana Madix episode on Call Her Daddy. In this solo Sunday episode Alex pulls back the curtain on her process from writing the interview to meeting Ariana for the first time. Be sure to WATCH this episode, not just listen, to follow along and get the entire experience. Enjoy!Call Her Daddy apparel is here. Shop at ⁠⁠⁠⁠⁠⁠shop.</description></item><item><title>Ariana Madix: The Vanderpump Affair [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490037/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490037/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Prepare for an explosive episode of Call Her Daddy as Ariana Madix exposes the shocking affair that unfolded between her boyfriend of nine years and one of her closest friends. Ariana takes us through the heart-wrenching night she discovered the betrayal, revealing new details that will leave you speechless. Ariana confronts the rumors head-on. Uncover the origins of the open relationship speculation and learn whether she turned a blind eye or fought to salvage the relationship.</description></item><item><title>Dealing With Body Image Insecurities [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490038/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490038/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Father Cooper is here with a solo Sunday episode. Alex takes us on her personal journey as she strives to implement new habits in her life. She&amp;rsquo;s breaking free from the grips of her phone addiction and urging the Daddy Gang to join her in a digital detox. When was the last time you went a whole day without checking social media? When was the last time you watched a movie without reaching for your phone?</description></item><item><title>Anitta: Secretos Para un Buen Sexo, Twerking y Mamadas (Spanish Subtitles) [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490040/</guid><description>Podcast Description (PODCAST DE VÍDEO) ¡Prepárate para subir la temperatura con Anitta en Call Her Daddy! La superestrella brasileña del pop se une al programa para darnos los consejos sexuales que todos ansiamos. Anitta reflexiona sobre el auge de su carrera y nos cuenta cómo alcanzó la fama internacional. También demuestra sus increíbles dotes para el twerking y habla de cómo sus movimientos se trasladan al dormitorio. Anitta se sincera sobre lo que le atrae de una persona y nos cuenta lo que no le gusta a la hora de salir con alguien.</description></item><item><title>Anitta: Secrets to Great Sex, Twerking, and Blow Jobs [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490041/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490041/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Get ready to turn up the heat with Anitta on Call Her Daddy! The Brazilian pop superstar joins the show to give the sex advice we&amp;rsquo;ve all been craving. Anitta reflects on the rise of her career and shares how she achieved such international fame. She also demonstrates her amazing twerking skills and talks about how her moves translate to the bedroom. Anitta gets real about what she finds attractive in a person and shares her deal breakers when it comes to dating.</description></item><item><title>Anitta: Segredos para um Ótimo Sexo, Rebolado e Boquetes (Portuguese Subtitles) [VÍDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490039/</guid><description>Podcast Description (PODCAST DE VÍDEO) Prepare-se para esquentar as coisas com Anitta em Call Her Daddy! A superestrela pop brasileira participa do programa para dar os conselhos sexuais que todos desejamos. Anitta reflete sobre a ascensão de sua carreira e conta como alcançou tamanha fama internacional. Ela também demonstra seu incrível rebolado e fala sobre como seus movimentos se traduzem entre quatro paredes. Anitta fala sobre o que ela acha atraente em uma pessoa e compartilha o que acha inadmissível num encontro.</description></item><item><title>Priyanka Chopra Jonas: Falling in Love With Yourself &amp; Then Your Soulmate [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490042/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Priyanka Chopra Jonas joins Call Her Daddy to discuss the obstacles she&amp;rsquo;s faced in life and throughout the rise of her career. Priyanka opens up about the bullying she experienced when she moved from India to the United States during high school and how it impacted her self-worth. She shares how she navigated moments where she felt alone and gives advice for others going through similar experiences.</description></item><item><title>My Trust Issues Are Ruining My Relationship (Solo Fatherly Advice) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490043/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Father Cooper is here with a solo Sunday episode. Alex begins by letting you in on some of her initial wedding planning thoughts. She answers questions from the Daddy Gang and provides some fatherly advice. Alex discusses how to overcome a fear of commitment in relationships and how to shift your outlook on dating in college. She talks about what to do when you bring trust issues into a relationship and how to avoid accidentally pushing your partner away.</description></item><item><title>Gwyneth Paltrow: The Ultimate Dating Roster [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490044/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Gwyneth Paltrow joins Call Her Daddy to reflect on past relationships and give the life advice we all need to hear. Gwyenth opens up about her engagement to Brad Pitt and discusses how she came to the decision that she wasn’t yet ready for marriage. Speaking of her exes, Gwyneth plays a little game called “Brad or Ben” where she determines whether Brad Pitt or Ben Affleck was the better boyfriend.</description></item><item><title>How to Spot a Narcissist in Dating | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490045/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490045/</guid><description>Podcast Description What are the signs of a narcissistic relationship? Is it possible to spot a narcissist on a first date? Clinical psychologist and narcissism expert Dr. Ramani joins Call Her Daddy to explain how to differentiate a healthy relationship from a narcissistic one. She talks through the differences between conflict in a healthy relationship versus conflict with a narcissist. Dr. Ramani gives advice on how to respond to gaslighting, how to preserve your own wellbeing and what types of people attract a narcissist.</description></item><item><title>I’m Engaged [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490046/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490046/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) This is not clickbait. Hi Daddy Gang, it’s me Alex. This week I am revealing every detail of my engagement, starting with the identity of my fiancé. As always, I want you to feel a part of this intimate moment with me, so I’ve included behind the scenes footage from the day I got engaged. I love you all, I wouldn’t be where I am today without you.</description></item><item><title>My Friends Make Me Feel Like Shit | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490047/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is it necessary to have a best friend? Is it okay to be friends with colleagues? Do I really need a “friend group”? Clinical Psychologist and friendship expert Dr. Miriam Kirmayer joins Call Her Daddy to discuss the different types of friendships we can have in our lives. She gives advice on what to do when a friendship feels unequal and how to determine if you’re a good friend to others.</description></item><item><title>Madison Beer: Blackmailed With My Nudes [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490048/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490048/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Madison Beer joins Call Her Daddy to tell her full story for the first time. Madison opens up about having nude videos spread across the internet, multiple instances of blackmail and public slut shaming. She reveals the trauma she endured in childhood and the impact of continuous violation and sexualization. Madison discusses her rock bottom and how these experiences, combined with constant online bullying, almost ended her life.</description></item><item><title>SOS I Keep Arguing with My Partner | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490049/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Everyone argues with their partner, it’s inevitable. But, many of us are getting it wrong…small issues turn into massive fights, we hold grudges, refuse to apologize, get defensive and say things we regret. Clinical Psychologist and relationship expert Nancy Dreyfus is here to teach how we can turn unproductive arguments into moments of connection. Alex and Nancy discuss the common mistakes couples make when arguing and provide tangible strategies to implement during conflict.</description></item><item><title>Lil Dicky: Learning to Love My Dick [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490050/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490050/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Dave Burd (AKA Lil Dicky) joins Call Her Daddy to discuss the evolution of his dating and sex life as he navigated deep insecurities with his penis. Alex and Dave both open up about their experiences with acne, the extreme lengths they went to in order to compensate and how it impacted their self worth. Dave discusses the liberating feeling of facing his insecurities head on and the conception of the rap name Lil Dicky.</description></item><item><title>Why Am I Never Horny? | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490051/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Does it feel like you’re never horny? Never in the mood for sex? Father Cooper is here with a SOLO mini episode to give you the answers. The reason we aren’t craving sex is because we aren’t orgasming. Alex breaks down how to reignite your sex drive and find your orgasm. She explains the conversations you should be having in the bedroom to shift the dynamic and focus to your pleasure and orgasm.</description></item><item><title>Christina Aguilera: Getting Dirty &amp; Talking Sex [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490052/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490052/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Christina Aguilera joins Call Her Daddy for her first ever podcast interview. We all know her from her countless hit songs and music videos, but Christina shares what was actually going on in her life behind the scenes as she gained international fame. She speaks about growing up in an abusive household and becoming the caretaker of her family at a young age. Christina opens up and discusses insecurities, comparison and feelings of not being good enough.</description></item><item><title>Getting Over a Cheater | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490053/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join Father Cooper for a SOLO mini episode to discuss how to move on if you’ve been cheated on. Alex recounts her own experience being cheated on in a past relationship and gives advice on how to change your mindset. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why I Was Forced to Hide My Pregnancy | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490054/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Women are often forced to believe they have to choose between their career and motherhood and are told that they can’t have both. Allyson Felix, the most decorated female track and field olympian of all time, joins Call Her Daddy to share her story and explain that you CAN have both. Allyson opens up about the discrimination she faced as a woman in sports and how she used her voice to speak up and enact real change.</description></item><item><title>John Legend: Addressing the Internet Rumors [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490055/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490055/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) John Legend joins Call Her Daddy. After being homeschool, John skipped multiple grades and was only 16 when he went to college. He shares how being the youngest person in the room impacted his dating life. John recounts the first time he met his wife, the difficulties they faced early in the relationship and the evolution of their love story. John opens up about the pregnancy loss he and his wife experienced and how they navigated through the difficult experience.</description></item><item><title>SOS: I’m Burnt Out on Life | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490056/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490056/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are tired, overwhelmed, and anxious. Burnout is real. But, why aren’t the bath bombs, essential oils and juice cleanses working? Dr. Pooja Lakshim joins Call Her Daddy to explain that REAL self care is an internal process, it’s not something you can buy, it’s a way to be. Pooja breaks down one of the core principles of real self care…boundaries. Alex and Pooja discuss why boundary setting is so difficult and how to move past feelings of guilt.</description></item><item><title>The Pilot for My Reality Show: Italy Edition [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490057/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490057/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) This week Call Her Daddy brings you a SOLO episode. Join Alex as she travels to Italy for Milan Fashion Week and takes you along for the chaos. She laughs, cries and verges on a mental breakdown. What’s a reality show without some drama? Alex gets into a heated argument and of course films the entire showdown. Enjoy Daddy Gang! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>Your Survival Guide to Dating Apps | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490058/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dating apps are here to stay - and when you ask anybody about their experience with the apps, the consensus is that dating apps are a soul sucking experience. Esther Perel joins Call Her Daddy to discuss why dating apps leave us feeling bad about ourselves and how we can add some humanity back into the process. Esther speaks about managing feelings of rejection, creating unrealistic standards, and why first dates often feel like a job interview.</description></item><item><title>Cole Sprouse: Exploited for Money and Fame [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490059/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490059/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Cole Sprouse joins Call Her Daddy this week for a sit-down interview, something he’s been reluctant to do in the past. Now, the former child star is ready to share like he never has before. He reveals the true reason he and his twin brother, Dylan, were thrust into acting at a young age and opens up about his complicated family dynamic. Cole doesn&amp;rsquo;t hold back when talking about his dating life.</description></item><item><title>Reneé Rapp: Sex Lives of College Girls [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490060/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490060/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Reneé Rapp joins Call Her Daddy to discuss the hardships she&amp;rsquo;s navigated while managing the rise of her career. Reneé speaks about growing up in North Carolina and the difficulties she faced when trying to come out to her friends and family. She explains why her first year on set at Sex Lives of College Girls was a horrible experience and why she hated going into work.</description></item><item><title>Kelsea Ballerini: Divorced at 29 [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490061/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490061/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Kelsea Ballerini joins Call Her Daddy, and for the first time ever, shares the full account of her relationship and divorce from country singer Morgan Evans. Kelsea and Morgan met when she was only 22 years old and the pair got engaged nine months later. Kelsea opens up about the struggles in their marriage and the moment she realized divorce was the only option. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Rebel Wilson: Dating Fails to Finding the One [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490062/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490062/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Rebel Wilson joins Call Her Daddy to discuss her journey to love and motherhood. Rebel reflects back on high school and her time in the “popular” crowd…that lasted one day. She discusses how she actively avoided dating all through her 20’s and was often left feeling friendzoned. Rebel dishes on her “year of love” where she said yes to every date proposed to her which ended with a few hilarious stories.</description></item><item><title>Grief: It’s OK That You’re Not OK | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490063/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Grief comes in many forms - it’s a universal experience. But, do you really know how to handle it? Psychotherapist and grief expert, Megan Devine joins Call Her Daddy to discuss her own journey with grief after the sudden loss of her partner. Megan provides tangible advice to support yourself and others managing grief. She shares exactly what NOT to do when it comes to supporting a grieving friend and offers the best ways to show up and support someone.</description></item><item><title>Adam Devine: Medium Dick Energy [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490064/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490064/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Adam Devine is here to set the record straight - he and his wife are doing amazing. He is categorically not the Adam who cheated with women he met on instagram. Adam joins Call Her Daddy to serve the Medium Dick Energy we all need, giving us a hilarious take on what it was like to grow up in Nebraska. He performs the song he used in his Pitch Perfect audition, and it’s not what you would expect.</description></item><item><title>The Guide to Navigating Friendship | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490065/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why does friendship get more difficult as we get older? Clinical psychologist and friendship expert Dr. Miriam Kirmayer is here to break down the various roadblocks that arise within friendships and provide practical tools for navigating the difficult times. She gives advice for making new friends later in life, setting boundaries within friendships, and maintaining connection when two people are at different points in their lives. Alex and Dr.</description></item><item><title>Jane Fonda: The GOAT [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490066/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490066/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Jane Fonda joins Call Her Daddy to offer her invaluable advice and wisdom. Jane talks about the importance of female friendship and reflects on the difficult times in her life that friendship helped her overcome. She speaks candidly about the pressure of being cast as the “girl next door&amp;quot; and the objectification that led to a 20 year battle with bulimia. Jane was married and divorced three times and now recognizes a pattern within those relationships.</description></item><item><title>How Our Parents Fucked Us Up | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490067/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490067/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s time to understand the impact our parents had on us. This episode breaks down a variety of parenting styles: the “checked out” parent, the helicopter parent, the substance abusing parent, and the parent who shows their love through gift buying … just to name a few. How can the way we were raised impact the way we react and respond in certain situations? How can we come to understand the types of relationships we seek out and the patterns we get stuck in?</description></item><item><title>Chelsea Handler: Getting High as Fuck [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490068/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490068/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Chelsea Handler joins Call Her Daddy to get high as fuck. After Alex attempts to grill Chelsea on the details of her recent breakup they contemplate Chelsea’s dating prospects … Elon Musk? Lil Wayne? Chelsea is here to give her honest and unfiltered take on a variety of topics. What’s the deal with “nepo babies”? Is there ever a good reason to resuscitate a dead friendship? Is going to Disney World as an adult without a child a good idea?</description></item><item><title>How to Become More Confident in Social Settings | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490069/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you ever think about the first impression you make when you walk into a room? Are you always the one offering up unsolicited advice? Do you find it difficult to connect in a conversation? Dr. Jennifer Freed is here to provide tools so that we can listen better and relate deeper. This episode will help you leave any social setting feeling more confident and at ease. Dr. Freed is here to teach us how to apply these same tools to romantic relationships.</description></item><item><title>Jay Shetty: The Rules for Falling in Love and Not Fucking It Up [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490070/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490070/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Jay Shetty joins Call Her Daddy to discuss the rules for falling in love and not fucking it up. Alex and Jay break down common mistakes people fall into when navigating the early stages of dating and how the pace of the relationship is a crucial part of not missing any potential red flags. Jay explains the link between the way our parents raised us, how that influences potential partners we seek out, and how to become aware we are even doing any of this.</description></item><item><title>The Chainsmokers: Cheating, Threesomes &amp; Toxic Exes [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490071/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490071/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) The Chainsmokers join Call Her Daddy to discuss their evolution — and if you love a wild and crazy story-time, this episode is for you. From the start, Alex Pall and Drew Taggart were a match made in heaven - the duo discuss working together for the past 10 years and how prioritizing the success of The Chainsmokers has impacted each of them personally. They don’t hold back when talking about their love lives and share all of their messiest, albeit hilarious, breakup stories.</description></item><item><title>How to Be Single and Happy | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490072/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you burnt out from one bad date after another? Are you sick of being single? Are your thoughts consumed with finding the right person? Life doesn’t have to start when you find a partner and couple up. Clinical Psychologist Dr. Jenny Taitz is here to give us all the tools to stop over-analyzing romantic encounters, get over regrets about past relationships, and identify what you want and need in a partner.</description></item><item><title>Keke Palmer: Codependent Relationships, Child Fame &amp; Insecurities [REVISIT] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490073/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Call Her Daddy will be taking a brief break this week, but we&amp;rsquo;ll return on January 11, 2023 with a brand new episode. Please enjoy this older favorite from Call Her Daddy in the meantime. Father Cooper sits down with Keke Palmer. Keke shares the effects childhood fame had on her life - and how achieving early success left her feeling completely alone. Alex and Keke discuss a shared insecurity - debilitating acne - and how they still struggle to find confidence during breakouts.</description></item><item><title>Amanda Knox: “I didn’t fucking do it.” [REVISIT] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490074/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Call Her Daddy will be taking a brief break this week, but we&amp;rsquo;ll return on January 11, 2023 with a brand new episode. Please enjoy this older favorite from Call Her Daddy in the meantime. Father Cooper sits down with Amanda Knox. The interview begins with Amanda giving a clear reminder to the world – “I didn’t fucking do it”. In 2007, while studying abroad in Italy, Amanda was wrongly accused and convicted of murdering her roommate Meredith Kercher.</description></item><item><title>John Mayer [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490075/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490075/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) John Mayer joins Call Her Daddy - and you’ve never seen him like this before. He discusses his rise to fame, relationships, love and what’s next. Get ready for the first ever Call Her Daddy Holiday Special, featuring live performances from John Mayer. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Aubrey O’Day: Overcoming Toxic Men (ft. Diddy, Trump &amp; Pauly D) [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490076/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490076/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Aubrey O’Day joins Call Her Daddy to reflect on nearly 20 years in the industry and the toxic men she met along the way. Aubrey shot to fame on one of MTV’s most popular shows, Making the Band, and was the first person selected in the girl group that emerged, Danity Kane. She recounts body shaming, manipulation and her experience with executive producer P. Diddy. Aubrey talks about the real reason Diddy fired her from Danity Kane - and it’s not what the public was told.</description></item><item><title>How to Have an Orgasm [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490077/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490077/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Dr. Emily Morse joins Call Her Daddy to help you finally achieve (or upgrade) your orgasm. What’s the deal with vibrators? Should everyone own one? Emily brought all her sex toys and is here to talk you through, step-by-step, how to explore and maximize your orgasm - with and without a partner. Alex and Emily discuss how to revive your sex life, admit you’ve been faking orgasms, and communicate with your partner about sex.</description></item><item><title>It’s Breakup Season | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490078/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490078/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Call Her Daddy brings you a SOLO episode. Alex talks about overcoming social anxiety during a recent night out. The night began with Alex attending a party solo, and hiding in the bathroom but ended with Big Al taking multiple shots with a new group of friends. Alex explains the secret to turning the night around - changing her mindset! Still haven’t been accepted to Raya? Alex shares a hack that will grant you access to the exclusive dating app without having to actually be on the app yourself.</description></item><item><title>Jackie Schimmel: Confident Girls > Mean Girls [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490079/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490079/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Jackie Schimmel joins Call Her Daddy and she has a lot to say. After roasting the CHD studio, Jackie reflects on her personal evolution and how she went from a gingivitis-having, headgear-wearing preteen to the beautiful Bitch Bible creator she is today. Jackie is so recklessly confident that she faked a diploma from UCLA in order to get a job - and it worked. We’ve all encountered a high school or college mean girl, but how do we handle mean girls in adulthood?</description></item><item><title>The Path to Trauma Recovery | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490080/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Unfortunately the journey to trauma recovery isn’t as simple as “time heals all wounds”. Clinical psychologist Dr. Arielle Schwartz illuminates the path to healing and debunks the misconceptions around trauma recovery. She advises on a variety of topics including, how to speak to your partner about your trauma and how to reclaim your relationship to intimacy after sexual trauma. Dr. Schwartz speaks about shame, forgiveness and what to do if you are in a situation where you have to see your abuser.</description></item><item><title>Elizabeth Banks: How Do I Know If He’s My Soulmate? [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490081/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490081/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Elizabeth Banks joins Call Her Daddy to share some wine, wisdom and laughs. She reminisces on meeting her husband on the very first night of college and how she knew he was the one - even though they were only eighteen. Elizabeth and Alex discuss and normalize not always knowing exactly what you want in life &amp;ndash; and give advice to those feeling confused after graduating college.</description></item><item><title>Introverts &amp; Extroverts: Dating Edition | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490082/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you an introvert, extrovert or somewhere in between? This week Call Her Daddy explores the dynamics that can arise between introverts and extroverts while dating and in relationships. I’m an extrovert and I feel rejected when my introverted partner needs alone time, how do I respond? My extroverted partner is overwhelming me with plans and I feel like the boring one in the relationship, what do I do?</description></item><item><title>How to Spice Up Your Relationship | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490083/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490083/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Call Her Daddy is bringing you a SOLO episode. Father Cooper finally moved into her new home she bought with her boyfriend and this has raised some serious concerns. Buying a house before marriage?! She discusses the pressures of a “timeline” and why this concept is absolute bullshit. Alex opens up about difficult family situations she’s had to overcome and what she is doing this year to take back the holidays.</description></item><item><title>Morgan Stewart McGraw: Boobs and Loubs [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490084/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490084/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Morgan Stewart McGraw joins Call Her Daddy to give us the advice we all need to hear. Morgan hits us with some hard fashion truths … say goodbye to your cut-out dresses, wedges, and even your beloved ankle boots. She opens up about her marriage to musician Jordan McGraw, and discusses how the two found their way back to each other after almost ten years apart. Morgan shares what it’s like to have Dr.</description></item><item><title>La La Anthony: Life After Professional Athletes [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490085/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490085/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) La La Anthony joins Call Her Daddy to talk about her career, how to be a great friend (keep secrets) and how she’s stayed grounded and classy af while navigating a shared life with a professional athlete. La La tells the story of getting a fake ID at 15 years old so she could begin working as an intern in radio. She reflects on her journey from radio personality to MTV host to actress and producer.</description></item><item><title>How to Stop Self-Sabotage | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490086/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490086/</guid><description>Podcast Description You get rejected after a date and tell yourself you’re going to end up alone. You procrastinate a huge assignment and end up pulling an all-nighter to barely complete the task. You don’t hit your goal when training for an upcoming race and decide to withdraw from the competition. These are all examples of self-sabotage. Dr. Judy Ho, triple board certified and licensed clinical and forensic neuropsychologist, joins Call Her Daddy to explain why we self-sabotage, how to recognize it, and provide tangible tools on how to overcome it.</description></item><item><title>Nessa Barrett: My Journey with Borderline Personality Disorder [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490087/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490087/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Nessa Barrett joins Call Her Daddy and isn’t here to hold back. She reflects on her childhood - and why she ran away from home at only 17 years old. She talks about what happened when she blew up online, her relationship with Josh Richards and the internet drama surrounding her dating timeline with Jaden Hossler. Nessa opens up about their recent breakup and directly addresses the cheating rumors.</description></item><item><title>Overcoming Social Anxiety | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490088/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anxiety sucks and we all experience it at some point. It can put a strain on your relationships, cause you to skip social events, and overall cause you physical and emotional discomfort. But we can’t allow anxiety to control our lives. This week, clinical psychologist Dr. Julie Smith is here with the answers. She provides tangible advice on how to manage all types of anxiety…from social anxiety to Sunday scaries to that moment when you are laying in bed at night with a million different thoughts racing through your head.</description></item><item><title>Fletcher: Should I Go Back to My Ex? [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490089/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490089/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Fletcher joins Call Her Daddy and is ready to expose her dating life. Alex and Fletcher reflect on their exes and bond over toxic themes in past relationships. Fletcher explains how her need for independence created a fear of intimacy, and ultimately led to her hurting partners. Alex gets vulnerable and discusses how she used prior relationships as a source of validation in order to mask her insecurities.</description></item><item><title>Fuck the Male Gaze | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490090/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490090/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do you feel about your body? Have you ever stayed home from a social activity or other opportunity because of concern about how you looked? Have you ever passed judgment on someone because of how they looked or dressed? Have you ever had difficulty concentrating on a task because you were self-conscious about your appearance? This is self-objectification and it is the result of our beauty-obsessed world perpetuating the idea that happiness, health, and ability to be loved are dependent on how we look.</description></item><item><title>An Abortion Story [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490091/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490091/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) How are we not advanced enough as a society where women are equal to men? Alex Cooper examines the reality women are facing in the fight to preserve autonomy over their bodies. This episode discusses adult subject matter, including descriptions of sexual assault and rape and is intended for adult consumption only. Listener discretion is advised. If you or someone you know has been sexually assaulted, confidential 24/7 help is available.</description></item><item><title>Hailey Bieber [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490092/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490092/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Hailey Bieber joins Call Her Daddy. For the first time ever, Hailey opens up about the public-generated controversy between her and her husband&amp;rsquo;s ex. Hailey makes it clear she wants to discuss this one time and one time only…on Call Her Daddy. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>COUPLES THERAPY (ft. Dr. Orna Guralnik) (Revisit) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490093/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Daddy Gang, while CHD is on a quick break, check out this revisit of a past favorite episode. New episodes of CHD will return on 9/28. Father Cooper is joined by clinical psychologist, psychoanalyst and star of the hit docu-series Couples’ Therapy, Dr. Orna Guralnik. This episode has something for everyone, whether you have never attended therapy in your life or you are years into the process. Dr. Guralnik begins with the basics (do I bring a PowerPoint presentation to my first therapy session?</description></item><item><title>How I Knew I Needed to End a Friendship | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490094/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonjour! Buckle up - we’re going to France. The classic dilemma, you fuck one person in a friend group and then you realize you want to fuck another…what do you do? Father Cooper is here with the answer. Let’s talk about texting, is it a red flag if a guy sucks at texting? Well, Alex’s boyfriend also is not an A+ texter and she’s here with advice speaking from personal experience.</description></item><item><title>Let’s Get High (4/20 Edition) (Revisit) [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490095/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Daddy Gang, while CHD is on a quick break, check out this revisit of a past favorite episode. New episodes of CHD will return on 9/28. (VIDEO PODCAST) Listen and watch your father as she gets stoned out of her mind in celebration of 4/20. Before getting completely baked, Big Al reminisces on the first time she got high- it was her, three men, in a car, with a water bottle.</description></item><item><title>How to Handle a Psycho Ex | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490096/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever dealt with a psycho ex? Did they bombard you with hundreds of texts and emails? Threaten to contact your friends, family or employer? Post your nudes online? Father Cooper is talking to victims rights attorney Carrie Goldberg, who is an expert at fighting psychos, assholes, pervs and trolls. Carrie speaks from personal experience, when she ended things with an abusive ex he went to great lengths to stalk and harass her and attempted to make her life a living hell.</description></item><item><title>Devon and Sydney Carlson: How a Guy Came Between Us (Summer Series) [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490097/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490097/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) This week, Devon and Sydney Carlson join Father Cooper. They’re sisters, best friends and business partners. Devon and Sydney recount how a bathroom run-in with Miley Cyrus led to the overnight development of their company, Wildflower. The sisters spill all of their secrets while playing a game of “Who is More Likely to &amp;hellip;” Which Carlson sister is more likely to get kicked out of the club and who will be texting their ex once they get drunk?</description></item><item><title>Rachel Bilson: From People Pleasing to Knowing Your Worth (Summer Series) [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490098/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) This week, Father Cooper sits down with Rachel Bilson. The pair reminisce on Rachel’s days starring in the hit show, The OC, and Rachel shares what it was like to date co-star Adam Brody. Let’s talk about sex. Alex and Rachel discuss bringing a toy into the bedroom for the first time and how to combat when sex begins to feel like a chore. Rachel addresses the infamous headline for the first time…that her breakup with actor Bill Hader was more difficult than childbirth.</description></item><item><title>Girl Talk With a GYNO | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490099/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Does hormonal birth control affect my fertility? How do I even know if I’m fertile, is that something I should be checking? How often should I be getting screened for STI’s? I recently had an abnormal pap - is this reason to panic? Constant UTI’s…is this normal? It’s time to finally make that appointment to see your gynecologist. Dr. Kameelah Phillips is here to explain why it is imperative to visit your OB-GYN and answer all of your questions regarding birth control, fertility, STI’s and more.</description></item><item><title>Demi Lovato [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490100/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490100/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) This week, Father Cooper sits down with Demi Lovato. Demi exposes the reality of what it was like to be one of the biggest stars on the Disney Channel. How much of Demi’s personal life did Disney have control over and what the fuck was up with the purity rings? Demi outlines how extreme management evolved into manipulation and brainwashing which led to drugs and alcohol. Now free of the control, Demi reflects back on problematic relationships and opens up about which relationship inspired the song &amp;ldquo;29.</description></item><item><title>Is Your Parent a Narcissist? [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490101/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490101/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Is your parent a narcissist? In this episode, clinical psychologist Dr. Sherrie Campbell breaks down what happens when you come to the realization that your mom or dad should never have been a parent in the first place…children know when their parents don&amp;rsquo;t want them. Dr. Campbell explains the effects narcissists have on their children. Survivors of this trauma can grow into adults who struggle with assertiveness, boundary setting and sense of self.</description></item><item><title>Remi Bader: Don’t Call Me Body Positive (Summer Series) [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490102/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490102/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Father Cooper sits down with model and content creator, @remibader. Remi got her start on TikTok posting realistic clothing hauls and her platform has since expanded beyond fashion. Remi opens up and reflects on discrimination she’s faced since launching her career; for the first time, she tells the story of what actually went down this summer at a Hampton’s ranch where she was publicly humiliated and forced to leave due to her weight.</description></item><item><title>Danielle Guizio: How to Build a Fashion Brand (Summer Series) [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490103/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490103/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) This week, Father Cooper is joined by fashion designer and entrepreneur Danielle Guizio. Danielle built a streetwear fashion company from the ground up. Now, her designs are everywhere - from dressing the cast of Euphoria to celebrities like Kylie Jenner, Sophie Turner and Bella Hadid. Danielle discusses her difficult journey to success, which started after dropping out of fashion school and overcoming a health scare. Danielle explains how she went from running a company out of her parent’s basement to earning a spot on the Forbes 30 Under 30 list.</description></item><item><title>Kristin Cavallari: So You Want to Date an Athlete? (Summer Series) [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490104/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490104/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) This week, Father Cooper sits down with Kristin Cavallari. Can you imagine being in high school and having grown men with cameras following you around to stir up drama? Kristin can - and she’s here to reflect on those Laguna Beach days and explains why MTV should now be paying for the entire cast’s therapy. And, with Alex and Kristin well experienced in the world of hooking up with professional athletes, they give the inside scoop on what it’s like to date (or marry) one.</description></item><item><title>How to Thrive When You’re Single [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490105/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490105/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Your Father is home from Europe and in NYC delivering a SOLO episode. The lesson of the week…how to embrace the single life and thrive. Alex is here to rid the idea that there is any shame in being single. Feeling pressure to settle down and find someone? NOT ANYMORE. There is no age that you become less desirable and we are here to tell all concerned friends and family to kindly mind their own f*cking business.</description></item><item><title>How to Manage Your Stress and Prevent Burnout | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490106/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you feel overwhelmed and exhausted and still worry that you aren’t doing enough? Do you ever find yourself thinking, “the worst that could happen is they’ll fire me and honestly… that would be a relief?” This is Burnout. And there is science that proves, Burnout is real. Burnout goes beyond your job and can also be experienced in relation to your relationship, family life or generally the state of the world.</description></item><item><title>Audrina Patridge: Surviving an Abusive Relationship (Summer Series) [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490107/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490107/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) This week, Father Cooper sits down with Audrina Patridge. Opening up like never before, Audrina details the abusive nature of her relationship and marriage to ex-husband Corey Bohan. She recounts the serial cheating, emotional abuse and extreme manipulation tactics that left her isolated from friends and family. After surviving years of abuse, Audrina escaped. She filed for a divorce and a restraining order and began to rebuild her life as a single mother.</description></item><item><title>Olivia Attwood: OnlyFans, Cam Girls, Pornhub and Sugar Babies (Summer Series) [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490108/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490108/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) This week, Father Cooper travels to London and sits down with Olivia Attwood. Olivia discusses her life before Love Island and recounts her days partying and traveling the world as a grid girl. Olivia’s dating life before Love Island? Tattoos on the first date and countless cheating stories…it was toxic. The pair then discuss Olivia’s experience exploring the world of OnlyFans and Pornhub and the lives of cam girls and sugar babies.</description></item><item><title>Plotting My Summer Threesome [REVISIT] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490109/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex welcomes her best friend, and soulmate since the second grade&amp;hellip;Laren, in this revisit! The girls discuss their lifelong friendship and give a huge announcement (boyfriend?!?). Plus Alex shares a behind-the-scenes look at the latest Call Her Daddy episode of Lottie Moss, and calls out nasty internet trolls. Big Al and Laren discuss the latest season of ‘Selling Sunset’ on Netflix and finish the show by answering questions from listeners live!</description></item><item><title>Euro Tour 2022: Life Updates | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490110/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Father Cooper is back at it again with a SOLO episode. Should you or should you not post your partner on social media? Alex gets personal, sharing the true reason why she will NEVER post her boyfriend on the internet. Speaking of social media, Alex takes a stand on influencers and their ability to influence… it may be controversial but someone needs to say it. Heading into summer single?</description></item><item><title>Father Cooper Goes Live [REVISIT] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490111/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Your founding father makes her live room debut in this revisit! Alex kicks things off with hot topics and life updates, followed by juicy pop culture hot takes, including celebrity couples &amp;ldquo;Bennifer&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Kravis.&amp;rdquo; Later she answers questions from listeners in the chat and gives some essential relationship advice. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>I cheated and got away with it, now what? | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490112/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490112/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Dr. Suzanne Wallach joins the show once again to answer the Daddy Gang’s toughest questions. Alex and Dr. Wallach discuss how to overcome the avoidance that stems from anxiety and strategies to help you stop comparing yourself to everyone else in the room. In the spirit of health and wellness, Dr. Wallach explains why you should NOT be snooping through your partners phone and provides techniques to rid your life of that behavior.</description></item><item><title>Spencer Pratt: How to Be Famous (Summer Series) [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490113/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490113/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) This week, Father Cooper sits down with Spencer Pratt. Spoiler alert: Spencer gets pissed and storms out of the interview after Alex asks a triggering question. But, before the tantrum, Spencer name drops practically everyone in Hollywood and gives us the 101 on how to become famous. We know the drill, Spencer Pratt walked so Kim Kardashian could run. But according to Spencer, fame isn’t even cool anymore!</description></item><item><title>Cancel Diet Culture | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490114/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490114/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper is joined by life coach and body positivity expert Susan Hyatt. Susan breaks down the prevalence of diet culture in today’s society and why it is so toxic. She provides tangible lifestyle changes that can lead to healthier and more fulfilled lives. How does your environment affect your mood and eating? What message is your closet sending to you? Summer often leads to anxiety around body image and Susan is here to challenge and shift our current mindset.</description></item><item><title>Nick Viall and Natalie Joy: Couple Goals (Summer Series) [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490115/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490115/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) This week, Father Cooper is joined by Nick Viall and Natalie Joy. But first, Alex has a solo chat with Nick and the two obviously have to discuss…Bachelor Nation. Nick reflects back on his time in the franchise, his transition into podcasting and offers up some dating advice of his own. Once Natalie joins the discussion we learn how their relationship began and how she played every move correctly - without being toxic!</description></item><item><title>Olivia Ponton: Happy Pride! (Summer Series) [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490116/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490116/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Welcome to the first episode of the CHD Summer Series. This week, Father Cooper sits down with Olivia Ponton. Alex and Olivia discuss their personal experience with long distance relationships…are they ever a good idea? Is it possible to live in the present while being in a long distance relationship? Summer has officially arrived and Pride Month has begun! Olivia reflects back on her first year of openly being a part of the LGBTQ+ community and shares what she has learned about herself along the way.</description></item><item><title>Insecure in Love: Exploring Attachment Styles | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490117/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490117/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is your attachment style and how does it affect how you view yourself and behave within a relationship? Before listening to the episode take the online quiz to determine your personal attachment style (free link below). Whether you realize you have a secure or insecure attachment style, this week Dr. Becker-Phelps, clinical psychologist and author, joins us to break down the role it plays within your life and provides tools to work towards a healthier way of relating to yourself and others.</description></item><item><title>Am I Dating a Narcissist? (ft. Dr. Ramani) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490118/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490118/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper is joined by clinical psychologist, author and expert on narcissism - Dr. Ramani. Dr. Ramani provides clarity and explains the core characteristics of a narcissist. She walks us through how to recognize if we are in a relationship with a narcissist and the steps to take to safely get out. Dr. Ramani breaks down two of the narcissists favorite tactics - gaslighting and love bombing.</description></item><item><title>Christine Quinn: Confessions of a Reality TV Villain [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490119/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490119/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) This week, Father Cooper sits down with Christine Quinn, the infamous villain on the hit reality television show ‘Selling Sunset.’ You either love her or hate her, but you absolutely know her name. There are two sides to Christine, the polarizing character she plays on television, and the calm and collected woman who joins CHD this week. How does somebody become a reality television villain? What emotional impact does portraying the bad guy on tv have on real life?</description></item><item><title>A Guide to the Female Orgasm | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490120/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490120/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper is joined by sex therapist and relationship expert Dr. Laura Berman. Daddy Gang, if you have never had an orgasm…you are not alone. If you are unsure if you’ve ever had an orgasm…you are not alone. If you’re only able to orgasm while masturbating, I once again repeat … you are not alone. In this episode, Dr. Berman breaks down what an orgasm is, how to know if you’ve had one, and gives VERY specific step by step instructions and advice.</description></item><item><title>You are the Fuck Buddy, nothing more. [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490121/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490121/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) This week, your father gifts you with a day in her life. This bitch is Vlog Podcasting again. Your father is a grown up… Alex has summer plans and she’s willing to share them. But first Alex reminisces on all the toxic men who gave her PTSD by planning trips, then ditching her ass seconds before flights were boarding. Your father recognizes she used to be a child.</description></item><item><title>Keke Palmer: Codependent Relationships, Child Fame &amp; Insecurities | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490122/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490122/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper sits down with Keke Palmer. Keke shares the effects childhood fame had on her life - and how achieving early success left her feeling completely alone. Alex and Keke discuss a shared insecurity - debilitating acne - and how they still struggle to find confidence during breakouts. What are the signs of a codependent relationship and how can you recognize if you are in one?</description></item><item><title>The REAL Ghosting Experience (ft. Jonathan Mark) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490123/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490123/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper is joined by celebrity medium Jonathan Mark. You may know him from his work on the infamous Gabby Petito case, but his work didn’t begin there and he’s here to tell us all about it. Jonathan describes how he first discovered his gift, his experience as a medium, and how his abilities have helped save lives and solve active crimes. Enjoy an episode filled with supernatural stories and decide for yourself - do you believe?</description></item><item><title>Lottie Moss: Threesomes, Toxic Men &amp; Only Fans [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490124/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490124/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) This week Father Cooper sits down with Lottie Moss. Sure, she’s supermodel Kate Moss’ little sister, but Lottie has stepped out of the shadows and paved a path of her own. Lottie opens up about the dark and destructive nature of the modeling industry, how they permitted her drug use, and even encouraged it. After a recent and very public stay in rehab, Lottie took ownership of her life and cut out the toxic people.</description></item><item><title>Let’s Get High: 4/20 Edition [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490125/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490125/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) This week, join Father Cooper for a SOLO EPISODE. Call Her Daddy debuts the very first vlog podcast. Listen AND WATCH your father as she gets stoned out of her mind in celebration of 4/20. Before getting completely baked, Big Al reminisces on the first time she got high- it was her, three men, in a car, with a water bottle. Do you like to fuck while you’re high?</description></item><item><title>How do I tell him I love him? | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490126/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490126/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a highly anticipated trip, we are heading to France. Let’s talk about the L-bomb and when to drop it. I’ve been with my partner for a year, is it appropriate to say I love you? What if they don’t say it back? There are so many questions surrounding this moment and Big Al addresses them all. We all know about Only Fans, but what about when your boyfriend is the one who has one?</description></item><item><title>RIP STASSIE BABY [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490127/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490127/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) This week, Father Cooper sits down with the woman who never does interviews…Stas Karanikolaou. Alex uncovers the mystery behind Stas and asks the questions we all want the answers to. How did Stas rise to her current level of fame? Is she still friends with a certain friend? Stas opens up about her social anxiety and the role her friends play in supporting her through it. Alex and Stas discuss the evolution of plastic surgery and how temporary trends can impact lifelong decisions.</description></item><item><title>Girl Talk: Drinking with Cazzie David [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490128/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490128/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) This week, Father Cooper is joined by Cazzie David. Recently, the girls reached a milestone in their friendship…they went on vacation together. Alex and Cazzie debrief their Cabo trip and breakdown their first ever fight. Did Alex commit the largest possible vacation sin or is Cazzie just being dramatic? Right when it seems the tension has died down, Alex calls Cazzie out…for her cameo in a Hannah Montana episode (low blow?</description></item><item><title>How to Fix a Broken Heart (ft. Guy Winch) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490129/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490129/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper is joined by clinical psychologist Dr. Guy Winch. There is the classic saying…only time heals a broken heart. WRONG! Thankfully Guy is here to provide us with tangible advice on how to navigate heartbreak and get ourselves back out there. What are the rules when it comes to stalking an ex on social media? Can I ever go back to “our” favorite restaurant again? How do I know when I’m ready to date again?</description></item><item><title>Nicole Byer [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490130/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490130/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) This week, Father Cooper sits down with comedian Nicole Byer. Alex and Nicole discuss the struggles of online dating and break down each of the dating apps. We all love a little positive reinforcement in the bedroom right? C’mon men, we need some moans! The duo discusses strategies to elicit verbal feedback from men during sex. While playing never have I ever, we learn that Alex had a sugar daddy, Nicole has fucked more than one person in 24 hours, and both have filmed themselves during sex.</description></item><item><title>Courtney Stodden [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490131/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490131/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) This week, Father Cooper sits down with Courtney Stodden. Courtney broke national headlines back in 2011 when at 16 years old they married 51 year old Doug Hutchison. At the time, Courtney received endless online hate and negative media coverage. Courtney, a child, received death threats, was stalked by the paparazzi, sexualized, and labeled a whore. Courtney is now 27 years old, has gotten into therapy, and started their recovery journey.</description></item><item><title>Anna Delvey [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490132/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490132/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) This week, Father Cooper interviews Anna Delvey from prison … or should we say Anna Sorokin. Alex doesn’t go easy on the fake German heiress who conned the elite of New York City. Find out the answers to the questions we all want to know. Watch the video for the full experience. You won’t be sorry. Enjoy. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Where'd all my friends go? (ft. Mel Robbins) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490133/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490133/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper is joined by author and motivational speaker, Mel Robbins. Have you ever felt insecure about the number of friends you have? Do you define your worth by your friend group? Alex and Mel normalize going through periods of life where friends fade and the focus shifts - to being a good friend to yourself. Mel shares concrete advice on how to alter this pattern of thinking, so that we stop defining ourselves by external factors and take control of our lives.</description></item><item><title>Chloe Cherry [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490134/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490134/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) This week, Father Cooper sits down with Euphoria star Chloe Cherry. Chloe provides the inside scoop of her time on set for Euphoria and details what it was like to work with some of the biggest names in the industry. Prior to joining the cast of Euphoria, Chloe was a highly accomplished porn star. Chloe opens up about the effect her porn career had on relationships with friends, family and her own body image.</description></item><item><title>To Those Feeling Lost in Their 20s… (ft. Mel Robbins) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490135/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490135/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper is joined by author and motivational speaker Mel Robbins. Have you ever felt lost or uncertain with the direction of your life? Why is this feeling especially amplified in our 20’s? Alex and Mel break down how this sense of uncertainty is rooted in insecurity, comparison, and regret. Mel shares concrete advice on how to regain control of your life and provides a new perspective on how to positively approach social media.</description></item><item><title>I Bought a House with My Boyfriend | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490136/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join Father Cooper this week for another SOLO episode. Alex addresses the “Uncuh Jahmz” phenomena and clarifies where her relationship with Julia Fox stands. Big Al has a BIG announcement … she bought a house with her boyfriend! She phones her bff Laren to discuss moving in with a partner and the obstacles that come with it. Alex then shares a recent lingerie fail and how she was able to bounce back at the last minute.</description></item><item><title>It’s Time to Ask About His Past… (ft. My Boyfriend) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490137/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join Father Cooper this week for a SOLO episode. A turn of events leads Alex to dig out her “ex-box” - you know the literal box where you keep possessions from your exes. She takes us along for the journey as she reads STD results, love letters, cheating apologies and a few other surprises. The real question…is it okay to keep possessions from an ex-partner? Alex hits us with the hard truth of why we should all be asking our partners about their exes.</description></item><item><title>Your Guide to Better Sex | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490138/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490138/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper is joined by clinical psychologist Dr. Lori Brotto. How should we overcome issues like low sexual arousal, lack of orgasm, and painful sex? What even is a “normal” sex drive? Do I have a sexual dysfunction? Dr. Brotto breaks down all of these questions and walks us through a variety of specific strategies anyone can implement in order to achieve better and more pleasurable sex.</description></item><item><title>My Ex Sent My Family My Nudes | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490139/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join Father Cooper this week for a SOLO episode. Alex tells us what REALLY happened on her recent trip to NYC. We find out the drama that went down after her interview with Julia Fox. And with the Super Bowl in LA last weekend, Alex takes the opportunity to expose a Bengals player for cheating and her ex for sharing nudes with her family…TUNE IN FOR THE TEA! Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Julia Fox [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490140/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490140/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) This week, Father Cooper sits down with Julia Fox. This year, Julia has been the center of media attention following her romantic relationship with Kanye West. But don’t get it twisted - Julia has been living a fascinating life way before Mr. West entered the building. Julia gives us the inside look at life as a dominatrix and describes what it is like to work in the ‘dungeon’ and her favorite characters to role-play.</description></item><item><title>Emma Chamberlain (Part 2) [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490141/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490141/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) This week, Father Cooper sits down with Emma Chamberlain for the second part of their conversation. Emma recalls feeling used by other Youtubers in order to gain views and how she was burned by the people she once looked up to. The pair discuss feeling out of control of their public perception and the need to consequently address and debunk fake rumors. Emma describes the anxiety she experiences as a result of constantly being surveillanced while out in public and the feeling of wanting to disappear.</description></item><item><title>Emma Chamberlain (Part 1) [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490142/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490142/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) This week, Father Cooper is joined by Emma Chamberlain for her first official in person sit down interview. The pair discuss Emma’s high school days and cover everything from being an only child, her parents divorce, and ultimately her decision to drop out and pursue Youtube full time (OH and they also discuss the classic high school dick pic). Alex and Emma open up and reflect on the fears associated with being a content creator&amp;hellip; Who am I outside of the content I post?</description></item><item><title>Cancel Call Her Daddy | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490143/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490143/</guid><description>Podcast Description I’m going to France. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jamie Lynn Spears (Part 2: The Conservatorship) [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490144/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490144/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Alex Cooper sits down with Jamie Lynn Spears for part two of their interview. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jamie Lynn Spears (Part 1) [VIDEO] | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490145/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490145/</guid><description>Podcast Description (VIDEO PODCAST) Alex Cooper sits down with Jamie Lynn Spears for a two part interview. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>My Plastic Surgery Story | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490146/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Father Cooper is back with a vacation recap. She details a fight with her sister, a non photoshop fail, the moment Mario Lopez appeared mid fuck, and how a teammate spreading gossip landed our father face to face with a plastic surgeon. And, because she is the greatest podcast host of all time, Alex reveals the controversial first guest of the new year. Enjoy daddies. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Mother Cooper (Revisit) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490147/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Transcript</description></item><item><title>PSA - He (Still) Doesn’t Like You | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490148/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Your Father, Alexandra, gets deep this week and walks women through the wake-up call they all need. Stop clinging on to every little thing a men says to you and LOOK AT THE BIG PICTURE FACTS. If you viewed your dating life from a third party view.. what would you think of yourself? An episode EVERY woman needs to hear. Also, giving a huge tip for women that are having a hard time achieving an orgasm/ have never had one (wink wink ASMR porn).</description></item><item><title>The Official Breakup Guide | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490149/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490149/</guid><description>Podcast Description It has arrived – the official Call Her Daddy breakup guide. Haven’t recently gone through a breakup? Well, a little birdie told us you are about to be broken up with, no one is safe, so listen up daddies. Father Cooper walks you through every step of what to do in the moment when you are broken up with (and no…it actually does not involve fucking his dad OR his brother!</description></item><item><title>Infiltrating a Girl Group | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490150/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hello you dirty daddies - let’s cuddle up together and ease our Sunday scaries. How might you ask? Two words…cruise control baby. Alex is providing the roadmap to getting through yet another week of work hell. Big Al opens up and shares a vulnerable side of herself, telling a story from her past that embodies rejection and desperation…haven’t we all been there. This week is filled with story-time and advice…breaking the ice with new friend groups, navigating a night out without drinking and drugs, and crushing a night out at the bar when you are single.</description></item><item><title>Fuck Me with a Dildo | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490151/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490151/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper is coming to you live from a secret snowy location…and she’s not alone! Big Al is currently sharing a home with her ENTIRE family and Mr. Sexy Zoom Man (the sexual frustration is real). Alex details her plans to creatively and secretly get it in without her father finding out her true identity – the throat goat. Alex’s problems are so big this week she phones an expert – sex therapist Dr.</description></item><item><title>Colton Underwood (A CHD Exclusive) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490152/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490152/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper sits down with Colton Underwood. Colton repressed his sexuality for the first 28 years of his life; a former NFL player and Bachelor star, Colton went to extremes to promote and perpetuate a heterosexual identity. Colton sits down with Alex to reflect on his manipulation tactics and the people he hurt along the way. Daddy Gang, tune in this week to hear Colton speak on the events that brought him to rock bottom, led him to make some of the biggest mistakes of his life, and ultimately reveal his true sexuality.</description></item><item><title>Esther Perel (Cheating 101) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490153/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490153/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper sits down with Esther Perel. Esther is a psychotherapist who is recognized as one of the leading voices in modern relationships. Her most recent book, The State of Affairs: Rethinking Infidelity, explores why people cheat and provides guidance on what to do in the wake of discovering this ultimate form of betrayal. Alex presents Esther with a situation…you open your boyfriends iPad to find messages that reveal he is cheating on you.</description></item><item><title>Cuffing Season is Here | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490154/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Your favorite neighborhood losers are back and delivering one spicy mini episode. Laren tells Big Al the story of her recent journey from small town Louisiana to Los Angeles, where she encountered both Santa Claus and Dwayne the Rock Johnson after narrowly escaping a kidnapping. The girls discuss coming across one lusty locksmith…but is it ever a good idea to become romantically involved with a man that can easily break into your apartment?</description></item><item><title>How Social Media Ruined My Life | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490155/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490155/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper sits down with her longtime best friend Laren, who recently deleted all of her social media accounts. The two reminisce on the evolution of social media throughout their lives, including Myspace top friends, Snapchat nudes, Facebook party albums, and the ultimate beast…Instagram. Laren tells all regarding her decision to completely delete her social media and reflects on how her life has changed since going off the grid.</description></item><item><title>Sister Talk | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490156/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Description: Secrets revealed. Love, Alex. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>I Brought my Boyfriend Home- a fail. | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490157/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490157/</guid><description>Podcast Description Let’s take a walk down memory lane…vodka in water bottles, clip in hair extensions and hook ups in your childhood home. Smells like the biggest drinking night of the year – aka blackout Wednesday. STORYTIME! Big Al has experienced a Blackout Wednesday (or two) … let&amp;rsquo;s expose a few more of Father Cooper’s hometown horror stories. How do you think it went the first time she brought Mr. Sexy Zoom Man home to meet her family?</description></item><item><title>Amanda Knox - “I didn’t fucking do it.” | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490158/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490158/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper sits down with Amanda Knox. The interview begins with Amanda giving a clear reminder to the world – “I didn’t fucking do it”. In 2007, while studying abroad in Italy, Amanda was wrongly accused and convicted of murdering her roommate Meredith Kercher. Meredith was the victim of a brutal murder. Amanda was the victim of trial by media. Her sexuality was used against her in order to manipulate a story that she was a sex crazed murderer - and that was the story that overtook international headlines.</description></item><item><title>Affording Therapy 101 | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490159/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Give me an “M”&amp;hellip;give me an “I”…you know where this is going. Father Cooper is back for another mini episode and with some advice you are sure to be ~thankful~ for ;) If you’ve ever listened to an episode of Call Her Daddy you know the drill – get into therapy ASAP. But, easier said than done, right? Well, grab your pen and notebook because Alex has done her research and is here to give you some answers on how to access affordable therapy.</description></item><item><title>Emily Ratajkowski | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490160/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490160/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper sits down with Emily Ratajkowski. While you may think you have an understanding of Emily’s seemingly perfect life, this interview reveals that you never know what someone is actually going through. Emily opens up about the traumatic experiences she has overcome throughout her life and how these events have reduced her to feeling like nothing more than a mannequin. Many are quick to dismiss Emily’s struggles because she has an envious body and posts provocative photos – but does one’s appearance diminish the pain and trauma they have experienced?</description></item><item><title>A Friendship VS. Reality Tv (ft. Hannah Berner &amp; Paige Desorbo) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490161/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490161/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper sits down with Hannah Berner and Paige Desorbo for the show’s first threesome. The episode takes a turn when Hannah and Paige reveal they haven’t spoken about the biggest challenge their friendship has ever faced - reality televisions attempt to prey on their relationship and tear them apart. There are tears, extremely uncomfortable moments and no one holds back. You will hear their friendship put to the test while sitting on the couch of your friendly local therapist…Dr.</description></item><item><title>The Ex Encounter | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490162/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490162/</guid><description>Podcast Description Halloween Sunday scaries got you down? Well this mini is sure to bring you up. Father Cooper begins by discussing the difficulty of managing your time between your friends and your significant other. Is it wrong to want to spend all of your time with your boyfriend? Are your friends just jealous? All of my struggling Catholics out there - please stand up. Big Al explains how she overcame the strict ideals of sex imposed by the Catholic church and how she currently fucks and sucks guilt free.</description></item><item><title>I got ghosted, now what? | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490163/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Halloween is upon us and what’s spookier than ghosting? ;) This week, Alex covers all things ghosting, including, a story you have never heard before - The tale of Slim Shady’s teammate ghosting Big Al. Then, Father Cooper shares her controversial take on ghosting - and why it’s incredible- while also sharing advice for those doing the ghosting and to those being ghosted. Are you the asshole still debating your Halloween costume?</description></item><item><title>Emma Kenney (ft. Shameless) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490164/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490164/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper sits down with Emma Kenney. Emma spent more than half of her life starring as Debbie Gallagher on the TV show “Shameless” and in this episode Emma spills all of the tea about growing up on set. Emma even dishes which co-star she had a crush on. She gets personal and opens up about her decision to go to rehab at a young age and shares new insight on that experience.</description></item><item><title>Stop Cyberbullying and Start Masturbating | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490165/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ask and you shall receive…this mini episode is the second part of Father Cooper’s conversation with Eileen Kelly. So if you have not yet listened to the full Eileen Kelly episode – go get her done and then come on back. Big Al and Eileen continue the conversation around masturbation and hope to soon see all you daddies out there flicking the bean. We heard Eileen’s revenge porn story, but it doesn’t stop there, Eileen was also the victim of online stalking and harassment.</description></item><item><title>Eileen Kelly (threesomes, revenge porn, &amp; blowjobs) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490166/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490166/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper sits down with podcaster Eileen Kelly. After the sudden loss of her mother at a young age, Eileen formed an online community through Tumblr and blogging where she discussed sex, relationships and growing up. Alex and Eileen reminisce on their catholic school days and the sex-ed they wish they were taught. Well, what would they teach…porn and pleasure? While we are educating the masses, let’s discuss all things masturbation.</description></item><item><title>Cazzie David (ft. pick me girls &amp; love bombing) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490167/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490167/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper sits down with Cazzie David (despite Cazzie’s last minute efforts to ditch). The two then get serious and discuss family relationships and social media. Cazzie details what the pilot episode of her family’s reality TV show would be and Alex reminds the world that she does in fact have a sister. Building upon last week’s episode, the duo discusses the negative impact of social media along with the popular Tik Tok trend, the notion of a “pick me girl”.</description></item><item><title>This is your sign, text him. | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490168/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mini mini mini minaaaaaaaaaay. Daddy Gang, we have much to discuss this week. What are the rules when it comes to nude etiquette? Do you have to delete your old nudes when a new partner comes along or are you able to build yourself a portfolio that lasts forever? Ah the classic stalemate situation, and no I’m not fucking talking about chess. I’m talking about the moment when you are so invested in the game of “who can give less fucks” but someone has to make a move.</description></item><item><title>I Got Caught Photoshopping | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490169/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490169/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper addresses a recent Tik Tok that went viral after exposing her for photoshopping. Opening up a larger conversation Alex discusses the role insecurities and bullying from her childhood play in her current relationship to social media. Why is there such a pressure to edit photos? Does it really matter if everyone does it? Is she only saying this because she was caught? Will she continue to edit photos?</description></item><item><title>Nico Tortorella | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490170/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490170/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper sits down with Nico Tortorella. Nico is both an accomplished actor and author. In June of 2016, Nico came out as sexually fluid, and in their book, Space Between, they wrote, “I am comfortable today calling myself a queer, nonbinary, bisuexual, happily married, polyamorous/non-monogamous human being.” In this interview the pair dives deep into Nico’s life and discusses topics ranging from sex and sexuality to overcoming alcoholism.</description></item><item><title>SOS I've been Friend Zoned | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490171/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490171/</guid><description>Podcast Description Did someone say…mini episode? This week, wisdom is spewing out of Father Cooper’s asshole like lava. Should you believe a guy when he says you need to be “friends” so he can “work on himself”? Big Al also advises on topics ranging from the classic small penis problem to how to properly go to titty-town. In the spirit of health and wellness (and growth) let&amp;rsquo;s revisit an old topic – do men love “the crazy”?</description></item><item><title>Alexis Ren | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490172/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490172/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper sits down with Alexis Ren for a raw and vulnerable conversation where Alexis shares stories she has never before discussed. The duo discusses Alexis’ upbringing being homeschooled and overcoming the loss of a parent and toxic relationship. For the first time, Alexis details what actually went down in her infamously known Instagram relationship. The interview concludes with the pair discussing an instance of sexual harassment Alexis faced in the workplace early on in her career.</description></item><item><title>Free Therapy and Drugs for All | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490173/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490173/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper sits down with Laren (that bitch still hasn’t left) in an attempt for redemption. The girls have put down the bottle and picked up … a book? After reading (a chapter) of Esther Perel’s Mating in Captivity, the pair get serious and analyze their own lives while contemplating the question, can passion and stability coexist in a relationship? The duo discusses a spectrum of dating topics ranging from being single to taking accountability within a relationship.</description></item><item><title>What Happens in Vegas - Goes on Call Her Daddy. (Ft. Mr. Sexy Zoom Man, Marshmello, Kygo, Logan Paul, Richard, Laren &amp; Country Club Man) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490174/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490174/</guid><description>Podcast Description I am still too hungover to write one of these. The title says it all. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Roast of my Past | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490175/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490175/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week the tables are turned and Father Cooper is the one being interviewed. In honor of her 27th birthday, Big Al is grilled with 27 questions that will reveal untold stories from her past. Have you ever wondered how many people she’s had sex with? Her first heartbreak? Has she ever successfully pulled off a catfish? Oh, and of course, the question everyone has been wondering…are her tits real?</description></item><item><title>Revealing the Biggest Cock I’ve Ever Taken | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490176/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490176/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome back for another mini episode! This week, Father Cooper breaks it down as to why her clit climax got cancelled in Hawaii. So, insert plan B (no not the pill) but french onion soup, dick and *****. Do you ever wonder the man behind the biggest cock Big Al has ever taken? Well, you are not alone, Mr. Sexy Zoom Man also had the same question – and Father Cooper gives us (and him) the answer.</description></item><item><title>Heidi Montag | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490177/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490177/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper sits down with Heidi Montag, and lots of champagne. The pair get things popping off immediately…poppin bottles that is. Heidi takes us to Italy (sorry not France) where she spent her final year of high school. If you are here for The Hills drama, Heidi does not hold back and dishes all of the tea regarding her plastic surgeries and her former co-star Lauren Conrad (i.</description></item><item><title>AnnaLynne McCord | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490178/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490178/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper sits down with AnnaLynne McCord as she recounts the life events that led up to her diagnosis of dissociative identity disorder. * Trigger Warning * - this entire episode may be triggering for those who have suffered from sexual abuse or would be triggered from the discussion of self harm. If this episode was at all distressing to you, please reach out to the 24/7 national crisis hotline at 1-800-273-8255.</description></item><item><title>I am the Star of Your Sex Dream | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490179/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to the first mini episode mother fuckers…save the date! These bad boys will be dropping every other Thursday. This episode, Father Cooper recalls an instance where a stiff sleepy dick was inserted into her throat…aka she starred in a sex dream. You are all aware of Big Al’s podcasting career, but did you know she is also a landlord? And currently having trouble with her tenants? When will you greedy whores ever be satisfied…god damn, yes you are going to fucking France (with a little Hawaiian twist).</description></item><item><title>Tiffany Haddish | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490180/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490180/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Father Cooper sits down with Tiffany Haddish. Need the perfect recipe for revenge? Take a note from Tiffany’s book and gulf down some corn and take advantage of that shit…literally. Corn shit isn’t your thing? Why not try a strategically placed billboard with your own face on it to really get back at an ex. Tiffany surely doesn’t hold back in this episode and shares her opinion on internet trolls, big dicks, dad bods, cuckolding and so much more.</description></item><item><title>Chelsea Handler | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490181/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490181/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week (and the start of the exclusive season with Spotify) Father Cooper sits down with Chelsea Handler. Alex recounts a vivid memory from the first time she met Chelsea, an instance Chelsea has absolutely no recollection of. The duo discusses topics ranging from cancel culture, the evolution of comedy… and drugs. Daddy Gang, get ready for an epic launch to a new era. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>“Block him” - My therapist | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490182/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490182/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, we begin the episode STILL in the fucking Hamptons. You thought things couldn’t get any wilder from last week? Oh, you thought wrong…get ready to meet the neighbors. Once Father Cooper finally makes it to Chicago she changes the pace up a bit and sits down with Lauren to discuss some therapist approved dating advice. Big Al and Lar chat about blocking, second dates, deciding what your type is and so much more.</description></item><item><title>What Happens in The Hamptons Does NOT Stay in The Hamptons | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490183/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490183/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hello, you have come to the right place to clear up any controversy regarding Father Cooper’s recent Fourth of July trip to the Hamptons. Kicked out of a bar? YUP…and don’t worry she is giving you the full story. Not only is she detailing the physical removal from a bar, but she is also reporting so many more stories that you sneaky little bastards missed with your iPhones. This episode is sure to be unlike any other and contains recordings from bar bathrooms, the Montauk highway, and hungover in bed.</description></item><item><title>Blacking Out in a City Near You (ft. me) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490184/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490184/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper begins by recalling a traumatizing memory from childhood that somehow managed to seep its way into her current relationship. Old habits never truly die and we all pause to witness a moment of regression in our dear daddy. Speaking of relationships, do we dare drop the L word…lube, labia, libido? Clench your assholes as Father Cooper finally and formally introduces Henry to the world (and I say ‘clench’ because I know a certain b-word really fires some of you up).</description></item><item><title>Infiltrating His Friend Group | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490185/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490185/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper takes you on her (mental) journey as she tries to figure out how she will get herself to the one and only…Kentucky. After narrowly escaping death, she takes a moment to reflect upon this upcoming season and how she can ensure the daddy gang continues to ~vibe~ in Dunkin Donuts. In a teaching moment, she recounts an old NYC tale involving everyone’s favorite rapper (or baseball player?</description></item><item><title>How I Glucked My Way to the Top. | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490186/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490186/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome back daddies. This week, as we kick off a new season of Call Her Daddy, Father Cooper wastes no time spilling every ounce of tea - starting with a “business meeting” in Harvey Weintstein’s office, to signing with Barstool Sports and the details of the show’s new home at Spotify. Daddy Gang, get ready for an episode full of big announcements, big stories, and big green dick energy.</description></item><item><title>121- The Season Finale | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490187/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490187/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is a season finale ever dull&amp;hellip; ;) Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>120- COUPLES THERAPY (ft. Dr. Orna Guralnik) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490188/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490188/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper is joined by clinical psychologist, psychoanalyst and star of the hit docu-series Couples’ Therapy… Dr. Orna Guralnik. This episode is sure to be both interesting and insightful whether you have never attended therapy in your life or you are years deep. The duo breaks it down beginning with the basics (aka do I bring a PowerPoint presentation to my first therapy session) and even moves on to address topics such as attachment style, dissociation, and transgenerational trauma.</description></item><item><title>119- WE DON'T NEED MEN (ft. Josie Canseco) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490189/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490189/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper is joined by new LA friend, Josie Canseco. The women discuss Josie’s dad sliding into Alex’s Dms and a formal apology from Alex. Also, Josie explains growing up as the daughter of a famous professional athlete, her childhood in the spotlight, the bullying that ensued, and her journey towards establishing her individual identity. Josie addresses the topic of body dysmorphia, struggles with self love, coping mechanisms, and her journey towards happiness.</description></item><item><title>118- "I AM THAT B*TCH" (ft. Rickey Thompson) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490190/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490190/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper is joined by actor, comedian, fashion icon, social media personality, and co-host of the &amp;ldquo;We Said What We Said&amp;rdquo; podcast - Rickey Thompson. The two sit down to discuss the impact of careers in social media and the pressure to remain relevant&amp;hellip; all while protecting one&amp;rsquo;s private life. Rickey discusses his experience growing up in North Carolina; a story that began with bullying and isolation, and ended with him as prom king.</description></item><item><title>117- Backstabbing D*ck (ft. Madison Lewis) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490191/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490191/</guid><description>Podcast Description DADDY GANG. This week we are diving into the truth behind a very public and messy TikTok real-life drama. Four best friends - two men, two women, now entwined in the ultimate cheating scandal. Madison Lewis’s boyfriend went behind her back and started a relationship with her best girlfriend. The raw emotion and heartache that unfolds in this episode is relatable whether you have 100 followers on social media, or 11 million.</description></item><item><title>116- Dirty Deets from The #1 Playboy Bunny (ft. Holly Madison) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490192/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490192/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper is joined by an ICONIC guest, former playmate, Holly Madison. During her 20s, Holly entered the Playboy mansion and became one of the many girlfriends of Hugh Hefner, the infamous founder of Playboy magazine. Holly walks the daddy gang through her childhood and relationship with her family, as well as the struggles she experienced internally and socially that eventually led her to not only become a Playboy bunny, but to join the inner circle of women exclusively intimate with Heff, who at the time was 74.</description></item><item><title>115- K-Holes &amp; Chlamydia (ft. Harry Jowsey) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490193/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490193/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper is enjoying spring break with the one and only&amp;hellip; Harry Jowsey. AND THINGS ARE GETTING INSANE. Harry immediately confront Alex about a man that is talking about her head game in LA.. drama. Then, the 2 discuss their experience getting chlamydia, uncovering if guys look at your butthole during doggy-style, bleaching your asshole, and drugs &amp;amp; k-holes. Lastly, Alex tell 2 college stories she has never told on the podcast before, one including a Patriot&amp;rsquo;s player she woke up in bed with in Foxborough and doing drugs with her ex-boyfriend gone wrong.</description></item><item><title>114- This is Mia Khalifa. (ft. Mia Khalifa) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490194/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490194/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Father Cooper sits down for an interview with the one and only Mia Khalifa…move over Oprah. Mia opens up about the struggles she faced while growing up as an immigrant in a post 9/11 society and the bullying and harassment that followed. She recounts the darkest time in her life and how she overcame global shaming, death threats, and ISIS. Mia tells her story with an inspiring amount of strength and affirms how one’s past does not define their future.</description></item><item><title>113- How to Trick Him into Proposing (ft. Hannah Berner) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490195/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490195/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s episode, Father Cooper is joined by OG guest and fan favorite, Hannah Berner. AND IT’S A BIG ONE BABY. Hannah sits in the hot seat and details for the Daddy Gang how she managed to get a man on TWO knees and propose to her. The dirty details of how unglamorous engagements are, picking out your own ring, putting a ring on chubby fingers, and the awful bachelor show effect on love will all be discussed on this week’s ep.</description></item><item><title>112- The Debaucherous Tails Aboard The Litty Titty Torture Train (Ft. Egg Farts) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490196/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490196/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, join Father Cooper aboard the litty titty torture train as she details the train wreck that has been her and Lauren’s life since moving to LA. They explore not only the impact covid has had on their alcohol intake, but also how it has affected their masturbation style&amp;hellip;cue bathtub masturbation. The girls really bring relatability this week when they discuss a classic topic, egg farts. If you smelt it, you dealt it!</description></item><item><title>111- The Map to Dating Apps &amp; Rich Dudes (ft. my holemate, Paige DeSorbo) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490197/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490197/</guid><description>Podcast Description Father Cooper is joined by NYC reality tv star, fashion blogger, beautiful human and holemate- Paige Desorbo. The two describe their sides of the story to knowing each other through an ex boyfriend&amp;hellip; as one of the girl&amp;rsquo;s matched with the other&amp;rsquo;s boyfriend on a dating app.. DRAMA!!! They also discover they were dating the same famous actor in NYC at the same exact time, going on the same exact dates LOL.</description></item><item><title>110- Will The Real Slim Shady Please Stand Up | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490198/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490198/</guid><description>Podcast Description A week into being in a relationship and shit has already hit the fan for Father Cooper. Although on a journey to health and wellness, when times get tough sometimes a little toxicity just slips out like an unexpected shart. This week, Father Cooper takes a back seat to the daddy gang and shifts the spotlight. Get ready for questions of the week like you’ve never heard before&amp;hellip; CUE HER RAP DEBUT.</description></item><item><title>I HAVE A BOYFRIEND | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490199/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490199/</guid><description>Podcast Description . Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>108- Pick me, Choose me, Love me. | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490200/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490200/</guid><description>Podcast Description Father Cooper is BACK AT IT AGAIN detailing her violent interaction with her former New York neighbor and the recent incident where she almost killed her new LA neighbors. Classic. Then, Alex turns into a full ASMR Erotica Performer and details the skull fucking rendezvous that ended with her bodily chunks on the floor. Alex’s roommate, Lauren, is back and Alex calls her out for her Corona Dating App 101 fails.</description></item><item><title>107- "I'm Just Not In Love With You Anymore." | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490201/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490201/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week is pure drama, drama and more drama. Father Cooper kicks off the episode by revealing a dirty package she sent across the pond.. but more importantly, she tells the Daddy Gang about a secret she’s been keeping from them. Tune in to find out what actually happened to Alex last month in London. This story includes the police and a very toxic third party that will be exposed and revealed.</description></item><item><title>106- New Year, Old Me (ft. Toxicity) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490202/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490202/</guid><description>Podcast Description Father Cooper returns in 2021, exploiting a psychotic toxic event that recently took place between her and the infamous Mr. Sexy Zoom Man. This drama filled story fully exposes Alex for attempting a manipulation tactic gone wrong. She fucked up her own scheme and now has to pay the price. WHO IS READY FOR TOXIC ALEX TO BE BACK?… her therapist is guaranteed to be getting ghosted this week.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to the Daddy Gang | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490203/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490203/</guid><description>Podcast Description From the Father’s mouth to your ears, Alex Cooper welcomes you to the worldwide phenomenon that is Call Her Daddy. Strap in for raw conversations on sex, relationships, mental health and more. New episodes every Wednesday. Listen free, only on Spotify! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>105- Goodbye 2020 | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490204/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490204/</guid><description>Podcast Description Goodbye 2020… Father Cooper takes on a solo episode this week and closes out the insane year of 2020 with the Daddy Gang. She talks highs and lows of her year as well as the Daddy Gang&amp;rsquo;s. She also gives a quick dick riding tip to girls on how to make sure the small dick stays in and doesn&amp;rsquo;t fall out, what to do when your boyfriend slut shames you for your past, training men like you train a dog, a story of a guy Alex fucked to use his rooftop pool in NYC, the issue of dating someone in college after you have graduated, what to do when you find your boyfriend saving photos on Instagram of other girls, the rules to being friends with your ex, the McRib?</description></item><item><title>104- The Roadmap to his A**hole | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490205/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490205/</guid><description>Podcast Description Father Cooper discusses what is about to happen in the next 24 hours of her life, and it includes 2 men. A DP?! No lol. Maybe. Then, she is joined by the brilliant sex therapist and Daddy Gang favorite, Emily Morse! Emily and Alex discuss how to tell your partner you have sexual trauma (TRIGGER WARNING 14:22-17:51), men that can’t get hard, dating a pre-mature ejaculator, how to ride dick with your legs around his head, ways to finger and eat his/her asshole, vaginismus, herpes AND MUCH MORE.</description></item><item><title>103- Tana Mongeau Exposed | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490206/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490206/</guid><description>Podcast Description 2 years later, the bitch showed up and immediately regretted it. TANA MONGEAU EXPOSED. #DADDYGANG Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>102- The Toxic Dick Daze (ft. Katie Florence) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490207/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490207/</guid><description>Podcast Description DADDY GANG-This week, Alex discusses the intense fallout of her decision to ghost her therapist for 3 straight weeks while being in a foreign country quarantining with a man. Not smart Big Al! Then, the first ever Daddy Gang member sits down with Alex to join the show this week! Katie Florence, who started her career as a substitute-school teacher now turned Tik-Tok star, initially caught Alex’s attention from the relationship comedy videos she was making during quarantine.</description></item><item><title>101- Boyfriend D*ck (ft. Harry Jowsey) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490208/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490208/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week’s episode, Alex details her Cabo excursion with a man, as well as why she is in London with a man. Then, Harry Jowsey, an irrelevant one-hit-wonder reality television star, joins the show to talk ALL THINGS SEX AND DATING. They discuss girls over performing in the bedroom, the terrifying experience Harry had when he first got his ass eaten by a wrestler, and his first disastrous anal experience.</description></item><item><title>100- MOTHER COOPER | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490209/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490209/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Transcript</description></item><item><title>99- BREAKING NEWS | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490210/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490210/</guid><description>Podcast Description DADDY GANG- BREAKING NEWS. At the beginning of this week&amp;rsquo;s episode, Alex divulges what is going on in her life and provides breaking news. THEN, Hannah Berner is back this week with Alex to discuss meeting the men they are dating’s parents… or not? Discussing men’s dating history and the fascinating question which is- what if the guy you are dating has a history of dating a type of girl and you aren’t it?</description></item><item><title>98- The Red Wedding (ft. Lauren &amp; Hannah Berner) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490211/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490211/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to The Red Wedding Mother FUCKERS. Alex is joined by childhood best friend, Lauren, to exploit the recent drama that she has been involved in with her ex- Slim Shady, his best friend who is getting married next week, and his current side hoe. Lots and lots of drama, which ends in Alex potentially attending a wedding? Then, Hannah Berner joins Alex to discuss an update on both of their dating lives.</description></item><item><title>97- The Life of a Porn Star (ft. Lana Rhoades) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490212/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490212/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Call Her Daddy introduces it’s first Porn Star guest, Lana Rhoades. Lana discusses life before, during, and after porn. Lana knew since she was 13 years old she wanted to do porn, she explains how the hard core scenes (gang bangs) have left her scarred, and her dating life after porn, money and happiness. The girls also discuss eating your man’s ass while he is on all fours, different types of balls, school girl role-play, and the strangest role-play Lana proposed to a boyfriend and got turned down to do.</description></item><item><title>96- The Orgasm Gap &amp; Forced Sex Fantasies (ft. Sex With Emily) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490213/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490213/</guid><description>Podcast Description DADDY GANG!!! This week Father Cooper kicks off the episode with an update on a man she is dating. The update includes a SERIOUS social media road block, one that she has never encountered with a man before&amp;hellip; so naturally the uncharted territory calls for a full mental break down!!! THEN, Emily Morse, the sex therapist best known for her podcast &amp;lsquo;Sex with Emily,&amp;rsquo; joins the show to discuss an array of sexual topics.</description></item><item><title>95- Mental Terrorism (ft. The Bitch Bible) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490214/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490214/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Alex discusses the scary reality that is now life in isolation. She explains the affects that the time alone has had on her love life, the two 30 year-old men she is currently dating, her journey towards health and the battle she’s facing in attempting to leave the crazy behind and in her past. THERE IS ALSO A GUEST THIS WEEK. Introducing, Jackie Schimmel, who is the host of ‘The Bitch Bible’ Podcast.</description></item><item><title>94- Bisexuality &amp; Depression (ft. Maggie Lindemann) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490215/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490215/</guid><description>Podcast Description Call Her Daddy gets a bit more serious, dark, and real this week. Father Cooper kicks it off with a sex update and some healthy news regarding her dating life and the show. Then, the guest this week, Maggie Lindemann, a singer/songwriter, joins the show and discusses her personal journey to coming out as a bisexual woman. Maggie explains when she knew she was bisexual, how she revealed the news to her family via text message and to the world via live stream (!</description></item><item><title>93- The Sloppy Toppy Delight | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490216/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490216/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week is a solo episode with your father! Alex is detailing her sexcapades with Mr. Sexy Zoom Man ft. her cum in his beard, his pussy eating skills, her sex with him, and a battle between him and another man that made her realize how she feels about him. Alex also gets deep and opens up to the Daddy Gang about anxiety and some hate she has been receiving.</description></item><item><title>92- MILEY CYRUS | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490217/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490217/</guid><description>Podcast Description THE DADDY OF ALL DADDIES HAS ARRIVED. Miley Fucking Cyrus joins the show this week and immediately hits it off with your father. Miley is officially Daddy Gang and spills an extreme amount of tea this week. So get your popcorn, relax, and enjoy the show folks. Heartbreak, trauma, therapy, guilt, girl-on-girl, being put on the no-fly list for smuggling drugs, her relationship with Hannah Montana, the first person she lost her male virginity to, her &amp;lsquo;Love Languages&amp;rsquo;, what she is looking for in a relationship, her personal sex advice, AND MORE.</description></item><item><title>91- Dabble with Emasculating Him (ft Olivia O'Brien) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490218/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490218/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, your single father brings you along the journey as she narrates her first date with Mr. Sexy Zoom Man, and you can clearly hear the sexual tension through the microphone. THEN, the beautiful and talented singer/songwriter Olivia O’Brien, well known for writing songs about the men she dates (very on brand with CHD) joins the show. Olivia dishes new information about the “house rule,” which will tell you who has the power in your relationship.</description></item><item><title>90- I'm Going to LA... | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490219/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490219/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex is going to LA for a business trip&amp;hellip;./ potential date?! This week, Father Cooper reveals that she might for the first time be mixing business with pleasure. But is convinced it is worth it&amp;hellip;lol. A man in entertainment and not an athlete?? We love to see it. She also discusses what is means when your boyfriend tells you to block a girl on social media BIG RED FLAG Also this week, HANNAH IS BACK.</description></item><item><title>89- "I F**ked the Mascot" (ft. Hannah Berner) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490220/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490220/</guid><description>Podcast Description Father Cooper is joined by a guest who is bringing the energy and a shit-ton of wild stories this week. Daddy Gang, give a warm welcome to Hannah Berner. In this week&amp;rsquo;s episode, Hannah fucks a mascot, Alex lies about Chlamydia, and a man does coke off Hannah&amp;rsquo;s tit. Are you READY?! Also, the Flirting Bible is revealed, the women dive into Hannah&amp;rsquo;s time on reality television, her parents watching her have sex, and their commonality of both having been Division 1 athletes, and also their love for f*cking athletes!</description></item><item><title>88- The L Word. | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490221/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490221/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex is coming clean about the man that has been in her life behind the scenes for 5 years&amp;hellip; and the L word is used. Also, A DADDY GANG MEMBER IS FEATURED ON THE SHOW THIS WEEK!!!!! Our guest is bringing you a very relatable situation- the &amp;lsquo;in between&amp;rsquo; stage. We are discussing how to navigate it and calling her out on misreading some clear signs. Lastly, the topic of initiating sex 50/50 in a relationship is hammered into the brains of every woman this week.</description></item><item><title>87- PSA: He Doesn’t Like You | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490222/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490222/</guid><description>Podcast Description Your Father, Alexandra, gets deep this week and walks women through the wake-up call they all need. Stop clinging on to every little thing a men says to you and LOOK AT THE BIG PICTURE FACTS. If you viewed your dating life from a third party view.. what would you think of yourself? An episode EVERY woman needs to hear. Also, giving a huge tip for women that are having a hard time achieving an orgasm/ have never had one (wink wink ASMR porn).</description></item><item><title>86- Fuckboy Love &amp; Fingering for Dummies (ft. Savannah Montano) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490223/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490223/</guid><description>Podcast Description HERE WE GO!!! THE RUNDOWN FOR THIS WEEK&amp;rsquo;S SHOW: We are instructing men on exactly how to finger a girl&amp;rsquo;s butt during doggy, which finger to use and the speed at which it should be happening; normalizing butt plugs and how it makes a women&amp;rsquo;s orgasm SO much better, how to get a guy to be ok with a vibrator in the bedroom, getting cheated on, why we pick fuck boys, the OG way to finger a girl, and handing over the secret potion for women of how to make a man fall in love by &amp;lsquo;fucking his fingers.</description></item><item><title>85- Let's Have Sex Again...(ft. Savannah Montano) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490224/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490224/</guid><description>Podcast Description 2 PART SERIES. Alex is joined by guest Savannah Montano, a girl she idolized at a young age because of the promiscuous lifestyle Sav promoted as a teen on the internet. The two girls, now in their 20s, have become friends through Instagram and are talking dating high profiled men, strategically not sleeping with men for an extended period of time (3 months), and Savannah addresses her favorite sex- the &amp;lsquo;slow stroke&amp;rsquo;- and gives details of how to give head/ride on top.</description></item><item><title>84- The 3rd Roommate Speaks... | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490225/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490225/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week&amp;rsquo;s guest is the infamous third roommate who lived with Alex and Sophia. The episode officially closes the chapter surrounding ALL the drama. ONWARD!!! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>83- Dave Portnoy- America's #1 Porn Star? | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490226/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490226/</guid><description>Podcast Description https://blacklivesmatters.carrd.co https://blacklivesmatters.carrd.co https://blacklivesmatters.carrd.co https://blacklivesmatters.carrd.co https://blacklivesmatters.carrd.co https://blacklivesmatters.carrd.co . Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>82- The Funeral | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490227/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490227/</guid><description>Podcast Description A new era begins. A single father, a divorced father, moves forward with the show. But first - we must attend this funeral and mourn the loss. Then&amp;hellip; WE PARTY! (Daddy Gang drinking game- drink every time Alex says the word f*ck… you’ll all be hammered). Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>81- Daddy Speaks | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490228/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490228/</guid><description>Podcast Description El Pres Explains the Call Her Daddy Fiasco From the Barstool Perspective Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>80- How To Keep Them Interested During Quarantine | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490229/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490229/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kesha&amp;hellip;The End . Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>79- OnlyFans = WHORES | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490230/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490230/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s all about to change&amp;hellip; Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>78- Seeking Arrangements: Our Story | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490231/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490231/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is how you should do Corona. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>77- Re-release (Corona Edition) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490232/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490232/</guid><description>Podcast Description We love you all, stay safe. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>76- Sorry for the Shit Show | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490233/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490233/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>75- We Had Fun | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490234/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490234/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>74- It's Over | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490235/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490235/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>73- SUPLEH | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490236/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490236/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>72- Prisoners of Azkaban | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490237/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490237/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>71- Floop's Fooglies | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490238/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490238/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>70- Dear Side Hoe... | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490239/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490239/</guid><description>Podcast Description The episode kicks off with a recap from the girls as they discuss their latest drama, specifically Alex who catches Slim Shady in a lie on her recent trip to visit him! Uh oh! They also address the proper way to behave during the early stages of dating and when to post to social media… daddies… we gotta reel it back in. Lastly, men with little dicks need to stop lusting after women with fat asses AND yes, we are giving hand jobs again.</description></item><item><title>69- EPISODE 69 (ft. Chlamydia) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490240/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490240/</guid><description>Podcast Description The episode you have all been waiting for&amp;hellip; and we have been dreading. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>68- Nudes &amp; The New York Post | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490241/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490241/</guid><description>Podcast Description The girls kick off this week&amp;rsquo;s episode discussing their photo shoot from HELL and what to do when you are dealing with a greedy little bitch boy who asks “Can I get more?” after you send a nude. Knock. It. Off. Also this week, the girls do something a little different as they discuss some pop-culture in way that is most likely going to get them sued! Yay! Last but not least, it&amp;rsquo;s now Alex&amp;rsquo;s turn to spill the deets on her dating life.</description></item><item><title>67- BACK AT IT AGAIN | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490242/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490242/</guid><description>Podcast Description WE ARE BACK. Get ready for a very different episode this week. The girls have decided to do Call Her Daddy a little different this year starting with a HUGE announcement from Sofia and a deeply personal account from Alex. The Fathers have feelings!? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, they are still just as unwell. This week&amp;rsquo;s episode addresses the topic of &amp;lsquo;first impressions&amp;rsquo; with your significant other&amp;rsquo;s friends and family and how to handle it.</description></item><item><title>Happy New Year | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490243/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490243/</guid><description>Podcast Description 2020 is the year for the Daddy Gang&amp;hellip;. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Merry Christmas | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490244/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490244/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Holidays Daddy Gang :) WE LOVE YOU Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>66- Why We Can't Cum | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490245/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490245/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week&amp;rsquo;s episode kicks off with a mental breakdown from Alex who went snooping at a guys house and saw something she shouldn&amp;rsquo;t have. Risky business! Also, the girls discuss why they (and women everywhere) can&amp;rsquo;t cum during sex and a revolutionary way to take an a** pic. Ladies, this will be the only nude you will want to take from now on, GUARANTEED. Plus, the girls debate if it&amp;rsquo;s ever okay to send a dirty video.</description></item><item><title>65- The Daddy Hotline (3) ft. Anal | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490246/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490246/</guid><description>Podcast Description “How has your dating life been affected since starting this podcast???” It&amp;rsquo;s a question the fathers receive regularly…and they are answering it candidly in this week&amp;rsquo;s episode. They also tackle some tough questions like “What is the best form of birth control?” and “How kinky is too kinky?” Tune in, as the fathers have some MAJOR differing opinions this week!!! Lastly, with the Holidays approaching, Alex and Sofia are telling us exactly what to get our fuck buddies for Christmas.</description></item><item><title>64- The Cocaine Chronicles | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490247/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490247/</guid><description>Podcast Description We all know Sofia has gotten into some trouble in her past….well now she is finally ready to tell the full story of her time behind bars! Get ready for some bend over and cough fun because this is a genuinely crazy story (our court system is f*cked!) Also in this weeks episode, the girls have had a complete change of heart and think you should NOT delete pictures of your ex but only under ONE condition: men, if you want to up your dick game, trust us on this one.</description></item><item><title>63- How Our Families Really Feel… | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490248/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490248/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex and Sofia get real as they dive into the family drama they have endured since starting this podcast…extended family is the worst! (LOL). Happy Thanksgiving! This week the girls are discussing a brilliant way to make friends (especially in a new city), the biggest dating app no-no that even the smartest men are committing (watch out for this one ladies), and lastly, THE BALL! As in mens&amp;rsquo; balls.</description></item><item><title>62- Oprah &amp; F*cking Your Friend's Ex | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490249/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490249/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yes. It is true. Call Her Daddy has been nominated for an award alongside OPRAH WINFREY. For what you may ask? It&amp;rsquo;s not what you would expect! Make sure to tune in, Alex and Sofia are giving us all the details. Also this week, the girls go on a rant resemblant of an exorcism as they express their disdain for all things pertaining to the gym…specifically girls that get dolled up to work out- STOP WEARING YOUR HAIR DOWN.</description></item><item><title>61- Revenge Porn | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490250/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490250/</guid><description>Podcast Description The girls partied hard this past week and are getting into all the wild details including strip clubs, head injuries, and an NHL team! Wahoo! Also, Alex and Sofia have breaking news regarding TWO major iPhone updates/hacks. If you have ever thought of sending a nude or having FaceTime sex, you better listen up! Lastly, the girls talk about revenge porn AND do a rate and review of a fellow daddygang member&amp;rsquo;s nude&amp;hellip; in real time.</description></item><item><title>60- You F*cked Up, Now What? | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490251/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490251/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex has a black eye and is telling us exactly what happened PLUS, she has a confession…she ended up in bed with an ex! Get the full story- it&amp;rsquo;s as crazy as it sounds. Also this week, the girls discuss drunken fuckups and exactly how to recover. Whether you got sloppy in front of a girl you&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to bang or texted your crush something super embarrassing, we&amp;rsquo;ve got you.</description></item><item><title>59- Backhand That Cl*t | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490252/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490252/</guid><description>Podcast Description The girls get serious as they tell a chilling story that took place in Elizabeth, New Jersey. One they will never forget involving an abandoned house, law enforcement, and oh yeah, they&amp;rsquo;ve got it all on film (check out the CHD Instagram). Also this week, Alex and Sofia discuss a sex tip so scary they&amp;rsquo;ve only seen it done in porn&amp;hellip; until now. Introducing ‘Scream&amp;rsquo; and ‘The Joker&amp;rsquo;- they tried it out for the daddies and are giving you all the details.</description></item><item><title>58- The Daddy Hotline (2) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490253/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490253/</guid><description>Podcast Description Covering everything from ‘how to fuck your professor&amp;rsquo; to ‘moving on from a fuckbuddy&amp;rsquo;, the girls are giving us a good mix of crazy and healthy in this week&amp;rsquo;s episode! They are also getting a little personal this week, as they share their worst date experiences and throw some shade at a shared nemesis of theirs (cough cough you know who you are!). Last but not least, the fathers are providing a solution to your Instagram stalking dilemma.</description></item><item><title>57- Every Man’s Achilles Heel | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490254/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490254/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week&amp;rsquo;s episode, the girls share their personal experiences with bondage…including special guest the HDMI cord! Sofia also shares another embarrassing story from her past…believe it or not it is arguably the most embarrassing thus far. Lastly, Alex and Sofia call out all the girls who are posting pictures HOLDING their ass in place. Enough is enough! Also, a sex/blowjob tip that has to do with only a guys LEFT side…his Achilles Heel.</description></item><item><title>56- The Instagram Scam | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490255/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490255/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sofia tells us about a traumatizing experience she had while her mom was in town this past week…just say no to drugs kids! Also in the episode, the girls discuss uncircumcised dicks. They can be complicated so listen up. Even if you have never encountered one, you should know how to Gluck it like a daddy. They also talk about fitness girls on instagram, ass injections, and last but not least, eating the puss* from behind.</description></item><item><title>55- Body Count &amp; The Social Vulture | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490256/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490256/</guid><description>Podcast Description The girls discuss past sexual partners, how many is too many, and everything you&amp;rsquo;ve ever wondered about body count- including the EXACT number girls should tell their man. Also, they dive into the taboo topic of bad personal hygiene for women… men have been complaining about the taste/smell of their girl&amp;rsquo;s clam (worst nightmare), but don&amp;rsquo;t worry we have a solution! Last but not least, bringing you the social vulture.</description></item><item><title>54- The Walk of Shame | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490257/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490257/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week&amp;rsquo;s episode, Alex and Sofia are giving health and wellness a good ol&amp;rsquo; fashioned try. You heard that right! The girls discuss the importance of “having your own life” in a relationship and where so many women go wrong- especially WAGS, (wives and girlfriends of professional athletes). They also discuss the most cringe-y thing a guy can post on his dating profile (no thanks), clout chasing, and most importantly WALKS OF SHAME.</description></item><item><title>53- Alex &amp; Sofia | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490258/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490258/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is an episode your therapist would HIGHLY recommend you do not listen to&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; The girls discuss the amount of time you wait in between sex with different people…as in, how many is too many in a day? In a week? In an HOUR? And should you feel bad or embrace your inner freak? Everything answered on this week&amp;rsquo;s episode. They also address the multiple personality wheel…aka the swift personality change that occurs when arguing with your partner and how to use it to your advantage.</description></item><item><title>52- College Life: Being Hot vs. Not | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490259/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490259/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to College 101 Daddies! Bringing you the ultimate guide for back to school- the College Playbook. Get ready to finesse the fuck out of your college campus and pay close attention, because navigating school is a little different when you are a 5 vs. 10 (apologies in advance)! They also talk about what to do when you&amp;rsquo;re BLOCKED, getting Shadow banned on Instagram, and a sex move that is so simple yet so effective…the Hamburger.</description></item><item><title>51- Win Your Ex Back | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490260/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490260/</guid><description>Podcast Description Men are out here sucking their own dicks, sticking them in tissue boxes, and comparing them to remote controls…and we are here to address it! Also, we discuss the ultimate strategy to win your Ex back, a hack to take the perfect selfie, and male dick pics. And last but not least, we talk about what to do AFTER he cums and how you SHOULD keep sucking&amp;hellip; Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>50- MILF HUNTER (Guest #1) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490261/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490261/</guid><description>Podcast Description No description needed. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>49 - Stop Ruining Your Relationship | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490262/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490262/</guid><description>Podcast Description Girls get more insecure after they get into a relationship. FACTS. This week, the fathers discuss why this is the case and how it leads to women doing bat shit crazy things&amp;hellip; including Alex&amp;rsquo;s most brilliant/insane behavior yet. They also get into a new sex position called “Time Out” for all you naughty hoes and how to get verified on Instagram REAL quick. P.S- Alex and Sofia reveal their personal experiences with some serious stalkers Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>48- The Daddy Hotline | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490263/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490263/</guid><description>Podcast Description The girls are covering everything from, “Is it okay to stay friends with your ex?” to the &amp;lsquo;bonus nude&amp;rsquo;- a nude that is saving relationships one send at a time&amp;hellip;milfhunter didn&amp;rsquo;t even know about it!!! They also discuss dealing with your significant others parents (cue pervy dads), men posting shirtless pics/food on the gram, and the most insane way this girl caught her man cheating. Lastly, there is a consent app celebrities are using and the girls are giving you all the details.</description></item><item><title>47- Open Relationships | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490264/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490264/</guid><description>Podcast Description The girls talk about their traumatic last week living in the Lower East Side of NYC (Sofia witnessed a stabbing). They also discuss dressing up in lingerie for your man…with some personal FAILS, everything about open relationships, and some super dirty school girl role-play. Including detailed, nasty, line-for-line things to say to pull it off. P.S. Enough with the b-day reposts, no one cares!!! Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>46- Hornier on Our Periods | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490265/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490265/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, the girls address two things men do that are total turn offs- baby talk and getting too drunk. Also, the girls tell a recent personal story of their own drunk escapades in NYC, Alex&amp;rsquo;s husband, throw-up, and a Restoration Hardware couch. They also have a confession…they too have taken pictures of men while they are not looking/sleeping…and explain the reasons why. Lastly, they discuss all things period sex (including oral) with some embarrassing personal stories!</description></item><item><title>45- Post Sex Tape Regret | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490266/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490266/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this weeks episode, Alex and Sofia recap their staycation experience at an old NY hotel and it is TERRIFYING. They also discuss nonconsensual sex tapes, when to know and accept you&amp;rsquo;re just a fuck, and groupies taking pics of the men they just had sex with….while they are asleep. Last but not least, introducing the PSTR-Post Sex Tape Regret. It&amp;rsquo;s a wild ride :) Also, they surprise the daddy gang with an added iPhone recording.</description></item><item><title>44- Girls He Fucks vs. Girls He Dates | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490267/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490267/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lots to cover on this weeks episode! Sofia and Alex talk about the types of girls men choose to fuck vs. date, and they are getting extremely specific/personal- talking about their exs. They are also discussing the REAL reason females cockblock their girlfriends, instagram bios that are preventing you from getting laid, and two new moves that will make your behind look like you got ass injections! Also, Alex reads a text from her mom that puts everyone&amp;rsquo;s stalking skills to shame.</description></item><item><title>43- Run-ins With Your Ex | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490268/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490268/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex and Sofia are talking about running into your ex (accidental or on purpose), how to handle it, and reminisce on their times of being total losers and letting a guy get the best of them. They also discuss escaping the friendzone for girls and an update for men who continue to marinate there. And lastly, TWO new blow job updates- The Gluck Gluck Turbo Edition. P.S- We gotta stop with birthday months&amp;hellip; Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>42- Let Him Watch Porn | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490269/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490269/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, the Fathers are discussing the highly anticipated porn debate-should your man be allowed to watch it? Uhhhhhh, duh. Strip clubs, massage parlors, boys nights, you name it, the girls are talking about it and get ready for a reality check. Also, presenting two new sex moves that will have men celebrating WAY more than just their independence this 4th of July. Introducing, the Superman and Glory Tit Shot (tits want facials too)!</description></item><item><title>41- How To Eat Pussy | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490270/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490270/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sofia and Alex PROMISE that after this episode, you will eat the clam and make her O in a way that has not been done before. The. Seven. Wonders. Of. The. Pussy. Eating. World. As an extension of the &amp;lsquo;Cooch Gobbler,&amp;rsquo; there is something for even the most advanced sex gurus to learn. Also, the girls finally discuss hooking up with co-workers, including some personal experiences. And lastly, we are telling you where you can get some cheap Plan B and it is NOT planned parenthood!</description></item><item><title>40- Rejection &amp; Exposing the Clit | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490271/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490271/</guid><description>Podcast Description The girls discuss their encounter with a #daddygang member at a drug store in NY and let&amp;rsquo;s just say shit got wild! They also introduce some new sex pointers, including a move that Alex said made a man cum in under one minute- cue the ‘Pendulum Pussy&amp;rsquo;. And lastly, they get into REJECTION. It&amp;rsquo;s happened to all of us, and this is how to deal, like a daddy. P.</description></item><item><title>39- Squirting &amp; Ghosting | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490272/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490272/</guid><description>Podcast Description The girls finally get into all things SQUIRTING. What is it, how to do it, how to fake it, are men into it? Give HIM a facial! Squirt or be squirted on. They also discuss some criminal activity they witnessed at the bar by multiple men, a serious Gluck Gluck update, and some new social media drama involving fake influencers. Lastly, listen up daddies, this is how you deal with being ghosted, once and for all.</description></item><item><title>38- Welcome to Slut Camp | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490273/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490273/</guid><description>Podcast Description The girls are discussing shower sex, panic boners, and Slut Camp. Yes, you heard that right. Welcome to Slut Camp, where you will learn how to conceal the slut and trick your man into thinking you are wifey material. Everyone deserves a slut phase with no repercussions! They also talk poop fetishes and where they originated (army bases?), embarrassing things bitches are doing on instagram, and last but not least, Alex tells a tragic tale involving her a** hole, a penis, and a cheating scandal.</description></item><item><title>37- Cheating Olympics &amp; Apartment Orgys | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490274/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490274/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this weeks episode, the girls tell a story of an unexpected visitor who showed up to their apartment…and shit got sexual. They also address what signs to look out for if you think your partner is being shady. Cheat or be cheated on! Lastly, they discuss hot, steamy bathroom sex, a serious tip to spice things up with your guy/girl in public group settings, and some hacks that could RUIN LIVES (Do Not Disturb, Reverse Phone Lookup, Uber locator).</description></item><item><title>36- Sex Sins &amp; Girls DMing First | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490275/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490275/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex and Sofia are talking datings apps and sliding into the DMs, specifically for girls who are not shooting their shot and absolutely need to be. They are also talking sex ‘sins,&amp;rsquo; where they cover the basics like foreplay, screaming and scratching but also include some you haven&amp;rsquo;t thought of and are probably committing. You don&amp;rsquo;t deserve to f*** if you are doing these!! Finally, the girls lose their shit while trying to explain the newest most underrated sex position.</description></item><item><title>35- Professional Athletes | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490276/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490276/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex and Sofia are getting into how to make your girl and/or guy jealous, especially out at the bar/in social settings. It&amp;rsquo;s unhealthy but it works! They also discuss a little black (manipulative) book a guy left behind that got his d*** sucked, their embarrassing makeup moments- when a guy walks in on the foundation/eyebrow/contour phase, and a PSA from milf hunter on how he likes girls to ride it on top.</description></item><item><title>34- Fu** Dave Portnoy | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490277/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490277/</guid><description>Podcast Description The girls discuss some scary things they witnessed at the bar this past weekend and are once again helping men get laid (we are giving you a makeover). They are also talking about how to use whiskey dick to fuck with a fuckboy and a jack-in-the-box nude to make a man cry. Lastly, they get into the scariest snooping hack to date which reveals ALL of your partner&amp;rsquo;s password.</description></item><item><title>33- Clits and Coke | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490278/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490278/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is it okay for people in relationships to like the opposite sex&amp;rsquo;s pics on instagram? The girls are addressing the topic and introduce a psychotic way to see ALL of your partner&amp;rsquo;s instagram activity. They also discuss an amazing way to dominate dating apps (that has worked for both of the girls), a serious criminal past involving the Fathers, and lastly a sex position that made a guy cry that involves girl-on-top and NO eye contact.</description></item><item><title>32- Cat Fishing &amp; Confetti Cumshots | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490279/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490279/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you know the 3 ways a guy orgasms? Introducing the Confetti Cumshot, the Warning Shot, and the Follow the Leader Cumshot. Also in the episode- Picking up a girl at the gym is NEVER okay, but if you must, we are telling you how to do it successfully ft. the water fountain aka watering hole. The girls have had it with the modern day catfishing on instagram, it&amp;rsquo;s now gone too far and they are calling celebs out on their bullshit.</description></item><item><title>31- You're Just a Hole | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490280/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490280/</guid><description>Podcast Description The girls are discussing some hard truths- men only care about the face, people who only mention eye color are ugly, and their sexual history together. They also talk public sex…high school forced the girls to hook up in some WEIRD places, (church, tractor, Dick Sporting Goods Tent, etc.) Lastly, they analyze a phenomenon that will have girls cringing and men clapping- WHY WOMEN ASK MEN SHIT THEY KNOW WILL HURT THEIR FEELINGS (relayed by the worst offenders).</description></item><item><title>30- Sex Toys &amp; How to Not Catch Feelings | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490281/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490281/</guid><description>Podcast Description FINALLY, the girls get into sex toys- their favorites, how to use them, and when to introduce them in the bedroom. They also discuss the tricky art of how to not catch feelings…that works every time. They also discuss a new shady trend amongst sugar daddies (beware), couples that have joint instagram accounts, and a new blow job technique that involves TEETH. Bonus: how to catch your girl cheating&amp;hellip;and it involves her toilet seat cleanliness Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>29- Why They Won't F*ck You | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490282/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490282/</guid><description>Podcast Description The girls are discussing the harsh reasons your boyfriend or girlfriend have stopped fucking you… always keeping it real on Call Her Daddy! They also explain how to take the perfect nude with detailed descriptions of their personal favorites, how dick pics can be sexy if done correctly, and talk about a new fetish that is as popular as it is disturbing, welcoming Party and Play porn. Lastly, they tell one of their most embarrassing stories together that took place on an airplane.</description></item><item><title>28- Finessing a Fuckboy (or girl) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490283/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490283/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex and Sofia listened to another podcast..and want to apologize to their listeners in this week&amp;rsquo;s episode. They also discuss a sex move they recently encountered that EVERY man should be doing to women- introducing the Mona Lisa. They also address plan B and faking pregnancies. Lastly, they discuss a huge trend in social media that needs to STOP and reveal an old internet hack that is pure gold (Hi Google).</description></item><item><title>27- Our First Foursome. | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490284/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490284/</guid><description>Podcast Description Attn: This episode is crazier than usual. Alex and Sofia recap Cabo, where they had Kylie Jenner&amp;rsquo;s smoking hot body guard in tow…the one rumored to be Stormi&amp;rsquo;s dad. They get into fingering the crazy out of a crazy girl and awkward sex (farts, pets, and death threats). They also talk missionary sex- which most of you are doing wrong, the New York slasher, and first date DONT&amp;rsquo;S for men.</description></item><item><title>26- Drunk Sex: Blackout Edition | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490285/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490285/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex and Sofia reminisce on the days when they worked corporate jobs and somehow didn&amp;rsquo;t get fired for their inappropriate behavior. They also break down a new strategy for men on how-to successfully transition from liking a girl&amp;rsquo;s pics on IG to sliding into her (DMs). Lastly, they get into the horrors of drunk sex, Instagram famous frauds, and an amazing iPhone technology hack that will elevate and spice up your sexting game.</description></item><item><title>25- Post D*ck Appointment Flashbacks | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490286/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490286/</guid><description>Podcast Description The girls discuss their crazy weekend, as Alex traveled to see a man and Sofia headed back to her hometown. They also give men brilliant pointers regarding their Instagram picture game (including some huge instagram DONT&amp;rsquo;S) and introduce the rotisserie chicken move that all freaks needs to be using in the bedroom. Finally, Sofia tells a horror story of a past relationship as well as her complicated relationship with Kid Cudi.</description></item><item><title>24- Confessions of a Mistress | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490287/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490287/</guid><description>Podcast Description In typical Call Her Daddy style, the girls unveil how to cheat or catch a cheater in 2019. They also get into high sex, provide a sure fire way to pick up girls at a bar, and expose a celebrity cheater- straight from the source herself. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>23- Cuckolding, Everyone’s Doing It | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490288/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490288/</guid><description>Podcast Description The girls give us a technology hack to help you get away with murder or better yet, cheating! They also give some advice regarding texting response time, Instagram filters, and initiating sex. Finally, they discuss all things cuckolding and end the episode with the craziest #daddygang stories to date. Stay till the end.. you don&amp;rsquo;t want to miss this. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>22- Condom Poker | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490289/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490289/</guid><description>Podcast Description The girls are here to discuss how to get over a breakup and introduce one of the riskiest games of poker ever played…condom poker. Watch out for STD&amp;rsquo;s! They also get into the ‘double tap&amp;rsquo; feature on the iPhone and how you can use it to become a master manipulator. Last but definitely not least, the girls bring us a new sex tip to make sure your sex is hot and steamy and it involves flipping the bird.</description></item><item><title>21 - Sex Tapes &amp; Cucumber Fun | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490290/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490290/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode the girls reveal a crazy Vegas story including a cucumber and Rachel Bush takes to twitter once again to bash the girls. Also, Sofia has a GYNO appointment that goes terribly wrong, and the girls talk role play, flacid d****, and fake IG accounts. Last but not least, the girls come to the rescue to tell you what to get your significant other or fuck buddy for Valentines day!</description></item><item><title>20- Butt Stuff | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490291/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490291/</guid><description>Podcast Description The girls talk about everything butt related (including ass eating), the best way to pick up a guy at the bar, and finally explain what the hell happened when they were stood up by celebrity guest- Tana Mongeau. They also address some #daddygang grievances, models turned DJs, and the ridiculousness of name dropping Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>19 - Men, Talk Nasty to Us | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490292/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490292/</guid><description>Podcast Description The girls give an update on their apartment and it includes a break in. They also address drunk snaps, thirst traps, and that promoter life. Finally they get into dirty talk for men, a man&amp;rsquo;s O face, and Alex introduces a new sex technique&amp;hellip;cue the &amp;lsquo;chopsticks move&amp;rsquo;. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>18 - Facetime Sex &amp; Morning Head | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490293/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490293/</guid><description>Podcast Description The girls get graphic as they give you yet another mind blowing blow job strategy and the hottest moves to nail the perfect FaceTime Sex. They also divulge one of their craziest stories from a trip they took to LA involving an A list celeb. PSA: Everyone should be putting #CallHerDaddy in their dating app bio. Listen to the episode to find out WHY. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>17 - Daddy Girls’ Arrested and Kinky Fetishes | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490294/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490294/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sofia gives us crazy new details surrounding her arrest and the girls discuss the genitalia of the men in their office. They also get into some bizarre fetishes while outing their foot fetish stalker. They implement a new rule for Facetune, Instagram stories, and pictures with your ex. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>16 - Double Penetration and a Happy New Year | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490295/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490295/</guid><description>Podcast Description The duo is back for 2019 talking double penetration, girls faking nudes, and the BEST Instagram trick for guys to get laid. They also share on masturbating to a friend in the other room and introduce the term “soaking,” something near and dear to Sofia&amp;rsquo;s heart. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>BONUS EP - Meet Biznasty And His Uncircumcised Dick | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490296/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490296/</guid><description>Podcast Description Biznasty talks squirters, flaps, and gets offended when the Daddy Girl&amp;rsquo;s ask him to get naked in the studio. Enjoy! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>15 - Escaping the Friend Zone | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490297/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490297/</guid><description>Podcast Description The girls get into masturbating and sharing toys. They also provide the blue print for men to escape the friend zone. Finally, they discuss the real life horror story that has become their neighborhood. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>14 - Are We F***ing on a First Date? | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490298/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490298/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex and Sofia have different opinions regarding sex on a first date. Shocker! And the pros and cons to both. Alex also discusses bringing a guy back to her ex-boyfriends apartment, and what would this episode be without some good ol&amp;rsquo; fashion talk about face f***ing. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>13 - Let it Snow...it’s Time for a Facial | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490299/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490299/</guid><description>Podcast Description With the Call Her Daddy Instagram page down…the girls go WILD in this weeks episode. They talk facials, hearing each other getting it on in the next room, and take notes people, they are getting uncomfortably graphic with how to talk dirty. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>12 - Ride it like an Equestrian | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490300/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490300/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex and Sofia give a detailed description on riding D to the finish line- introducing the ‘Rocket&amp;rsquo; and the ‘Reverse Cyclone.&amp;rsquo; They revisit the ideal outfit for a guy, address going through your partners phone, and dive into their shadiest cheating scandal story to date. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>11 - MILF Hunting Season | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490301/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490301/</guid><description>Podcast Description The duo explains how they faked their grandfathers death to get out of an airline fee. They provide multiple ways to finding a third for a threesome, get into a detailed strategy for hunting MILFs, and how to navigate that fuck buddy life if you want more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>10- Stop Nutting Early Please | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490302/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490302/</guid><description>Podcast Description We discuss our favorite topic which is how to out crazy the crazy. We also provide the four important steps for men to last longer in the bedroom along with sugar daddies and queefs. Enjoy! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>9 - Faking O’s and Threesomes-Oh My! | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490303/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490303/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this weeks episode, the duo addresses their families disapproval of them and revisit the subject of nudes. They also discuss the hard truth about faking O&amp;rsquo;s and everyone&amp;rsquo;s favorite topic- threesomes-ending with some of the craziest #daddygang stories yet. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>8 - Plot Twist- Small Dicks for the Win and Using Tears for Lube | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490304/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490304/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex and Sofia discuss manscaping, why Adriana Lima blocked Alex on instagram, period sex, and why small dicks are great. They also divulge their sexual love story and why they are done with girls blaming the other woman (cough cough Rachel Bush). Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>7 - Sliding into the DMs - It’s Time to Get Laid Boys | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490305/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490305/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex and Sofia give men the ultimate guide to DM success and break down the do&amp;rsquo;s and don&amp;rsquo;ts of their social media habits. They elaborate on dirty talk in the bedroom, and why girls with hair extension are an easy f**k Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>6 - The Post Nut Clean Up &amp; the Gluck Gluck continued... | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490306/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490306/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex and Sofia discuss the importance of the cleanup after he nuts, incorporating the balls and the butt in the Gluck Gluck, proper ghosting etiquette (we approve), AND Sofia&amp;rsquo;s criminal history&amp;hellip; Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>5 - Fine Dining: An Eating Out Special (ft. The Cooch Gobbler Combo) | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490307/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490307/</guid><description>Podcast Description You guys asked for it, we are giving it to you. Introducing the blow job special for girls- Cooch Gobbler Combo style. In Episode 5, Alex and Sofia reveal the ultimate way to land a girl at a bar, dish some celeb hookup stories, and give a detailed description of the power women hold between their legs- featuring the Voodoo Clam. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>1 - SEXT ME SO I KNOW IT’S REAL | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490311/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490311/</guid><description>Podcast Description Follow along vlogger Alexandra Cooper and best friend Sofia Franklyn as the duo dives into the explicit details of their life in NYC. In their 20s, the two exploit the f*ck out of their lives, making you feel a hell of alot better about yours. Relationships, sex, the NY social scene, embarassing moments, and weiner holes are all addressed here on CALL HER DADDY. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>2 - If you’re a 5 or 6, Die for that D*ck | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490310/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490310/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex and Sofia dive into the differences between 5&amp;rsquo;s and 6&amp;rsquo;s vs 9&amp;rsquo;s and 10&amp;rsquo;s. Depending on where you land on the scale&amp;hellip;you may need to work over time in the bedrooom. Plus, Sofia discusses getting caught cheating thanks to her fat a$$. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>3 - The Gluck Gluck 9000 | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490309/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490309/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex and Sofia touch on making money from guys&amp;rsquo; foot fetishes (hey dirty coachella sandals!), secret sugar daddys, and the ultimate blow job technique that is guaranteed to be every man&amp;rsquo;s krytopnite. Introducing- The Gluck Gluck 3000 vs 9000. LADIES AND GENTS, listen up! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>4 - Nudes Never Die | Call Her Daddy</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4365490308/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4365490308/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex and Sofia discuss sending nudes and an important technology hack they have discovered- one they guarentee will save the credibility and integrity of your nude. Also, they dive into the &amp;lsquo;porn test challenge,&amp;rsquo; shaving your vagina at 3 am, and guys spitting on girls backs to fake an orgasm. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>