<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Overlap with Gary Neville on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-overlap-with-gary-neville/</link><description>Recent content in The Overlap with Gary Neville on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 06:32:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-overlap-with-gary-neville/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Craig Bellamy Reveals All On Golf Club Incident &amp; Newcastle Fall-Out | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 06:32:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890001/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week’s episode on The Overlap, brought to you by Sky Bet, we are joined by former Wales captain and Premier League footballer turned coach Craig Bellamy.
Craig takes on Gary at the Cube in Manchester before a fascinating sit-down interview.
Having clocked up over 500 professional appearances and represented nine clubs over a career that spanned almost 20 years, Bellamy does not lack in stories to tell.</description></item><item><title>Theo Walcott: I’m Hanging Up My Boots | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 16:47:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890002/</guid><description>Podcast Description On The Overlap this week, brought to you by Sky Bet, we have an exclusive interview with former England, Arsenal, Everton and Southampton forward Theo Walcott who has announced his retirement from professional football.
During the episode we talk about Walcott’s shock inclusion as a 17-year-old into England’s 2006 World Cup squad and how much of a psychological effect this had on him and his family. We also chat about his England career as a whole and about the weight of expectation of his career which was magnified from the start, as well as how he handled the fame of being a top-level footballer from a young age.</description></item><item><title>Fan Debate New Season 2023/24 | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 08:28:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890003/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Fan Debate season preview is here brought to you by Sky Bet.
Gary Neville is joined by Josh Denzel, Jamie Carragher, Tom Skinner, and some of the biggest fan channels across England ahead of what’s billed up to be an incredible 2023/24 Premier League season.
From Treble winners Manchester City, their title contenders, and top four hopefuls to relegation battles and everything in between, we talk through the biggest debates from the best league in the world.</description></item><item><title>Marcus Rashford Exclusive with Gary Neville | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 09:09:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890004/</guid><description>Podcast Description On The Overlap this week, we have an exclusive interview with England and Manchester United star Marcus Rashford, brought to you by Sky Bet.
We caught up with Rashford during a pre-season training camp in Portugal as he gears up for his ninth season as a first-team player and his second under Erik ten Hag.
Following his 30-goal haul last campaign – his most prolific yet – Rashford reveals how much his personal psychologist and strength &amp;amp; conditioning coaches have helped him recover from setbacks and injuries since bursting onto the scene in 2016.</description></item><item><title>Dele: "Now is the Time to Talk" | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890005/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 10:38:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trigger warning: Sexual abuse, addiction and mental health.
In this powerful episode of The Overlap, Gary Neville sits down to have a heartfelt conversation with Dele, as he courageously speaks about his recent circumstances on and off the pitch and the profound challenges he endured throughout his childhood and long-lasting effects of trauma it has caused him.
&amp;nbsp;
Dele opens up about his recent battle with addiction and his remarkable journey of rehabilitation as well his unwavering aspiration to inspire those facing similar circumstances to speak up.</description></item><item><title>Kompany Reveals All On Man City Career &amp; Burnley Premier League Return | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890006/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 07:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890006/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on The Overlap brought to you by Sky Bet, I'm with Burnley manager Vincent Kompany for an exclusive interview at the Barnfield Training Centre in Lancashire to discuss his incredible football journey and his future in football management.
From his upbringing shaped by his parents, to his time at Manchester City, we cover it all.
We start with Vincent's early days at Manchester City. Initially he played in midfield under Mark Hughes, but it was under Roberto Mancini and later Manuel Pellegrini and Pep Guardiola that he fell in love with defending and became a Premier League winning captain.</description></item><item><title>Access All Areas at Crystal Palace with Steve Parish &amp; Roy Hodgson | The Overlap | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 16:50:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890007/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The Overlap I visited Crystal Palace going behind-the-scenes as we gain exclusive access to the club.
We begin with a tour of Crystal Palace's state-of-the-art academy, where I'm joined by the club's charismatic chairman, Steve Parish. In a candid conversation, Steve provides valuable insights into the demanding role of a Premier League team chairman. We delve into the challenges faced by a club operating without a lavish budget and discover how the pursuit of survival each year is paramount to remaining in the fiercely competitive Premier League.</description></item><item><title>Roy Hodgson reflects on highs and lows of his incredible 47-year long career | The Overlap | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890008/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 16:02:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890008/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of The Overlap, I sit down with legendary football manager Roy Hodgson, where we reflect on his incredible 47-year career in the game. From managing huge names like Ronaldo and Roberto Carlos at Inter Milan, to his short time managing Liverpool and his tenure as the head coach of the England national team, Hodgson has been at the forefront of football for decades.
In this interview, Roy shares his experiences managing some of the biggest names in football at Inter Milan, and the challenges he faced in bringing together a team of such talented individuals.</description></item><item><title>Poch to Chelsea? Spurs Job, United &amp; Liverpool Ownership, Relegation &amp; Top 4 | Fan Debate Part 2 | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890009/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 08:00:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to the final part of our Fan Debate, with Gary Neville, Jamie Carragher &amp;amp; the fans. Who will be the next manager at Tottenham? The fans debate the candidates from Nagelsmann to Kompany. Then the attention turns to their London rivals Chelsea as the fans discuss if Pochettino will be a good fit. Gary and Jamie breakdown the ownership situation at Manchester United and Liverpool. Then focus turns to the relegation battle.</description></item><item><title>Have Arsenal “bottled it” will Man City be Champions? | Fan Debate Part 1 | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890010/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 19:29:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890010/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are back with The Overlap Fan Debate part 2! We are getting stuck into the debate with Gary Neville, Jamie Carragher, and the fans!
“The title decider” between Manchester City &amp;amp; Arsenal ended with Man City taking a major step forward in the title race.
Robbie and Pippa (AFTV) &amp;amp; Steven McInerney (Esteemed Kompany) and Buvey (The Club) have their say on how the title race will go for the front runners, as well as takes from the fans of all the other Premier League teams.</description></item><item><title>Jill Scott talks winning the Euros with Lionesses, I'm a Celebrity... &amp; becoming a coach | The Overlap | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890011/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 16:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890011/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The Overlap, I sit down with Jill Scott, one of England's most accomplished and loved female footballers.
Filmed in her very own coffee shop in Manchester Boxx2Boxx, Jill opens up about her journey to becoming a footballer, from her childhood experiences to the challenges she faced along the way. As a trailblazer in women's football, Jill also shares her thoughts on the current state of the sport and the strides that have been made in recent years.</description></item><item><title>Ruud van Nistelrooy talks his Man United career, Sir Alex Ferguson &amp; life as a manager | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890012/</guid><description>Podcast Description I'm thrilled to share this incredible interview with the one and only Ruud van Nistelrooy brought to you by SkyBet. We’re in Holland at the home of PSV Eindhoven, where he now manages the first team.
In this exclusive interview, Ruud opens up about his early career and how he first got into football. He also reveals how he nearly didn't sign for Manchester United due to a serious knee injury that threatened to derail his career.</description></item><item><title>Aleksander Čeferin reveals all on the Super League, football integrity &amp; Liverpool's UCL Final | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 15:00:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890013/</guid><description>Podcast Description UEFA President Aleksander Čeferin joins Gary Neville on the latest episode of The Overlap. Aleksander speaks on his childhood &amp;amp; growing up in Slovenia, before becoming a defence lawyer.
They then discuss Liverpool's Champions League final, and Aleksander issues an apology to the club.
Finally the UEFA President talks about the European Super League and the following fallout.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Manchester United’s New Potential Ownership Explained | In Focus | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890014/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 14:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Finally on this edition of In Focus, we discuss the potential sale of Manchester United. Gary is joined by Jamie, Shay Given, Carl Anka &amp;amp; Laurie Whitewell from The Athletic and fans from Manchester United &amp;amp; Newcastle United.
With potential buyers on the table, the group discusses who could take over at Manchester United, and the ramifications of the purchase.
What would state ownership mean for the club? How much would the club sell for?</description></item><item><title>The title race: Arsenal or Manchester City? | In Focus | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890015/</guid><description>Podcast Description The second part of In Focus is here, all about the title race. We’re joined by Gary, Jamie, James McNicholas from The Athletic &amp;amp; fans from Arsenal &amp;amp; Manchester City.
Our Arsenal fans are as confident as ever, but Gary is still sceptical on Arsenal’s title challenge, doubting their experience.
But is this a different Manchester City team to their previous title winning sides? Did Manchester City make a mistake selling Zinchenko &amp;amp; Jesus to Arsenal?</description></item><item><title>The Carabao Cup Final Aftermath | In Focus | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 23:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890016/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re back with a brand new strand, in focus. With voices from the fans &amp;amp; respected journalists, we dive into the biggest topics in football.
Up first is the aftermath from the Carabao Cup Final. Gary is joined by Jamie Carragher, Carl Anka &amp;amp; Laurie Whitwell from the Athletic and fans from Manchester United &amp;amp; Newcastle. We discuss Manchester United’s rise and what this means for the club going forwards.</description></item><item><title>Who will win the league? Who makes top 4? | Overlap Fan Debate Part 3 | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890017/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:53:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890017/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the third and final part of our Fan Debate, Gary Neville, Jamie Carragher &amp;amp; the fans tackle the title race.
Can Arsenal keep Man City at bay? Gary has his doubts with City for the first time this season.
Then the attention turns to the top four. Can Newcastle make the top 4? Will Manchester United &amp;amp; Spurs be able to claim a Champions League place? And could the likes of Brighton, Fulham &amp;amp; Brentford sneak into Europe?</description></item><item><title>The Relegation Battle | Overlap Fan Debate Part 2 | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890018/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:31:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890018/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s time for part 2 of the debate, where we focus on the relegation battle.
Gary Neville, Jamie Carragher, and the fans take a look at the clubs fighting to survive. We’ve got Part Three coming out very soon, subscribe now &amp;amp; make sure to turn notifications on.
00:00-4:54 Sean Dyche at Everton
4:55-9:46 Who’s next at Leeds? Can they survive?
9:47-14:14 Nottingham Forest’s survival hopes
14:15-15:48 Bournemouth’s worries</description></item><item><title>Manchester City’s Alleged FFP breaches &amp; Chelsea’s spending spree | Overlap Fan Debate Part 1 | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890019/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:21:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890019/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Overlap is back and we’re in our brand new home, ready for a debate.
We’ve got Gary Neville, Jamie Carragher, and some of the biggest fan channels across the country. First up we look at Manchester City, and the news surrounding the alleged FFP breaches. We’re joined by Matt Slater &amp;amp; Sam Lee from The Athletic to share insight on the rulings, before diving into Chelsea’s spending spree.</description></item><item><title>The Overlap Fan Debate Midseason Special Part 2 | With Gary Neville &amp; Jamie Carragher | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 10:59:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Part two of the Fan Debate is here!
I’m back with Jamie Carragher, Robbie Lyle and the best English fan channels.
In this part we chat to the Manchester clubs as well as Wolves, West Ham, Bournemouth, Forest and Leeds.
Chapters:
00:00-17:08 Manchester United
17:09-26:41 Manchester City
26:42-30:08 Liverpool and Man U in Europe
30:09-32:48 Unai Emery
32:49-36:52 Wolves
36:53-40:16 Nottingham Forest 40:17-47:24 James Maddison and Jamie’s England squad</description></item><item><title>The Overlap Fan Debate Midseason Special Part 1 | With Gary Neville &amp; Jamie Carragher | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890021/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Fan Debate is back and before the World Cup kicks off, we got the thoughts of Jamie Carragher, Robbie Lyle and the biggest fan channels across England on how the Premier League season is going so far.
From Liverpool going up for sale, to Arsenal’s chances at the title, along with Graham Potter’s start at Chelsea and the rise of Newcastle United.
Part two will drop tomorrow where we discuss the rest of the teams in the Premier League including the two Manchester clubs.</description></item><item><title>Virgil Van Dijk talks Klopp, Carra &amp; being the world's best CB with Gary Neville | The Overlap | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 15:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890022/</guid><description>Podcast Description My full interview with Liverpool centre back and Netherlands captain Virgil Van Dijk is here, brought to you by Sky Bet.
&amp;nbsp;
Virgil opens up about growing up in Holland and slowly becoming the brilliant footballer he is today.
&amp;nbsp;
He talks about his move to Liverpool, life at Anfield and what it’s like working with Jurgen Klopp.
&amp;nbsp;
Plus he answers some questions from fans of the Overlap.</description></item><item><title>Arsenal on top, Liverpool's struggles, Haaland &amp; Man Utd resilience | Overlap Fan Debate Xtra | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 19:40:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890023/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re back for another Fan Debate Xtra, brought to you by Sky Bet, as I’m joined by The Athletic’s David Ornstein &amp;amp; Laurie Whitwell and some of the biggest fan channels from Arsenal, Liverpool, Manchester City &amp;amp; Manchester United.
We dive into Arsenal’s rise &amp;amp; Liverpool’s poor start, then talk about Haaland’s dominance &amp;amp; Manchester United’s resilience.
Plus we predict where these four clubs will finish this season.</description></item><item><title>Amir Khan opens up on his low points, Anthony Joshua and much more with Gary Neville | The Overlap | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 09:42:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amir is back for his full interview, brought to you by Sky Bet, as we walk around Bolton and visit his gym.
We dive into his childhood, how he got into boxing and then how Amir lost £5 million.
He shares all on the drama with AJ and how it ruined their relationship, before revealing how he was held at gunpoint.
If you enjoyed this episode give it a like &amp;amp; subscribe, and let me know who you want on future Overlaps.</description></item><item><title>Man Utd &amp; Arsenal Special | The Overlap Fan Debate Xtra with Gary Neville &amp; Jamie Carragher | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890025/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 06:42:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890025/</guid><description>Podcast Description After Man United's victory against Arsenal, Jamie &amp;amp; I sit down with The Athletic's David Ornstein and Carl Anka, as well as familiar fans of both clubs for the first Fan Debate Xtra – brought to you by Sky Bet.
We reflect on Sunday's game and discuss the current state of these two Premier League giants in more detail.
Subscribe and leave a comment if you want more of The Overlap Fan Debate Xtra ❤️</description></item><item><title>Gary Neville’s exclusive full interview &amp; behind the scenes at MNF | The Overlap | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890026/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 15:16:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890026/</guid><description>Podcast Description My full interview is here with Geoff as we flipped the Overlap, brought to you by Sky Bet. We chat around why I started this channel, and getting into punditry at Sky Sports.
I reflect on 1999 in Barcelona, life after football, and how I collapsed during the 2021 EUROs. Plus I open up on my dad and my grandad.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>The Overlap Live Fan Debate with Gary Neville &amp; Jamie Carragher | Start of Season 22/23 Part 2 | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 14:13:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Part 2 is here of our start of season Premier League fan debate, brought to you by Sky Bet, and I’m back with Jamie Carragher, Josh Denzel and the biggest fan channels in the country.
The discussion continues, with breaking up the top 6, to who we think will go down, and much more.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Overlap Live Fan Debate with Gary Neville &amp; Jamie Carragher | Start of Season 22/23 Part 1 | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890028/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 13:35:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890028/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re back with the Fan Debate ahead of the brand new Premier League season, with Jamie Carragher, Josh Denzel and the biggest fan channels across England, brought to you by Sky Bet.
We discuss the major talking points, including the Lionesses historic win, who will win the league, the battle for top four, and if Ronaldo needs to leave Manchester United.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Paddy the Baddy &amp; Meatball Molly take Gary Neville to the octagon | The Overlap | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890029/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 14:26:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>David Beckham’s World Cup Special with Gary Neville | The Overlap | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890030/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Overlap Live Fan Debate 4.0 with Gary Neville &amp; Jamie Carragher | The End of Season Special | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890031/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 18:00:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Gerard Pique talks Barcelona, the Super League &amp; Guardiola with Gary Neville | The Overlap | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890032/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 14:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Steven Gerrard shares all to Gary Neville on management, Villa, Liverpool &amp; more | The Overlap | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890033/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 14:16:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890033/</guid><description>Podcast Description My full interview with Aston Villa manager and Liverpool legend Steven Gerrard is here, brought to you by Sky Bet.
&amp;nbsp;
Steven tells me about how he became a manager, with Klopp giving him the u18s to manage at Liverpool.
&amp;nbsp;
He then talks about his time with Rangers, his management style and his ambitions with Villa.
&amp;nbsp;
We finally chat about the Chelsea game, and how he coped with the aftermath.</description></item><item><title>The Overlap Live Fan Debate 3.0 with Neville, Carragher &amp; Keane | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890034/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 17:06:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890034/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re back for another Fan Debate, brought to you by Sky Bet. I’m joined by Jamie Carragher, Roy Keane, Josh Denzel and some of the biggest fan channels across England.
With the Premier League returning we discuss some of the biggest topics, from Ten Hag or Pochettino, to Chelsea’s sanctions, the state of Everton and so much more.
Give this channel a follow if you enjoyed listening and please let me know who you want on future episodes of The Overlap.</description></item><item><title>The Overlap Live: An Audience With Gary Neville, Jamie Carragher &amp; Roy Keane | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890035/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 13:59:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890035/</guid><description>Podcast Description I am delighted to share with you our first ever Overlap Live event at the Manchester Apollo, brought to you by Sky Bet . Kelly Cates and Josh Denzel host Jamie Carragher, Roy Keane and I in front of over 2,700 fans .&amp;nbsp;
The night was amazing, and here‘s some of our favourite parts from the show: from my first MNF appearance to our all-time Premier League XIs and so much more .</description></item><item><title>Declan Rice talks West Ham, Chelsea, England and more | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890036/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 15:02:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890036/</guid><description>Podcast Description I am so happy to share my full interview with Declan , brought to you by Sky Bet . Easily the most switched on 23 year old I‘ve ever talked to .
We chat around his home town, Chelsea, signing for West Ham, losing to Italy with England and so much more.
Plus he teaches me a thing or two on the snooker table…
Make sure you follow this channel and let me know who you want on future episodes too .</description></item><item><title>Frank Lampard reveals how he was sacked by Chelsea, spy-gate &amp; more | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890037/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890037/</guid><description>Podcast Description I am absolutely delighted to share this episode with you all, brought to you by Sky Bet. Frank Lampard takes me to a pub that’s close to his heart, as we tackle cocktails, starters and more in the kitchen.
We discuss how Frank moved on from Chelsea, and then how he dealt with retirement.&amp;nbsp;
We chat all things Derby, including the infamous spy-gate… And then move on to the Chelsea job.</description></item><item><title>Alan Shearer reveals all on all Mike Ashley, Manchester United &amp; more | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890038/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890038/</guid><description>Podcast Description My full interview with Alan Shearer is here, brought to you by Sky Bet. We went for a walk around Newcastle, from the Docklands to St James’ Park.
&amp;nbsp;
We chat around growing up in Newcastle, to then move away to Southampton at such a young age.
Alan shares his thoughts on Mike Ashley, from becoming manager of the club to the statue drama.
We then discuss the new ownership, and I’ve even got a quiz for him at the end!</description></item><item><title>Jamie Carragher takes Gary Neville around Bootle: Liverpool, England, MNF &amp; more | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890039/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 15:12:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ahead of Manchester United v Liverpool, my full interview with Jamie Carragher, brought to you by Sky Bet, is out now.
Carra takes me to his local gym and puts me through my paces , before a walk around his home-town, Bootle.
From all things Liverpool , to his time with England Carra shares all.
He even films a mini-doc for a Liverpudlian take on me...
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>The Overlap Fan Debate 2.0 Part 2 | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890040/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 16:01:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Part two, brought to you by Sky Bet, is out now ! I'm back with Jamie Carragher, Paul Scholes, Josh Denzel and some of the biggest fan channels in the UK.
We chat about Newcastle's takeover, a World Cup every two years and so much more.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Overlap Fan Debate 2.0 Part 1 | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890041/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 14:49:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brought to you by Sky Bet, the debate is back ! I’m joined by Jamie Carragher, Paul Scholes, Josh Denzel and some of the biggest fan channels across the UK.
With the Premier League returning from the international break, we dive into how the season has gone so far .
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tyson Fury shares all on Anthony Joshua, Deontay Wilder &amp; more | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 13:04:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890042/</guid><description>Podcast Description My full interview with Tyson Fury, brought to you by Sky Bet, is out now - I really hope you all enjoy it.
We discuss why he lives in Morecambe, his childhood and how much family means to him. Tyson shares his side on why the Anthony Joshua fight fell through, and how he’s preparing ahead of Deontay Wilder.
We then dive into Tyson’s remarkable comeback story, and his mental health battle, before sitting down for a cup of tea and 10 Questions.</description></item><item><title>10 Questions with Tyson Fury! The full-interview warm-up! | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890043/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tyson Fury's 10 Questions with Gary Neville | Overlap Xtra
We're back with another episode of 10 Questions, with heavyweight Champion Tyson Fury.
From mastering time travel to hating when his mates duck out of getting their round in, Tyson shares all.
The full episode will be out very soon, make sure to subscribe &amp;amp; turn notifications on.
Brought to you by Sky Bet.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>The big one with Roy Keane! A dog walk through Keano's career | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890044/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 11:05:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here it is, the full interview (and dog walk) with Roy Keane to share with you all.
Gary dives into Roy's management career, his time at United, starting his Instagram account and so much more.
Let us know what you think to this episode, and be sure to leave a like &amp;amp; subscribe for more.
Who do you want to see on future episodes?
Brought to you by Sky Bet</description></item><item><title>50 Questions with Keano! Gary and Roy's quick-fire Q&amp;A | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890045/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890045/</guid><description>Podcast Description To celebrate Roy's 50th birthday, Gary had 50 quick-fire questions ready for him.
From favourite food, to superheroes, to the Gallagher's, we cover everything! And get ready for the full episode with Roy, which will be out very soon.
As always, let us know if you enjoyed this video in the comments, and subscribe to never miss a video - we've got plenty coming up!!
Brought to you by Sky Bet.</description></item><item><title>The Overlap Live Fan Debate - Part 2 | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 08:25:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here's part two of our first ever Live Fan Debate, where Gary is joined once more by Jamie Carragher, Roy Keane, Josh Denzel and some of the biggest fan channels across England.
Our Premier League preview continues, as we cover Rafa Benitez at Everton, Newcastle's struggles, racism in football and much more.
Leave a like and comment with your favourite moment from the debate! We really hope you all enjoy this - we'll be looking to create more throughout the season.</description></item><item><title>The Overlap Live Fan Debate with Gary, Roy Keane &amp; Jamie Carragher | Part 1 | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890047/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 09:39:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our first ever Live Fan Debate is here, where Gary is joined by Jamie Carragher, Roy Keane, Josh Denzel and some of the biggest fan channels across England.
We preview the Premier League season, covering everything from title favourites, to the impact of Jack Grealish, Harry Kane's desire to leave and so much more.
Part two will be released, imminently, make sure to subscribe and turn notifications on!</description></item><item><title>In the ring with Anthony Joshua. Just why did the Fury fight fall through? | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890048/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 12:35:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890048/</guid><description>Podcast Description One not to miss, as Gary is put through his paces by World Champion and Olympic gold medallist, Anthony Joshua.
We discuss why the Tyson Fury fight fell through, with the blame falling on Tyson's camp.
AJ then shares all, getting into boxing, Usyk, his relationship with Hearn and so much more.
Who do you think would win the Battle of Britain?
Let us know what you thought of this episode, and make sure to leave a like &amp;amp; subscribe to never miss an episode.</description></item><item><title>Dina Asher Smith and her Olympic Dream | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890049/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 12:35:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joining Gary on the fourth episode of The Overlap, is World Champion and Olympic hopeful, Dina Asher-Smith.
One of our brightest hopes for the Tokyo Olympic games, Dina shares all, from her upbringing, to Olympic preparations, to tackling racism. Gary and Dina even go head to head on the track… before Gary's hamstring gave way!
Make sure to watch to the end, to see a special present from David Beckham for Dina &amp;amp; her mum.</description></item><item><title>Harry Maguire on Manchester United captaincy, World Cup heart-break and turning down Pep | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890050/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 12:35:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joining Gary on the third episode of The Overlap, is Manchester United Captain Harry Maguire.
Harry talks about what it was like breaking through at Sheffield United, and which defenders inspired him as a kid.
We reflect on England, talking about the experience of Russia in 2018, and the heart-breaking loss against Croatia. He even reveals why he turned up to the England squad with bin bags!
We find out why Harry chose United over City, and then what it’s been like becoming Captain of Manchester United.</description></item><item><title>Harry Kane and his career cross-roads | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890051/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 12:34:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joining Gary on the second episode of The Overlap, is England and Tottenham captain Harry Kane.
We discuss Harry's Tottenham career, and he shares how he is fast approaching a cross-roads, and how an honest conversation with Chairman Daniel Levy is needed.
Gary dives into his time with England, reflecting on Iceland, the World Cup, and his hopes for the EUROs.
Harry shares his inspirations, and how the Michael Jordan documentary "</description></item><item><title>Richard Scudamore and the European Super League | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890052/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 12:34:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890052/</guid><description>Podcast Description In our first episode Gary sits down with the former chief executive of the Premier League, Richard Scudamore.
We dive into Richard's past and how he became CEO of the Premier League.
Gary grills Richard over the power of the big six clubs and question the need for independent regulation, before discussing the impact of the European Super League.
Does the Premier League need an independent regulator? And should the 'Big-Six' clubs be punished?</description></item><item><title>Introducing The Overlap with Gary Neville. Have a listen, if you like! | The Overlap with Gary Neville</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7412890053/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 10:28:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7412890053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to The Overlap! The biggest names in football and world sport will be sharing real stories with me, Gary Neville, and reflecting on their careers &amp;amp; vulnerabilities.
Plus we’ll have Overlap Live where I'll answers your questions &amp;amp; Overlap Reacts, where I'll react to the biggest incidents in sport.
Make sure to subscribe to never miss an episode. Brought to you exclusively by Sky Bet.
Hosted on Acast.</description></item></channel></rss>