<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Inspired Unemployed on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-inspired-unemployed/</link><description>Recent content in The Inspired Unemployed on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 18:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-inspired-unemployed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dedicated to Falcalicious | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520001/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520001/</guid><description>Podcast Description We kick off today&amp;rsquo;s episode live from the marathon afterparty! Asking if Jack managed to cross the finish line and how Falcalicious is feeling in his final moments before going on stage. Lou and Jarch are then back to settle another great debate - are you really a huge fan if you haven’t read the books? Finally, the boys call their mate Beau to ask what life is like for him considering he has never had social media or been on a dating app, ever.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Girls Not Liking Us | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520002/</guid><description>Podcast Description The hilarious Lou and Jarch from We Mean Well podcast are here to bring back ‘the Great Debate’. This time we’re settling once and for all, AUS or NZ? Jack and Falcs then chat about what girls do when they don’t like you. Only to realise the girls definitely don&amp;rsquo;t like them. Finally, the boys present their guide on how to be confident.
Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to The Vault | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to ‘The Vault’. The Vault is a safe space to absolutely lose it over all the little stupid things that piss you off that shouldn’t. It’s a judgement-free zone. Next, we hear from listeners about the worst possible timings and situations they’ve been broken up with. Finally, Jack and Falcs discuss the things that guys do when they don’t like you. Buy tickets to Club 42 here Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to being a Psychopath | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520004/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s time for a weekend recap! Did Jack run 30km and go to Pilates like he was supposed to? Did Falcalicious produce a hit song with the Jungle Giants? Dom then shares a particularly upsetting rattled story. Safe to say festivals and heartbreak don’t mix. Finally, Sarah and the boys ask if the weird little things they do are fine or if they might actually be a psychopath. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Rejection | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520005/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get ready to be vulnerable. Dom, Falcs, Jack and Bill kick off this episode with a roundtable discussion on rejection. Specifically, the core memory from their very first rejection. Next up, Falcs loses it over a special phone call from his favourite DJ. Finally, the boys put their reverse parking skills to the test. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to a Rattled Night Out (ft. Lucy and Nikki) | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520006/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520006/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is heavy on the night out antics. First up, Dom and the boys cringe over their biggest nights out over the break. Which included a wrapped party, a UFC fighter, a disappointed Mick Fanning and Falcons birthday party. The boys are then comforted by a few funny ‘lowest of the low’ listener submissions. Finally, Lucy and Nikki from the Happy Hour podcast join the pod!! Lucy shares her worst rattled story from a wild night out.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to being a Tradie | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520007/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520007/</guid><description>Podcast Description To mark four years since the boys left the jobsite, they decide to ring their good mate Beau to get the latest on smoko chat and provide a welfare check on his apprentice. Will Gibb then joins the pod with a list of highly stressful hypothetical situations. Jack then announces he’s going to run a marathon, so Falcon decides he needs an announcement of his own. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Cheating or Not Cheating | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520008/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happens if you can’t sleep for four days and then travel to a country where the sun doesn’t set? Jack trauma dumps in a new chapter of the travel guidebook. The boys and Sarah then play a game of ‘cheating or not cheating’. Finally, the boys laugh over the number of coincidental celeb run ins they’ve had recently.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to being ‘That Guy’ | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jack shares a disgusting rattled story that involves Chris Hemsworth and tickling toes. Dom and the boys answer the most asked questions about their TV show - how the hell did people not recognise you? Did people not get angry? Finally, Jemma from the Psychology of your 20s Podcast sits down with Jack to discuss his problems with intensity addiction and fantasy bonding.
Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Nellie (Jack's Dead Dog) | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520010/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys are back after the longest break ever. First up we get an update on Jack’s European love life! Dom then joins the boys to share their worst moments while filming their TV show. Finally, the boys and Sarah each share their ‘lowest of the low’ moments each from the last four months. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Europe | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520011/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520011/</guid><description>Podcast Description To get Jack and Falcs excited for their travels, the boys react to a bunch of DMs sent in about everyones best and worst Europe stories. After recently being caught out and filmed by a random, Falcon begins to question if content really is king. Finally, the boys introduce their new favourite saying. https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Pick Up Lines | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520012/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jack can’t sleep, so, we’ve got Wendy back in studio to try and help explain why some people can fall asleep in two seconds while others are left counting sheep. The boys then dig through their personal DMs to find some of the best pick up lines they’ve been sent. Finally, the boys add a new chapter to their travel guide book, this time sharing their best Europe tips.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to the Better Wingman | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520013/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520013/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s time for the reverse - what is it that girls do that guys don’t know about? Liam then joins the boys in studio to talk about their recent drama class and other times they’ve felt vulnerable. Finally, Jack and Matt decide who the better wingman is. https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Powerbands | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Liam and the boys laugh over the dumbest arguments they’ve had while in a relationship, from not taking the right picture to watching ahead on a TV show. Wendy is then back in studio to try and answer the question everyone’s been asking, is vaping really that bad for you? Finally, the boys take the ultimate trip down memory lane with a fresh set of Powerbands. https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Hangover Cures | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520015/</guid><description>Podcast Description After seeing the Tik Tok trend ‘things guys do that girls don’t know about’, Jack and Falcs decide to create a list of their own to share with Sarah. The boys then invite Wendy Zukerman, the host of Science Vs, into the studio so they can find out what hangover cures actually work or not. Then it’s time to announce the winner of Tadpole Tank! https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Jack's Adult Tantrum | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jack threw an adult tantrum while playing a game of tennis at a fancy clubhouse (huge ick). Safe to say, he learnt his lesson. Sex therapist and all round legend G-spot then joins the podcast to chat different fetishes and kinks. Finally, it’s time for Tadpole Tank!!
https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Irrational Fears | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520017/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a terrifying trip to the dentist, Falcs wants to know what fears he has are rational or irrational. Liam, Dom, Sarah and the boys kick off a new segment called ‘the roundtable’. This week, they discuss if the advice “if he wanted to he would” is fair or not. The boys then share a few tips and tricks to help those who are employed and uninspired. https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Our First Double Date | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520018/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520018/</guid><description>Podcast Description First up, we asked you guys to send in your best horrible online dating stories and you did not disappoint. The boys cringe over tales of impromptu musical performances and vampire re-enactments. Dom then joins the pod to discuss what white lies they told their parents as kids. Finally, the boys get some very direct feedback after a recent double date. https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to FOMO | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520019/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys have diagnosed themselves with a severe case of FOMO. Thankfully they’ve found the cure - FOFU. The Better Beer competition went truly wild over the long weekend, with a few finalists finding themselves in some red hot situations. The boys decide to give them a ring along with the lucky winner. Finally, the boys put their new favourite gen z slang to the test. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to F1 | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520020/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520020/</guid><description>Podcast Description First up, the boys recap a hectic weekend away in Melbourne which included making videos with Danny Ricciardo and dancing with Kylie Minogue. Sarah and the boys then complete a new round of ‘would you rather’ thanks to the countless DMs we received. Finally, the boys admit there is nothing more humiliating than being yelled at as an adult by an adult. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Gen Z | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Will Gibb and Sarah do their best to teach Jack and Falcs the meaning behind the latest Gen Z words. It’s giving major L. The boys then call a listener after being told he has rattled story worth sharing. Finally, Jack learns his lesson after having a particularly bad reaction to a certain substance. https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to ChatGPT | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can guys be the little spoon in a cuddle train? Matt and Falcs investigate. Falcs finds himself ‘rattled’ at a party when delayed symptoms of Bali Belly decided to kick in. And finally, the boys decide to take full advantage of everything ChatGPT has to offer.
https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Reverse Cowgirl | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dom and the boys have arguably the least sexy sex talk ever after Jack somehow stumbles across a buzzfeed article titled ‘top 10 sex positions’. Following up from Falcon’s terrible past job interviews, Sarah shares a few funny yarns found in the DMs. Finally, Jacks Dad joins the boys in studio to tell them about a time he woke up somewhere he definitely shouldn’t have. https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ 00:00 Sex Positions with Dom 13:48 Job Interviews 23:40 Waking up where you&amp;rsquo;re not supposed to 32:56 DM&amp;rsquo;s Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to the Haunted House | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520024/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520024/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys head off to stay a night in Australia’s most Haunted House!
Arriving in sudden rain and strikes of lightening, the scene is set for a haunted tour and a series of challenges and scares that make it very hard for the boys to fall asleep. Both kinda funny and weird - you’ll need to strap in for this weeks pod. https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Roadtrips | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520025/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520025/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys are in the car and on their way to the Monte Cristo Homestead aka the most Haunted House in Australia. With four and a half hours to kill, the boys decide to record this entire episode on the road. First off, they list the best and worst classic roadtrip moments. Then they stop off in Yass, a small country town, to have a pub feed and retell a few past favourite roadtrip memories.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Falcon’s Old Instagram | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520026/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Will Gibb joins the boys in studio to confront his very own doppleganger. Falcon then admits to shooting his shot by sending a series of uncomfortable voice memos to his celebrity crush, Dua Lipa. Jack then continues Falcon’s embarrassment with a deepdive into his questionable 2012-2016 instagram posts. https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Shoey’s | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520027/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520027/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys are paying the price for ditching their health cleanse as soon as they arrived in Perth for the UFC. The bender that followed, resulted in crashing a wedding crashing with Dylan Alcott and a shoey on live TV. Sarah joins in for a game of ‘Would you rather …?’ which tumbles the boys into a mini existential crisis. Finally, old mate Forrest joins them in the studio to share an awkward memory from the days he worked with Falcs at the Surf Shop.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Anti-Valentine’s Day | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520028/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Will Gibb joins the pod this week in need of a bit of therapy. Just like Jack, Will is a repeat love bombing offender. The boys then announce they were proudly ‘anti-valentine’s day’ this year. So, if you were also rattled after seeing everyone’s loved-up posts yesterday, they’ve got you covered with a bunch of ‘self care’ tips. Sarah and the boys then share a few horror stories from past job interviews.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Party Tricks | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520029/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Does everyone really love a party trick? Dom tells the boys about that time his ‘party trick’ didn’t get the crowd reaction he was hoping for. Caleb from Spacey Jane joins us in the studio to share a personal ‘rattled’ story. And finally, Falcon gives us all a highly anticipated update on his last date.
https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to 2am Kickons | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520030/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520030/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Great Debate is finally back! The boys call on ‘recovering partygirl’ Jules and their trusty mate Dom to argue if anything actually fun happens past 2am. Next up, Jack creates a long list of things he considers a little weird to do with your mates. Inspired by the Onsen spas they visited while in Japan. Finally, Falcon has the comeback of the century. https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Falcons Masseuse | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520031/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jack and Matt are pinching themselves this week after they got to film and direct a skit with mega A-lister, Margot Robbie. As expected, the boys shared a few embarrassing moments in front of their celeb crush. Falcon then reveals why he struggles to relax when having a massage. Jack’s sister Bonnie then joins the pod to talk about Jack&amp;rsquo;s strict no-falling-in-love contract. https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Being Left on Read | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520032/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jack and Matt recap everything they’ve been up to over summer break, including a large Christmas and even larger NYE. Falcon then admits to being left on read by a girl he recently shot his shot with. To make it worse, he then attempted the double text. Finally, the boys share a funny story from their recent Japan trip. https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to 2022 | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520033/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520033/</guid><description>Podcast Description For the final episode of the year, the boys take a walk down memory lane! Laughing as their top 5 cringiest moments from the podcast are ranked. Jack and producer Craig then decide to pull a prank on Falcs, proving that he is in fact too nice for his own good. Finally, it’s time to set 2023 new years resolutions! https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to The Poo Room | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520034/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520034/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Matt opens up about the end of his relationship and talks it through with Jack. Then the housemates sit down to reveal who won the housemate games and decide which room everyone is taking. Ryan shares his wisdom about what anxiety is and how to cope with it. And finally the guys from Peking Duk tell a horrifying rattled story from a big night on tour.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Tuning a Relative | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520035/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520035/</guid><description>Podcast Description The housemate games kick off this week with all the guys picking their challenges out of a hat. Dom and Falcon have to make two traumatising phone calls, and then Liam and Jack listen back to the audio from the physical challenges they had to do. Cast your vote to determine who will get the best room in the house and who will get the ‘poo room’. The stakes could not be higher.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Fake Orgasms | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520036/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matt is still rattled after Jack set him up to say something intensely cringey at an awards ceremony. Then they are joined by vulva expert Ellie Sedgwick, who gives the guys a crash course, and even has some vulva-shaped waffles for them to practice on. And finally, all the housemates pitch the challenges they’ve thought of for the housemate games.
https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to the Master Bedroom | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520037/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jack and Matt are shocked by even more terrible first date stories sent in by listeners. Sarah then reads out a bunch of new shower thoughts to the boys which leads to a few surprisingly philosophical discussions. Finally, their housemates Dom and Liam join for a very important great debate. https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to UK Pubs | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520038/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520038/</guid><description>Podcast Description A work trip to the UK has highlighted for Jack and Matt that they are not qualified to be their own boss, especially when British pubs are involved. The boys decide the warm weather is ‘Ick Season’, because nothing is ickier than bindis, magpie swoopings and hot sand. Then the Dads are put to the test with a random phone call, to see if they have actually retired, or are still on the tools.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Love | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520039/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520039/</guid><description>Podcast Description This weeks episode has one clear theme, love. First up, Falcon goes completely off track and designs his own rom com after him and Jack declare old school love is dead. The boys then help a listener to hard launch his new relationship on Instagram. From picking the photo to writing the perfect caption, the boys offer their best (and worst) advice. Finally, the boys ‘spiritual geezer’ Ryan joins the pod again!</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Guilty Pleasures | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520040/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lets talk guilty pleasures. From listening to Nickleback to buying yourself flowers, the boys shamelessly admit to everything they not-so-secretly enjoy. Then, Matt and Jack hear a few more cringey ‘meet the dad’ horror stories from listeners. Finally, inspired by Kylie Jenner, the boys pull a prank on Falcons poor mum Bernie. https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Nedd Brockmann (BONUS EP) | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520041/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520041/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys sit down for an in depth chat with our newest Aussie legend, 23 year old Nedd Brockmann. Nedd ran 4000 kilometers from Perth to Sydney in just 46 days to raise over $2.5 million for Mobilise. The boys dive into details about the injuries he endured, the incredible mental game he played, his inspiration, the people he met and his hardest days. Donate: https://www.neddsrecordrun.com/ https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to the Worst Date Ever | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520042/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520042/</guid><description>Podcast Description In an attempt to make Jack feel better about his recent dating disasters, Falcs and Sarah go tit for tat with their own worst date stories. Miraculously, they manage to find a story worse than flashing your bank account. The boys then cringe over having one too many drinks at a work event. Laughing at their recent NZ work trip, where they completed 12 interviews on the brink of black out.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Kevin Parker | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520043/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520043/</guid><description>Podcast Description All round Aussie legend Kevin Parker from Tame Impala joins the pod this week! We find out what’s in his rider, what it’s like working with some of the biggest names in the industry and attending Freemantle house parties. Jack and Falcs bravely decide to call the poor girl Jack flashed his bank account details to on a date. Then Dom and the boys reveal the best high-risk locations for a ‘Danger Wank’.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Back Scratches | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520044/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dom is back in the booth to tell a story involving a drunken night out and an overly affectionate bandmate. The boys and Sarah then complete a knockout round to figure out what simple pleasures in life are better than sex. Then out of the goodness of his heart, Jack enrols Falcon to the June Daly Watkins School for fine young gnetlemen. Falcon is taught how to hold a knife and fork and which one is a wine glass.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to The Swans | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520045/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520045/</guid><description>Podcast Description In todays ep, the boys share how karma got them good after selling their souls for AFL grand final tickets. Jack and Falcon are left shocked by our listener stories about the most petty things they’ve ever done. And finally with festival season fast approaching, Jack and Matt make the definitive list of what to and what not to bring. https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Jack’s Ego | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520046/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jack’s ego is pretty hurt this week after his strange attempt to impress a girl backfires. He is now a certified walking cringeboard. Dom is back in the booth! In memory of Queen Lizzie, the boys have their royal knowledge put to the test in a new round of ‘definitions’. Matt then talks through an insane list of jobs that you probably never knew existed. https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Meeting the Dad | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520047/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is Jack 28 years old or 29 years young? Falcon decides to assess if Jack is overdue for a quarter life crisis. Jack quizzes Falcon about properly meeting his new girlfriends Dad. And finally, the boys admit to getting overly emotional everytime they board a flight.
https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Anal Gazers | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520048/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520048/</guid><description>Podcast Description What lies did your parents tell you as a kid? From the TV making your eyes square to special prisons for naughty kids, the boys laugh over the best lies they’ve been fed. Falcs then talks us through how to successfully ‘launch’ your new partner on Instagram. Finally, the boys admit to trying out a new form of self care - anal gazing. https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Shaq | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520049/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520049/</guid><description>Podcast Description They’re back! The boys kick off the ep with a rapid fire round of questions to get us up to speed with what has gone on over the break. Revealing their biggest night out in LA, various girl updates, most embarrassing texts and their dumbest purchase. Finally, Jack and Matt fanboy over their new best mate, basketball megastar Shaquille O&amp;rsquo;Neal. https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Love Languages | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520050/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520050/</guid><description>Podcast Description After reading their terrible year 10 report cards, Jack and Matt decide it’s best to get Dom back in the studio to help with a new round of ‘definitions’. Jack’s dad then jumps on the line to confess to accidentally eating a ‘special’ brownie while on his way to yoga. Finally, Matt takes a quiz to figure out what his love language is. https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Andy Wandy | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520051/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520051/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys were pretty chuffed by how much everyone seemed to love the baby talk segment from a few weeks ago&amp;hellip;Although of all the voice memos and videos they received of boyfriends being caught out, one celebrity made them laugh the most. Dom then jumps on the line to give an update on how his romantic holiday to Bali went. Jack and Matt then discuss the chaos which was ‘Splendour in the Mud’.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to PDA | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520052/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520052/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s time to meet Ryan. He’s an all round health guru who looks like he’s just walked off the set of Peaky Blinders. He’s the man the boys turn to for all matters of life advice. This episode, Ryan will host a ‘couples therapy session’ before Jack picks a bone with Matt and his new Mrs. Then we tune in for a series of nightmare stories about getting caught out in a white lie.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Kelly Slater | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520053/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520053/</guid><description>Podcast Description To gee the boys up for their stay in Australia’s most haunted house, they get some real life ghost stories from listeners. Then, the noble quest for finding the most annoying thing in the world continues, from housemates eating the food you’ve been looking forward to all day, to that one person (Jack) who asks questions all the way through movies. Finally, a caller describes the text they sent to Kelly Slater that they’d do anything to be able to unsend.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Baby Talk | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520054/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520054/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys hilariously trick unsuspecting friends into ‘speaking their language’. Proving that there is nothing more hilarious or sickening than hearing your mates baby talk. Dom and Cal join the booth to help the boys figure out what their ‘ticks’ are, before Jack brings the Ultimate Travel Guide book back. https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Holiday Romance | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520055/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Will Gibb and Dom join the boys to talk about how letting a new fling go from zero to 100 does not guarantee a happy ending. Jack gives Falcon&amp;rsquo;s old boss a buzz to see if his work ethic has improved and finally, we get to the bottom of what is truly the most annoying, ‘little’ thing that has ever happened to you.
https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to The Walk of Shame | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520056/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ever sent a DM or text that you instantly wished you could unsend? Jack, Matt and a few listeners share their nightmare stories. The boys have a laugh about being caught on a Walk of Shame, before debating whether or not parents should be allowed to bring crying babies on a plane. And finally, get excited for the next challenge Matt sets for Jack. https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Jack's Stand Up Comedy Gig | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520057/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 22:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520057/</guid><description>Podcast Description First up, Will Gibb and the boys sit down for a much-needed writing session before Jack&amp;rsquo;s first stand-up comedy show. Then, the moment we’ve all been waiting for, Jack takes the stage! All the best punchlines from his live performance are played out so you can laugh and cringe along. Finally, the boys are back in the studio to share a new travel guide tip! https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Listen to Will Gibb&amp;rsquo;s Podcast &amp;lsquo;Ok, But What If?</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Swingers | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520058/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Warning of unexpected, hilarious and overly sexual content when listener Ben calls the boys to share a rattled story from a recent country wedding. Jack gets stitched up big time by Falcon with the help of comedian Will Gibb. The boys then chat about the dumbest nicknames that have managed to stick. dms@theinspiredunemployed.com https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Shower Thoughts | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520059/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520059/</guid><description>Podcast Description From manning a BBQ to fixing a car; Jack and Matt discuss the skills you need to ‘enter manhood’. After receiving hundreds of DM’s, we bring back a new segment of ‘Shower Thoughts’. Jack then debates whether or not you should dry off in the shower first or not. Finally, the boys talk about the dumbest injuries they’ve copped for the sake of content.
dms@theinspiredunemployed.com https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Crying | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520060/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Before we let the laughs roll, the boys take a minute to get real about mental health. Jack and Matt share their own anxieties and remind us all that it’s okay to not be okay. We then introduce a new segment, the opposite of The Ick … The Tick. A surprisingly long list of random things guys do that are actually a turn on. Then it’s story time about the latest boys trip in Indonesia - on a boat.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to High School History Class | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520061/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520061/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys are back with a fresh take on their favourite game, definitions. A listener joins the pod to share an absurd story about an ex fling and a few missing fingers. What does a world without Google Maps look like? Jack and Matt take to the streets to find out. Finally, the boys trade rattled stories about running into an ex while on a night out. dms@theinspiredunemployed.com https://www.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Frat Boys | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520062/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Parmi or Parma?! Famous Sydney chef Matt Moran and a local Melbourne dish pig go head to head in the next Great Debate. The boys add a new chapter to their Ultimate Travel Guidebook; a rattled listener joins the show to share an unfortunate pocket dial; and while in LA, the boys decided to ask a few overly confident frat boys to share their love advice. dms@theinspiredunemployed.com https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Fake IDs | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520063/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520063/</guid><description>Podcast Description The ongoing snoring debate has brought sleepwalking to the boys attention and makes us wonder if it is hilarious or terrifying … Jack and Falcon admit they have absolutely no clue what’s happening in business meetings. Bernie and Lori join the pod to share embarrassing childhood stories about their boys and finally, Dom joins to reminisce about sneaking into events while underage.
dms@theinspiredunemployed.com https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Love Bombing | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520064/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520064/</guid><description>Podcast Description When the reality is not what you expected, Jack and Matt are finally ready to share with us their Coachella experience. Then it’s time to be updated on several new dating terms including ghosting, breadcrumbing and love bombing. The Travel Guide Book returns with a brand new chapter and the boys share a laugh over some of Australia’s more ridiculous sayings.
dms@theinspiredunemployed.com https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Snorers | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520065/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Having been in and out of airports for weeks now, the boys are reminded of all their past airport messups. The boys then introduce a new great debate: is it fair to hate on snorers? Jack then admits that he does miss one thing from their old job - smoko. Finally, Dom joins the boys to share a rattled story about a date gone very, very wrong. dms@theinspiredunemployed.com https://www.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to the Friendzone | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520066/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520066/</guid><description>Podcast Description After spending the day in NYC with new friend, dudewithsign, the boys have a few more mindblowing facts to share. Dom then joins to talk about their first ever crushes. The boys then admit to having mastered the art of bludging. Finally, its time for the return of the ‘texting advisory board’. dms@theinspiredunemployed.com https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to LA Parties | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520067/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520067/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys have finally touched down in the US! Although, have been quickly served a slice of humble pie after an underwhelming experience at their first Hollywood party. The boys then catchup with Aussie UFC champ Volco after watching his win in Florida. Matt then dishes on his recent ‘bad first date’ experience. Dom then joins the boys to reminisce their Catholic upbringing. dms@theinspiredunemployed.com https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Falcon's New Girlfriend? | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520068/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520068/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode, Jack and Matt find out if it’s cool to rev your car in a pedestrian zone or if you just look like a wanker. The boys get excited about their upcoming US trip while cringing over the last time they went to Coachella. Falcon shares some huge news about the state of his love life, and an afternoon with UFC fighter Bam Bam leaves Falcon with a suspected broken bone.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to The Mexican Sweat Lodge | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520069/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520069/</guid><description>Podcast Description A voice memo found in the DM’s causes Jack and Matt to reassess what they do in the bathroom. The boys then attempt to complete a ‘best friends quiz’. Another chapter is added to the Travel Guide Book, this time advising not to trust the man with one tooth. Finally, the boys get honest about what stupid things still scare them. dms@theinspiredunemployed.com https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Our First Boner | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520070/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jack and Matt have set up a ‘texting advisory board’ to offer moral support to other lovestruck fools. The boys then remember their first time getting a boner. Opinions about the new reality tv show ‘Byron Baes’ are shared. Finally, Jack challenges Matt to a game that involves Jane Austen and shots of gin. dms@theinspiredunemployed.com https://www.instagram.com/theinspiredunemployedpod/ Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Crypto | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520071/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jack and Matt chat about just how nervous guys can get when replying to a girls text. The boys then complain about being in over their heads with their recent crypto and NFT investments. Jack then proves why white lies are necessary. Finally, Matt surprises Jack with a Clairvoyant. dms@theinspiredunemployed.com Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Sexting your Boss | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520072/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Zach is looped in this week to prove there is nothing more awkward than texting the wrong person. But can it get worse than texting your boss for some saucy pics? Jack hilariously decides to test out his language skills and Falcon asks for help with his table manners. Then it’s a footy round up with Dom, to reminisce about footy days.
dms@theinspiredunemployed.com Ways to help those affected by the floods: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Baby Elle | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520073/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520073/</guid><description>Podcast Description First up, Dom joins the pod to share a rattled story involving his poor grandparents. Jack and Matt take a walk down memory lane to find out what their ‘core memories’ are. The boys are then left alone to care for a 6 month year old baby with zero babysitting experience. Finally, a little empathy is shown for the victims of the Tinder Swindler. dms@theinspiredunemployed.com Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Pete Davidson | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520074/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520074/</guid><description>Podcast Description With the help of a few mates, the boys determine if they have any girl ‘icks’ of their own; Jack introduces us to a new chapter in the Ultimate Travel Guide; there is much discussion about the boys new idol Pete Davidson - and shared anxiety about buying a new car.
dms@theinspiredunemployed.com Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Facebook Memories | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520075/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520075/</guid><description>Podcast Description After so many hilarious DM’s, the boys showcase a new list of ‘icks’, Jack surprises Falcon with a walk down Facebook memory lane and the Ultimate Travel Guidebook returns with the help of old mate Corkey. To round it up, the boys discuss the awkwardness around not being invited to a wedding.
dm@theinspiredunemployed.com Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to The Ick | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520076/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520076/</guid><description>Podcast Description With Valentines Day fast approaching, the boys have decided to focus a little more on their love lives. First, they discuss a new dating dilemma, girls getting ‘the ick’. Then, an astrologist joins them in-studio to tell them what to do if their date asks for their star sign. Jack then digs up an embarrassing teenage memory he had buried deep. Finally, the regret radar is back to judge another cringey ‘you up?</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to New Year, New Me | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520077/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520077/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys are back! They’ve kept up their crazy antics all summer and now have plenty of stories to share. Kicking off, the boys explain how they managed to mess up both Christmas and New Years. Jack then addresses how awkward it is joining a gym in January. They then tell us about their experience at a silent retreat. Finally, Falcon shares his most embarrassing moment to date. dm@theinspiredunemployed.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Bad Tattoos | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520078/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520078/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s the final episode of the year which means the boys finally find out who will have ‘day for it’ tattooed forever. There’s time for one last round of Definitions before rounding out the year with a handy ‘Christmas Day Survival Kit’. Then Jack and Matt decide to set each other a New Year’s Resolution. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to TikTok Boys | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520079/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520079/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys are still reeling from their first proper hosting gig at the TikTok For You Fest. Safe to say they’ve still got plenty of room for improvement. Dom then joins to share his own rattled story, involving Falcs and a cursed bowl of carbonara fettuccine. Finally, it’s time to collectively cringe over a few more horrific ‘you up?’ text messages. dm@theinspiredunemployed.com Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to “hey, you up?” texts | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520080/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ever sent a cringey late night text? How did you deal with the shame? Jack, Falcs and Dom share plenty of their opinions and examples. The boys then decide what three Christmas gifts are foolproof. Jack then gives us the details for Falcs first live performance . Finally, Jack gets his ass waxed. dm@theinspiredunemployed.com Link to tickets: https://oztixspecialoffers.oztix.com.au/outlet/event/64533fe9-bb29-4d02-9802-bc02d2923802 Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Jack's Sex Life | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520081/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520081/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys are back with another rattled story, this time about an embarrassing doctor&amp;rsquo;s visit. Then it’s time to get to the bottom of why Jack has been struggling in the bedroom. Then Falcon is left pretty unimpressed by a new challenge Jack has set for them. Finally, it’s time to try and secure a venue for Falcons debut performance. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Volcano Acatenango | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520082/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Falcon forces Jack to explain his embarrassing YouTube search history. Dom joins the boys to explain why NOT to include volcano climbing in the Ultimate Travel Guidebook. Lead singer of The Vanns gives feedback on Falcs’ singing potential. Then the boys round it out with a deep dive into their favourite self help book. dm@theinspiredunemployed.com Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Angry Customers | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520083/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520083/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys cringe over a rattled story involving Jack and a particularly distasteful nude. Falcon&amp;rsquo;s dream of becoming a rockstar feels real after Delta Goodrem gives him a much needed singing lesson. Finally, Jack forces Falcs to face his greatest fear: confrontation. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Ed Sheeran | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520084/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to a special episode of the Inspired Unemployed, co-hosted by global superstar Ed Sheeran. That’s right, Ed Sheeran is on the pod to give Falcon advice on how to become a rockstar - but not before the boys ask him a few rogue questions first. dm@theinspiredunemployed.com Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Dom’s Cousin | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520085/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520085/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys give context to their favourite, go-to phrase “winging it”. A new chapter is added to the Ultimate Travel Guide book (hint: don’t go to Paris with only two euro’s). The boys then open up about their greatest concern, needing the bathroom while people can hear you. Finally, their mate Dom admits to bullying his younger cousins. dm@theinspiredunemployed.com Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Mystery Girl | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520086/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jack relives the moment he first realised his parents were not as straight and narrow as he thought they were. Then, after plenty of back and forth, Falcon finally meets up with Mystery Girl for a drink! Next up, the boys decide to bring back their much loved game, ‘Guess the Definition’, this time mediated by their mate Dom. Then finally, the boys introduce the first item on their very own Bucket List.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to My Ex’s Nan | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520087/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jack admits to not always making the best first impression when it comes to meeting a girlfriend&amp;rsquo;s family for the first time. Falcon then pours his heart and soul into a love letter written for one lucky lady. Then finally, the boys are given an update on the state of their home after being left in the hands of their not-so-capable roommate for four months. dm@theinspiredunemployed.com Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to the passenger in 34C | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520088/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Falcon kicks off the ep with a rattled story about getting a little too over-excited on a plane. The boys then react to a very creative, romantic gesture sent in by a fan. Finally, it’s time for another chapter in the Ultimate Travel Guide book, this time set in Amsterdam. dm@theinspiredunemployed.com Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Hammock Man | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520089/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get ready to go deep as the boys serve up some real talk for the start of October, mental health month. Then, after days of providing creative (and somewhat terrifying) entertainment, the moment we’ve all been waiting has arrived… Hammock man’s true identity is revealed! Then last but not least, the boys are joined by their hometown mate Grant to provide a new chapter in the Ultimate Travel Guide book.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Calvin Harris’ Cousin | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520090/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520090/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys laugh over a string of texts Matt sent out on a particularly lonely Sunday afternoon. Theories are shared over what makes people “left lane” or “right lane” drivers. Jack launches chapter one of his ‘Ultimate Travel Guidebook’ with tips on how NOT to book a holiday. Then finally, to end the awkward ‘how should we split the bill?’ conundrum, Matt invents a new game. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated to Zendaya | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520091/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get your goggles on because we’re diving straight in. The boys cringe as they remember their disastrous first attempts at being entertainment reporters. They then call their mate to hear an excuse so good it’s taken on mythical proportions in their hometown, before Matt drops a MAJOR secret of his own. Oh, and then they decide to put their literary skills to the test. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Trailer | The Inspired Unemployed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9813520092/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9813520092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Best mates Jack and Matt are coming in hot with their very own podcast. Great yarns, skits, dares, embarrassing confessions and random call-ins with their tradie mates. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>