<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Date Yourself Instead on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/date-yourself-instead/</link><description>Recent content in Date Yourself Instead on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 08:04:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/date-yourself-instead/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>If they wanted to, THEY WOULD. | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300072/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 08:04:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300072/</guid><description>Podcast Description If they wanted to, they would&amp;hellip;? Or maybe they just can&amp;rsquo;t. Maybe they don&amp;rsquo;t have the capacity to love you the way you love them. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive into this topic together.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>5 BIG ways to level the f*ck up in 2024 | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300001/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you're ready to step into your POWER in 2024, this episode is for you. JOIN THE DARE TO DETACH MASTERCLASS HERE
DOORS OFFICIALLY OPEN FOR NEW MEMBERS ON DECEMBER 19TH, 2023.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Decenter that toxic man now. YOU are the main character. | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300002/</guid><description>Podcast Description A reminder to focus on you, because you have one f*cking life to live. Stop making someone else the main focus of your orbit. You are the SUN. You deserve to be front and center in your own movie. Xoxo.
JOIN THE DARE TO DETACH MASTERCLASS
(DOORS OPEN DECEMBER 19TH)
Use code SELFLOVE for a discount, exclusively for the podcast listeners.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>DETACH to ATTRACT - how being detached helps you manifest faster | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300003/</guid><description>Podcast Description DETACHMENT SPEEDS UP MANIFESTATION. When you truly let go, miracles happen. I WANT YOU TO UPLEVEL. UPGRADE. DETACH. BE FREE. BE F*CKING HAPPY. Because...why not? If you need a little push or a sign from the universe, this episode is for YOU.
Detach to attract. LINK TO THE DARE TO DETACH COURSE
Download instantly and get started on creating your dream life. Also be sure to sign up for my free meditation and reframe worksheet.</description></item><item><title>Feeling lonely this holiday season? I've got you. | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Being alone during the holiday season or any celebration day in general can feel like sh*t, let's just be honest. HOWEVER, it can also be empowering and fun if you make it that way - which is why I created this episode. TIS THE SEASON to embrace yourself and love yourself even more. I love you lots. Here is the link to my masterclass, use code selflove for a discount.</description></item><item><title>SEND THEM LOVE anyway - the ultimate healing guide | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Send them love. They need it the most. When someone hurts you, it can be easy to hate them - but what I've learned is that healing works from the inside out by becoming an energetic vessel of LOVE. JOIN DARE TO DETACH MASTERCLASS
Doors open November 16th officially for all new members! We'd absolutely love to have you. Transcript</description></item><item><title>Stop procrastinating, your future self needs you | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why do we procrastinate? I was the queen of procrastination and I would always assume things would just happen for me, but YOU NEED TO take action to get results and become your best self. Stop putting shit off! ;) I love you. Much love. Xoxo, Lyss.
JOIN DARE TO DETACH - DOORS OPEN NOV 11TH Use code &amp;quot;selflove&amp;quot; for a discount when you join us. DOORS OPEN NOVEMBER 11TH FOR ALL NEW MEMBERS.</description></item><item><title>It's time to upgrade, uplevel, and become f*cking unstoppable this fall season | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you know how special and important you are??? Do you know how much you bring to the table? NO ONE IS YOU and that is your superpower. In this episode, I discuss ways to level up, create boundaries, know your worth and much more.
The Dare to Detach MASTERCLASS doors open November 16th, 2023 for new clients! Learn more HERE.
Use code &amp;quot;selflove&amp;quot; for $20 off the course when you join us.</description></item><item><title>How to handle rejection &amp; move on | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 13:45:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rejection is redirection - everyone has dealt with rejection at a point. Sometimes the universe is here to just guide you into a much bigger and better situation that you could've even imagined for yourself.
In this episode, I dive into a dating story time about a guy who got me hooked on him and then ghosted me - ultimately leaving me feeling rejected, hurt, and embarrassed. I also talk about how to know your value and how it was fairly easy for me to overcome this situation after time had passed.</description></item><item><title>Dare to Detach | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300009/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300009/</guid><description>Podcast Description JOIN DARE TO DETACH
Tap HERE to join our amazing community!
Are you tired of constantly holding onto what isn't good for you? Are you feeling stuck and discouraged because you KNOW your higher self is calling for a massive upgrade? It is TIME to uplevel into the most amazing version of you. This masterclass is designed to help you let go and set yourself free so you can UPGRADE YOUR LIFE baby.</description></item><item><title>The power of being direct and communicative (stop playing games) | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300010/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, I talk about the power of being direct, forward and just communicating versus running from your problems - especially when it comes to dating. Sometimes I&amp;rsquo;ve been anxious or afraid to speak my truth because of the fear of messing things up. But, as of recently, that changed. Here&amp;rsquo;s everything I&amp;rsquo;ve learned about being honest and direct about my feelings. If you enjoyed this episode, always dm me @lyss and let me know your feedback.</description></item><item><title>Mastermind - how to get anything or anyone you want | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300011/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Become a mastermind and manifest anything or anyone you want with just a simple mindset. Trust the process baby. You've got this. If you enjoyed this episode, dm me on instagram and check out the new masterclass, Dare to Detach, coming October 11th!
My new masterclass coming out October 11th.
instagram.com/daretodetach
My personal ig:
instagram.com/lyss
Transcript</description></item><item><title>If you can't match my energy, BYEEE (masculine vs. feminine energy) | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300012/</guid><description>Podcast Description If I'm dating you, you better bring the same vibes and energy to the f*cking table. If you don't reply to me for days, it's not the vibe. If you could go 48 hours without a reply...it's a no. Here are some of my dealbreakers, my opinions on matching energy in dating, and alllll the coverage on masculine versus feminine energy. If you enjoyed this episode, dm me @lyss and feel free to share it - it helps the pod grow.</description></item><item><title>5 signs you need to breakup + my views on sex &amp; casual hookups | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300013/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you're in a sticky situation where you are attached to someone but you just can't seem to let them go, this episode covers the major warning signs and red flags that I personally feel could make or break a relationship. These are some of my dealbreakers that I find are helpful when deciding when to leave a relationship. In the second half of this episode, I talk about my views on sex and intimacy for the first time ever on the pod, and my perspective on casual hookups.</description></item><item><title>You deserve consistency. It should feel good - if it doesn’t, let that sh*t go. | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Just listen. This is a goodie.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>YOUR THOUGHTS CREATE YOUR REALITY | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300015/</guid><description>Podcast Description SURPRISE to the video episode :) It's the 1 year anniversary of DATE YOURSELF INSTEAD baby!!! Wow. I can't believe just one year ago I started the podcast and it became what it is today. In this episode, I discuss my mental health journey, as well as this idea of your THOUGHTS creating your reality. Thinking positively about your life and yourself, and your future...is SO essential in order to live the life of your dreams.</description></item><item><title>How to know if they're the 1 - GREEN FLAGS | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Self love leads to true love. There is some wholesome loving content on today's episode. This is your reminder that you deserve true, deep, unconditional love. You deserve peace and safety. You deserve to feel secure in a relationship. Xoxo, Lyss &amp;lt;3
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Stop diluting your power for a man | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300017/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's easy to lose focus when you're so fixated on someone else. But baby, you have to remember that YOU ARE THE MAIN CHARACTER. When it comes to relationships, we often dilute our power and give our energy away instead of directing it towards OURSELVES. Agree or disagree?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>He's just not that into you | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Signs that he's just not that into you. He's being hot and cold. Flaky with plans. Distant. A bad texter. Says he doesn't know where he stands or what he wants. In this episode, I dish the hard truth and the signs of when someone is just not...that interested.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Here's what to do when they pull away | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300019/</guid><description>Podcast Description When someone pulls away, it can be difficult to navigate. Often times we feel like we did something wrong to mess the relationship up. It can cause a lot of anxiety if we're not sure where the other person stands or why they're distancing themselves...when everything seemed to be going well. In this episode, I talk about what to do when they pull away from you - and how to handle it like a pro.</description></item><item><title>Why we broke up - the breakup that changed me forever | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why my ex and I broke up - the full detailed story. I wasn't sure if I would ever speak on this relationship and the breakup that changed me forever. In this episode, I am finally sharing my experience and more details about the breakup that inspired the Date Yourself Instead podcast. If this resonated with you in any way, I would love to hear your story as well.</description></item><item><title>How to raise your standards HIGH AF | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cause you deserve the best :-) I love you.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The POWER of solo traveling | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ahhhh. SOLO TRAVEL. One of the most highly requested topics I get asked to cover is my experience doing shit alone. And yeah, it can be intimidating, scary and crazy to go off on adventures completely solo. In this episode, I talk about a few experiences I&amp;rsquo;ve had solo traveling, the lessons I&amp;rsquo;ve learned, my honest thoughts on it, and a wild story time about my study abroad journey in Australia.</description></item><item><title>How to master detachment | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300023/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's a detached girl summer. Psssst if you loved this episode, DM me on instagram @lyss
and stay updated by following the podcast on Spotify.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to be unbothered, go no contact, deal with cheating, &amp; more | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300024/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s official - I am HERE to answer all of your questions on this very juicy episode of Date Yourself Instead. In this episode, I discuss the art of being unbothered and how to live your truth, how to go no contact and my thoughts on blocking someone if you&amp;rsquo;re broken up, my honest thoughts on cheating, and more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The red flags you see now are the reasons you'll leave later | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Self explanatory. If you see some major issues early on, my best advice is to get out while you still can. The red flags you see in the beginning are the reasons you'll most likely leave the relationship later - or they'll be the reason you're unhappy in a relationship. Yes, people can grow and change, however, I've noticed that my gut was always telling me to run prior to diving deeper into a situation with someone.</description></item><item><title>How to really DATE YOURSELF INSTEAD | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300026/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 04:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dating yourself instead. What does dating yourself really mean? I'm in London right now, and I decided to push myself out of my comfort zone. Here's a full breakdown of how I've recently started to date myself, take myself out and dive into a brand new timeline to change my life and open my heart up to the idea of meeting new people. When you go through a breakup, it can be difficult to put yourself out there and learn how to be alone, so this episode covers everything you need to know.</description></item><item><title>How to trust the process of your life &amp; manifest faster | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300027/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 23:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trusting the process of your life can be a scary thing to do when it feels like everything is falling apart. It's also harder when you're trying to manifest things and you just feel blocked, stagnant and not your best self. Here is my best advice when it comes to trusting your journey, and how to manifest and attract the best things into your life faster. If you loved this episode, would mean the world if you rated on Spotify and sent me a dm on instagram @lyss @dateyourselfinstead.</description></item><item><title>Work on yourself so much until they're not your type anymore | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300028/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 23:00:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300028/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you're overly consumed by the idea of a person instead of focusing on yourself, this episode is for you. We get so caught up and easily fixated on a new relationship, or a partner that isn't giving us the love we deserve, and it becomes an ultimate form of distraction away from who we are, our goals, and what truly makes us happy. This episode is really just a reminder to work on yourself and your goals, and find the passion that drives you, instead of focusing on someone that isn't showing up for you.</description></item><item><title>The worst dates I’ve been on in New York City | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300029/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300029/</guid><description>Podcast Description You asked for it, and here we are. The worst dates I&amp;rsquo;ve ever been on in New York City. Dating can be a whirlwind, and an absolute mess - especially with easy access to dating apps. In my late 20&amp;rsquo;s, I would go on dates for fun that often were either really fun or a total disaster. In this episode, I talk about some of the worst experiences I&amp;rsquo;ve had.</description></item><item><title>How to avoid getting attached too quickly | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300030/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300030/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s easy to get attached to someone we&amp;rsquo;ve just met&amp;hellip;because they&amp;rsquo;re nice. Because they&amp;rsquo;re attractive and treat us right. But how soon is too soon to get attached? Often times I&amp;rsquo;d become so fixated on one person early on, only to realize it was all smoke and mirrors. This person was not at all who I thought they were. So here&amp;rsquo;s an episode talking about that experience, and how to avoid getting attached too fast.</description></item><item><title>I was LOVE BOMBED - a dating story time | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300031/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 04:00:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300031/</guid><description>Podcast Description The first half of this episode talks about self worth, valuing yourself and to avoid jumping into a new relationship before you&amp;rsquo;ve processed a breakup. The second half of this episode talks about love bombing and a story time of a guy I dated super briefly that was fucking obsessed with me for a hot minute and then put me in a really uncomfortable situation, and THEN vanished off the face of the earth.</description></item><item><title>Stop being desperate &amp; needy in love | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300032/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 04:00:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300032/</guid><description>Podcast Description I definitely have had my moments in relationships where I felt like I smothered my partner with desperate energy. I was needy and insecure because I didn&amp;rsquo;t love or value myself enough to know who I truly was. I didn&amp;rsquo;t know my worth, so I would project my insecurities often onto my boyfriends in hopes that would make them want to be with me more, but instead it often backfired and became messy.</description></item><item><title>Stop giving SO much to someone you’re not even dating | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300033/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 04:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300033/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, I dive into a storytime about a guy I was taking on dates around New York City. I was putting in an unreasonable amount of effort…and for what? When someone isn’t your boyfriend, you shouldn’t be the only one making concrete plans.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to feel GOOD being alone | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300034/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Being alone can be a scary experience at first, especially after a breakup. In this episode, I dive into my advice about being by myself and what I’ve learned from being my own company.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>I did magic mushrooms in mexico - here's what I took from it | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300035/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Psyliocybin. Magic mushrooms. Tulum. This experience changed my life and my perception of everything in the world. I was going through one of the worst depressions, and I met a Spirit Guide in Mexico who altered the course of my life permanently. She guided me through a magic mushroom trip that would ultimately lead me to creating the podcast, and free me from a great deal of trauma I had carried with me over the course of my life.</description></item><item><title>Forgiving yourself when you've f*cked up | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300036/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300036/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happens when you're the problem? Forgiving yourself when you've made a mistake can be challenging. We all go through periods of time in our live where we're bound to make mistakes, but those mistakes can turn into valuable learning lessons. In this episode, I give various examples of how we can f*ck up and how it can be helpful to just own up to those mistakes and be honest with who you are.</description></item><item><title>Not everyone is going to like you | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300037/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Not everyone is going to like you or accept you - that's just how life is. The most important thing is that YOU like you. In this episode, I talk about my personal experiences with how people treated me poorly for no apparent reason at all - and what those experiences taught me. If you enjoyed this episode, always feel free to DM me on instagram @lyss and @dateyourselfinstead.</description></item><item><title>How to know if you're with the wrong person vs. right person | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300038/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 07:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Being with the wrong person can feel heavy on your heart and on your mind. It could feel like you're constantly trying to change for someone else or try to compromise your needs for someone else. In this episode, I dive into what it feels like to be in the wrong relationship, or in a relationship that needs some work. I also dive into what it feels like to be in a good and healthy relationship with a partner.</description></item><item><title>Going through a breakup? Here's the ultimate best friend pep talk | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300039/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sign up ⁠HERE ⁠for my limited edition, exclusive hoodies: ⁠http://www.dateyourselfinstead.co⁠
They are dropping SO soon and there are only 100 hoodies available, so sign up for the waitlist to snag one before they sell out.
Going through a breakup? Today I'm talking to you as your best friend. You deserve the world. You deserve to be happy. Remember that you have the power to create the life you want, and that you deserve to be surrounded by people who appreciate and value you.</description></item><item><title>Twin flames and karmic relationships | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300040/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 07:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Twin flames - are they a good or bad thing? In this episode, I dive into my personal twin flame experience and the valuable lessons I learned from dating mine. I reflect on how my twin flame taught me a lot about myself, and helped me grow &amp;amp; mature as a person. As always, if you enjoyed this episode, feel free to rate the podcast on Spotify, and send me a message on instagram @lyss or @dateyourselfinstead.</description></item><item><title>How to let go and move on because you deserve BETTER | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300041/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 07:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300041/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the ultimate breakup guide and podcast for anyone trying to move on and let go, because you deserve better. You deserve someone who will commit to you and give you the world. Why are you settling? In this episode, I discuss my perspective on this topic and dive into my own emotions as well. Remember, you can always message me on instagram @lyss or @dateyourselfinstead if you enjoyed this episode.</description></item><item><title>The power of walking away | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300042/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 07:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why are we so afraid to walk away from a toxic relationship?
Sometimes we're afraid to leave relationships for a variety of reasons, including:
Fear of being alone
Fear of the unknown
Fear of change
Children and family obligations
And so much more. In this episode, I talk about the power of walking away from a relationship that isn't serving you, and some useful tips to navigate a breakup.</description></item><item><title>Love letter method - manifest your soulmate instantly | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300043/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 14:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Surprise!!! I decided to release this one early because, well...I love you all dearly. Manifest your soulmate literally instantly, this works every time ;) This video is about how I manifested 3 different people into my life using a letter. It's simple, effective, and can bring magic and miracles into your life really quickly. &amp;nbsp;Let's connect on my socials! If you decide to try this, let me know. &amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>How self-respect changes everything | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300044/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 08:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300044/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is all about self-respect, taking a stand for what you believe in, and valuing who you truly are.
Self-respect means honoring yourself over anyone else, and ignoring what other people are saying about you. For most of my life, I've been bullied for my image and my looks, and as I've gotten older, I've realized that the only way to honor who I am is to block out the noise and focus on self-love.</description></item><item><title>Right person, wrong time | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300045/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 08:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300045/</guid><description>Podcast Description The phrase "right person, wrong time” is an expression that describes a situation where two people are deeply in love but are unable to be together due to circumstances beyond their control.&amp;nbsp;So, is this concept real? In today's episode, I dive into why I think the right person, wrong time is not necessarily true. I also dive into different examples and stories that prove that true love will always find its way back if it's really meant to be.</description></item><item><title>Setting boundaries in love &amp; how toxic relationships can make you sick | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 08:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300046/</guid><description>Podcast Description I am guilty of doing too much for the wrong person and I know I’m not the only one, so I wanted to dive a little bit into people pleasing and boundary setting in this episode. Plus, I have some insight on how toxic relationship can impact your physical health, so we are also talking about the signs to watch for and things I’ve learned from personal experience.</description></item><item><title>50 ways to date yourself at any age | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300047/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dating yourself - what does it REALLY mean? In today’s episode, I dive into why I think Valentine’s Day is a scam, why learning to love yourself is important regardless of your relationship status, and 50 ways to date yourself at any age. Learning the power of self-love and treating yourself to a day of fun with or without a partner is always a good idea. PS - this Valentine’s Day, I’ll be treating myself to a romantic dinner for one.</description></item><item><title>Let go of them and become MAGNETIC as f*ck | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300048/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300048/</guid><description>Podcast Description We all know how this story goes; You’re in love or like with someone but you’re holding on too tight. When you choose to let go of them, they sense it and try to come right back into your life. In this episode I build on how to take your POWER back after a breakup and talk about what being magnetic means, what letting go looks like and the empowerment you’ll feel when you experience the freedom of stepping into your higher self.</description></item><item><title>You’re not “crazy” - why trusting your gut is SO powerful | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300049/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300049/</guid><description>Podcast Description I pride myself on my sense of intuition, but those gut feelings can be easy to ignore especially if you’re like me and like giving people the benefit of the doubt. In this episode I share a story where gaslighting and red flags were ignored until my gut was screaming at me. Sometimes we get too in our heads to listen to that built-in accuracy radar but know that feelings of insecurity are normal, and the right person will work through those feelings with you.</description></item><item><title>How to manifest your dream life in 2023 | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300050/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 08:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300050/</guid><description>Podcast Description With the fresh start 2023 is giving us, it’s the perfect time to start attracting abundance and transforming into your best self. I share the stories of the power of manifesting in my own life and how you can harness your own power and manifest your dream life too! Have you heard about this lucky girl syndrome trend? I’m going to experiment with this over the next few months.</description></item><item><title>30 things I learned before my 30th birthday | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300051/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 08:00:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300051/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a big thing to be turning 30 and a lot has happened in the past couple of years to make me who I am today. This week I am talking about 30 things I learned before turning 30. I also wanted to say a belated Happy New Year and I’m so excited about getting listeners involved in the future of the podcast; bringing on guests and incorporating your topic suggestions!</description></item><item><title>Proving people wrong is fun | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300052/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 08:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300052/</guid><description>Podcast Description I’ve had a lot of hate over the years in my career and I have learned that I don’t need to prove myself to anyone. All of the energy I put into listening to what other people thought of me never helped me get anywhere. In this episode, I share some of these pivotal moments and tips I use to harness that energy to create an amazing life for myself.</description></item><item><title>How to detach, let go, and REALLY move on | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300053/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 08:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Detaching is an art that can be very emotionally challenging. Becoming aware of what is NOT serving your growth then letting go of it can make you MAGNETIC. This episode lays out the steps to detach in a healthy way and how I have applied them to relationships in my life. If this is a part of your journey, go easy on yourself. Detaching can be such a beautiful thing!</description></item><item><title>Stop being impressed by the BARE MINIMUM | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300054/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 08:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we talk about the many reasons why you should raise your dating standards but what does it ACTUALLY mean to claim your power? You are not somebody’s backup plan! I share what I do to remember my worth and the shift that can happen when you learn how to show up for yourself and not tolerate shitty behavior. Once you love yourself so fucking much, you’ll attract someone that matches your love!</description></item><item><title>Let’s talk situationships | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300055/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 08:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300055/</guid><description>Podcast Description One of the questions I get in my DM’s regularly is: Am I doing the right thing by staying in this situationship? As always, no pressure to jump out of a situationship if you’re loving where you’re at but if you want to address the pros and cons, we are talking expectations, standards, communication and genuine happiness. If your happiness is being compromised right now, remember that you deserve unconditional love and you are amazing!</description></item><item><title>Falling in love with a narcissist | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300056/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300056/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you’re dating a person based on a conceptualized version of them vs. the person they are consistently showing you that they are, I’ve been there. Today I am sharing my challenging experience with a narcissist and what I learned from it. Once you understand narcissistic personalities then start to turn inward to examine your worth, your transformation can begin!
Connect with the Date Yourself Instead Movement: Website | Instagram</description></item><item><title>Why are female friendships so hard? | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300057/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300057/</guid><description>Podcast Description I got a DM that hit hard: How do you make friends to easily in NYC? Just like other relationships, female friendships can be toxic. If you always gravitate toward masculine energy, maybe you can relate to this. A lot of what I have experienced in the social media space has been superficial, but in this episode you’ll hear about how I balance surrounding myself with genuine, empowering people and wondering, am I the problem?</description></item><item><title>How to manifest your soulmate | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300058/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 08:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300058/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you’re ready to receive someone into your life, this story may inspire you manifest it. Once, after listening to a podcast suggesting manifesting a love by writing a letter, I immediately met a new person. It’s easy to match someone’s energy for too long and lose yourself. Instead, you can use your positive thoughts to manifest someone that you can be your true self with.
Connect with the Date Yourself Instead Movement: Website | Instagram</description></item><item><title>Feeling lonely on the holidays | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300059/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 08:00:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Feeling cozy and celebrating the holidays with a significant other is such a great feeling but when I realized that I will likely be alone for the holidays this year... the anxiety spiral began. If you’re feeling left out during the holiday season, I share some tips what can shift your perspective. You’re welcome to feel your feelings but if you’re ready to embrace this season in a new way, focusing on being alone can be a super positive experience!</description></item><item><title>Do all men come back? | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300060/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 08:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300060/</guid><description>Podcast Description I am constantly flooded with this question: Do all men come back? If you’re in a waiting period right now, this episode validates all of the feelings that come along with that. Sharing from my personal experience in situationships and relationships, I talk about how to assess if this is a connection worth exploring and if it is, how to become a magnet. Either way, know that you deserve a healthy and amazing love and that the universe has got you!</description></item><item><title>how to take your POWER back after a breakup | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300061/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 08:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300061/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is probably my favorite one yet, because it’s going to teach you how to TAKE YOUR POWER BACK after a bad breakup. It’s so easy to lose yourself in a toxic relationship, and this episode covers everything you need to know about claiming who you are again and focusing on healthy ways to heal. You know you’re unstoppable and you have all the power you need within yourself; it’s just about finding it again.</description></item><item><title>A Halloween storytime and my best manifestation tips | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300062/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 07:00:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300062/</guid><description>Podcast Description HAPPY HALLOWEEN! For all of you fellow witches out there, I know this day is very special to you because it is to me. This episode is going to be different. I’m diving into a crazy story about how my mom was almost murdered while she was pregnant with me. I’ll also be covering my best manifestation tips and practices for this spooky season. PS - if you have any fun Halloween plans, DM me on instagram @Lyss.</description></item><item><title>Stop Comparing Yourself To Everyone Else | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300063/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 07:00:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode is going to talk about COMPARISON and why there is no point in ever comparing yourself to anyone else. In the world of social media, it is so difficult sometimes to pull yourself away from what everyone else is doing. The truth is, most of what you see isn't real. I also talk about my personal experiences dealing with social media and the reality of what I've been through.</description></item><item><title>it’s okay to be depressed | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300064/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300064/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s okay to allow yourself to feel your feelings. Lyss tells the story of entering therapy and the lows she had to let herself fully experience in order to get to the root of her issues. The only way out is through and Lyss talks about the loss and shock she felt before finding her purpose and reinventing herself. Don’t put off moving your body, trust the process &amp;amp; lean into what make you feel alive.</description></item><item><title>My Red Flags When Dating | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300065/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever been love bombed or felt underwhelmed by the texting character shown by the person you’re talking to? This week Lyss shares her personal experience with red flags while dating. When no effort is put in to making plans and excuses start to stack up, follow your intuition. Stay tuned for part two!
Connect with the Date Yourself Instead Movement: Website | Instagram
Connect with Lyss: TikTok | Instagram | YouTube</description></item><item><title>So he ghosted you…now what? | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300066/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 07:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ok so he ghosted you, now what are you supposed to do? In this episode, I take it step by step on what to do when someone ghosts you. Because we all know getting ghosted can be a shitty feeling. Don’t worry, I’ve got you covered.
Connect with the Date Yourself Instead Movement: Website | Instagram
Connect with Lyss: TikTok | Instagram | YouTube
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How I Attracted My Ex Back with The Law of Attraction | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300067/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300067/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you’re skeptical about the Law of Attraction, the stories in this episode will convince you otherwise. Lyss was in a loose relationship that ended brutally when months later a symbolic necklace pulled his energy back into her space. Lyss also followed her intuition in a different relationship which built a connection that was a crucial part of her personal development.
Connect with the Date Yourself Instead Movement: Website | Instagram</description></item><item><title>Free Girl Fall, F*ck Boy Fall (And A Dating Story Time) | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300068/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 07:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lyss is kicking off the fall season in a positive and inspirational way. Join her mental freedom journey as she explains the new routines she’s putting in place to set the tone for the rest of the year. Life is short so Lyss is focusing on fueling her passions + she ends this episode with a classic f*ck boy fall dating story that is to be continued.
Connect with the Date Yourself Instead Movement: Website | Instagram</description></item><item><title>How to Heal from a Heartbreak | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300069/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 07:00:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today Lyss speaks on a highly requested topic: Heartbreak. She relives one of the most painful breakups she has ever experienced and covers all of the very relatable insecurities that come post-breakup. This episode is full of practical steps Lyss took to begin the healing process and the inspiration that came after the healing began.
Connect with the Date Yourself Instead Movement: Website | Instagram
Connect with Lyss: TikTok | Instagram | YouTube</description></item><item><title>Trusting Your Intuition and Inner Voice | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300070/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 07:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today Lyss shares takeaways from past dating experience on valuing herself, trusting her intuition + the amazing things that she has attracted when she wasn’t mirroring a toxic partner. Lyss also had a new experience with a psychic this week and is feeling the pressure of being at a crossroads at work.
Connect with the Date Yourself Instead Movement: Website | Instagram
Connect with Lyss: TikTok | Instagram | YouTube</description></item><item><title>Welcome to Date Yourself Instead | Date Yourself Instead</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5623300071/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 20:27:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5623300071/</guid><description>Podcast Description You’ve made it to Date Yourself Instead, a podcast intended to inspire you to become the best version of yourself. In 2021, social media personality Lyss started a self-love series on TikTok which amassed over 100+ million views on her videos and counting. In this podcast, she gets candid about her relationship experiences, and touches on other topics including business, beauty, wellness, and so much more. Welcome to the #dateyourselfinstead movement.</description></item></channel></rss>