<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/new-heights-with-jason-and-travis-kelce/</link><description>Recent content in New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 10:50:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/new-heights-with-jason-and-travis-kelce/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Eagles Frustrations, Travis' Touchdown That Wasn't and Shohei's $700 million Contract | Ep 68 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420070/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 10:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420070/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with another episode of New Heights sponsored by Uncrustables, the best part of the sandwich™. In this episode, we’ve got some huge New News from our friends at Homage. To check out the limited edition New Heights Starter Jacket, visit www.homage.com/NewHeights. Quantity is limited. The sale starts at 7AM EST. We also answer some “No Dumb Questions” about what to eat in Cleveland, who can lift more, where we almost went to school besides Cincinnati, and what happens to a player after they get ejected from a game.</description></item><item><title>Birds' Beatdown, Chiefs Controversial Ending and the Florida State Playoff Snub | Ep 67 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420069/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 10:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420069/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with another episode of New Heights presented by our friends at Walmart. Get going on their holiday wish list &amp;amp; shop amazing deals from Walmart Ready? Set. Gift! In this episode, we’ve got some huge New News from our friends at Spotify, New Heights is officially a sandwich, Travis could be lacing up the skates, and we might have an official “mom fight” on our hands.</description></item><item><title>Jalen's Walks Off, Chiefs Offense Bounces Back and "The Gang Starts a Bidding War" | Ep 66 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420068/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 10:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420068/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with another episode of New Heights presented by our friends at Experian and the all-new Experian Debit Card and Digital checking account! In this episode, we’ve got some huge New News about the winner of the auction for the (04:45) Kylie Kelce signed Eagles jacket, (24:50) some not dumb questions about locker room interviews, and the guys pick their all NFL hockey starting 5. We then recap the (38:18) Chiefs offense rebounding against the Raiders, (44:34) Travis breaking yet another career milestone, (49:18) Rashee Rice’s breakout game, and Travis gets a recruitment phone call from one of Cleveland’s finest (56:10).</description></item><item><title>Jason’s Late Birthday Gift, Travis’ Old Tweets and Thanksgiving Sides Power Ranking | Ep 65 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420067/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420067/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with another episode of New Heights presented by our friends at Experian and the all-new Experian Debit Card and Digital checking account! In this episode, we’ve got some big New News about our duet “Fairytale of Philadelphia” (5:30), Travis has a new collaboration with his clothing brand Tru Kolors (12:28) and Jason asks Travis about being the December/January cover star of Wall Street Journal Magazine (13:47).</description></item><item><title>The Sexiest Batman Alive, The Guy on the Chiefs and A Kelce Duet | Ep 64 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420065/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 10:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420065/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with another episode of New Heights presented by our friends at Experian and the all-new Experian Debit Card and Digital checking account! In this episode, we’ve got some huge New News (01:45) coming your way about the “Family Reunion” Watch Party, Jason lets us know what it’s like to be a “Sexiest Man Alive” finalist (07:45), and we get the details on the Kelce Christmas duet dropping today.</description></item><item><title>Travis Footballs Abroad, Jason’s Birthday Scream, and Shark Attack Stories | Ep 63 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420064/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 10:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420064/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with another episode of New Heights presented by our friends at Experian and the all-new Experian Debit Card and Digital checking account! In this episode, we’ve got some huge New News (01:40) coming your way about the “Kelce Family Reunion Game,” we try and start a petition to send Travis to space (06:25), Jason lets us know why he’s staying out of the water (08:40), and we find out who had the worst part-time job in college (17:17).</description></item><item><title>Jordan Mailata on Journey From Rugby to NFL, Jalen Hurts Dynamic and Greatest Australians | Ep 62 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420001/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420001/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with a special guest episode of New Heights presented by our friends at Experian and the all-new Experian Debit Card and Digital checking account! In this episode, we’re joined by Jason’s teammate Philadelphia Eagles offensive tackle Jordan Mailata to talk about the new Eagles Christmas album (2:27), and the guys also revisit a not-dumb question about rugby players in the NFL utilizing Jordan’s rugby expertise (12:29).</description></item><item><title>Eagles Offensive Highs, Chiefs Mile High Lows, and A New Heights Halloween | Ep 61 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 10:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420002/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with another episode of New Heights presented by our friends at Experian and the all-new Experian Debit Card and Digital checking account! In this episode, we review some of your GOAT Halloween candy suggestions, make a major announcement about our new official fan club, reveal our guest for the next special episode dropping this Friday, and answer some of your NOT dumb questions about hard counts.</description></item><item><title>Jason’s Throwback Win, Travis Reacts to “Swift Stats", and The Halloween Candy Debate | Ep 60 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420003/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with another episode of New Heights presented by our friends at Experian and the all-new Experian Debit Card and Digital checking account! In this episode, we break the news about another Kelce Christmas album (01:47), Travis trying to take F1 (04:10), and answer your not-dumb questions about the best Halloween Candy (19:07). Travis also defends National Tight End Day (42:20), breaks down the Chiefs offensive explosion against the Chargers (47:03), and how he feels about the media inventing “Swift Stats.</description></item><item><title>Eagles First Stumble, SNL Cameos and The Kelce’s Red October | Ep 59 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420004/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with another episode of New Heights presented by our friends at Experian and the all-new Experian Debit Card and Digital checking account! In this episode, we get into all your biggest questions about Jason’s nasty locker (02:00), Travis moonlighting as a security guard (05:30), the most confusing penalty in football (22:00), and some cute-ass No Dumb Questions (23:35). Travis also breaks down Chiefs/Broncos on Thursday night football (30:52) including what he was thinking on that lateral play (37:40), how the Chiefs are improving in the red zone (40:45), and the momentous occasion that was Big Ed Kelce the Swiftie (45:10).</description></item><item><title>Road Wins, Turf Bans and Getting Called Out By Lebron | Ep 58 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 10:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420005/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with another episode of New Heights presented by our friends at Experian and the all-new Experian Debit Card and Digital checking account! In this episode, we react to LeBron James wanting to bring his game to New Heights, probably give a too-technical explanation of zone coverage, and reminisce about Travis starting food fights at good ol’ Cleveland Heights High. We also recap Jason’s first trip to SoFi Stadium, his reaction to the Swiftie that caught his pre-game warmup, the new way the NFL might ban the “Brotherly Shove,” and why he got heated on the sideline.</description></item><item><title>Jason Survives Overtime, Travis Escapes from New York and The NFL Needs to Calm Down | Ep 57 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 09:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420006/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with another episode of New Heights presented by our friends at Experian and the all-new Experian Debit Card and Digital checking account! In this episode, we get into the Eagles&amp;rsquo; overtime win against the Commanders, the analytics behind the decision to go for the TD at the end of regulation, and the new ways defenses are attacking “The Brotherly Shove.” We also recap the star-studded affair that was Sunday Night Football between the Chiefs and Jets, Isiah Pacheco’s homecoming performance, and get into the penalties that have one specific Jets fan incredibly mad online.</description></item><item><title>Chris Jones on Missing Training Camp, Tyreek Hill’s Trash Talk and His NSFW Combine Moment | Ep 56 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420007/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420007/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with a special guest episode of New Heights presented by our friends at Accelerator Active Energy! In this episode, we’re joined by Kansas City Chiefs DT Chris “Stone Cold” Jones! The guys talk to Chris about his new contract (01:52), what it’s really like to miss training camp (3:30), and if he thinks this current Chiefs defense isn’t being talked about enough (5:13). Jason, Travis and Chris also answer your not-dumb question about which NFL players should join the WWE when they retire (6:20).</description></item><item><title>Eagles Stay Unbeaten, Travis’ "Biggest Catch" and New Football Eras | Ep 55 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420008/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92 %ers, and probably a lot of you entering your “football era”, we are back with another episode of New Heights presented by our friends at Accelerator Active Energy! In this episode, we break down the Eagles&amp;rsquo; dominant win on Monday Night Football (6:00), how much better this Eagles D-line might be than last year (12:10) and the right time to go for the hurdle (16:25). We also recap the most talked about 30-point win in the history of the NFL, the Chiefs&amp;rsquo; big win against the Bears (25:29).</description></item><item><title>Jason Defends the Push, Travis’ Record-Breaking Connection and Coach Prime Makes History | Ep 54 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420009/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with another episode of New Heights presented by our friends at Accelerator Active Energy! In this episode, we finally address the topic that you guys have been blowing us up about, did Jason ever find his Super Bowl ring? We also answer your not-dumb questions about the most quotable movie and find out why Travis is so good at taping ankles. We also get to talk about the Eagles bringing back the most dominant play in football, the D’Andre Swift breakout game on Thursday Night Football, and why we don’t actually hate the touchback rule.</description></item><item><title>Travis' Status Update, Jason's “Ugly” Week 1 Win, and Rodgers Reactions | Ep 53 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420010/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with another episode of New Heights presented by our friends at Accelerator Active Energy! In this episode, we will get to the madness that was Week 1 of the NFL season, but first, we hit on how Travis is showing off his sweet ride for a good cause (03:14), why Jason is blaming Kylie for his premiere fit (09:15) and we rank the greatest elementary school PE games of all time (21:13).</description></item><item><title>Kylie Kelce on life as an NFL spouse, Jason’s Tinder Bio, and Setting Up Travis | Ep 52 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420011/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with a new episode of New Heights presented by our friends at Accelerator Active Energy! In this episode, we’ve got a guest that you guys have been asking for since we started this show. The field hockey phenom, the mother of three future Andy Reid Draft Picks, and Jason’s incredible wife, Kylie Kelce! (02:30) In this incredible conversation with Kylie, we get her thoughts on the upcoming ‘Kelce’ Documentary (04:15), her take on the chaos that was Catching Kelce, why she doesn’t play matchmaker for Travis (19:51), and what she really thought of Jason from his Tinder profile.</description></item><item><title>New Season Kick-Off, Training Camp Battles &amp; Conspiracy Theories | Ep 51 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 22:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420012/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are finally back with a new season of New Heights presented by our friends at Accelerator Active Energy! In this episode, we get Jason’s thoughts on the upcoming “Kelce” documentary (01:55), why Travis needs some work on baby security, how it feels to get ranked in the NFL’s Top 100 (13:00), and if Sexy Batman is now the official sex symbol of Philadelphia (17:42). We also break down everything that happened at Chiefs and Eagles training camps.</description></item><item><title>Training Camp Previews, Madden Rating Reactions &amp; Ed Kelce's Art of War | EP 50 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420013/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with another episode of New Heights presented by our friends at Buffalo Wild Wings. For a limited time, buy one 6, 10, or 15-piece traditional wings, get one of equal value free on Tuesdays. In this episode, Travis recaps his time at the American Century Golf tournament (02:45), we find out Ed Kelce’s secrets to winning a bar fight (09:30), and Jason reveals the one Madden rating that still makes him mad (14:50).</description></item><item><title>Julian Edelman on His Brady Relationship, Being Scared of Belichick and Randy Moss' Hot Tub | EP 49 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420014/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with another episode of New Heights presented by our friends at Buffalo Wild Wings. For a limited time, head to BDubs and get some wings with their new sauces, General Tso and Sweet Chile Lime. They won’t be around forever so get ‘em while supplies last. In this episode, we are joined by former New England Patriot, three-time Super Bowl Champion, and Super Bowl MVP Julian Edelman!</description></item><item><title>Travis Dominates The Match, Jason Goes Full Cowboy, and NFL’s Gambling Problem | EP 48 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 14:39:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420015/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with another episode of New Heights presented by our friends at Buffalo Wild Wings. For a limited time, head to BDubs and get some wings with their new sauces, General Tso and Sweet Chile Lime. They won’t be around forever so get ‘em while supplies last. In this episode, we cover a lot of ground for being at the end of the NFL Offseason. We discuss the dangers of naming your kids after people (4:50), how we really felt about The Beer Bowl (8:00), and Travis walks us through what it was like coming up big in The Match with Patrick Mahomes (15:00).</description></item><item><title>The Beer Bowl with Landon Dickerson, Jeff Stoutland, and $50,000 Grand Prize | EP 47 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420016/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers it’s finally here, The first-ever New Heights Beer Bowl! This episode is brought to you by our friends at Buffalo Wild Wings. The Beer Bowl was recorded live at the world-famous Ocean Drive bar in Sea Isle City, New Jersey to support the Eagles Autism Foundation. If you still want to make a donation to EAF, Jason and Travis are competing in a donation challenge to see whose fans can donate the largest sum of money.</description></item><item><title>Alejandro Villanueva on his NFL Career, Serving in Afghanistan and Blocking James Harrison | EP 46 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420017/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420017/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are a little late but we are back with another episode of New Heights presented by our friends at Fireball. In this episode, we are joined by maybe the most interesting man in the world, former Army Ranger turned Pro-Bowl left tackle for the Pittsburgh Steelers Alejandro Villanueva. In our incredible conversation with Alejandro, we get the back story on what happened when he was cut from the Eagles (17:55), why he thinks the NFL Regional Combine is a scam (31:00), how he gained almost 100lbs to play for the Steelers (37:02), what is was really like going up against Jame Harrison in practice every day (49:20), and why Mike Tomlin might be selling himself short (56:26).</description></item><item><title>Mahomes Who, Best Throwbacks, and Whale Wars | EP 45 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420018/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with another episode of New Heights presented by our friends at Fireball. In this episode, we finally get to announce this is an &amp;ldquo;award-winning podcast,&amp;rdquo; show some more of our favorite Beer Bowl entries, and take a look at what might be the first Kelce Brother oil painting. We also attempt to save a marriage with a body wash debate, pitch some new ideas for Tight End U, decide the best NFL throwback jersey, discuss some off-season bulletin board material, and pick sides in the great Orca War of 2023.</description></item><item><title>First Pitch Redemption, Minicamp Reactions, Worst Sports Video Game | EP 44 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 21:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420019/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with another episode of New Heights presented by our friends at Fireball. In this episode, we come out the gate hot and share some of our favorite videos you guys have sent us for the Ocean Drive Beer Bowl, find out the real reason Jason had a mohawk in college, and learn about the legend of Big Craig—at least everything we’re allowed to share about him.</description></item><item><title>Charles Barkley on the NBA Finals, Golfing with Jordan, Favorite Inside the NBA moment &amp; More | EP 43 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420020/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with another episode of New Heights presented by our friends at Fireball. In this episode, we are joined by an absolute sports legend. NBA Hall of Famer, Emmy Winner, Olympics Gold medalist, the round mound of rebound…Charles Barkley! Before we get to Charles, Travis has to address some rumors that we might have started on this show, we recap the Chiefs&amp;rsquo; visit to the White House and what Travis was going to say at the podium, and we give you guys an update on the Ocean Drive Beer Bowl.</description></item><item><title>Best Teams for Hopkins, Tackling Derrick Henry and New Heights Beer Bowl | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420021/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with another episode of New Heights brought to you by our friends at @FireballWhiskyOfficial In this episode, we have more details on how you, yes YOU, can compete in the first-ever New Heights Beer Bowl and have a chance to walk away with the $50k cash prize. Send your submission video to @NewHeightShow or email us at NewHeightShow@gmail.com (01:45) If you want to attend the New Heights Beer Bowl, be one of the top donors supporting Team 62 and the Eagles Autism Foundation at the link below.</description></item><item><title>Saving Special Teams, Dumbest Rookie Purchases and Tom Brady Owns the Raiders | EP 41 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420022/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with another episode of New Heights brought to you by our friends at Fireball! In this episode, we look at some of our favorite comments from the live show (4:10), we settle one of the internet’s dumbest debates involving straws (12:30) and let you know what piece of football equipment isn&amp;rsquo;t doing a damn thing (18:00). We also react to all the rules changes coming out of the NFL Spring Meetings (29:00).</description></item><item><title>New Heights Live with Patrick Mahomes, Roger Goodell, Tony Gonzalez, Eric Stonestreet &amp; more | EP 40 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420023/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers our first-ever live show filmed in front of an electric crowd on April 26th at the historic Kansas City Music Hall is finally here! This show features opening remarks delivered by the commissioner of the National Football League himself, Roger Goodell (03:00), and guest appearances by Creed Humphrey, Eric Stonestreet (25:00), Chiefs legend Tony Gonzalez (51:40), and the Super Bowl Champion quarterbacks for the Kansas City Chiefs, Chad Henne, and Patrick Mahomes (01:14:30).</description></item><item><title>NFL Schedule Release Recap, Travis Goes International and LeBron to the Finals? | EP 39 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420024/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with another episode of New Heights brought to you by our friends at Fireball! In this episode, we have some major updates for you guys about how you can help us win our first major award, when we’re releasing the Kansas City live episode, our favorite comments on the Andy Reid episode, and some of our favorite not dumb questions. We also break down all things NFL schedule release; from the team social media videos, games we’ve already got circled, how Travis might spend his time in Germany, and for some reason, a long discussion on tubular-shaped meats.</description></item><item><title>Andy Reid on Drafting the Kelce Brothers, Coaching Mahomes, Super Bowl Memories &amp; More | EP 38 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 09:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420025/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with another episode of New Heights presented by our friends at Fireball. In this episode, we are joined by maybe our most requested guest. It’s the two-time Super Bowl Champion head coach of the Kansas City Chiefs Andy Reid! Coach Reid talks with the guys about his real first impression of Travis (8:50), what advice led him to become an NFL head coach (14:10), the biggest takeaway from his time in Philly (24:10), and if Travis will ever get another shot at QB (28:41).</description></item><item><title>NFL Draft Recap, Why Jalen Carter Fits in Philly and Best Rookie Advice | EP 37 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420026/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with another episode of New Heights and today we are recapping all things NFL Draft. In this episode, we try and figure out the rules for the “Official” New Heights drinking game (01:53), recap what went down at the live show and when that will be available on our channel (10:50), check in on how Jason’s family reacted to his new haircut (19:00), and find out if Travis spiked the real Lombardi trophy on stage at Kelce Jam (31:35).</description></item><item><title>Early vs Late-Round Picks, NFL Draft Preview Pt. 2 &amp; Throwing Lefty with 49ers Brock Purdy | EP 37 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420027/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 09:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420027/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with part 2 of our special NFL Draft Preview episode presented by our friends at Buffalo Wild Wings. In this episode, the guys break down what it takes for late-round picks to make an NFL roster (16:50), how we’d steal from the Premiere League to make the draft even better (22:40), and Jason has incredibly strong opinions on the best donut (3:55). This episode also includes our “Purdy Good” conversation with 49ers Quarterback, Brock Purdy (22:50).</description></item><item><title>Jalen Hurts Gets Paid, Draft Preview Pt. 1 &amp; Recruiting Rodgers w/Sauce Gardner | EP 36 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420028/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with part 1 of our special NFL Draft Preview episode presented by our friends at Buffalo Wild Wings. Part 2 will be dropping next Monday so make sure you’re subscribed so you don’t miss it. In this episode, we take a look at the Big Yeti getting buckets in High School, Donna Kelce making the NFL Hall of Fame before Tom Brady, give a breakdown of Travis’ just a bit outside first pitch, and give a shoutout to the NFL’s new highest-paid player Jalen Hurts.</description></item><item><title>Shannon Sharpe on Mentoring Travis, Tight End Mt. Rushmore, Playing in Today's NFL &amp; More | EP 35 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420029/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420029/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with another episode of New Heights presented by our friends at Fireball. In this episode, we are joined by an NFL Hall of Famer, Tight End legend, and the man better known as “Unc,” Shannon Sharpe. Shannon talks with the guys about how his mentoring relationship with Travis started (07:20), how the secret to Tight End success might be all in the hips (14:30), and who is on Shannon’s TE Mt.</description></item><item><title>Easter Mock Draft, Jason’s Dad Advice &amp; Play Calling w/Shane Steichen | EP 34 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420030/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420030/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with episode thirty-four of New Heights presented by our friends at Fireball. In this episode, we have a huge update about how you could snag some tickets to the live show in Kansas City (03:40), we get Travis’ thoughts on going viral last week (14:33) and dive back into a debate that has haunted this show for months, can NFL players hoop? (18:51) We also get Travis’ story about stepping into the batter’s box against a Cy Young winner (21:21), Jason has some advice for all the potential new dads out there (25:08), and we have our first-ever New Heights mock draft about what else, Easter Candy.</description></item><item><title>Fixing the No Fun League, Best Teams for Lamar &amp; Rebuilding with Howie Roseman | New Heights | EP 33 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420031/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 21:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420031/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with episode thirty-three of New Heights presented by our friends at Fireball. In this episode, we’re breaking down all the news coming out of the Annual Owner’s Meeting. Including, Jason’s thoughts on the “Tush Push” surviving another season (10:15), why we secretly enjoy kickers getting lit up (14:45), and the number 0 getting added to jerseys (26:10). In sports, we also have an electric debate on the best digit, yes singular digit (31:25), a chaotic breakdown of the annual coaches&amp;rsquo; photo (32:54), and Travis’ attempt to name every NFL head coach (37:15).</description></item><item><title>Free Agency Rumors, NFL Players as Pokemon &amp; Rich Eisen | New Heights | Ep 32 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420032/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420032/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with episode thirty-two of New Heights presented by our friends at Fireball. In this episode, we have a huge announcement! (02:00) On April 26th we will be bringing you “New Heights Live” a one-night-only event at the Kansas City Music Hall. Tickets will be available for purchase via Ticketmaster starting Friday, March 24, 2023, at 10:00 am. For more information on the show and to purchase tickets, please visit Ticketmaster.</description></item><item><title>Jason’s Coming Back, Rodgers Decision &amp; Nick Sirianni | New Heights | Ep 31 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420033/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420033/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with episode thirty-one of New Heights presented by our friends at Fireball and it has already been a crazy start to free agency. In this episode, we look at some of the best unsanctioned New Heights Merch (03:55), probably spend too much time sorting NFL players into Hogwarts houses (07:00), and try to figure out who Jerry Jones has been using as a horcrux (13:50).</description></item><item><title>The Real Combine Experience, Blown Interviews &amp; NFL Scouting w/Daniel Jeremiah | New Heights | Ep 30 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420034/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420034/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with the thirtieth episode of New Heights presented by our friends at Fireball and we have an exceptional one for you guys. In this episode, we are talking about all things NFL Combine. Yes, we know this is the start of tampering season, but with Travis hosting SNL we had to delay the recording on this one a little bit. We break down how getting invited to the combine actually works (07:10), what kind of training goes into preparing for the on-field drills (10:00) and revisit some of the formal interviews that didn’t go exactly as planned (17:35).</description></item><item><title>Hosting SNL, Drunken Parades and Meeting Spielberg | New Heights | Ep 29 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420035/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420035/</guid><description>Podcast Description 92%ers we are back with the twenty-ninth episode of New Heights presented by our friends at Fireball and we have a lot to catch you guys up on. On this episode we jump right into the biggest ‘New News,’ we’ve got a New Niece and why Jason doesn’t think he’ll win father of the year anytime soon (03:22). We also look at some Calvin and Hobbes-inspired fan art (08:49), and crown the Quip Podcast MVP (09:57).</description></item><item><title>Super Bowl Reactions, Tears of Joy &amp; the Fan Base Name Revealed | New Heights | Ep 28 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420036/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420036/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the twenty-eighth episode of New Heights presented by our friends at Fireball, this is the definitive recap of Super Bowl 57. Jason and Travis weigh in on what they thought of the field conditions during pre-game warm-ups (23:53), what they felt during the anthem (34:00), what it was like seeing Donna Kelce on the jumbotron (38:45), and if there was any shit-talking during the coin toss (41:01). We then break down the game itself starting with a very Kelce-centric first quarter (42:05), how the Eagles responded to a huge second-quarter turnover (45:05), and what adjustments the Chiefs made in the locker room at halftime (48:34).</description></item><item><title>Eagles - Chiefs Preview, Leaked NFL Scripts and Super Bowl Memories | New Heights | Ep 27 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420037/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420037/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the twenty-seventh episode of New Heights presented by our friends at Fireball, we are coming to you LIVE from Radio Row at the Super Bowl. On this definitive preview of the Super Bowl (aka the Kelce Bowl), we have an update on the New Heights takeover of North America (02:48), if the guys are switching positions for the Super Bowl (10:30), and the results of the fan base name vote (17:30).</description></item><item><title>Mom and Dad on the Kelce Bowl, raising NFL sons and Kelce Family Secrets | New Heights | Ep 26 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420038/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 13:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420038/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the twenty-sixth episode of New Heights, we sit down with the two people the whole country has been waiting to hear from, Donna and Ed Kelce! Donna reveals how she feels about the Kelce bowl (07:00), who she’s really rooting for during the game (10:00), and if she’s going to actually do the pregame coin toss (16:30). We also get answers on who broke the couch growing up (27:20), if Mom really wanted a daughter (29:20) and the truth behind Travis’ name (30:25).</description></item><item><title>Championship Sunday, Jabronis and The Kelce Bowl | New Heights | Ep 25 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 12:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420039/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the twenty-fifth episode of New Heights, the Kelce Bowl is officially happening! Over the weekend everyone’s phones exploded with all the Kelce Bowl shoutouts (02:50). So we try and recap some of our favorites in New News, show off some of the new merch we’re dropping to celebrate the occasion (12:10), and look at some of our favorite fan art that you guys sent us over the week (16:15).</description></item><item><title>Divisional Wins, Season-Ending Plays and Alien Conspiracies | New Heights | Ep 24 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 06:07:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420040/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the twenty-fourth episode of New Heights, we have a massive announcement about something that might be going down in Arizona in a couple of weeks (01:53), we try to recap Travis’ appearance on the Pat McAfee show but somehow end up in a debate about alien conspiracy theories (02:51), look at maybe our most adorable fan mention of all time (21:00), and answer another of your not-dumb questions about NFL rule changes (25:55).</description></item><item><title>Crazy Wildcard Endings, The Vape-Gate &amp; The Waffle House Debate | New Heights| Ep 23 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420041/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420041/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the twenty-third episode of New Heights, Jason and Travis respond to some of your reactions to our very special Gronk episode and try to figure out who to bring on next (01:40), we go through some of the absolutely insane fan art submissions that all involved shaving the big yeti (13:30), and we answer the not dumb question, “Could the average person rush for 1 yard in the NFL?</description></item><item><title>Gronk on Travis Rivalry, NFL Comeback &amp; Relationship with Tom Brady | New Heights | EP 22 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420042/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420042/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the twenty-second episode of New Heights, we&amp;rsquo;ve been asking you guys who you wanted on the show and there was one name that came up every time, or at least 92% of the time. So we finally got the 5x pro bowler, 4x first-team NFL all-pro, 4x Super Bowl Champion, and one of the best to ever do it, Rob Gronkowski. In this episode, Jason and Travis get the details about why Gronk is kicking a field goal at the Super Bowl (03:00), the return of “Gronk Beach” (06:20), and acting alongside GILFs (09:15).</description></item><item><title>Chiefs Trick Play Explained, Playoff Seeding &amp; Introducing ‘The Newsies’ | New Heights with Jason &amp; Travis Kelce | Ep 21 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420043/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the twenty-first episode of New Heights, Jason and Travis react to some of your incredible fan art (01:35) and we answer another of your not-dumb questions, “Which animal could actually play on a football team?” (08:03) We react to both the Eagles and the Chiefs clinching the #1 seeds in the playoffs and how the playoff bye week impacts players physically and mentally. (17:24) Travis breaks down how the Chiefs “Ring Around the Rosie” play actually happened against the Raiders (26:15) and shares some of his favorite stories of his decade with Coach Reid (32:12).</description></item><item><title>Jason and Travis discuss the Damar Hamlin incident and how it impacts the entire NFL | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Not our usual episode this week, right now with only one topic on everyone’s mind it felt right to dedicate our entire video to discussing the incident that happened during Monday Night Football involving Bills Safety Damar Hamlin. The thoughts and prayers from everyone here at New Heights are with Damar, his family, and everyone from the Bills and Bengals organizations. Watch and listen to new episodes of New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce every Wednesday during the NFL season &amp;amp; check us out on Instagram, Twitter and Tiktok for all the best moments from the show Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Playoff Football, Pro Bowl Memories &amp; JJ Watt Retires | New Heights w/Jason &amp; Travis Kelce | Ep 19 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420045/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420045/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the nineteenth episode of New Heights, Jason and Travis react to being named Sports Illustrated’s “Podcast of the Year” (2:00), we have an update on the fanbase name suggestions (5:30), and we answer the not-dumb questions, “What do head coaches do during games if they don’t call plays?” (9:00) We then jump into Travis finally getting on the scoreboard against Geno Smith (17:50), why nipples are nature’s thermostats (20:30), and find out who had the idea to give Andy Reid a cheeseburger for Christmas (24:10).</description></item><item><title>Shocking Endings, Trap Games &amp; Best Christmas Gifts | New Heights w/Jason &amp; Travis Kelce | EP 18 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420046/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420046/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the eighteenth episode of New Heights, we get a peek inside an NFL locker room during the Holidays (05:40), hear how Jason and Travis almost ruined Christmas one time growing up (14:02), and we have another amazing installment of “No Dumb Questions,” (16:50). Thank you guys for sending so many great not dumb questions. Keep them coming. Also, Travis explains how we might not be giving enough credit to the 1-win Texans after they took the Chiefs to OT (25:52), what ridiculous record Patrick Mahomes might break next (31:50), and how Shannon Sharpe has been an incredible mentor throughout his career (33:10).</description></item><item><title>MVP Faves, Travis Latest Record &amp; Is Brady a Good Sport? | New Heights w/Jason &amp; Travis Kelce | EP 17 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420047/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Before we get into the episode, we have some incredible “New” News! (01:49) There’s been an update to our merch store so if you’re part of the 92% go and take a look at https://homage.com/newheights Also, we really need to finally decide on a name for the fanbase. So if you want to submit your official vote, email us your name, fanbase name suggestion, and your reason why at NewHeightShow@gmail On the seventeenth episode of New Heights, Jason breaks down the clutch moments from the Eagles playoff-clinching win over the New York Giants (20:40) and makes the case for Jalen Hurts as the MVP front-runner (31:10).</description></item><item><title>Jason Stays Hot, Owning Mistakes and Andrew Luck Reactions | New Heights with Jason &amp; Travis Kelce | EP 16 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420048/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420048/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the sixteenth episode of New Heights, Jason describes the “whoopin’” that AJ Brown and the Eagles put on the Titans (12:50) and debate if Jason finally played dress-up before the game with his 50 First Dates tribute (26:30). And we gotta talk about it, Travis breaks down the Chiefs coming up short against the Bengals (31:55), how he felt after the critical 4th quarter fumble (33:20), and after seeing “Air Mahomes” we debate if anyone in the NFL could play in the NBA (37:35).</description></item><item><title>Patrick Mahomes on QB Rivalries, Brady Advice, Steph Curry Comparisons and More | New Heights with Jason &amp; Travis Kelce | EP 15 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420049/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420049/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the fifteenth episode of New Heights, we finally got him despite the fastest invitation of all time (5:15). We finally got to sit down and have an incredible conversation with 4-time pro bowler, NFL MVP, and Super Bowl Champion Quarterback for the Kansas City Chiefs, Patrick Mahomes. In this episode, Jason and Travis get Pat to explain why the Chiefs might not be running the QB sneak any time soon (6:50) We also dive into our most heated New Heights debate, who has the best fast food burger (11:40), the insane story about why Pat crushed his draft interview with Andy Reid (15:20), how his relationship with Alex Smith made him a better pro (20:35), and the legendary first meeting that led to his bromance with Travis (29:00).</description></item><item><title>Record-Breaking Offense, Game Balls and Heads Up Plays | New Heights W/Jason &amp; Travis Kelce | Ep 14 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420050/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420050/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the fourteenth episode of New Heights, we try and tease the Patrick Mahomes episode we’re dropping later this week but maybe give too much away (02:05), Jason lets us know the response he’s gotten to the Eagles Christmas album(03:05), and we take a look at some of the incredible fan art we saw at Arrowhead this weekend(07:45). We break down our games from Week 12 starting with the Chiefs big win over the defending Super Bowl champion Rams(14:30).</description></item><item><title>Primetime Comebacks, Clutch Drives and the Thanksgiving Draft | New Heights with Jason &amp; Travis Kelce | EP 13 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420051/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420051/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the thirteenth episode of New Heights, we’ve got some incredible New News that has been many weeks, and many tweets, in the making Patrick Mahomes will be stopping by the show next week. So make sure you’re subscribed and have the notifications turned on so you can know exactly when that episode drops. Also on the show, We break down Travis’ Sunday Night Football hat trick in the Chiefs’ win over the Chargers and debate how real his MVP candidacy might be this year.</description></item><item><title>Breakout Stars, Missed calls and Crying in football |New Heights with Jason &amp; Travis Kelce | EP 12 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420052/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420052/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the twelfth episode of New Heights, we react to the incredible response to the Jalen Hurts episode (01:00) and see if Travis will finally be able to ask Patrick Mahomes to stop by (01:25) We also look at all of the great guest suggestions you sent in (05:00), more fanbase name ideas (6:30), and answer another of your great questions which leads to an incredible story of Travis’ time as a telemarketer (9:40).</description></item><item><title>Jalen Hurts on Draft Night Surprises, Patrick Mahomes, MVP and More! | New Heights with Jason &amp; Travis Kelce | EP 11 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420053/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420053/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the eleventh episode of New Heights, we have our first-ever in-person sit-down interview with the #1 quarterback for the Philadelphia Eagles, Jalen Hurts. Jalen is currently having an MVP-caliber season so it’s really exciting to be able to share this conversation with everyone. In this episode, Jason and Travis get an answer to maybe the most important New Heights question, what’s Jalen calling on 4th &amp;amp; 1. (5:25) We also touch on Jalen&amp;rsquo;s first impressions of being under center behind Jason (9:50), the backstory to the squat video everyone can’t stop talking about (12:20), why he hopes Jason keeps playing for at least a few more years (23:02), and his surprising reaction to hearing his name called by the Eagles on Draft Night (26:00).</description></item><item><title>Helmet Tosses, NFL Bromances and Jeff Saturday?? | New Heights with Jason &amp; Travis Kelce | EP 10 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420054/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 12:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420054/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the tenth episode of New Heights, Travis goes deep on the Chiefs physical win against the Titans (17:25) and lets us all know it was actually a perfectly executed helmet toss(21:15). Jason breaks down the Eagles road win against the Texans (45:33) and updates us on why his relationship with Jalen Hurts might be the most important in the NFL(01:00:40). The guys also let us know why NFL players should only play on grass fields (01:08:15) and react to the wild breaking news that the Colts hired Jeff Saturday as interim head coach (01:14:20).</description></item><item><title>Russell Wilson's Flight, Jalen Hurts for MVP and Football Movies Debate | New Heights with Jason &amp; Travis Kelce | EP 9 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420055/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420055/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the ninth episode of New Heights, we recap our primetime debut on the “Manningcast”(01:25), read through your submissions for the New Heights fanbase name(06:25), and debate the greatest football movie of all time(10:00). Jason gives us the details from the Eagles blowout win against the Steelers (15:30), what he thinks of Jalen Hurts MVP odds (20:05), and lets us know who didn&amp;rsquo;t love the debut of “sexy batman (27:10).</description></item><item><title>Video Game Chemistry, Coaching Lessons and Bye Week Tales | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420056/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420056/</guid><description>Podcast Description On a very special in-person eighth episode of New Heights, Travis explains the secret to the Chiefs offensive explosion against the 49ers (18:00) and how the team has changed without Tyreek (33:10). Jason recaps his epic bye week (55:30) and debates who is on the Philly Mt. Rushmore (01:07:45). The guys also dive deep into what makes the perfect NFL head coach (01:09:50) and which coaches made the biggest impact on their careers(01:22:30).</description></item><item><title>NFL Rivalries, Brady’s Rant and Trade Talks | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce | EP 7 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420057/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420057/</guid><description>Podcast Description On episode six of ‘New Heights’, Jason celebrates the Eagles beating the Cowboys (13:45) and reveals the secrets behind the Eagles&amp;rsquo; 6-0 start (31:55). Travis breaks down the latest chapter in the Chiefs/Bills rivalry (35:18) and addresses the trade rumors surrounding his recent contract change (48:35). The guys also go deep on NFL rivalries (50:04) and discuss which players they’ve looked up to during their careers (55:32). We also explain why Brady gets a pass for yelling at his lineman (01:08:48) and what really goes on during the NFL trade deadline (01:11:55).</description></item><item><title>Breaking Records, Coaching Changes and Big Contracts | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce | EP 6 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420058/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420058/</guid><description>Podcast Description On episode six of ‘New Heights’, Travis breaks down his record-breaking Monday Night Football win and how the Chiefs were able to hang on against the Raiders (10:01). Jason talks about the Eagles&amp;rsquo; nail-biter against the Cardinals and their incredible 17-play drive to take the lead (28:12). The guys also share stories of playing overseas (47:19), explain what happens when coaches get fired mid-season (52:03), and decide if big-time expectations come with big-time contracts (58:03).</description></item><item><title>Best Tight Ends, Bad Media and Birthdays with Paul Rudd | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce | EP 5 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420059/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 11:03:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420059/</guid><description>Podcast Description On episode five of ‘New Heights’, Travis walks us through what went into the Chiefs’ bounce-back win against Tom Brady and the Bucs (08:30) and who is on his all-time tight end Mt Rushmore (23:50). Jason reveals how the Eagles managed to stay undefeated in a rainy game against the Jags (28:22) and the mastermind behind the Eagles&amp;rsquo; dominant O-Line (34:00). We also figure out if the media is going too far in criticizing Baker Mayfield (39:03) and try and explain what goes into a modern NFL offense (42:00).</description></item><item><title>Big Plays, Butt Punts and Brady Stories | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce | EP 4 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420060/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420060/</guid><description>Podcast Description On episode four of ‘New Heights’, Travis walks us through the Chiefs&amp;rsquo; struggles against the Colts (08:17). Jason explains how the Eagles are off to a hot start led by Jalen Hurts, AJ Brown and Devonta Smith (16:45). The brothers then talk about the scary head injury that Tua appeared to suffer in the Dolphins game and what it is like to be put into the protocol as a player (38:30).</description></item><item><title>Body Slams, Blown Leads and Days Off | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce | EP 3 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420061/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 12:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420061/</guid><description>Podcast Description On episode three of ‘New Heights’, Travis talks about the Chiefs win over the Chargers (07:00), being body slammed by Derwin James and how it compares to the time he shattered a hardwood floor (07:38), and why players should care about their PFF rankings (23:19). Jason breaks down the Eagles dominant win over the Vikings (28:07), Jalen Hurts emergence as QB1 (29:40), and why the Eagles/Vikings rivalry might just be for the fans (40:25).</description></item><item><title>Chiefs Offense, Eagles Playmakers and TNF Games | EP 2 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420062/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 17:14:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420062/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the second episode of ‘New Heights’, Jason and Travis tackle the 12 biggest questions from Week 1 in the NFL (03:39). Find out how the Chiefs offense stays in sync(07:16), the most insane play in football (14:39), Jalen Hurts keeping the Eagles alive Detroit (20:33), Plus, is the Super Bowl hangover real (33:22) and how players really feel about Thursday night games (43:07). ﻿New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce is a Jukes Original series, presented by Wave Sports + Entertainment.</description></item><item><title>New Offenses, Last Dances and Epic Super Bowl Rings | EP 1 | New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8123420063/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8123420063/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the very first episode of ‘New Heights’, Jason and Travis tackle 12 pressing questions heading into a new NFL season. Find out why they finally have a show together, the chances this season could be Jason&amp;rsquo;s “Last Dance” with the Eagles and Travis’ thoughts on the Chiefs’ offense without Tyreek Hill. Plus, fun stories from their rookie years and a can’t-miss brotherly debate on who has the more epic Super Bowl ring.</description></item></channel></rss>