<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Working Hard, Hardly Working on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/working-hard-hardly-working/</link><description>Recent content in Working Hard, Hardly Working on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 03:00:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/working-hard-hardly-working/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ep. 67: Plan With Me: A Step-by-Step Framework For How to Actually Achieve Your Goals in 2024 | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780068/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 03:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780068/</guid><description>Podcast Description The end of the year means my planning senses start tingling!! So, today's episode is a step-by-step talk through of how I plan for each upcoming year. We cover vision boarding, goal setting, habit tracking, staying accountable and lots more. I felt like it would be easier to do it together and take you through exactly how I do it to ensure I actually reach the things I say I want to.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 66 Lydia Millen: The Inside Story | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 03:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780001/</guid><description>Podcast Description With over 3 million followers, Lydia Millen has been blogging for over a decade.
She very rarely does interviews, so I wanted to sit down with Lydia to get some insight into the woman behind the handle and dig into her life, her career &amp;amp; the criticism she's faced. She really opens up.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 65 “I was an emotional wreck”: Saffron Barker on the secrets and sacrifices of growing up online | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Influencer, YouTuber and podcast host, Saffron Barker has taken the internet by storm. With a YouTube following of almost 3.5 million subscribers across her two channels as well as 1.8 million Instagram followers, Saffron is well-loved for her engaging content.&amp;nbsp;
Stepping into the TV spotlight when she joined the 17th series of Strictly Come Dancing with dancing partner AJ Pritchard, she’s made the leap into the mainstream after a string of TV appearances, taking part in Celebrity Hunted and The Celebrity Circle.</description></item><item><title>Ep.64 “People Pleasing Is Manipulative”: A Boundary Setting Bootcamp With Michelle Elman | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 03:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michelle Elman is a woman with a psychology empire. Her qualifications speak for themselves: she’s a five-board accredited life coach, a Master Practitioner, a Master Hypnotherapist and a psychologist, plus she’s published four bestselling books. But these accolades are more than just a job for Michelle. They’re personal. She faced serious health challenges throughout her childhood, having to endure 15 surgeries, followed by periods of intense self-doubt and low body confidence due to her many scars.</description></item><item><title>Ep.63 The Proposal Episode: What Really Happened! Behind The Scenes With My Agent And Some G+Ts | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 03:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Extra special podcast alert! 💍
I sat down with my amazing agent Lauren to chat all about how she teamed up with my fiancé to organise THE surprise proposal (no I'm not over it nor will I ever be). We cracked open the gin and got spilling the secrets: the highs, the lows, the freakouts. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep.62 Know Nothing About Investing? This Episode’s For You. | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 03:00:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780005/</guid><description>Podcast Description DISCLAIMER: The information does not constitute financial advice or recommendation and should not be considered as such.
AD: In this episode Grace mentions Revolut, Grace has previously worked with Revolut on a brand partnership.
In this episode
Today’s episode is all about a subject that is very important to me, female investment &amp;amp; funding, and I couldn’t think of a more qualified person to be discussing this with than Anna Sophie Hartvigsen.</description></item><item><title>Ep.61 A Masterclass In Defying Stereotypes: How Jordan Brompton Built A Nine-Figure Green Energy Empire | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 03:00:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jordan Brompton is the Co-Founder of myenergi, one of the world’s fastest-growing renewable energy technology companies. Building a nine figure green energy company with 400 staff, it’s safe to say myenergi is turning heads in the renewable tech space. The company’s huge success started with the invention of the Zappi-charger, the world’s first solar charger for electric vehicles capable of using 100% renewable energy. It began as an idea over a bottle of wine with her business partner, and now drives tens of millions of sales each year.</description></item><item><title>Ep.60 "I was pushed to the side": Tasha Ghouri on her mission for a more accessible world | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 03:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tasha Ghouri is a television personality, activist, dancer and model, most recognised for her stint on the 2022 Summer series of Love Island UK, with Tasha being the first deaf person to enter the Villa.&amp;nbsp;
Referring to being deaf as her ‘Superpower’, Tasha was born deaf - with her parents identifying her disability when she was just 12 months old - and wears a cochlear implant in her right ear.</description></item><item><title>Ep.59 An Ultimate Guide To Skincare With Expert Caroline Hirons | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 02:00:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Once described as ‘The Most Powerful Woman in Beauty’ Caroline Hirons is the Founder, presenter, best-selling Author and all-round figurehead within the skincare industry. With a career spanning 35 years in retail, 26 years in skincare and a fully trained aesthetician, Caroline offer gives expert advice to the masses, giving her honest truth behind the products we are using and the big do’s and don’ts of what we should and shouldn’t be putting on our faces.</description></item><item><title>Ep.58 FashionInflux On The Social Media Strategy Behind Her 2.7 Million Followers | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780009/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 02:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Having accumulated over 2.7 million Instagram followers alone, Lydia Rose a.k.a Fashion Influx is thought of as the OG of social media styling and master of functional fashion. Becoming famous with her high-street fashion, Lydia grew a dedicated fan base from her recognisable styling videos. Now leading the way with beauty hacks, fashion forward styling look-books and shopping hauls, Lydia has opened up her personal life online, sharing her most intimate moments, from getting engaged, planning her wedding and home and relationship content.</description></item><item><title>Ep.57 So You Want To Educate Yourself On The Climate Crisis? Start Here with Mikaela Loach. | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 02:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Climate justice activist Mikaela Loach advocates for environmental justice, racial justice, sustainable fashion, and fights human rights issues. Along with her fearless attitude, Mikaela has been hailed as a leading influencer in the climate change crisis, in 2019 she even took the government to court for using taxpayers money to fund North Sea oil and gas companies supported by the environmental non profit Uplift and the Paid to Pollute campaign.</description></item><item><title>Ep.56 From Homelessness to a Multimillion £ Brand: Founder Rokeya Khanum's Truly Incredible Story | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780011/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 02:00:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780011/</guid><description>Podcast Description In her own words, Rokeya Khanum has achieved the goals she once referred to as impossible acts. Born to parents who moved from Bangladesh to East London, she was raised alongside her seven siblings and Rokeya has always been really honest about her childhood, opening up about her teen pregnancy at 17 years old where she was then made homeless, moving from hostel to hostel and barely affording the basic necessities.</description></item><item><title>Ep.55 How To Stand Out From Your Job Application (From An Employer's POV) | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 02:00:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780012/</guid><description>Podcast Description in this week's solo episode we're looking at how to stand out from a job application alone - from the POV of someone who's been going through application after application! i've been hiring a LOT this year and I've learned so much as to what stands out, and what is an absolute no-go, especially in a really competitive market.
answering your top questions and dilemmas from how to make your application stand out, how to brand yourself as 'long-term' for future employers when your experience is short term and how to deal with constant rejection - now let's go job hunt🕵️</description></item><item><title>Ep.54 Perfectionism Is Holding You Back: How To Achieve AND Be Highly Productive [SOLO EP] | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 01:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780013/</guid><description>Podcast Description “You have this false perception that perfectionism is good for your work, but realistically it’s actually harming your work in the long term” 💅🏼
In this week's solo ep, we're talking all about perfectionism - in work, relationships and life in general, with the aim to reframe our mindset away from perfectionism being the goal, and to get to the bottom of how we achieve highly without trying to be a perfectionist!</description></item><item><title>Ep.53 How I Processed My Brother's Suicide: Dr Alex On Tackling The Men's Mental Health Crisis. | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 02:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rising to fame in 2018 for his dating escapades on Love Island, Dr Alex George has since taken the media world by storm, becoming a TV doctor, writer and now Youth Mental Health Ambassador to the government, improving the support that young people receive regarding their mental health. He has also since published two Sunday Times Number 1 Bestsellers as well as bringing out his newest book, The Mind Manual.</description></item><item><title>Ep.52 How To Build a Business On Social Media: Posting, Scaling + Hiring | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 02:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780015/</guid><description>Podcast Description in this week's solo ep, we are bringing it right back to the start of it all and diving into the world of social media. answering your dilemmas and giving tips and tricks on how to grow a business on social media 👩🏼‍💻
including answering what I should be posting for my business on social media, what content should I use for ads, when I should be making my first hire and how to grow a side hustle !</description></item><item><title>Ep.51 Victim or Scammer: Who Really Is Caroline Calloway? ft. Caroline Calloway | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 02:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Known for her hugely captivating story, writer, social media influencer and self titled ’Scammer’ Caroline Calloway doesn’t shy away from being controversial.&amp;nbsp;
Caroline started to build her online presence between 2013 and 2016, documenting her experience during her time at Cambridge university after dropping out of New York University. She rose to fame creating an Instagram following who were given ‘exclusive access’ into the life of Caroline Calloway and her adventures.</description></item><item><title>Ep.50 How To Survive Your 20s? The Handbook I Needed [SOLO EP] | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 02:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780017/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week's solo episode we're having a heart to heart about navigating your 20s - relationships, getting on the career ladder, moving out, reaching your own and other people's expectations. It's a big one!
How do I deal with the time pressures of my 20s?
Is changing career direction in your 20s a good idea?
How do you know what you truly want in your 20s?
Is there a right time to move out after graduating?</description></item><item><title>Ep.49 A Rare Behind The Scenes Into REFY'S Jess Hunt + The Untold Story Of How She Shook The Beauty Industry | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 02:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780018/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s no question Jess Hunt, co-founder of REFY, social media influencer and model has taken on the entire beauty industry. Having amassed a huge 1.8 million followers just on Instagram, Jess has turned her influencing empire into entrepreneurial success. In November 2020, Jess launched the beauty brand REFY with co-founder Jenna Meek. Having wild success with the revolutionary Brow Sculpt having a 100k waitlist and once launched had sold out within just 6 weeks.</description></item><item><title>Ep.48 Am I Having Enough Sex? Sex Expert Kate Moyle Answers Most Asked Questions On Your Sex Life | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 02:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Difficulties in our sexual and intimate relationships, Pyschosexual and Relationship Therapist Kate Moyle, claim to be much more common than we think. Her aim? To open the discussion by providing a unique and confidential space to have those important conversations. Kate addresses the challenges couples are facing in their sex lives and relationships such as “what sex should we be having?” to “how do we communicate better in order to have better sex?</description></item><item><title>Ep.47 How To Nail A Job Interview From An Employers POV [SOLO EP] | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 02:00:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780020/</guid><description>Podcast Description answering your dilemmas on 🥁 nailing a job interview 🥁 from an employers pov!
What are the most common questions asked in a job interview?
How do I go for my dream job from an unrelated role?
How do I get a job in fashion from a different industry?
How much research should I do for a job interview?
HELP! What should I wear for my job interview?</description></item><item><title>Ep.46 From Childstar To Girlband, TV Broadcaster &amp; Entrepreneur: How To Constantly Evolve With Rochelle Humes | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 02:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Having risen to fame when she was just 12 years old, Rochelle Humes has gone from childhood popstar featuring in the band S Club 7 juniors to becoming a member of the hit UK girl group The Saturdays and now the best-loved online personality and TV broadcaster. Having had it all from such a young age Rochelle is transparent about the highs and lows, being raised in a single parent household and understanding the absence her father left on the family, to the hard graft of being in a pop group, meeting her now husband Marvin Humes member of the boy band JLS and sharing the journey of becoming a mother.</description></item><item><title>Ep.45 Why Aren’t My Diets Working? Food Myths, Weightloss &amp; Calorie Counting With Dr Tim Spector | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 02:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do we really know what we should be eating? Multi-award winning expert Tim Spector argues we might not. Professor of genetic epidemiology at King's College London and honorary consultant physician at Guy's and St Thomas' he aims to point us in the right direction so we know the hard truths behind food fads, dieting, nutrition and gut health. Having written five books, including the bestsellers Spoon-Fed and The Diet Myth he is one of the most cited scientists in the world.</description></item><item><title>Ep.44 The Truth About Menstrual Cycle-Syncing: Working Out And Your Period With Dr Frankie Jackson-Spence | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 02:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr Frankie is an NHS Doctor, media and content creator who offers factual and relatable health advice in preventative medicine.&amp;nbsp;
A qualified doctor working on the frontline, Dr Frankie graduated with a degree in Medicine and Surgery in 2018. During this time, Dr Frankie set out to better understand the risk factors for cancer,&amp;nbsp;becoming heavily involved in clinical trials at Barts Cancer Institute for Renal and Bladder cancer.&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>Ep.43 How To Use Impostor Syndrome to Your Advantage [SOLO EP] | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780024/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 02:00:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780024/</guid><description>Podcast Description well well well if it isn't the first ever working hard pod solo episode! 🎙
there are so many 'dilemmas' podcasts about relationships and general life out there, but I've always wanted to be able to listen to one for work and careers and all the boring shit like that. It's always nice to hear that other people feel the same and we can all learn so much from each others work and careers, so here we are!</description></item><item><title>Ep.42 Let's Talk About ADHD: The TikTok Stars That Changed The Conversation | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 02:00:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Richard Pink &amp;amp; Roxanne Emery are the husband-and-wife team behind the social media account @ADHD_Love, sharing a fearless, often outrageously funny account of life with ADHD. With viral videos that have been viewed more than 200 million times, their mission is to remove the stigma around ADHD, share strategies to improve communication and find happiness so they can move from frustration to patience, understanding and love. Their book ‘DIRTY LAUNDRY’ published this year, is an unfiltered look into the chaos of life with ADHD, answering the most asked questions and has become an invaluable resource for neuro-divergents and the people who love them.</description></item><item><title>Ep.41 Know Nothing About The Economy? This Episode's For You. | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780026/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 02:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rupal Patel is a senior economist at the Bank of England and co-author of the best-selling pop-economics book Can’t We Just Print More Money, the Bank of England’s first book in its over 325 year history. Today, Rupal advises governors at the Bank of England on their policy decisions and is passionate about improving economic literacy amongst young women.
Rupal makes sure there is no stupid question left unanswered, from what actually is money, why aren’t Freddos 10p anymore to why shouldn't I hoard all my money under the mattress?</description></item><item><title>Ep.40 When Do You Know It's Time To Walk Away? Taking Career Risks With Iconic TV Presenter Jake Humphrey | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780027/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 02:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jake Humphrey is one of the UK’s most iconic television broadcasters. Jake is best known for presenting Premier League Football on BT Sport or the F1 on BBC Sport. He has also previously hosted children’s television on CBBC. in 2020, Jake launched the successful High Performance Podcast with professor Damian Hughes, offering an insight into the lives of high-achieving individuals who share their success stories. Their spin-off book High Performance: Lessons from the Best on Becoming Your Best has also become a Number 1 Sunday Times Bestseller, revealing the methods of the most remarkable athletes, coaches and entrepreneurs.</description></item><item><title>Ep.39 "The Aim Is Not To Have Fun, The Aim Is To Be Rich" The Reality Of Serial Entrepreneurship With Debbie Wosskow | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780028/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 02:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Debbie Wosskow is recognised as one of the most prominent serial entrepreneurs in the UK. She is the founder and former CEO of Love Home Swap, the world’s largest online home exchange platform which is where she made her name in the industry. Her current venture, AllBright, is Britain’s first-ever member’s club for women, and a place for women to connect, upskill and network both in person and online.</description></item><item><title>Ep.38 All The Things They Never Told Us About Female Bodies With Dr Hazel Wallace | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780029/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 02:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr Hazel Wallace is doing it all, from a trained medical doctor to Founder of the blog ‘The Food Medic’ a registered nutritionist, and also a best-selling author of recipe books, she’s made it her mission to research how your diet can help women live happy and healthy lives. The Food Medic is dedicated to the science of eating, she asks the questions we all need answering from what we should and should not be eating, to how eating can improve fertility and wellbeing to debunking eating myths.</description></item><item><title>Ep.37 Let's Talk About Sex With TikTok Star Hayley Morris | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780030/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 02:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780030/</guid><description>Podcast Description With 6 million followers across Instagram and TikTok, Hayley Morris is loved for her hilarious and relatable sketches on the weird and wonderful ways our brain and body mess with each other. She is also one of the UK’s hottest up and coming comedy writers developing scripts with BBC Comedy and the makers of Catastrophe and Gavin &amp;amp; Stacey. Comforting, insightful and hilarious, the book explores everything from body anxiety, how to manage an over-active inner monologue, how to handle embarrassing moments and getting back up from setbacks.</description></item><item><title>Ep.36 What Cancer Taught Me About Life &amp; Love with Lauren Mahon | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780031/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 02:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Creator of the online community Girl vs Cancer, and host of You, Me and the Big C, Lauren Mahon has launched a social media community with the aim of raising awareness and driving support towards women with cancer. After being diagnosed with breast cancer at 31, Lauren has used this to drive important conversations about cancer and raise awareness of the disease.
In March 2018, Lauren’s BBC podcast You, Me and the Big C was born with the focus on sharing Lauren’s cancer journey and experience in a positive light.</description></item><item><title>Ep.35 TikTok Uncovered: What It Really Takes to Go Viral With GK Barry | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780032/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 02:00:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Grace Keeling, better known online as GK Barry, is one of the wildest TikTok stars out there creating content that is both relatable, hilarious and at times controversial. She rose to fame during the pandemic with her TikTok account, and since 2020 has gained a staggering 2.9 million followers on the social channel alone with content around her day-to-day life, reaching millions of views per month. Grace not only has reached popularity as a well-known TikToker in the UK with an ever-growing platform she’s also become a household name appearing on the show 'Locked In' with Footasylum.</description></item><item><title>Ep.34 "I Was Public Enemy Number 1" The Truth Behind The Media Storm With Deliciously Ella | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780033/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 02:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ella Mills is an award-winning author, entrepreneur and champion of plant based living. She was the founder of Deliciously Ella in 2012, a plant-based food &amp;amp; wellness platform sharing delicious ways to feel better. Although it originated as a recipe website, Ella Mills has developed the business into a restaurant, a range of plant based food products, an app, a podcast and a collection of best-selling recipe books.&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>Ep.33 How Viral REFY Beauty Broke All The Rules with Co-Founder Jenna Meek | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780034/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 03:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jenna Meek is a Manchester-based entrepreneur and CEO, whose passion for all things beauty led her to creating two powerhouse beauty brands. Her latest venture is as co-founder and CEO at REFY, Instagram’s hottest and most disruptive beauty brand, famous for its three-step brow collection which became an overnight social media sensation.
Jenna launched her first business SHRINE, formerly Gypsy-Shrine, from her bedroom in Manchester. A brand born out of the festival culture in 2016, Jenna set up a cosmetic glitter and gem business initially bought and sold in festival tents around the country.</description></item><item><title>Ep.32 So You Want To Start a Business? Listen To This First. Will Stirrup: Founder of Maeving | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780035/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 03:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Will Stirrup is the Co-Founder of Maeving, the UK’s first electric motorcycle manufacturer, but after going totally bankrupt in his first year as an entrepreneur, Will’s journey is one of honesty, realism and business burnout. Raised in South Africa, Will came to the UK for university and quickly found himself on a career trajectory to working in finance. After becoming the youngest person ever to become double ACA CFA qualified, and securing a role within the M&amp;amp;A team of a top tier investment bank, Will packed it all in and chose his dream of being an entrepreneur.</description></item><item><title>Ep.31 Do We Share Too Much Online? Influencer Sarah's Day Reveals The Dark Side Of Being A Social Media Star | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780036/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 03:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sarah Tilse, more commonly known as ‘Sarah’s Day’ is an Australian fitness influencer and YouTuber best known for her fitness, diet and wellness content. Whilst studying to become a teacher, Sarah began her online journey by posting about her hormonal acne online as a way to source advice but also to help others who were struggling with it as well. This expanded into fitness, wellness and lifestyle content, and on the date of this recording Sarah has over 3 million followers across her Instagram and YouTube channels, and is the founder of multiple companies including Sarah’s Day, her personal brand, fitness ebooks and app, Sunee App - her recipe app, The Healthcode Podcast and The House of Groms, a creative strategy and production company.</description></item><item><title>Ep.30 A Masterclass on Climbing the Corporate Ladder with Shopify MD Shimona Mehta | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780037/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 03:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shimona Mehta is an acclaimed tech pioneer with extensive experience in retail, technology, food and beverage. Awarded for being one of the UK’s most influential retail leaders, Shimona is best known for being the Managing Director of EMEA for Shopify - the leading e-commerce hub for independent brands. Designed to make buying and selling easy, Shopify offers businesses a range of tools to design, manage and grow an online store, hosting numerous high-growth brands including Deliveroo, Lindt, and Heinz.</description></item><item><title>Ep.29 Love It Or Lose It: Managing A Startup With Founder Josephine Philips | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780038/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 03:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josephine Phillips is the 24 year old visionary behind the Sojo app, the online platform on a mission to make clothing alterations and repairs mainstream. Founded to shape a more sustainable fashion future and dubbed by Vogue as the ‘deliveroo of clothing repairs’, Sojo connects buyers of pre-loved clothes with local seamstresses who can tailor the garments to fit. The app not only extends the lifespan of our clothes but allows us to fall in love with them all over again and has already been integrated by several brands including Ganni and Hurr.</description></item><item><title>Ep.28 Toxic Pressures &amp; Dark Secrets: How Original Fitspo Steph Claire Smith Took On The Modelling Industry | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780039/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 03:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stephanie Miller, known online as Steph Claire Smith, is the COO and co-founder of Australian health and wellness app, Keep It Cleaner (KIC).
From Melbourne Australia, Steph started her career modelling at aged 7. After moving to America to pursue modelling as a career, Steph was exposed to the extremely toxic side of the industry, which led to disordered eating, negative body image and an unhealthy relationship with exercise.</description></item><item><title>Ep.27 “An Hour Before We Served Him Papers, He Served Us Papers” Nearly Losing It All With Entrepreneur Hannah Bronfman | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780040/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 03:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hannah Bronfman is an entrepreneur, angel investor, DJ, activist and author. She is among New York's most renowned health and well-being professionals, responsible for building the popular online portal HBFIT. Before this, Hannah built a reputation as a celebrity and influencer through her work as a set DJ, playing at events for high-profile brands including Gucci. Hannah’s first book “Do What Feels Good” was published in January 2019.</description></item><item><title>Ep.26 "I Would Rather Die Than Put My Children Through What I Went Through” - Mez's Refuge-Seeking Journey | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780041/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 10:05:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today I introduce to you Mez, a young, courageous refugee with an extraordinary story. When he was just 13 years old, Mez fled his home in Eritrea to escape some of the worst human rights conditions in the world, including forced military conscription and widespread persecution, starting a perilous journey as a child refugee across the world. For an entire year, Mez experienced the chaos and terror of refugee camps, experiencing extreme and treacherous conditions that would leave him scared and struggling to get enough to eat.</description></item><item><title>Ep.25 Girls Gotta Eat Reveal All: Dating, Friendships And The Power Of Saying Yes | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780042/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 03:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rayna Greenberg and Ashley Hesseltine are the hilarious hosts behind Girls Gotta Eat, one of the biggest US comedy podcast’s all about dating, sex and relationships. With over 200 episodes and 2.5 million downloads per month, Girls Gotta Eat has been educating and entertaining listeners on all things sexual fetishes to finances, bringing in special guests including therapists, comedians and authors to offer expert advice. Dating, break-ups, sex fails, getting rejected and being ghosted have happened to everyone, and this podcast explores it all; featuring honest and hilarious conversation along the way.</description></item><item><title>Ep.24 Here’s What The Government Doesn’t Want You To Know: Kwajo Tweneboa On The Social Housing Crisis | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780043/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 03:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kwajo Tweneboa, known as the hero of social housing, is a remarkable 23-year-old campaigner demanding urgent reform in public-sector housing. Amid the housing crisis, Kwajo has emerged as an influential voice online for social housing tenants, known best for naming and shaming some of the largest accommodation associations in the UK.
Haunted by memories of his own housing hell, Kwajo joined the fight to improve conditions after his father, a care worker, died in their family home among a sea of cockroaches, mould and vermin.</description></item><item><title>Ep.23 ‘If Things Aren't Going To Plan, You Need To Question The Plan’ The Power Of Failing With Elizabeth Day | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780044/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 03:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Elizabeth Day is an award-winning British author, broadcaster, and influential host of the hugely successful How to Fail podcast. A podcast that celebrates failure and lessons learned, every week How to Fail invites a new influential guest to open and talk honestly about challenges and vulnerabilities in their personal life, in a bid to show listeners that perfection doesn't exist.
Elizabeth was inspired to start the podcast following a particularly challenging period in her own life - a time when nothing went according to plan.</description></item><item><title>Ep.22 The Secret to Successful Dating: Relationship Expert Anna Williamson On Matchmaking And Mental Health | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780045/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 03:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anna Williamson is a broadcaster and lifestyle coach, best recognised for fronting the UK's most exclusive dating agency on E4's Celebs Go Dating. She is the best in the business for trusted lifestyle advice and holds accredited qualifications in counselling, life coaching, psychotherapy and neuro-linguistic programming (NLP).
Anna's presenting career accelerated when she began hosting children's television, fronting shows on CITV, Nickelodeon, Channel 5 and the Disney Channel. However, behind the scenes and during production, Anna faced a complete emotional breakdown.</description></item><item><title>Ep.21 'We Became Victims Of Our Own Success': The Unheard Story Of Sudden Fame With Jordan Stephens | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 03:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jordan Stephens is an English singer-songwriter, performer, and rapper, best known for being one-half of hip-hop duo Rizzle Kicks who dominated the charts for several years, with their music still being heard on mainstream radio today. However, despite enjoying the success, Jordan came into the limelight when he was just a teenager, putting him through the hardship of the music industry at an extremely vulnerable age. Unaware he was suffering; Jordan veiled his depression with a toxic combination of booze and drugs to cope, hitting rock bottom when he tragically lost two people close to him.</description></item><item><title>Ep.20 From Make Up Counter To Millionaire Mogul; Jamie Genevieve On Building Her Empire | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780047/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 03:00:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jamie Genevieve is the 29-year-old founder of VIEVE, a makeup empire built on inclusivity, self-expression and positivity. She is a pro-makeup artist turned vlogging sensation, finding fame on YouTube for her original online makeup tutorials and lifestyle content.
Having built a following of over 3 million people, Jamie decided to quit her full-time job and invested her influencer earnings in VIEVE, launched in 2020 with nude lipsticks, lipliners, highlighters and an eyeshadow palette.</description></item><item><title>Ep.19 Gang Leader Turned Venture Capital Investor - Karl Lokko On How He Turned His Back On Crime. | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780048/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 03:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Karl Lokko is an ex-gang leader turned activist, campaigner, influencer and entrepreneur. Growing up on a tough estate swarming with gangs, Karl's childhood was far from plain-sailing, witnessing his first shooting when just 12 years old.
Though at the time this had felt shocking, within four years Karl found himself behind the trigger, eventually becoming the ringleader of his own notorious gang. Before he was even 16, Karl had already been shot at, cut on his face, stabbed in the chest and watched one of his best friends get killed.</description></item><item><title>Ep.18 Courtney Black: From Personal Trainer To Multi-Millionaire | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780049/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 03:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780049/</guid><description>Podcast Description TRIGGER WARNING Courtney Black is the 26-year-old serial entrepreneur and 2x Sunday Times Bestselling author who transformed her personal training career into a multi-million-pound fitness business during the pandemic.
Courtney is the founder of the Courtney Black App, an online fitness platform she launched just two weeks before the lockdown with every penny in her savings. Initially launched as an app to be used in tangent with equipment found in a gym, Courtney was devastated when COVID closed sports centres nationwide, forcing her to rethink her business.</description></item><item><title>Ep.17 'Failure Was New To Me, I Wasn't Ready For It' - Fisayo Longe On Forging Your Own Path To Success. | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780050/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 03:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fisayo Longe is the founder and CEO of Kai Collective, the womenswear brand offering attainable clothing with luxury aesthetics. A brand crafted intentionally to make women feel their most confident Kai Collective is one of London's 'most talked-about online boutiques, Fisayo was personally recognised for her success on the Forbes 30 Under 30 Art &amp;amp; Culture list in 2021.
Fisayo launched Kai back in 2016, a time when her popular fashion and travel blog 'Mirror Me' gained popularity and simultaneously began to attract large brand partnerships.</description></item><item><title>Ep.16 How Finding Your Niche Will Help You Defeat The Odds, with Sharmadean Reid MBE | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780051/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 02:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sharmadean Reid MBE is a leading entrepreneur and beauty visionary on a mission to digitally connect like-minded females. She is the founder of The Stack World, an exclusive platform for female founders, leaders and entrepreneurs to connect and share experiences.
Sharmadean is a serial entrepreneur with three impressive startups. Before launching The Stack, Shamadean first took the beauty industry by storm with her business WAH Nails, which featured in collaborations with global brands including Nike and Marc Jacobs.</description></item><item><title>Ep.15 Why Stress Is Your Superpower, And How To Cut Out The Bad Bits - The Science-Backed Method with Physiologist Oli Patrick | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780052/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 03:09:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Oliver Patrick is a leading physiologist, entrepreneur, and expert in lifestyle management who is on a mission to teach others the skills required to build stress resilience. A multiple business owner, Oliver is both co-founder of the world’s most advanced health evaluation service Viavi and founder of the first lifestyle medicine gym, Viavi:be. He is also an admirable public and keynote speaker for functional and lifestyle medicine, for which he has extensive clinical experience.</description></item><item><title>Ep.14 'I wanted to hold a pen, not a gun' - Activist Jaz O'Hara on the Reality of The Refugee Crisis | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780053/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 02:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jaz O’Hara is the founder of The Worldwide Tribe, an organisation and online community committed to supporting refugees and asylum seekers globally. The platform uses methods of innovative storytelling to share the narratives of refugees embedded in the crisis, inspiring others to get active and inform a new lease for change. Since its founding in 2015, The Worldwide Tribe has been met with overwhelming love and support by its followers, physical and monetary donations inundated by concern and care for the refugee crisis.</description></item><item><title>Ep.13 From 'Uncool' Niche to 9 Figure Business with Simon Mottram, Founder of Rapha | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780054/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 02:00:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Simon Mottram is the Founder of Rapha. Hailed as one of the greatest marketers and business innovators in modern cycling; he made cycling cool. Having founded the brand in 2004, Rapha has transformed the industry and blurred the lines between fashion and cycling through its stylish, high-quality performance products, creative and engaging storytelling, direct to consumer model and innovative approaches to physical retail and membership.
Simon has been a passionate cyclist for more than 30 years and has successfully transferred his passion to the Rapha brand and internal culture.</description></item><item><title>Ep.12 'I would much rather a 5-figure guy who's going to exalt me than a 7-figure guy who's going to oppress me' - Candice Brathwaite gets real on female breadwinning. | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780055/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 02:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Candice Braithwaite is the Sunday Times best-selling author, presenter, journalist and founder of Make Motherhood Diverse: an initiative fighting for equal representation for mothers and parents. Initially a content creator and 'mumfluencer', Candice began posting on her socials in 2015 to document her journey of motherhood, keen to disrupt the flawless 'yummy mummy' facade online. The authenticity of her account resonated with thousands online, empowering her to write her first of three bestseller books.</description></item><item><title>Ep.11 Michelle Kennedy: From Billion Dollar Deputy-CEO to Raising Millions whilst Pregnant | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780056/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 02:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michelle Kennedy is the founder and CEO of Peanut, one of the fastest-growing social networking apps for women focusing on fertility, pregnancy, motherhood and menopause, which has raised $23m to to date. Peanut was founded in 2017 when Michelle had her first baby, serving as a gift to like-minded mothers during their most uncertain and uncanny moments. Women now use the Peanut app for all sorts of reasons, whether that be trying to find a playdate for their children or networking with other working mums.</description></item><item><title>Ep.10 Everything You Need To Know About Raising Investment From Top Investor Jason Mahendran (Soho House, Rapha, Honest Burgers) | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780057/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 02:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jason Mahendran is a Senior Investor at Active Partners, one of the UK’s leading investment firms committed to the search for the next prosperous unicorn brand. Through his venture capital and investing experience, Jason has helped to build several outstanding consumer-based, founder-led brands including the reputable LEON, Honest Burgers and Rapha. Active Partners have also recently invested in my own brand TALA in our $5.7m seed round, Jason himself joining the board.</description></item><item><title>Ep.9 Far from Ordinary - Nicola Kilner's $2.2 Billion Dollar Story | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780058/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 02:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780058/</guid><description>Podcast Description *Trigger Warning* Nicola Kilner is the co-founder and CEO of DECIEM, ‘the abnormal beauty company’ and hub of science-backed beauty brands that pave the future for skincare. Part of the DECIEM family ‘The Ordinary’ has taken the skincare world by storm, providing an evolving collection of clinical technologies and treatments at drugstore prices. In just 9 years DECIEM has completely revolutionised the beauty industry, its long-term mission to curate brands that educate and inform consumers about products best for their skin.</description></item><item><title>Ep.8 Tolly T on Taking Opportunities, Dreaming Big &amp; Living Life | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780059/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780059/</guid><description>Podcast Description My guest today is Tolani Shoneye, writer, producer, host of&amp;nbsp;10/10 Would Recommend and 1/3 of The Receipts Podcast - a leading award-winning UK podcast and one of my personal favourites for YEARS. While Tolani is best known for hosting The Receipts, she has established herself as a trusted voice that resonates with millennial women on and off the mic. A former beauty editor for Buzzfeed UK, Tolani's credits include Elle, The Independent and Refinery29.</description></item><item><title>Ep.7 Running a Business, Being a Mother, Making it work with NEOM Founder, Nicola Elliott | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780060/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 10:18:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780060/</guid><description>Podcast Description My guest today is Nicola Elliot, Founder and Creative Director of NEOM Organics - one of the first, and fastest growing wellbeing brands in the UK, which specialises in 100% natural fragrances. Nicola’s inspiration for NEOM came whilst working as a magazine editor, when she realised the wellbeing of her friends and colleagues was suffering due to the demands of their fast-paced lives. She chose to retrain in aromatherapy and fast forward to today, NEOM has 4 standalone stores and is stocked with renowned retailers.</description></item><item><title>Ep.6 Living a Life of Constant Improvement with Represent Clothing Founder, George Heaton | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780061/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 09:12:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780061/</guid><description>Podcast Description My guest today is George Heaton, Co-Founder of luxury British streetwear brand Represent. Represent was founded by George and his brother Mike in 2012 after he started creating T-shirts while studying at the University of Salford. The brand now has more than 150 stockists worldwide, including Selfridges and Harvey Nichols in the UK. Inspired by British designs, the brothers showcase their ranges at top fashion destinations worldwide, and their pieces have been featured in top publications from British GQ to Vogue Paris.</description></item><item><title>Ep.5 The Science Behind Career Success with Dr Grace Lordan | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780062/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 19:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780062/</guid><description>Podcast Description My guest today is Dr Grace Lordan, Associate Professor in Behavioural Science at LSE and the author of recently published Think Big, Take Small Steps and Build the Future you Want, which is all about how to create a framework that will move you towards your goals. Her academic writings have been published in international journals and she currently advises the UK Government as a board member on the Skills and Productivity Board.</description></item><item><title>Ep.4 Doing Whatever It Takes To Succeed with Reece Wabara | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780063/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780063/</guid><description>Podcast Description My guest today is Reece Wabara, CEO of Manière De Voir - former professional footballer turned e-commerce powerhouse. West Midlands born Reece began his career playing for Manchester City in the Under 16s team and went on to play for the England U21 squad before a strategic pivot into the fashion industry.&amp;nbsp;
MDV, the design-driven brand founded by Reece in 2013 has gone on to see incredible growth, listed in the most recent Sunday Times Virgin Atlantic Fast Track 100, and with 187% year on year increase in net revenue, worn by stars from Raheem Sterling to Anthony Joshua.</description></item><item><title>Ep.3 Fail Fast, Learn Fast, Build a Career You Love with Shopé Delano | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780064/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 18:29:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780064/</guid><description>Podcast Description My guest today is Shopé Delano, VP of Marketing at Charlie Oscar, a new-era group of digital consumer brands, and Founder of her own upcoming workwear brand Kind Regards . Shopé's internet life began back in 2010, with a fashion blog and youtube channel that saw her work freelance with the likes of Nike, Puma and ASOS. After a successful stint in academia, she entered the world of startups and venture capital, working with the likes of Depop, Forward Partners and now Charlie Oscar.</description></item><item><title>Ep.2 The Power of Building Your Confidence with Steven Bartlett | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780065/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 22:59:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780065/</guid><description>Podcast Description My guest today is Steven Bartlett, the 28-year-old founder of social media marketing agency Social Chain. From a bedroom in Manchester, Steven dropped out of his university course and built what would become one of the world’s most influential social media companies at just 21 years old, before taking his company public at 27 with a market valuation of almost £200m. Steven’s debut book, 'Happy Sexy Millionaire, is a Sunday Times Bestseller and more recently Steven and I chatted on his own podcast about self-belief, mental health, running a business and pretty much everything in between.</description></item><item><title>Ep.1 Knowing &amp; Growing A Multi-Million Dollar Brand with House of CB Founder, Conna Walker | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780066/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 22:59:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780066/</guid><description>Podcast Description My guest today is Conna Walker, Founder and CEO of House of CB and Mistress Rocks. Conna started House of CB at just age 17 with a £3,000 family loan. Since then House of CB has grown into a multi-million-pound business with over 40 retail locations and a worldwide community of over 3m. Worn by Chrissy Teigen, Jennifer Lopez, the Kardashians, and many more... Conna’s business is an innovator in brand marketing and her goal is to embrace the female form in order to champion female empowerment.</description></item><item><title>Working Hard, Hardly Working Trailer: The Reality behind the Hustle with Grace Beverley | Working Hard, Hardly Working</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5708780067/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5708780067/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this podcast series, author and entrepreneur Grace Beverley moves away from the traditional 9-5 work rhetoric, to get a better understanding of what ACTUALLY goes on behind the scenes and how that looks for us as individuals. Are you good at taking time off? What’s the side to your work life that no one else sees? How do you avoid burnout? Each week Grace and her guest open an honest dialogue about these topics, and share practical tips to help make our work and home lives more balanced, successful and fulfilling.</description></item></channel></rss>