<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Trial on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-trial/</link><description>Recent content in The Trial on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 01:10:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-trial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>BONUS: An Exciting Update | The Trial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4105210001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 01:10:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4105210001/</guid><description>Podcast Description The verdict is in - The Trial is an international hit. We&amp;rsquo;ve just received some end-of-year accolades from Apple Podcasts, being named as the #1 True Crime podcast in Australia and New Zealand and the #2 new show overall. We just wanted to say a huge thanks for listening and helping us achieve this recognition. You can read more about it here. The Trial is brought to you from the newsroom of The Press in Christchurch.</description></item><item><title>Episode 8: Resolution | The Trial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4105210002/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 23:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4105210002/</guid><description>Podcast Description After months of evidence from dozens of witnesses across two trials, the jury returns - with a verdict. Michael McGrath&amp;rsquo;s family reacts and Martin Van Beynen offers expert analysis - including what David Benbow might do next. WARNING: This episode contains discussion of mental health and suicide. If you or anyone you know needs help, free call or text 1737 for assistance from a trained counsellor, 24 hours a day.</description></item><item><title>Episode 7: The retrial of David Benbow | The Trial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4105210003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 23:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4105210003/</guid><description>Podcast Description With the jury in the original trial unable to reach a verdict, David Charles Benbow finds himself back in the dock. And three key areas of evidence are updated as the prosecution tries once more to secure a conviction. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 6: Not quite the end | The Trial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4105210004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4105210004/</guid><description>Podcast Description After listening intently to more than 100 witnesses over two months, the jury left the courtroom to begin its deliberations. Those left behind waited. And waited. But even when the wait was over, the Benbow trial still held a twist or two. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 5: 'Did you do it?' | The Trial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4105210005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 01:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4105210005/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the investigation intensified, David Benbow&amp;rsquo;s behaviour prompted questions from close friends, and police exploited his interest in the media coverage with a cunning press release. With the jury asked to consider the importance of Benbow&amp;rsquo;s missing rifle - the alleged murder weapon - the defence dismisses the Crown case as hollow, &amp;ldquo;like a cheap Easter egg&amp;rdquo;. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 4: The burden of proof | The Trial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4105210006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4105210006/</guid><description>Podcast Description After playing parts of David Benbow&amp;rsquo;s police interviews to the court, the prosecution makes much of his inability to fully account for his movements on the day - and day after - he allegedly murdered Michael McGrath. But the defence underlines one key fact: there is no physical evidence Benbow did anything wrong. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 3: Monday, 9am | The Trial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4105210007/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4105210007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Did Michael McGrath keep an appointment to shift some wood at David Benbow’s place? The prosecution says that’s where - and when - he was murdered. But the defence has doubts about Crown evidence involving the finer points of power consumption and CCTV footage. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 2: The love triangle | The Trial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4105210008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 03:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4105210008/</guid><description>Podcast Description One relationship faltered and another blossomed. Police argued that was a motive for murder. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 1: The disappearance of Michael McGrath | The Trial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4105210009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4105210009/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Michael McGrath started looking less scruffy, his friends started talking. When he failed to show for his weekly dinner with his mum, his new partner, Joanna Green, called the police, kickstarting an investigation that took six years to reach court. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Trial - Trailer | The Trial</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4105210010/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4105210010/</guid><description>Podcast Description In May 2017 49-year-old builder Michael McGrath disappeared - almost without trace. No crime scene was ever found. No weapon was ever found. No body was ever found. So how could his longtime friend be arrested and charged with murder? In February 2023, the trial of David Charles Benbow finally began. Benbow stood accused of murdering McGrath because he’d started a relationship with Benbow’s former partner, Joanna Green. The prosecution said that, while based entirely on circumstantial evidence, its case was so comprehensive there could be no doubt Benbow was guilty.</description></item></channel></rss>