<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/uncomfortable-conversations-with-josh-szeps/</link><description>Recent content in Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 10:50:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/uncomfortable-conversations-with-josh-szeps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>BONUS: Why Jews Are Literally Nazis - Reflections on a Collapsing Conversation | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 10:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, over 3,200 of Josh’s arts-industry colleagues are engaging in a Palestinian Day of Action, wearing Palestinian scarves during performances nationwide. Josh, you’ll be shocked to learn, has some thoughts.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Peter McCormack: Digital Currencies &amp; Spy States | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910002/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a future of digital spying, inflationary economies, incompetent central banks and petty authoritarians, could Bitcoin be the guarantee of all your other freedoms? Josh was on Peter’s blockbuster podcast, What Bitcoin Did, and now Peter stops by the Uncomfy Convos studio on a recent trip to Sydney. He’s a super smart thinker about the role of the individual, the state… and your wallet.
To subscribe to Josh’s premium podcast feed, hit the Substack page at https://uncomfortableconversations.</description></item><item><title>David Pakman: How's America Doing? | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910003/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Pakman is a progressive American political commentator who hosts one of the world’s most popular left-wing talk shows, with over 1.8 million subscribers. Josh picks his brain about the state of the media, of the Left… and of America.
To subscribe to Josh’s premium podcast feed, hit the Substack page at https://uncomfortableconversations.substack.com/subscribe
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Premium: Ask Me Anything | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 11:24:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910004/</guid><description>Podcast Description There's a LOT going on in the Uncomfy Convo world. You probably have a lot of questions. I'm here to answer them. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Paul Bloom: Against Empathy | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910005/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910005/</guid><description>Podcast Description What's wrong with empathy? Is effective altruism better? How did you develop your sense of right and wrong? Is suffering necessary for pleasure? These are the questions the psychologist Paul Bloom wrestles with. Enjoy the ride.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bari Weiss: Quitting The Mainstream Media | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910006/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yippee-ki-yay, Josh has quit his ABC Radio show to double down on Uncomfortable Conversations. Starting in the new year, you'll get additional free episodes, a YouTube channel, a live tour and more. Before embarking on his adventure, Josh wanted to speak with the most successful person who has recently pulled it off. Bari Weiss was an opinion writer and editor at The New York Times and The Wall Street Journal.</description></item><item><title>"What Are UFOs?" with Brian Dunning | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910007/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brian Dunning is an expert on critical thinking, science and skepticism. His weekly podcast, Skeptoid, debunks conspiracy theories, and his new film is “The UFO Movie THEY Don't Want You to See”. Here, Josh tries to get to the bottom of what’s really going on with UFOs.
To subscribe to Josh’s premium podcast feed, hit the Substack page at https://uncomfortableconversations.substack.com/subscribe
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"The Cancelling of the American Mind" with Greg Lukianoff &amp; Rikki Schlott | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can you work at a corporation or university and openly contradict elite opinion? Can you freel y suggest that gender is binary, land acknowledgments are silly, that there are biological reasons why more men become CEOs, or that racial diversity quotas are patronising? Not without being punished, according to a tsunami of cases being catalogued by the Foundation for Individual Rights and Expression. Its CEO, Greg Lukianoff, who co-wrote the bestseller “The Coddling of the American Mind” , has a new book, “The Cancelling of the American Mind”, with the Gen-Z journalist Rikki Schlott to explain what’s going on.</description></item><item><title>Julia Zemiro, Australian Legend | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910009/</guid><description>Podcast Description What does it take to sustain a career in the performing arts? Julia Zemiro is one of Australia’s most beloved perfomers. An actor, improv comic and TV host, she has hosted the official New Year's Eve telecast from Sydney Harbour, the music quiz show “RocKwiz”, and her own beloved television interview show “Julia Zemiro's Home Delivery”, I sit down with her to muse on what it takes to make it in a tough biz.</description></item><item><title>BONUS: Should Israel Exist At All? | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josh shares fresh thoughts on Gaza, Palestine and Israel in this special bonus episode. To subscribe to the premium podcast feed, hit the Substack page at https://uncomfortableconversations.substack.com/subscribe
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Gaza &amp; Israel" with Eli Lake | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910011/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eli Lake is the former senior national security correspondent for The Daily Beast and Newsweek. He’s a contributing editor to Commentary Magazine and the host of the Re-Education Podcast. He was a syndicated columnist for Bloomberg between 2014 and 2022 and a former reporter at the New York Sun, the Daily Beast and the Washington Times. He and Josh debate Israel’s responsibility for the current crisis in Gaza.</description></item><item><title>"Are We Handing Putin Victory?" with Marcus Walker | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910012/</guid><description>Podcast Description How are you feeling about the war in Ukraine? We may be at a fork in the road and about to blow it. The Wall Street Journal's Marcus Walker recently returned from Ukraine. He shares with you everything from the fascinating little details to the bracing geopolitics.
To subscribe to Josh’s premium podcast feed, hit the Substack page at https://uncomfortableconversations.substack.com/subscribe
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>BONUS: Josh's thoughts on Israel &amp; Gaza | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910013/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 07:10:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910013/</guid><description>Podcast Description I’ve been asked many times about my thoughts on situation in Israel and Gaza…. So here they are.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"What The Voice Referendum Really Means" with Jack Latimore | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910014/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910014/</guid><description>Podcast Description On October 14th, Australians will vote about whether to recognise the country’s First Peoples in the Constitution by establishing a body called the Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander Voice.
Jack Latimore is a Birpai man and the Indigenous affairs journalist for The Age and the Sydney Morning Herald. He joins the show to explain it all.
You can read Jack’s work at the link below.
https://www.theage.com.au/by/jack-latimore-p4ywbz
To subscribe to Josh’s premium podcast feed, hit the Substack page at https://uncomfortableconversations.</description></item><item><title>LIVE FROM NEW YORK: The Fifth Column Guys | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 02:29:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josh is in New York, where he just stopped by the studios of one of America’s greatest podcasts, The Fifth Column, to record this special crossover pod. Find Michael Moynihan, Kmele Foster and Matt Welch at https://wethefifth.com and https://wethefifth.substack.com.
To subscribe to Josh’s premium podcast feed, hit the Substack page at https://uncomfortableconversations.substack.com/subscribe
Grab your Exclusive NordVPN Deal by going to nordvpn.com/Conversations to get a Huge Discount off your NordVPN Plan + 4 extra months for free.</description></item><item><title>Premium: Dan Savage “The World Before Gay Marriage" | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910016/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 02:25:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910016/</guid><description>Podcast Description A long, long time ago, The Gays couldn’t marry. What was it like in that mediaeval nightmare? The world’s most popular sex advice columnist, Dan Savage, joined Josh in New York on the set of his television talk show in 2013. Enjoy this fascinating time portal, unavailable anywhere else on earth, except on the premium podcast feed at https://uncomfortableconversations.substack.com/subscribe
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"The Ape That Understood The Universe" with Steve Stewart-Williams | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 05:45:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are there biological differences between male and female brains? How much of what you do is dictated by evolution? As a part of our Permission To Think collaboration with the University of Technology Sydney's Faculty of Arts and Social Sciences, evolutionary psychologist Professor Steve Stewart-Williams describes how you came to be an ape who understands the universe.
To subscribe to Josh’s premium podcast feed, hit the Substack page at https://uncomfortableconversations.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Josh's Thoughts on The Voice | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 07:18:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Australians are about to vote on whether to change the constitution to create a special advisory body for Indigenous Australians. Is it an overdue forum for justice? Or a risky, undemocratic game of identity politics? It’s the listener question Josh gets the most. Here, he tries to inject some sanity into an increasingly toxic debate.
To subscribe to Josh’s premium podcast feed, hit the Substack page at https://uncomfortableconversations.substack.com/subscribe</description></item><item><title>"The Identity Trap" with Yascha Mounk | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yascha Mounk is one of the world’s most interesting thinkers about diversity, liberalism and democracy. His new book, The Identity Trap, is an ambitious account of the origins, consequences, and limitations of “wokeness”. How did a relatively marginal set of ideas – postmodernism, postcolonialism, critical race theory – come to rule the world?
To subscribe to Josh’s premium podcast feed, hit the Substack page at https://uncomfortableconversations.substack.com/subscribe
Grab your Exclusive NordVPN Deal by going to nordvpn.</description></item><item><title>“Campus Craziness” with Amna Khalid | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910020/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Has Louis CK reeeeeeally been “cancelled” if he still has a face? I mean, he wasn’t beheaded, ergo, “cancel culture” doesn’t exist. Amna Khalid is an equal-opportunity defender of free speech—a professor who slams wokesters… at the same time as legally opposing Florida’s war on woke universities. Anna’s blog and podcast, “Banished”, are about the history of censorship. This episode is part of Permission to Think, a collaboration with the University of Technology, Sydney, where Josh is a visiting fellow.</description></item><item><title>“Is Israel Immoral?” with Antony Loewenstein | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is Zionism a noble goal, or a form of colonial apartheid? Is a two-state solution possible? Desirable? Antony Loewenstein is a fierce critic of Israel and of the whole Zionist project. His new book is The Palestine Laboratory: How Israel Exports the Technology of Occupation Around the World. He and Josh debate the rights and wrongs of a Jewish homeland.
To subscribe to Josh’s premium podcast feed, hit the Substack page at https://uncomfortableconversations.</description></item><item><title>Premium: My Thoughts on Barbie | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is Barbie the triumphant feminist critique of modern society it claims to be? The dust has settled on the mega-hit, so Josh finds some time to weigh-in.
To subscribe to Josh’s premium podcast feed, hit the Substack page at https://uncomfortableconversations.substack.com/subscribe
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Premium: Australia vs America with Ed Kavalee | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910023/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ed Kavalee is a legend of Aussie radio, and a bloody funny bloke. Josh and Ed sit down to compare the best and worst of Australia vs America. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>“Your Wild A.I. Future” with Toby Walsh | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910024/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910024/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s being compared to the discovery of fire or of electricity. Either way, artificial intelligence will revolutionise human civilisation. How?
Toby Walsh runs the AI Lab at UNSW and is a world-leading expert in AI. His most recent book is “Machines Behaving Badly: The Morality of AI.” Join him and Josh all the way down the rabbit hole.
To subscribe to Josh’s premium podcast feed, hit the Substack page at https://uncomfortableconversations.</description></item><item><title>Premium: How Josh Quit Booze | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910025/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 22:56:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josh used to drink a lot, and now he doesn't. One of the most frequently asked questions on our Ask Me Anythings, is how and why he quit. It deserves a longer explanation. Here it is. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Fired For a Tweet" with David Volodzko | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910026/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 11:42:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910026/</guid><description>Podcast Description “If you’re explaining, you’re losing,” said Ronald Reagan, who never had to explain himself to a baying Twitter mob. Respected journalist David Volodzko, an expert on political extremism, got the newspaper job of his dreams… and lost it all within days. If you’ve ever wondered whether cancel culture exists, don’t miss his stunning tale.
To subscribe to Josh’s premium podcast feed, hit the Substack page at https://uncomfortableconversations.substack.com/subscribe
And you can support David at his Substack page at https://substack.</description></item><item><title>"Comedy In An Age Of Cancel Culture" with Mark Normand | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910027/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jerry Seinfeld personally chose Mark Normand to be his opening act. He’s a favourite of Joe Rogan and has appeared on CONAN, the Tonight Show &amp;amp; Late Show. Josh caught up with him, live and in-the-flesh, during Mark’s Australian tour.
Mark’s new special Soup To Nuts is available on Netflix now. Check out the trailer HERE. Follow Mark on Twitter HERE.
To subscribe to Josh’s premium podcast feed, hit the Substack page at https://uncomfortableconversations.</description></item><item><title>"Why We're Tribal" with Cory Clark | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910028/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you more forgiving of people you agree with than those you don’t? Have humans evolved to favour our own kind, to avoid ostracism, and to gain social status? Cory Clark is a behavioral scientist who studies tribalism and group identity. Her findings are shocking… but they offer us a path out of this mess.
To subscribe to Josh’s premium podcast feed, hit the Substack page at https://uncomfortableconversations.substack.com/subscribe</description></item><item><title>Premium: When Josh Met Russell Brand | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910029/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 07:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910029/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a TV interview that put Josh on the map, Russell Brand shows up at Josh’s New York studio for the wildest ride of Josh’s life. Nipples are tweaked. Laptops are ruined. Wild minds are in flight. It’s one for the history books. Enjoy.
To subscribe to Josh’s premium podcast feed, hit the Substack page at https://uncomfortableconversations.substack.com/subscribe
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Owning Right Wing Trolls" with Destiny | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910030/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Destiny, aka The Omni Liberal, aka Steven Bonnell is the debater who most terrifies right-wing trolls on Twitter. He was among the first people in the world to stream video games online full-time and now live-streams political debates in which he crushes his conservative opponents. What makes him tick?
To subscribe to Josh’s premium podcast feed, hit the Substack page at https://uncomfortableconversations.substack.com/subscribe
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Premium: Sean Szeps - Not Like Other Dads | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910031/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 08:19:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josh's husband Sean’s memoir Not Like Other Dads was released in early June and has been a raging success. For this premium episode, they sit down and talk about the book, his motivations for writing it, and his experience, of their experience, of becoming parents.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Who Killed Creativity?" with Andrew &amp; Gaia Grant | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910032/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrew &amp;amp; Gaia Grant study the world’s biggest companies and coach them to be nimbler, more creative, and more diverse. How did we get so uncreative… and what separates the best from the rest?
To subscribe to Josh’s premium podcast feed, hit the Substack page at https://uncomfortableconversations.substack.com/subscribe
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"The Next Level of Comedy" with Myq Kaplan | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910033/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myq is a New York comic who’s been on the Tonight Show, Conan, Letterman, James Corden, Seth Meyers, Comedy Central, Last Comic Standing, and America’s Got Talent. He also introduced Josh to ayahuasca. What happened next?
To subscribe to Josh’s premium podcast feed, hit the Substack page at https://uncomfortableconversations.substack.com/subscribe
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"What Hitchens Would Make of the Left" with Matt Johnson | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910034/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Despite his reputation as a defector to neoconservatism, Christopher Hitchens was more faithfully committed to liberal principles than many on the left today: Free expression, internationalism, individual rights and universalism as opposed to identity politics. That’s the argument Matt Johnson makes in his book, How Hitchens Can Save the Left: Rediscovering Fearless Liberalism in an Age of Counter-Enlightenment.
To subscribe to Josh’s premium podcast feed hit the Substack page at https://uncomfortableconversations.</description></item><item><title>Premium: Travel Hacking 101 | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910035/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 04:01:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josh is a travel hacker and aviation nerd. He's one of those people who knows all the ways to get as many frequent flyer miles as possible, and cash them in for luxury, first-class experiences on the world's best airlines. He sits down with producer Stef to take him through how the whole thing works. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"The Witch Trials of J.K. Rowling" with Megan Phelps-Roper | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910036/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Megan Phelps-Roper was brought up in one of the most hated sects of American Christianity – the Westborough Baptist Church. Now, she sits down with the woman at the centre of an equally vicious firestorm, J.K. Rowling, in a new podcast from The Free Press. Josh and Megan reflect on the trans wars, religion, and the power of the mob.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Premium: Ask Me Anything - Fitness, Ukraine, Gender Ideology &amp; A.I. | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910037/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 08:15:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josh answers all your questions about A.I., fitness, Ukraine, gender ideology, and vacationing in Europe in winter.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"RFK, Joe Rogan &amp; Vaccines" with Michael Shermer | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910038/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 09:43:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Presidential candidate Robert F Kennedy Jr blew up the internet when he pushed anti-vaccine claims on Joe Rogan’s show. It’s déjà vu all over again for Josh, who had his own little vax run-in with Rogan last year. Should scientists and medical researchers do a better job of engaging with alternative media? America’s leading skeptic, Michael Shermer, thinks so. He and Josh hash it out. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Premium: Josh's First Podcast - The Dawn of #WeThePeople LIVE | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910039/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910039/</guid><description>Podcast Description On a summer night in Brooklyn in 2015, in the week when Trump descended a staircase to declare his ridiculous stunt candidacy for the Republican nomination, Josh launched his first ever podcast. Jim Norton, Abbi Crutchfield and Kevin Allison lit up a dive bar, guzzling cocktails and bantering about the news. Be transported back to that event.
To get your very own premium version of Josh’s podcast, hit the Substack page at https://uncomfortableconversations.</description></item><item><title>"Untangling Wokeness" with Sarah Haider | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910040/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sarah Haider is a Pakistani-American writer and a ferociously clear-headed thinker about culture, society, identity politics, religion, cancel culture, sex and gender. She’s been featured on the BBC and in The Economist and recognized as a “Freethought Heroine” for her work co-founding a non-profit that assists dissident Muslims. Her podcast, A Special Place In Hell, is co-hosted by the equally curious contrarian feminist Meghan Daum. Here, Sarah and Josh wrestle with the biggest questions of contemporary culture.</description></item><item><title>"The University Echo Chamber" with Katy Barnett | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910041/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Permission to Think is a collaboration with the University of Technology, Sydney, where we debate the vigour, rigour and freedom of the academy. Today, the Melbourne University Law Professor Dr Katy Barnett sticks her neck out to argue against activist academics.
To subscribe to Josh’s premium podcast feed. Hit the Substack page at https://uncomfortableconversations.substack.com/subscribe
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Will A.I. Take Over?" with Stephen Marche | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 08:44:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910042/</guid><description>Podcast Description The world’s leading A.I. researchers have released an open letter warning of the “existential threat” the technology poses to human civilisation. Stephen Marche begs to differ. He’ll go down in history as the man who created the world’s first mainstream novel written by A.I. To do so, he spent months interacting with Chat GPT. Join Josh as he and Stephen argue about the fate of artificial intelligence… and of humankind.</description></item><item><title>Premium: A First Date With Josh | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910043/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you know Josh? You may be surprised to hear his surprise when the show’s producer, Stefan Posthuma, turns the tables and puts Josh on the spot with some First Date Questions of his own.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Richard Dawkins: LIVE! | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910044/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910044/</guid><description>Podcast Description In front of a packed crowd at a sold-out Brisbane City Hall, Josh interviews the world's most influential living biologist, Richard Dawkins.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Why Conspiracy Theories Work" with Michael Shermer | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910045/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael Shermer is a titan of the rationalist movement. He’s been on Oprah. He’s been on Donahue. He’s argued on TV with Deepak Chopra. He had a column in Scientific American for twenty-odd years. He’s the executive director of The Skeptics Society and the founding publisher of Skeptic magazine. His latest book is Conspiracy: Why the Rational Believe the Irrational.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Premium: When Josh Met Susan Sarandon | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910046/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Susan Sarandon is an Academy Award winning actor, philanthropist and progressive activist. She joined Josh on his old TV show to talk about her rise in Hollywood, gun laws, drug laws and being a “milf”.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"The Life of a Dominatrix" with Eva Oh | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910047/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eva is a high-end dominatrix: A sex worker who flies around the world, servicing people’s most carnal desires. What makes them -- and her -- do what they do?1
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Premium: Ask Me Anything | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910048/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910048/</guid><description>Podcast Description What are your non-negotiable travel essentials? What catch phrase would you put on a billboard? What are your most left-wing and right-wing views? From deep and insightful to low-brow and fun - the audience asks Josh... anything. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Is Polarisation Good?" with Shadi Hamid | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910049/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shadi Hamid is a Muslim-American writer and professor whose latest book is “The Problem of Democracy”. In his new Substack, Wisdom of Crowds, he makes the case against consensus… and in favour of polarisation. Josh wants to figure out what the hell he means.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Premium: Reflections On A Trip To West Africa | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910050/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 04:04:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910050/</guid><description>Podcast Description As Josh comes to the end of his trip to West Africa. He sits down with his travel companion Dan to share their summary of the adventure.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Fleeing Islam" with Yasmine Mohammed | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910051/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910051/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a dramatic youth that included a forced marriage to an Al-Qaeda operative, Yasmine became an activist for women’s rights in the Muslim world. Her charity, Free Hearts, Free Minds, helps ex-Muslims escape Muslim theocracies. Ironically, some of her toughest adversaries are western progressives, too timid to criticise Islam.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Booze, Meat &amp; Ultramarathons" with Rich Roll | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910052/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910052/</guid><description>Podcast Description He’s a one-man wellness, publishing and podcasting empire. Rich Roll started getting fit in middle age and is now a world-renowned vegan ultra-endurance athlete.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Premium: When Josh Met Dick Cavett | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910053/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dick Cavett is one of the greatest television talk show hosts of all time. After being a writer on the original NBC Tonight Show (first with Jack Parr, then with Johnny Carson), Cavett got his own show in 1968. It ran for nearly 40 years and cemented him as a titan of American broadcasting, hosting seminal political debates as well as Hollywood’s biggest stars. A few years ago, Cavett appeared on Josh’s TV show.</description></item><item><title>"Is Trump Insane?" with Anthony Scaramucci | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910054/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910054/</guid><description>Podcast Description “The Mooch” was a wildly successful investment banker when he joined Donald Trump’s presidential campaign. He became the White House Communications Director in 2017. Anthony tells Josh about his time in the White House, his relationship with Trump, and what kind of a guy he really is. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Premium: Josh Is In West Africa! | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910055/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josh is backpacking around West Africa. As you do. What’s it like? He’s here to tell you, recorded live from the road (or the dusty track, as the case may be).
Sign up below on our FREE Substack tier to hear the whole thing. https://uncomfortableconversations.substack.com/subscribe
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"The Death of the University?" with Peter Boghossian | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910056/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Universities are now dominated by diversity, equity and inclusion mandates, says the philosopher Peter Boghossian… and the result is a stultifying climate of intellectual conformism. In this all-new instalment of Permission to Think, our collaboration with the UTS Faculty of Arts and Social Sciences, Josh and Peter debate how universities, and our culture at large, can reclaim true intellectual freedom.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Is Nuclear Power The Answer?" with Zion Lights | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910057/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910057/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you're a greenie, you're supposed to be anti-nuclear. That was true of the former Extinction Rebellion spokesperson Zion Lights... until she became one of Britain's most prominent advocates for nuclear power. But do her claims stand up to Josh's scrutiny?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Premium: Artie Lange, Jon Ronson, Guys We F****d | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910058/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 03:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josh walked into a bar in Brooklyn and, in front of a packed crowd of drunks, argued about the news with some of the funniest, smartest people in New York. This is that event.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Will Trump Be Arrested?" with James Kirchick | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910059/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jamie Kirchick knows everything about the secret, spooky, saucy, seedy side of Washington DC. Hear him hold forth on the secret history of gay spies, trans activists and, of course, the never-not-impending arrest of Donald J Trump.
To hear the full episode for FREE, sign up to the free tier on Josh's Substack at: https://uncomfortableconversations.substack.com/subscribe
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Premium: The Deep Questions - How Loudly May I Poo In Public? | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910060/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910060/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this brand new venture, Josh addresses some of life's deepest questions as posed by his friend and work colleague Robbie Armfield. In this first episode, Robbie has anxiety about generating sounds and aromas in the office toilet cubicle. Robbie has questions. Josh has the answers. You can find more from Robbie on his podcasts "Welcome to Meet You" and "Robbie's Modern Life".
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>"Getting Real On Race" with Coleman Hughes | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910061/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910061/</guid><description>Podcast Description The brilliant Coleman Hughes is an American writer, podcaster and musician. He burst onto the intellectual scene at a young age with his ruthlessly well-articulated opinions on race and public policy issues. He joins Josh this week with his giga-brained thoughts on race, equity and inclusion. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Premium: Zach Cregger - From The Archives | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910062/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910062/</guid><description>Podcast Description You probably know Zach Cregger from comedy shows like Wrecked and Whitest Kids U'Know. He also wrote and directed Barbarian, one of the horror films of 2022. This chat from the #WeThePeople LIVE archive is a conversation Josh and Zach had in Puerto Rico in 2016 where they spoke about the process of making good comedy, procrastination and how social media kills creativity. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>"The Transgender Who Wasn't" with KC Miller | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910063/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910063/</guid><description>Podcast Description For most transgender people, transitioning is one of the greatest experiences of their lives. For others, it deforms into crippling regret. KC Miller is one of them.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Predictions Of A Scientific Futurist" with Dr Catherine Ball | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910064/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr Ball is a scientific futurist whose book is Converge: A futurist's insights into the potential of our world as technology and humanity collide." She and Josh wrestle with artificial intelligence, the future of food, radical life extension, and air fryers.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Premium: Ask Me Anything | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910065/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 06:18:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Remember a while ago Josh asked you, to ask him anything? Yep, he only answered one question - which turned into a full episode about JK Rowling... Well, there were many more tasty morsels in that cauldron of questions, so he's back to answer more! See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"The Problem With Everything" with Tim Urban | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910066/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 16:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tim Urban’s first appearance on this show remains one of the all-time favourites. Now, this explosive thinker of cosmic, civilisation-level thoughts returns with a book: “What&amp;rsquo;s Our Problem? A Self-Help Book for Societies”. He and Josh wrestle with what’s going wrong. Why is everything a mess? Why is everyone acting like a baby? When did things get so tribal? Why do humans do this stuff?
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>Premium: Myq Caplan - From The Archives | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910067/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 10:15:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910067/</guid><description>Podcast Description From the #WeThePeople LIVE archives this week to a 2016 chat with the wonderful Myq Caplan. First and foremost Myq is comedian. Josh and Myq chat about what funny is, how he became funny, and the creative process he uses to stay funny. Enjoy.
For the full episode sign up at uncomfortableconversations.substack.com
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Left Is Not Woke" with Susan Neiman | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910068/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 16:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Susan Neiman is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most respected living philosophers. She was born in America and educated at Harvard but now lives in Germany, where she&amp;rsquo;s the director of the Einstein Forum and a member of the Berlin-Brandenburg Academy of Sciences. She&amp;rsquo;s a leading expert on the Enlightenment. Her new book is Left is not Woke.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Premium: Is JK Rowling Transphobic? | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910069/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 23:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910069/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, the world&amp;rsquo;s biggest LGBTQI+ event, World Pride, kicks off in Sydney. Right on cue, activists are calling to boycott a new Harry Potter video game because Rowling is a famous anti-trans bigot. But&amp;hellip; is she?
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"What Happened To The IDW?" with Ross Anderson | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910070/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 23:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910070/</guid><description>Podcast Description The so-called &amp;ldquo;intellectual dark web&amp;rdquo; was supposed to shine a light on issues too thorny for the mainstream media to touch. Now, it&amp;rsquo;s a basket case of kooks. The journalist Ross Anderson recently wrote an amazing feature on the &amp;ldquo;red-pilling&amp;rdquo; of the gay conservative online host Dave Rubin. He&amp;rsquo;s here to explain what&amp;rsquo;s going wrong. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>"The Climate Optimist" with Saul Griffith | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910071/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 16:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josh gets excited, at long last, about a realistic plan for fighting climate change while creating new jobs and a healthier environment. In short: electrify everything. For more about Saul, check out his website HERE.
Subscribe to our Substack HERE. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Premium: Oliver Burkeman - From The Archives | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910072/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 10:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Going back some five years to Josh's first ever chat with the now Uncomfy Convos regular, the self-help psychology sage Oliver Burkeman. On this episode we talk about happiness, drawing on his 2012 book The Antidote: Happiness for People Who Can't Stand Positive Thinking. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"The New Gurus" with Helen Lewis | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910073/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 16:00:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Helen Lewis&amp;rsquo;s new BBC Radio 4 show, The New Gurus, investigates why so many of us have turned away from mainstream medicine, mainstream politics and the mainstream media to embrace the power of charismatic individuals instead. Helen went viral in 2018 with her legendary interview with Jordan Peterson. She&amp;rsquo;s a brilliant interrogator and a thoughtful critic of the culture wars, wokeness, gender ideology and the far right.
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Josh's Soap Box: Josh Is Getting Sued! | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910074/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910074/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Josh reflects, in a somewhat heated way, on the surreal injustices of the justice system. Plus: Aussie-made shoulder-launched drone guns. And sharks in Sydney harbour.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sam Harris: What The Hell Happened? | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910075/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris is a best-selling writer, philosopher and neuroscientist who hosts one of the world's most influential intellectual podcasts, Making Sense. Josh wants to pin down, once and for all, Sam's feelings about his former associates in the "intellectual dark web" who've gone off the rails. They also discuss Elon, Twitter, and the best flavour of cookie.
To subscribe to the premium podcast feed via substack head to: https://uncomfortableconversations.</description></item><item><title>Premium: Scott Adams - From The Archives | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910076/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 06:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Scott Adams is the creator of the cartoon strip Dilbert. He rose to Twitter prominence ahead of the 2016 US election where he picked Trump as the winner, praising him as a master persuader. We leave Trump aside in this episode and focus on Scott&amp;rsquo;s advice on creativity and success that he details in his 2014 book - How to Fail at Almost Everything and Still Win Big. Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>The Best Of Vol. 3: Kurt Fearnley, Me &amp; Alice Dreger | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910077/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 16:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910077/</guid><description>Podcast Description For this last Best Of episode we have the amazing Kurt Fearnley - paralympian, media personalist and advocate, who brings an amazing perspective on the global experience of disability. Then, the show I get the most feedback on, my diatribe about gun laws. And finally, one of the world’s foremost experts on sex differences - the historian and bioethicist Alice Dreger. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Josh's Soap Box: Is It Racist To Ask Where You're From? | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910078/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 16:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910078/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Josh airs what&amp;rsquo;s on his mind. Did the NFL star Damar Hamlin suffer cardiac arrest because he was vaccinated, or because he was smashed in the chest by six-foot-four, 220-pound receiver? Was the musical editor of The Simpsons, who died this week, the greatest TV composer of all time? We revisit the best-ever Simpsons songs to find out! Is there anything redeeming about seagulls? And as we learn new facts about the Buckingham Palace racism scandal, Josh finds himself confused&amp;hellip; Is it always racist to ask where you&amp;rsquo;re from?</description></item><item><title>The Best Of Vol. 2: Andrew Denton, Tim Flannery &amp; Ana Marie Cox | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910079/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910079/</guid><description>Podcast Description The holiday interlude continues with our top podcast moments. Andrew Denton is a giant of Australian media. Now out of the limelight, he focuses much of his work on voluntary assisted dying advocacy. Tim Flannery - ecologist, explorer, and Australian of the Year winner brings us an amazing perspective on what it is to understand nature, and humanity’s place within it. And finally Ana Marie Cox - one of the most uncomfortable conversations of the last year.</description></item><item><title>Ask Me Anything - 2022 | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910080/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 16:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Well what a year it has been! And as we end every year here on Uncomfortable Conversations, it’s time for me to answer your questions. What have you been noodling on in 2022? And what do I reckon about it all? It’s time to find out. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Best Of Vol. 1: Tim Urban, Clementine Ford &amp; Malcolm Turnbull | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910081/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 16:00:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910081/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s time for a Christmas interlude, the best parts of our favourite uncomfortable conversations. Tim Urban is still probably my all-time favourite guest. The creative genius behind the blog Wait But Why brings his brain melting takes on the world, and our place within it. Clementine Ford and I have some disagreements. Neither of us pull a punch. Our chat gets to the heart of what we’re trying to do here.</description></item><item><title>Premium: Rutger Bregman - From The Archives | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910082/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 16:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910082/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Guardian has called Rutger Bregman "the Dutch wunderkind of new ideas". He has a forward thinking, earnest approach to the small task of making the world a better place for everyone - something he's been working on this since his early 20's. This episode is taken from the #WeThePeople LIVE archive.
To get the full episode go to www.uncomfortableconversations.substack.com/listen
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>"The Intellectual Dark Web" with Eric Weinstein | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910083/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 16:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eric runs the investment firm of the right-wing multi-billionaire Peter Thiel, the co-founder of PayPal and the first outside investor in Facebook. Yet Eric is a left-wing political dissenter. With a PhD in mathematical physics from Harvard, he’s a confounding genius. He coined the term “the intellectual dark web”. His journey is perplexing. His vision of the future is ominous. Join Josh on his journey down the Weinstein rabbit hole.</description></item><item><title>Premium: Louis Theroux - From The Archives | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910084/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 16:00:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910084/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this special episode from Josh&amp;rsquo;s archive, he speaks with legendary British documentarian Louis Theroux. For decades, Louis has thrust himself into strange and extreme worlds, casting a light on the fringes of the human experience. This interview took place at the time of the release of his first feature film: My Scientology Movie. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"A Very Sober Christmas" with Bridget Phetasy | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910085/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 16:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bridget is a podcasting and publishing phenomenon. She and Josh discuss everything from Peruvian ayahuasca ceremonies, to Joe Rogan, to cancel culture, to the Byron Bay cult she momentarily joined. Oh, and how motherhood has made her finally appreciate Christmas.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Who Screwed Millennials?" with Tom Ballard | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910086/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 16:00:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Ballard is one of Australia&amp;rsquo;s most successful comedians. He may be the millennials’ most prominent, hilarious voice of fury against capitalism and boomers. Tom and Josh argue about the benefits and perils of 21st-century capitalism, free speech and liberalism. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Join the Josh Club! | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910087/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 21:21:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910087/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;re launching a new Uncomfortable Conversations community. Get loads more content for free! This is the most important thing you&amp;rsquo;ll hear this month. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss it.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"The Fallout of #MeToo" with Kat Rosenfield | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910088/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 16:00:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kat is a feminist who takes no bullshit. She created a stir with her piece “Why I Keep Getting Mistaken for a Conservative”. She and Josh discuss the challenges faced by women and the fallout of the #metoo movement.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Off The Rails?" with James Lindsay | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910089/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 16:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910089/</guid><description>Podcast Description James Lindsay is one of the most controversial figures on the American right. He was permanently banned from Twitter in August, until Elon reinstated him this week. He initially gained famed debunking the social-justice left. Since then, he has become notorious for increasingly dire warnings about an authoritarian leftist takeover of culture. Is he a crank, or a genius? Josh tries to figure him out. Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>"Is Everything A Hallucination?" with Anil Seth | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910090/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 16:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910090/</guid><description>Podcast Description When you see the colour blue, is it the same as when I see the colour blue? How does your brain create an image of the world&amp;hellip; and of yourself? Dive into the wild world of the matrix with one of the world&amp;rsquo;s leading neuroscientists, Anil Seth. His bestselling book is Being You: A New Science of Consciousness. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Josh's Soap Box: What I Got Wrong About Covid | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910091/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 16:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josh is being eviscerated on social media for spreading pro-vaccine misinformation. Did he? What did he, and we, get wrong about Covid?
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"The People vs Democracy" with Yascha Mounk | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910092/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 16:00:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910092/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do you stitch together diverse immigrant societies into a common future? How do you avoid collapsing into quarrelling tribes? Yascha Mounk is an optimistic academic who understands how democracies thrive&amp;hellip; and decay.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Josh’s Soap Box: Twitter &amp; Antisemitism | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910093/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 16:00:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josh reflects on Elon Musk, Kanye, Israel, and the rise of online Jew-hate.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Big Tech &amp; Free Speech" with Jordan Guiao | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910094/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 16:00:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910094/</guid><description>Podcast Description What will Elon Musk do with Twitter? Who wants to live inside Mark Zuckerberg&amp;rsquo;s Metaverse? Should Facebook censor hate speech? Jordan Guiao lived and worked in Silicon Valley and he knows big tech inside and out. We was formerly a digital strategist and the head of social media for the ABC and SBS respectively, and is currently a Research Fellow at The Australia Institute’s Centre for Responsible Technology. His new book is Disconnect - Why We Get Pushed to Extremes Online and How to Stop It.</description></item><item><title>Josh’s Soap Box: Kanye, hijabs and Taylor Swift | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910095/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 10:08:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josh reflects on Kanye&amp;rsquo;s antisemitic meltdown, Taylor Swift&amp;rsquo;s supposed fat shaming video and activism in Iran. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Maoism In The West" with Prof. David Martin Jones | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910096/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 01:35:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910096/</guid><description>Podcast Description David got his PhD in political thought from the London School of Economics and now teaches at King’s College London. He was a political science lecturer at the National University of Singapore and an associate editor of the University of Malaya’s South East Asian Studies journal. He explains the echoes he sees in the West of Mao&amp;rsquo;s Cultural Revolution. A politics of rage. Intellectual conformism. Cancel culture. This episode is a collaboration with the University of Technology Sydney as part of its &amp;ldquo;Permission to Think&amp;rdquo; series.</description></item><item><title>"Should We Talk To Nazis?" with Academy Award winner Emile Sherman &amp; Dr. Lloyd Vogelman | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910097/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 22:04:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emile is the Academy Award-winning producer of Lion, The King’s Speech, Rabbit-Proof Fence and The Power of the Dog. His cousin is a high-flying corporate consultant and former anti-apartheid activist. They have a podcast, Principle of Charity, which seeks to find common ground between opponents on controversial issues. But how far can talk take us, really? Don’t miss this electrifying debate.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>"Are Women And Men The Same?" with Louise Perry | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910098/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 05:42:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Should women aspire to the same things as men? Or have they been betrayed? Louise says we lie to young women about who they are and what they should want. She&amp;rsquo;s a journalist, anthropologist, activist and the writer of the new book &amp;ldquo;The Case Against the Sexual Revolution&amp;rdquo;.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>BONUS: "Fact Check" with Jesse Singal | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910099/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 16:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910099/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the previous episode of Uncomfortable Conversations, the trans activist Dianna Anderson alleged bad journalism by Jesse Singal, who wrote the bombshell 2018 Atlantic magazine piece, &amp;ldquo;When Children Say They&amp;rsquo;re Trans&amp;rdquo;. Josh left the issue dangling, agreeing that it deserved a fact-check. Don&amp;rsquo;t listen to this episode until you&amp;rsquo;ve heard Dianna&amp;rsquo;s. Here, Jesse responds.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Is Gender Made-Up?" with Dianna E. Anderson | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910100/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 16:00:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dianna E. Anderson is a gender non-binary writer and activist whose latest book is “In Transit: Being Non-Binary in a World of Dichotomies”. They and Josh disagree on a lot: the reality of biological sex, journalists who criticise trans issues, and whether burqas are sexist. Here, they hash it all out.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"War Correspondent" Misha Zelinsky | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910101/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 17:00:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Misha is a former trade union boss who now reports from Ukraine for the Australian Financial Review.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"When Whitefellas Talk With Blackfellas" with Tyson Yunkaporta | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910102/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 17:00:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tyson is a researcher, writer, and traditional wood carver. He works as a senior lecturer in Indigenous Knowledges and is the founder of the Indigenous Knowledge Systems Lab at Deakin University. His podcast, &amp;ldquo;The Other Others&amp;rdquo;, discusses how Indigenous knowledge can solve the world’s problems &amp;ndash; which is also the topic of his book, Sand Talk. He and Josh debate the far right, the woke left, structural racism, acknowledgments-of-country, and conspiracy thinking in Aboriginal communities.</description></item><item><title>"Are Aussies Sexist?" with Sarah Wilson | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910103/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 20:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910103/</guid><description>Podcast Description What's wrong with Australian men? What expectations do single, middle-aged women&amp;nbsp;face? What happened to the Left?&amp;nbsp;Sarah&amp;nbsp;Wilson&amp;nbsp;is a global phenomenon -- an activist, journalist, speaker, writer, podcaster and host. She joins Josh on this special crossover episode to wrestle with the biggest questions in our lives.&amp;nbsp;
Notes
Sarah mentions the following study during the show. Details here: A 2019 Harvard University study that looked at global economies and innovation found that Australia, paradoxically, was both one of the richest nations and the least innovative .</description></item><item><title>"What Is Gender?" with Courtney Act (aka Shane Jenek) | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910104/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 17:00:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910104/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is a man? What is a woman? What is transgenderism? What is drag? When are we acting out gender stereotypes, and when are we just being ourselves? Shane is the man behind Australia’s most popular drag queen, Courtney Act. Josh and Shane debate gender, sex, and the imminent death of heterosexuality (maybe). Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"The Scott Morrison Fiasco" with Peter van Onselen | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910105/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 17:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910105/</guid><description>Podcast Description During the pandemic, did the Australian prime minister subvert democracy? One of Australia’s leading political commentators takes Josh deep into the bizarro world of Morrison’s multiple ministries.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Would 'The Satanic Verses' Be Published Today?" with Sami Shah | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910106/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 17:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910106/</guid><description>Podcast Description As Salman Rushdie recuperates, Josh debates Islamophobia, blasphemy and cancel culture with the Pakistani-Australian writer and comic Sami Shah.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Why We Keep Secrets" with Michael Slepian | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910107/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 17:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael Slepian is an Author and Associate Professor of leadership and ethics at Columbia University. His new book is called The Secret Life Of Secrets - How Our Inner Worlds Shape Well-being, Relationships, and Who We Are.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"How To Be Happy" with Pandit The Monk | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910108/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 17:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pandit Dasa was a monk for more than 15 years. Now he&amp;rsquo;s ditched the robes and helps people ease their way into more thoughtful, generous, fulfilling mental states. Josh wants to know whether that&amp;rsquo;s an invaluable contribution to modern life&amp;hellip; or a spiritual cop out. Pandit&amp;rsquo;s book is Closing The Apps: How to be Mindful at Work and at Home.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>"What IS 'Diversity'?" with Antoinette Lattouf | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910109/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Antoinette Lattouf is a journalist, author and diversity advocate. She co-founded Media Diversity Australia. Her new book is How To Lose Friends and Influence White People. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"America's Next Civil War" with Stephen Marche | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910110/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 17:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stephen Marche is a Canadian author and political commentator. He writes for The New York Times, The Atlantic and Esquire among others. His new book The Next Civil War is a bracing look at what Stephen believes is a likely culmination of US division. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Why The Doomsayers Are Wrong" with Tyler Cowen | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910111/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 17:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tyler Cowen is a celebrated American economist, blogger, author and podcaster. He currently sits as the Holbert L. Harris Chair of Economics at George Mason University. He&amp;rsquo;s also an optimist about how the division we face today might end. His new book is Talent: How to Identify Energizers, Winners, and Creatives Around the World.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"The Slate Political Gabfest" with David Plotz | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910112/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 17:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910112/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Plotz was the editor of Slate magazine during its glory days. In fact, he was Josh&amp;rsquo;s first guest after the election of Donald Trump in 2016. The two reconnect about how to have difficult conversations in the 21st century.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"The War On The West" with Douglas Murray | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910113/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 17:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Douglas is a gay English conservative, columnist, and the best-selling author of the new book The War on the West. He and Josh debate the collapse of faith in western liberal democracy, and the threat posed by Trump and illiberal leaders like Viktor Orbán, and woke culture in general.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Woke Capitalism" with Prof. Carl Rhodes | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910114/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 17:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910114/</guid><description>Podcast Description From Nike supporting Colin Kaepernick to Qantas supporting same-sex marriage, corporations are going woke. Carl Rhodes is the Dean of the Business School at the University of Technology, Sydney&amp;hellip; and, perhaps surprisingly, a leftist. He decries &amp;ldquo;woke capitalism&amp;rdquo; so much that he&amp;rsquo;s written a book about it. He and Josh wrestle with the threat of wokeness and ask: Should companies keep their noses out of cultural questions, or is a corporate social conscience better than none?</description></item><item><title>Do We Need Gay Pride? | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910115/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910115/</guid><description>Podcast Description As part of Acast&amp;rsquo;s audio pride parade, Josh shares his thoughts on growing up gay in Sydney, and what pride means to him. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Are We Scientifically Illiterate?" with Prof. Luke O'Neill | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910116/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 17:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910116/</guid><description>Podcast Description How should we communicate science to the public? Celebrated scientist and popular Irish science communicator Professor Luke O’Neill joins Josh to plead for better scientific understanding in the general population. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Peter Singer: Live - The World's Greatest Moral Philosopher | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910117/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 17:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Peter founded the animal liberation movement in the 1970s and is a driver behind the Effective Altruism movement around the world. This is a recording of &amp;ldquo;An Evening with Peter Singer&amp;rdquo;, a live Q&amp;amp;A which Josh moderated at Sydney&amp;rsquo;s Enmore Theatre on March 27th, 2022.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Is Wokeness Made Up?" with Ana Marie Cox | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910118/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 17:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910118/</guid><description>Podcast Description An argument between Josh and veteran progressive muckraker Ana Marie Cox about whether wokeness is a real problem or a phantom of the right. Ana Marie founded Wonkette, was the senior political correspondent for MTV News and wrote for the New York Times magazine, among much, much else.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr Drew - America's Favourite Doctor | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910119/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 17:00:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr Drew is a physician, addiction medicine specialist and media personality. Since 1984 he has been beloved by American audiences for his candid communication of issues like AIDS, addiction &amp;amp; recovery, sexual health and harm reduction. His new book, co-authored with his daughter Paulina is It Doesn&amp;rsquo;t Have To Be Awkward. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Would The US Defend Australia?" with Cecile Shea | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910120/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 17:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cecile was a US diplomat in Japan, Pakistan, Thailand, Scotland and Israel, and a political advisor to the US Marine Corps in the Pacific. As the Ukraine War drags on, she and Josh debate the limits of American power&amp;hellip; and whether allies like Australia can depend, any longer, on a broken superpower.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Who's Really Disabled?" with Kurt Fearnley | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910121/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 07:22:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kurt Fearnley, AO, is one of Australia&amp;rsquo;s most successful paralympians. He began life crawling the dusty streets of Carcoar in central New South Wales and is now a disability rights advocate, humanitarian and media personality.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Roe v Wade: When Josh &amp; Joe Rogan Debated Abortion | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910122/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 21:40:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910122/</guid><description>Podcast Description A leaked opinion from the US Supreme Court suggests that women&amp;rsquo;s right to an abortion may be overturned in America. Who gets to decide hot-button cultural issues? What would this bombshell tell us about democracy? In 2017, Josh and Joe Rogan argued about exactly this. Today, Josh reflects on that exchange. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"The Language Of Woke Taboos" with Nick Enfield | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910123/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 17:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910123/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do taboo words develop, and why do we seem to be getting worse and worse at understanding each other? N. J. Enfield is a professor and the chair of linguistics at the University of Sydney, and a research associate in the Language and Cognition Group at the Max Planck Institute.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Social Media Is Ruining Everything" with Jonathan Haidt | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910124/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 17:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jonathan Haidt is considered one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most influential living psychologists. He&amp;rsquo;s just penned a piece for The Atlantic titled Why The Past Ten Years Of American Life Have Been Uniquely Stupid that looks at how social media erodes trust, shared narrative and social capital. He joins Josh on this new instalment of Permission To Think - a collaboration with The University of Technology Sydney School of Social Sciences.</description></item><item><title>"The Man Who Predicted Covid" with Dr. Eric Feigl-Ding | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910125/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eric Fiegl-Ding is a Harvard epidemiologist and health economist. In January of 2020 he became one of the first prominent scientists to raise the alarm about the potential of a Covid catastrophe through his viral HOLY MOTHER OF GOD tweet. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Will Europe Stand Firm?" with Nathalie Tocci | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910126/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 04:23:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nathalie Tocci is a political scientist, Honorary Professor at the University of Tübingen, and international relations expert specialising in the EU&amp;rsquo;s role in peacekeeping. She also directs the Istituto Affari Internazionali - a non-profit think tank which aims to contribute to the advancement of European integration and multilateral cooperation.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Are Universities Too Woke?" with Lee Jussim | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910127/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 16:00:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lee Jussim is an American social psychologist and distinguished professor leading the Social Perception Laboratory at Rutgers University. He joins Josh for this fifth instalment of Permission To Think, in collaboration with the University of Technology Sydney Faculty of Arts and Social Sciences.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Michael Kimmage, Obama's Ukraine Chief | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910128/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 05:45:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael Kimmage held the Russia/Ukraine portfolio in President Obama&amp;rsquo;s State Department. He&amp;rsquo;s an expert on international affairs, U.S.-Russian relations and American diplomatic history.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Why Aren't We Happy?" with Scott Barry Kaufman | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910129/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 16:00:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Scott is the founder of the Center for the Science of Human Potential and the host of the #1 psychology podcast in the world. His latest book is Transcend: The New Science of Self-Actualization. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Toomas Hendrik Ilves, ex-President of Estonia | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910130/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 16:00:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Toomas Hendrik Ilves was the president of Estonia from 2006 to 2016. He led the country through Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasions of Georgia and Crimea. Previously, as foreign minister, he had successfully lobbied for Estonia to join NATO.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"The Case For Heroin" with Dr. Carl Hart | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910131/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 11:35:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Should all drugs be legal? Dr. Carl Hart - neuroscientist and Professor of psychology at Columbia University is an advocate for drug legalisation and responsible recreational drug use. His new book is Drug Use For Grown Ups: Chasing Liberty In The Land Of Fear. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Is The West To Blame For Ukraine?" with Eliot A. Cohen | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910132/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 11:01:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eliot A. Cohen is a military expert, foreign policy academic and former advisor to Secretary of State Condoleeza Rice.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"The Price Of Having Opinions" with Mike Pesca | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910133/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 16:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mike Pesca is an award winning journalist and host of the wildly successful daily podcast, The Gist. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>“The Man Who Defied Trump” with Justin Amash | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910134/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 16:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Justin Amash was the first Republican member of congress to call for Donald Trump’s impeachment. He was subsequently described by Trump as “one of the dumbest &amp;amp; most disloyal men in Congress”.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"The Problem With Covid Contrarianism" with Cathy Young | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910135/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 16:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cathy Young is a former Boston Globe columnist and contributing editor at Reason. She writes a weekly column on politics, social issues and culture at Arc Digital. Why have so many independent thinkers careened off into knee-jerk contrarianism and conspiratorial thinking during the pandemic? Feminist, journalist and contrarian herself, Cathy Young, has a theory. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"How I Lost Millions In Crypto" with Peter McCormack | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910136/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 08:33:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Peter made millions in crypto, lost millions in crypto, and bought an English soccer club with crypto. He now hosts the world&amp;rsquo;s biggest podcast about bitcoin. How the hell did he do it?
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Stop Being Such a F*%#ing Baby!" with David Frum | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910137/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910137/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Frum is the former George W Bush speechwriter who invented the phrase “an axis of evil”. He is now a senior editor at The Atlantic. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Everything You Need To Know About Joe Rogan | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910138/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 04:39:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910138/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s been a hell of a week. Josh is back from America and jumps in solo to discuss the post-Rogan Twitter fallout, Myocarditis fact checking, what public health means, so-called &amp;ldquo;concentration camps&amp;rdquo; and some of the more stupid takes on the whole thing.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Can We Have Sex Back?" with Alice Dreger | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910139/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 10:45:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910139/</guid><description>Podcast Description What’s sex? What&amp;rsquo;s sexuality? What’s gender? Are trans women “real” women? Are woke activists expanding womanhood, or deranging it? Alice Dreger is one of the world’s foremost academic experts on sex, sexuality and intersexuality. Her recent Quillette article is “Can We Have Sex Back?”
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ask Me Anything | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910140/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 16:00:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910140/</guid><description>Podcast Description For the last show of 2021, its about time we heard from you. Your questions, for Josh, answered. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Did We Go Too Far?" with Brigid Delaney | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910141/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 16:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Did the pandemic turn Australia into a nation of paranoid, boot-licking dobbers? Brigid Delaney is a Guardian Australia columnist whose upcoming book is about Stoicism. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Are We Training Victimhood?" with Dr. Dina McMillan | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910142/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 16:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910142/</guid><description>Podcast Description The latest in of Permission To Think, a collaboration with the University of Technology Sydney - Josh speaks with social psychologist and the host of the podcast Unmasking The Abuser, Dr. Dina Mcmillan.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Why Eat Animals?" with Jamie Woodhouse | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910143/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jamie Woodhouse is the founder of Sentientism, a movement for granting evidence, reason and compassion to all sentient beings.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Are Men Toxic?" with Clementine Ford | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910144/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 16:00:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910144/</guid><description>Podcast Description Clementine Ford is Australia&amp;rsquo;s most controversial, firebrand feminist. Her latest book is &amp;ldquo;How We Love&amp;rdquo;. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Wait But Why?" with Tim Urban | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910145/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 16:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why are you here? Are we alone in the universe? Will we extinguish ourselves? Why do you procrastinate? And what does social media reveal about your chimpanzee mind? Tens of millions of viewers watch philosopher-blogger king Tim Urban wrestle with these questions in TED Talks and on his comic blog, &amp;lsquo;Wait But Why&amp;rsquo;. Spark up a reefer and join Josh on a cosmic journey into a genius mind.</description></item><item><title>"Is Islam Sexist?" with Dr. Elham Manea | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910146/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 16:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910146/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a Muslim girl wears a burqini to the beach, is that religious freedom, or sexist oppression? Dr. Elham Manea is a Yemeni professor who lives in Switzerland. In this second instalment of &amp;lsquo;Permission to Think&amp;rsquo;, our collaboration with the University of Technology, Sydney, she makes a passionate case for the universality of human rights. This is one helluva chat. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>"Freedom For Girls" with Ayaan Hirsi Ali | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910147/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ayaan Hirsi Ali is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most prominent activists for the rights of women in Islam. She and Josh discuss coronavirus, immigration, fatherless families, Justin Trudeau&amp;hellip; and Dave Chappelle.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Will Bitcoin Fail?" with Mark Carnegie | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910148/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910148/</guid><description>Podcast Description You mightn&amp;rsquo;t expect the founder of a billion-dollar asset management company to be a crypto nerd. But Mark Carnegie is one of the few big-time venture capitalists who actually understands Bitcoin. Most of what you hear about cryptocurrenc&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Corporations Go Woke" with John Safran | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910149/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 16:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Before Ali G and Borat, John Safran blew up Australian TV as a troublemaker extraordinaire. His new book &amp;ldquo;Puff Piece: How Philip Morris set vaping alight (and burned down the English language)&amp;rdquo; is a gonzo glimpse into the bi&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"What Is Creativity?" with Charlotte Wood | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910150/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910150/</guid><description>Podcast Description One of Australia&amp;rsquo;s greatest novelists opens up about the pandemic, Twitter, and finding your voice amid the cacophony. Her new book is The Luminous Solution: Creativity, Resilience and the Inner Life.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Do Universities Punish Free Thinkers?" with Peter Boghossian | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910151/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Peter recently quit his job as an assistant professor of philosophy, saying that universities have sacrificed ideas for ideology. The more he spoke out against illiberalism on campus, the more retaliation he faced. This is the first episode of&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Permission to Think" with Prof. Alan Davison | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910152/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 02:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910152/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Faculty of Arts and Social Sciences at the University of Technology Sydney, where Josh is a Professional Fellow, is launching a series of conversations with world-class intellects. The mastermind behind the series, the Faculty’s D&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Flashback: Norm Macdonald | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910153/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 04:29:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910153/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedy legend Norm Macdonald died today. Revisit his deranged 2015 interview with Josh on HuffPost Live.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"The Miracle of Science" with Tim Flannery | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910154/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Professor Tim Flannery received Australia&amp;rsquo;s highest honour, the Australian Of The Year award, for his work as an ecological historian, explorer and environmentalist. He and Josh discuss tree kangaroos, climate change, anti-vaxxers, and giant dinos&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Todd Sampson - Bodyhacking Mastermind | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910155/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Todd Sampson is an adventurer, advertiser, and award-winning documentary-maker whose new TV show, Mirror Mirror, looks at body image dissatisfaction. Oh, he also climbed Mt Everest before it was cool.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Has Australia Gone Too Far?" with Conor Friedersdorf | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910156/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 10:37:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Americans have been going craycray over Austraystray. From Fox News to social media, images of Australia&amp;rsquo;s lockdowns are being presented as a descent into totalitarianism. The concern-mongering came to a head with an article in T&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"When Will Lockdowns End?" with Dr Stephen Duckett | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910157/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910157/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the Health Department Secretary, Dr Stephen Duckett was Australia&amp;rsquo;s most senior health official. He now runs the health program at the think tank that helped shape Australia&amp;rsquo;s hardline response to COVID-19. Josh is fed up with loc&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus Rant: Vaccines &amp; Lockdowns, Oh My! | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910158/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910158/</guid><description>Podcast Description Record vaccinations in NSW, the National Cabinet plan to re-open, vaccine hesitancy, Covid is here for good. What a time for some more bonus Covid musings.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"In Defence Of Boys" with Christina Hoff Sommers | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910159/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Christina Hoff Sommers is a feminist philosopher. She and Josh discuss gender, boys, cancel culture, and whether she is secretly her own Nixon-loving uncle in disguise.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Are Psychedelics The Answer?" with James Mathison | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910160/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910160/</guid><description>Podcast Description James MathisonPsychedelic TV HostThe former host of Australian Idol makes a case for magic mushrooms in public life. Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Time Management For Mortals" with Oliver Burkeman | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910161/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910161/</guid><description>Podcast Description Oliver Burkeman describes himself is &amp;ldquo;unreasonably obsessed with the question of how people organise their days&amp;rdquo;. He returns to the show for a chat about time, and how to use it. His new book is Four Thousand Weeks.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Story of a Survivor" with Stuart Diver | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910162/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910162/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;Stuart Diver is the sole survivor of Australia&amp;rsquo;s deadliest landslide. He was buried alive by a mountain of frozen sludge for 65 hours. His new podcast is The Elements.&amp;rdquo;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Is Fiction Going Woke?" with Kat Rosenfield | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910163/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 17:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kat is an author and culture critic. She and Josh discuss feminism, sexual assault, Woody Allen, and whether it&amp;rsquo;s okay for a fantasy writer to discriminate against wolf-men.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>BONUS: Josh’s Covid Lockdown Thoughts | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910164/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 17:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910164/</guid><description>Podcast Description With violent freedom protests, bickering states, a bungled vaccine rollout and over half of Australia&amp;rsquo;s population in lockdown, its time to talk.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Malcolm Turnbull | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910165/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Malcolm Turnbull was the 29th Prime Minister of Australia
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Is Politics Beyond Satire?" with Mark Humphries | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910166/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910166/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mark Humphries the preeminent political satirist on Australian TV.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Toxic Taboos" with Jesse Singal | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910167/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910167/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the culture wars, Jesse Singal is either the world&amp;rsquo;s supervillain or its superhero, depending on your point of view. His original Atlantic article is at https://bit.ly/3zZ9Msq and Jonathan Kay&amp;rsquo;s article about the smear campaign against him&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tim Minchin Live - Part 2 | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910168/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Part #2 of Josh&amp;rsquo;s live show with musical comedy legend Tim Minchin.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tim Minchin Live - Part 1 | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910169/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Musical comedy legend Tim Minchin joins Josh live on stage for a sold-out podcast performance.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Botox Feminism?" with Jessie Stephens | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910170/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is it feminist to f*#k with your face? Mamamia’s Jessie Stephens joins Josh on the comfy couch to unleash.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Andrew Denton | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910171/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910171/</guid><description>Podcast Description A giant of Australian media, Andrew Denton is a producer, writer and former television and radio star who now spends much of his time advocating for Voluntary Assisted Dying laws through his organisation Go Gentle Australia and his podcast Better Off D&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Will We Ever Re-Open?" with Prof. Mary-Louise McLaws | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910172/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do lockdowns work? Will we reach herd immunity? Will Australia ever re-open to the world? As Melbourne endures another lockdown, Josh grills Australia&amp;rsquo;s leading epidemiologist, the World Health Organisation advisor Professor Mary-Louise McLaws, ab&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Is Israel Doomed?" with Chloe Valdary | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910173/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910173/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chloe Valdary is the founder of The Theory of Enchantment, an anti-racism program. She and Josh discuss whether Israel can be redeemed.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"The Death of Policy?" with John Hewson | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910174/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910174/</guid><description>Podcast Description He&amp;rsquo;s been called &amp;ldquo;the best Prime Minister Australia never had&amp;rdquo;. As Australia&amp;rsquo;s Opposition Leader, John Hewson lost an unlosable election. Was his problem that he had big ideas?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Did The Left Create Trump?" with David Roth | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910175/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910175/</guid><description>Podcast Description Just before Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s election, Josh sat down with the ferocious critic David Roth to discuss what Trump taught us about populism and power. Did wokeness help create a climate in which Trumpism could grow? And might it again?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jessie Stephens joins the Comfy Couch | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910176/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910176/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jessie is a writer, podcaster, and the assistant head of content at Mamamia. When, she wonders, did bitching on Twitter become a full-time career?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Stop The Boats" with Dr Kim Huynh | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910177/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910177/</guid><description>Podcast Description Border walls. Offshore detention. Kids in cages. What do we do about refugees? Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Abolish Political Parties" with John Opdycke | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910178/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910178/</guid><description>Podcast Description Imagine no Republicans. No Democrats. No Labor or Liberals. Would democracy flourish? Or corrode? John Opdycke is the president of Open Primaries, the non-profit that wants to end the stranglehold of the two-party system. In a hyper-partisan world, is &amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Eddie Izzard | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910179/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910179/</guid><description>Podcast Description One of the Britain&amp;rsquo;s most prolific and influential stand-up comics sits down with Josh to discuss death, humour, marathons, gender fluidity and the American Civil War. Why not?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Is Cancel Culture Real?" with Katie Herzog | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910180/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Katie is a journalist and one of the most insightful commentators on the modern culture wars. co-hosts the podcast &amp;ldquo;Blocked and Reported&amp;rdquo; with Jesse Singal.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"America and Guns" | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910181/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910181/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the past 10 days, more than 20 Americans have been killed by three gunmen in a string of mass shootings. How should we understand America&amp;rsquo;s gun curse&amp;hellip; and is there any way to overcome it?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Darren McMullen joins the Comfy Couch | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910182/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 23:57:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910182/</guid><description>Podcast Description Every other week Uncomfortable Conversations brings you a Comfy Couch episode, in which Josh and a friend chat about whatever is on their mind. This week, the Australian host of The Voice, Darren McMullen, dives deep into the Clubhouse app and finds wo&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"What Is Womanhood?" with Meghan Daum | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910183/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910183/</guid><description>Podcast Description Meghan Daum is a feminist, firebrand, and former opinion columnist for The Los Angeles Times. Her podcast is The Unspeakable.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"What's Wrong With Men?" with Michael Ian Black | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910184/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910184/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael Ian Black is one of America&amp;rsquo;s most popular stand-up comics. His new book is &amp;ldquo;A Better Man: A (Mostly Serious) Letter to My&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"The Madness Of Fame" with Osher Günsberg | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910185/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910185/</guid><description>Podcast Description Osher is Australia&amp;rsquo;s biggest TV star and the host of Australian Idol, The Bachelor, The Bachelorette and The Masked Singer. He opens up&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Are You Awake?" with Sam Harris | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910186/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910186/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris is a neuroscientist, philosopher and New York Times best-selling author. He and Josh wrestle with what it means to be self&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Will The Virus Win?" with virologist Peter Kolchinsky | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910187/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910187/</guid><description>Podcast Description Peter Kolchinsky is a scientist and biotechnology investor, with a deep understanding of how viruses outsmart us. His company, RA&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Is Free Thought Dead?" with Claire Lehmann | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910188/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910188/</guid><description>Podcast Description Claire is the founder and Editor-in-Chief of Quillette, the magazine for dangerous ideas.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Ignore the News!" with Oliver Burkeman | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910189/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910189/</guid><description>Podcast Description Would we all be better off if we knew less about the world? If we took less, not more, responsibility for fixing distant problems? If&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Am I Racist?" with Stan Grant | Uncomfortable Conversations with Josh Szeps</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5663910190/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5663910190/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josh doesn&amp;rsquo;t think he&amp;rsquo;s racist. But maybe that&amp;rsquo;s the surest proof that he is. Should he be cancelled? Should statues be torn down? Are&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>