<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Intrigue on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/intrigue/</link><description>Recent content in Intrigue on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 17:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/intrigue/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Million Dollar Lover – Ep 8: Taking Control | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Things are reaching a head as worries grow about Carolyn’s decision to sell two houses, on a single plot. One of the houses is home to her grandson and his family and Carolyn does not appear to be totally sure about her decision. Her daughters are so concerned that they approach the estate agent begging him to stop things.
If he does not and the sale goes ahead, Dave could be looking at a sizeable amount of money being transferred into his name.</description></item><item><title>Million Dollar Lover – Ep 7: Hidden Lives | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 16:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550002/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the idyllic seaside town of Cayucos, on the Californian coast, property is expensive, a home here can easily cost a million dollars or more. The property boom which has made people of Carolyn’s generation well off, has priced so many out of the market and made it expensive to rent. There is a growing problem with homelessness, a world that Dave knows well. Even now that he is living with Carolyn he has not cut his ties with the homeless and is determined to help when he can.</description></item><item><title>Million Dollar Lover – Ep 6: Unforgettable | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 07:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550003/</guid><description>Podcast Description At first glance Carolyn appears to be a lucky woman who has led a charmed life: loved by her husband and daughters – prosperous and secure. But she has endured great hardship and in this episode it becomes a bit easier to understand why she initially felt so drawn to Dave and what he has come to represent in her life.
For his part, Dave is reluctant to dwell on his childhood, but he undoubtedly had a difficult start in life.</description></item><item><title>Million Dollar Lover – Ep 5: Family Fortunes | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550004/</guid><description>Podcast Description With Carolyn’s encouragement, Dave is making more effort to see his children, including his daughter, Cody. Like her Dad, Cody has struggled with crystal meth addiction and is sometimes sleeping rough in her car as she waits for a place in a recovery unit. She longs for her Dad’s love, but she has been let down by him in the past and cannot really trust that he has changed</description></item><item><title>Million Dollar Lover – Ep 4: Rewards of Love | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550005/</guid><description>Podcast Description One of the consequences of the family falling out about Dave is that Carolyn has decided to take back control of her bank accounts from her daughter, Sally, who had always helped her Mum in the past. Carolyn’s daughters fear that she will start giving money to Dave and that there is nothing they can do about it. In the early days of the relationship, the daughters had got Carolyn and Dave to sign a legal agreement protecting her money and properties.</description></item><item><title>Million Dollar Lover – Ep 3: The Fight | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Carolyn is facing mounting opposition to her relationship with Dave, who is 23 years younger than her and a world away in terms of wealth and lifestyle. She is being forced to make the most difficult choice possible: between her daughters and her new lover. The situation becomes so heated that it finally erupts into violence.
Opposition to Dave makes Carolyn more determined to support him and she decides to take back control of her finances from her daughters.</description></item><item><title>Million Dollar Lover – Ep 2: A Lady Never Tells | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Carolyn had not expected to fall in love at 80 and certainly not to someone 23 years younger. But she has embraced all aspects of her new relationship, including having sex and being open with her daughters about that. Her honesty has not gone down well and even her Pastor, Dale James, is shocked that the couple are now living together in this way.
Concerned about the speed of the relationship and the direction it's taking, Carolyn's daughters turn to the police and outside agencies for help.</description></item><item><title>Million Dollar Lover – Ep 1: Stranger in Town | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Million Dollar Lover is an unlikely love story, recorded in real time as the relationship unfolds between Carolyn, who is 80 and has a valuable property portfolio, and Dave, 57, a former drug addict who is homeless and has spent a decade in jail. The story captured the attention of the BBC Journalist Sue Mitchell, as it was unfolding on her street. She spends a lot of time in California – she married an American and her award-winning journalism has been about the lives of people like Dave who inhabit the dangerous margins of society.</description></item><item><title>Introducing - Intrigue: Million Dollar Lover | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550009/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Million Dollar Lover is an unlikely love story, recorded in real time as the relationship unfolds between Carolyn, who is 80 and has properties worth a few million dollars, and Dave, 57, a former drug addict who is homeless and has spent a decade in jail.
The story captured the attention of the BBC Journalist Sue Mitchell, as it was unfolding on her street. She spends a lot of time in California – she married an American and her award-winning journalism has been about the lives of people like Dave who inhabit the dangerous margins of society.</description></item><item><title>The Immortals - Ep 10: After the Dragon | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550010/</guid><description>Podcast Description The idea of living forever has captivated us for millennia, but rarely do people imagine what would happen the day after the fountain of youth is discovered. Today’s technology entrepreneurs pushing an immortality agenda - through their investments and their influence - seem only focussed on the pursuit.
Whether or not immortality is a distant possibility, how do we cope with living longer en route to forever? Where’s the planning for that?</description></item><item><title>The Immortals - Ep 9: Nerd Rapture | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550011/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550011/</guid><description>Podcast Description The immortalist movement in Silicon Valley shares a lot with evangelical religions, says Dr Emile P Torres, a philosopher and former Nick Bostrom acolyte. In both, he explains, there’s a heaven in which the faithful will experience unsurpassed bliss and delight, and an apocalypse, which will separate out the people who can go there. After a decade at the epicentre of the transhumanist research community, Emile became concerned with the number of apocalyptic stories of techno-utopia that were being shared online.</description></item><item><title>The Immortals - Ep 8: The Prophet | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550012/</guid><description>Podcast Description A new philosphical movement is gathering steam in Silicon Valley, one that promises immortality by using technology to solve the problem of death. This movement is led by Oxford philosopher Nick Bostrom. Professor Bostrom is the author of Fable of the Dragon Tyrant, the original manuscript of the modern immortality movement. It was published in 2005 in the Journal of Medical Ethics as a response to what Bostrom described as the absurdity of the inevitability of accepting ageing and death.</description></item><item><title>The Immortals - Ep 7: Vitalik | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vitalek Buterin is the billionaire founder of Ethereum, one of the most successful blockchains and cryptocurrencies in the world. With his fortune, he is attempting to solve the problem of death by creating a longevity state - which will fast track life everlasting, without the need for regulation. They will crowdsource their longevity solutions and organise them through the blockchain. His north star is the Fable of the Dragon Tyrant.</description></item><item><title>The Immortals - Ep 6: Longevity Escape Velocity | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Many of the longevity innovators in the Valley want to extend human life. But there are others who are trying to eliminate death. A lot of them. The tech billionaires who have never been told ‘no’ are driven to tackle the most insurmountable problems. They believe they can solve death by re-engineering the human in code. Problem is, it’s unlikely to happen in their natural lifetime.
But technology is on their side.</description></item><item><title>The Immortals - Ep 5: The Trial | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Loyal for Dogs is one of the companies in the longevity industry doing serious science. They are well-founded, have a killer team, and a very clear mission: to be the first to get a drug that treats ageing - not just the diseases of ageing, but ageing itself - to pass the rigorous Food and Drug Administration approval process.
Their CEO, Celine Halioua, is a maverick founder whose life has been guided by her ability to work systems.</description></item><item><title>The Immortals - Ep 4: The Hype Cycle | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jesse Karmazin’s Ambrosia Plasma clinic promised the fountain of youth, two litres of young plasma at a time. For a fee, anyone could go to his treatment centre in the redwood forest outside Silicon Valley and receive an infusion. The results - according to Karmazin - were remarkable. Silicon Valley billionaires were rumoured to be queuing up for their young blood. The problem was, the scientists whose work in mice he claimed to be bringing to the people disagreed with what he was doing, and he never backed up his claims with data.</description></item><item><title>The Immortals - Ep 3: The Plasma Clinic | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550017/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Conboys’ experiment gave a young Harvard medical school graduate a big idea. But, there is a big gap between the experiments they did with mice in the lab, and pumping young blood into human beings.
Still, he registered his company, Ambrosia Plasma, on the Food and Drug Administration clinical trials website and began an ambitious human research experiment. For $8,000 in cash, cheque or digital transfer, anyone over the age of 35 could receive two litres of blood plasma from 16-25 year olds in their veins.</description></item><item><title>The Immortals – Ep 2: The Experiment | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mike and Irina Conboy are a couple of tie-dye clad scientists in the bio-engineering department at the University of Berkeley. When they started researching ageing more than 20 years ago at Stanford, the field was nothing more than a spin-off from geroscience - most of their time at the lab bench was spent documenting signs and signals that our bodies are reaching their ends. But in 2005, they published an article in Science that suggested there is hope for reversing ageing our tired old bodies.</description></item><item><title>The Immortals – Ep 1: Dracula | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the last 100 years, we’ve seen global life expectancy double. Could it happen again? Technology reporter and psychologist Aleks Krotoski explores the frontiers of the extreme longevity pioneers. They've made their money in Silicon Valley. And with their technology solutions - PayPal, Facebook, cryptocurrencies - they've ushered in the world that we live in today, with all its unintended consequences. Some of them now want to solve the "</description></item><item><title>Introducing - Intrigue: The Immortals | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550020/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 12:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the last 100 years, we’ve seen global life expectancy double. Could it happen again? In The Immortals, technology reporter and psychologist Aleks Krotoski explores the frontiers of the extreme longevity pioneers. They've made their money in Silicon Valley. And with their technology solutions they've ushered in the world that we live in today. Some of them now want to solve the problem of aging - or even death itself - and they are making bigger strides than we may think.</description></item><item><title>Burning Sun - Ep 6: The Reckoning | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550021/</guid><description>Podcast Description The K-pop stars are jailed for their crimes and some women hope this and other sex abuse scandals might finally spark a real social change. Instead, all it does is fan the growing divisions between men and women. Then the gender war goes mainstream and plays out during the recent presidential election.
For the first time, we give the definitive account of the sex scandals that brought down some of Korea’s biggest K-pop stars.</description></item><item><title>Burning Sun - Ep 5: An Extreme Decision | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Journalist Kang receives a surprising call from K-pop royalty Goo-Hara, who wants to help her with her investigation, as some of the people in the chatroom were her friends. Goo Hara, like many South Korean women is a victim of digital sex crime. Her very public battle in taking a stand against it, receives enormous coverage into her private life and she is mercilessly trolled. It’s too much for her, and will end in tragedy.</description></item><item><title>Burning Sun - Ep 4: Consent | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550023/</guid><description>Podcast Description The scandals are making headlines around the world and K-pop fans react. Jung’s superfan watches as one after another K-pop star is arrested. She has had enough and becomes part of a feminist movement for change against spy cam crimes and misogyny. The woman who made the original allegation against Jung says she regrets not pursuing it. She was viciously trolled after her accusation, and she campaigns to make sure this never happens again to another woman who dares to speak out.</description></item><item><title>Burning Sun - Ep 3 : The Nightclub | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550024/</guid><description>Podcast Description A rival broadcaster reveals a shocking scandal at the exclusive Burning Sun nightclub, co-owned by Seungri – one of the members of Big Bang, and a global K-pop star. There are disturbing accounts emerging of underground rooms where women are taken, and the police investigate. And Journalist Kang is about to drop a bombshell.
For the first time, we give the definitive account of the sex scandals that brought down some of Korea’s biggest K-pop stars.</description></item><item><title>Burning Sun - Ep 2: Kakao Talk | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Someone is holding popstar Jung’s phone in their hands. And what they see on it is shocking. Another journalist Kang Kyung-Yoon gets a tip-off and starts investigating the chat-rooms, and is overwhelmed by the crimes she sees. Sex videos being shared by well-known celebrities, and in some the women are unconscious and being sexually assaulted. She tracks down some of the victims, and the more she digs, the more she uncovers.</description></item><item><title>Burning Sun - Ep 1: The Phone Call | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550026/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550026/</guid><description>Podcast Description “I had no idea how big it was going to be….”
Journalist Park Hyo-sil gets a tip off that music and TV star, Jung Joon-young, is being investigated by police for secretly filming a woman during sex. We find out about Jung, his wholesome, attractive personality and wide popularity. And we meet one of his superfans whose whole life revolves around him. She, like many others, don’t want to believe the accusations against Jung.</description></item><item><title>Introducing - Intrigue: Burning Sun | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550027/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550027/</guid><description>Podcast Description The sex scandals that brought down some of the world’s biggest K-pop Stars. A tale of depravity, power and excess - hidden behind a facade of wholesome pop music.
In 2019 some of the world’s biggest music stars were found guilty of sharing secretly filmed sex videos, others of rape. Korean heart-throbs, used to being mobbed by adoring female fans, had been videoing themselves committing acts of terrible abuse and sharing them on group chats with each other.</description></item><item><title>Mayday - Bonus: The Evidence Gatherers | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 19:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550028/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a secret location in a European city is an archive that contains over a million documents. It’s run by a tough-talking Canadian, Bill Wiley, who set up an evidence-gathering organisation funded by Western governments. Using undercover criminal investigators operating inside a war zone, the Commission for International Justice and Accountability (CIJA) has spent the last eight years extracting official documents from Syria. Wiley says that evidence will prove that the Assad regime has been responsible for a campaign of torture and murder against its own people.</description></item><item><title>Mayday - Bonus: Update | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550029/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550029/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Evidence Gatherers, a new episode of Mayday coming soon, available from 6 April.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mayday - Bonus: The Canister on the Bed | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550030/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550030/</guid><description>Podcast Description “The crime scene had been left unguarded for two weeks”. What really happened in the Douma massacre? This episode is a diversion from the story of the life and death of James Le Mesurier. It’s about one of the most contested events in the war - the chemical attack in the town of Douma in 2018. Unravelling what really happened there takes us to the heart of the global race to control the narrative of the Syrian war.</description></item><item><title>Mayday - Ep10: The Second Casualty | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550031/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 14:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550031/</guid><description>Podcast Description “They will be targeted for the rest of their lives.” Where does that leave everyone else? When James Le Mesurier fell to his death in Turkey in 2019 he left behind a tangle of truths and lies. Mayday tells the extraordinary real story of the man who organised the White Helmets – rescuers who film themselves pulling survivors from bombed out buildings in rebel-held areas of Syria – and investigates claims that, far from being heroes, they are part of a very elaborate hoax.</description></item><item><title>Mayday - Ep9: The Boiling Frog | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550032/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 06:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550032/</guid><description>Podcast Description “My love it’s 10 times worse than we thought.” Things start to unravel. When James Le Mesurier fell to his death in Turkey in 2019 he left behind a tangle of truths and lies. Mayday tells the extraordinary real story of the man who organised the White Helmets – rescuers who film themselves pulling survivors from bombed out buildings in rebel-held areas of Syria – and investigates claims that, far from being heroes, they are part of a very elaborate hoax.</description></item><item><title>Mayday - Ep8: Operation Magic Carpet | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550033/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 06:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550033/</guid><description>Podcast Description “I had to do it because my colleagues faced death.” Now the rescuers need saving. When James Le Mesurier fell to his death in Turkey in 2019 he left behind a tangle of truths and lies. Mayday tells the extraordinary real story of the man who organised the White Helmets – rescuers who film themselves pulling survivors from bombed out buildings in rebel-held areas of Syria – and investigates claims that, far from being heroes, they are part of a very elaborate hoax.</description></item><item><title>Mayday - Ep7: Managed Massacres | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550034/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 06:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550034/</guid><description>Podcast Description “ I have these epiphanies all the time, especially if I had anchovies on my pizza..” Could the White Helmets be involved in staging chemical attacks? When James Le Mesurier fell to his death in Turkey in 2019 he left behind a tangle of truths and lies. Mayday tells the extraordinary real story of the man who organised the White Helmets – rescuers who film themselves pulling survivors from bombed out buildings in rebel-held areas of Syria – and investigates claims that, far from being heroes, they are part of a very elaborate hoax.</description></item><item><title>Mayday - Ep6: The One With Sean Penn | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550035/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 06:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550035/</guid><description>Podcast Description “I went to meet with Assad to see what kind of access we might get.” James is accused of a horrific crime. When James Le Mesurier fell to his death in Turkey in 2019 he left behind a tangle of truths and lies. Mayday tells the extraordinary real story of the man who organised the White Helmets – rescuers who film themselves pulling survivors from bombed out buildings in rebel-held areas of Syria – and investigates claims that, far from being heroes, they are part of a very elaborate hoax.</description></item><item><title>Mayday - Ep5: God Bless Syria | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550036/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 06:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550036/</guid><description>Podcast Description “He hadn’t really understood that he would be singled out.” How to tell who the jihadists are. When James Le Mesurier fell to his death in Turkey in 2019 he left behind a tangle of truths and lies. Mayday tells the extraordinary real story of the man who organised the White Helmets – rescuers who film themselves pulling survivors from bombed out buildings in rebel-held areas of Syria – and investigates claims that, far from being heroes, they are part of a very elaborate hoax.</description></item><item><title>Mayday - Ep4: Hoax Producers | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550037/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 06:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550037/</guid><description>Podcast Description “There’s something addictive about uncovering the world as it really is.” The allegations begin. When James Le Mesurier fell to his death in Turkey in 2019 he left behind a tangle of truths and lies. Mayday tells the extraordinary real story of the man who organised the White Helmets – rescuers who film themselves pulling survivors from bombed out buildings in rebel-held areas of Syria – and investigates claims that, far from being heroes, they are part of a very elaborate hoax.</description></item><item><title>Mayday - Ep3: The Miracle Baby | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550038/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 06:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550038/</guid><description>Podcast Description “This was just one baby out of thousands and thousands of other babies.” How James got involved in a war. When he fell to his death in Turkey in 2019 James Le Mesurier left behind a tangle of truths and lies. Mayday tells the extraordinary real story of the man who organised the White Helmets – rescuers who film themselves pulling survivors from bombed out buildings in rebel-held areas of Syria – and investigates claims that, far from being heroes, they are part of a very elaborate hoax.</description></item><item><title>Mayday - Ep2: The Pizza in the Suitcase | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550039/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550039/</guid><description>Podcast Description “I was naked having a strip search and I just know James was somewhere laughing his head off.” Who was James Le Mesurier? When he fell to his death in Turkey in 2019 James Le Mesurier left behind a tangle of truths and lies. Mayday tells the extraordinary real story of the man who organised the White Helmets – rescuers who film themselves pulling survivors from bombed out buildings in rebel-held areas of Syria – and investigates claims that, far from being heroes, they are part of a very elaborate hoax.</description></item><item><title>Mayday - Ep1: On the Ledge | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550040/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550040/</guid><description>Podcast Description “The story sounds like a purely English murder.” The rumour mill starts over who or what killed James Le Mesurier. When he fell to his death in Turkey in 2019 James Le Mesurier left behind a tangle of truths and lies. Mayday tells the extraordinary real story of the man who organised the White Helmets – rescuers who film themselves pulling survivors from bombed out buildings in rebel-held areas of Syria – and investigates claims that, far from being heroes, they are part of a very elaborate hoax.</description></item><item><title>Introduction to Mayday | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550041/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 14:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550041/</guid><description>Podcast Description When James Le Mesurier fell to his death in Turkey in 2019 he left behind a tangle of truths and lies. Mayday tells the extraordinary real story of the man who organised the White Helmets – rescuers who film themselves pulling survivors from bombed out buildings in rebel-held areas of Syria – and investigates claims that, far from being heroes, they are part of a very elaborate hoax. James Le Mesurier – his detractors say – was a British secret agent, pulling the strings.</description></item><item><title>Coming soon to Intrigue: Mayday | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550042/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550042/</guid><description>Podcast Description When James Le Mesurier fell to his death he left behind a tangle of truths and lies. Hear the full story from 9 November.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tunnel 29 - Ep10: The Shoes | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550043/</guid><description>Podcast Description “I started dancing with Eveline.” A final twist in the final chapter.
Thirty years after the fall of the Berlin Wall, Helena Merriman tells the extraordinary true story of a man who dug a tunnel into the East, right under the feet of border guards, to help friends, family and strangers escape. The series is based on original interviews with the survivors as well as thousands of documents from the Stasi archives and recordings from the tunnel.</description></item><item><title>Tunnel 29 - Ep9: The Signal | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550044/</guid><description>Podcast Description “If you don’t have a coffee, then bring me a cognac.” Ellen's plan is derailed.
Thirty years after the fall of the Berlin Wall, Helena Merriman tells the extraordinary true story of a man who dug a tunnel into the East, right under the feet of border guards, to help friends, family and strangers escape. The series is based on original interviews with the survivors as well as thousands of documents from the Stasi archives and recordings from the tunnel.</description></item><item><title>Tunnel 29 - Ep8: The Messenger | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550045/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550045/</guid><description>Podcast Description I said "ok, I'll do it”. Ellen, Mimmo's girlfriend, agrees to play a dangerous role.
Thirty years after the fall of the Berlin Wall, Helena Merriman tells the extraordinary true story of a man who dug a tunnel into the East, right under the feet of border guards, to help friends, family and strangers escape. The series is based on original interviews with the survivors as well as thousands of documents from the Stasi archives and recordings from the tunnel.</description></item><item><title>Tunnel 29 - Ep7: The Interrogation | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550046/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550046/</guid><description>Podcast Description “That’s the first time I saw her again.” Wolfdieter's show trial begins.
Thirty years after the fall of the Berlin Wall, Helena Merriman tells the extraordinary true story of a man who dug a tunnel into the East, right under the feet of border guards, to help friends, family and strangers escape. The series is based on original interviews with the survivors as well as thousands of documents from the Stasi archives and recordings from the tunnel.</description></item><item><title>Tunnel 29 - Ep6: The Gun | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550047/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550047/</guid><description>Podcast Description “And then my interrogation began.” The escape operation unravels.
Thirty years after the fall of the Berlin Wall, Helena Merriman tells the extraordinary true story of a man who dug a tunnel into the East, right under the feet of border guards, to help friends, family and strangers escape. The series is based on original interviews with the survivors as well as thousands of documents from the Stasi archives and recordings from the tunnel.</description></item><item><title>Tunnel 29 - Ep5: The Trap | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550048/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 15:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550048/</guid><description>Podcast Description “We had no chance to be together.” The diggers hatch a new plan, unaware the Stasi are onto them.
Thirty years after the fall of the Berlin Wall, Helena Merriman tells the extraordinary true story of a man who dug a tunnel into the East, right under the feet of border guards, to help friends, family and strangers escape. The series is based on original interviews with the survivors as well as thousands of documents from the Stasi archives and recordings from the tunnel.</description></item><item><title>Tunnel 29 - Ep4: The Death Strip | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550049/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550049/</guid><description>Podcast Description “If we could hear them, they could hear us.” The diggers reach the terrifying death strip.
Thirty years after the fall of the Berlin Wall, Helena Merriman tells the extraordinary true story of a man who dug a tunnel into the East, right under the feet of border guards, to help friends, family and strangers escape. The series is based on original interviews with the survivors as well as thousands of documents from the Stasi archives and recordings from the tunnel.</description></item><item><title>Tunnel 29 - Ep3: The Deal | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550050/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 14:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550050/</guid><description>Podcast Description “We have a tunnel.” The diggers are on the hunt for money and make an unlikely alliance.
Thirty years after the fall of the Berlin Wall, Helena Merriman tells the extraordinary true story of a man who dug a tunnel into the East, right under the feet of border guards, to help friends, family and strangers escape. The series is based on original interviews with the survivors as well as thousands of documents from the Stasi archives and recordings from the tunnel.</description></item><item><title>Tunnel 29 - Ep2: The Spy | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550051/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550051/</guid><description>Podcast Description “I choose the codename Fred.” A hairdresser becomes a Stasi spy.
Thirty years after the fall of the Berlin Wall, Helena Merriman tells the extraordinary true story of a man who dug a tunnel into the East, right under the feet of border guards, to help friends, family and strangers escape. The series is based on original interviews with the survivors as well as thousands of documents from the Stasi archives and recordings from the tunnel.</description></item><item><title>Tunnel 29 - Ep1: The Escape | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550052/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 14:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550052/</guid><description>Podcast Description “I didn’t want to be a part of this new world.” Joachim is on holiday in East Germany when he hears Berlin is to be divided. The wall is built and the escapes begin. Joachim has to decide whether he'll be among them.
Thirty years after the fall of the Berlin Wall, Helena Merriman tells the extraordinary true story of a man who dug a tunnel into the East, right under the feet of border guards, to help friends, family and strangers escape.</description></item><item><title>Tunnel 29 full-length trailer | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550053/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Thirty years after the fall of the Berlin Wall, Helena Merriman tells the extraordinary true story of a man who dug a tunnel into the East, right under the feet of border guards, to help friends, family and strangers escape. The series is based on original interviews with the survivors as well as thousands of documents from the Stasi archives and recordings from the tunnel. Producer &amp;amp; Presenter: Helena Merriman</description></item><item><title>Coming soon... Tunnel 29 | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550054/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 12:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Introducing the true story of an extraordinary escape.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Ratline - Bonus: Stephen Fry meets Philippe Sands | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550055/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550055/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a bonus episode of Intrigue: The Ratline, Stephen Fry interviews Philippe Sands in front of an audience at the BBC Radio Theatre in London. They discuss a range of issues brought up by the series including historical responsibility and the nature of evil. Plus as a special extra, there is a full version of The Ratline theme music by Catrin Finch and Sekou Keita.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Ratline – Ep.10: Persilschein | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550056/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Philippe and the team work out the identity of the mysterious man Otto lunched with on Lake Albano, and discover he too is connected with the Nazi Bishop. They take a trip to the lake to meet the Priest who buried the man and he reveals an unbelievable family secret.
A story of life, love and a curious death told by writer and barrister, Philippe Sands. A cold war mystery that reveals shadowy forces at work and consequences that stretch across generations.</description></item><item><title>The Ratline – Ep.9: The Lucids | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550057/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Philippe travels to Albuquerque to meet Tom Lucid Jnr, the son of the CIA agent who recruited Karl Hass, chief source on Project Los Angeles and the man Otto had lunch with on Lake Albano. How much does he know about his father's role in recruiting Nazis and a close relative in Geneva?
A story of life, love and a curious death told by writer and barrister, Philippe Sands.</description></item><item><title>The Ratline – Ep.8: Nest of Spies | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550058/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Philippe and the team work out the identity of the mysterious man Otto lunched with on Lake Albano, and discover he too is connected with the Nazi Bishop. They take a trip to the lake to meet the Priest who buried the man and he reveals an unbelievable family secret.
A story of life, love and a curious death told by writer and barrister, Philippe Sands. A cold war mystery that reveals shadowy forces at work and consequences that stretch across generations.</description></item><item><title>The Ratline – Ep.7: The Nazi Bishop | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550059/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Philippe accesses the Vatican archives to find out about Otto's protector in Rome, the man who was by his side as he lay dying, Alois Hudal. Hudal's archivist reveals something extraordinary.
A story of life, love and a curious death told by writer and barrister, Philippe Sands. A cold war mystery that reveals shadowy forces at work and consequences that stretch across generations. Producer: Gemma Newby
Sound Design: Neil Churchill</description></item><item><title>The Ratline – Ep.6: The men who murdered Nazis | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550060/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Otto contracts a strange illness and Charlotte rushes to Rome to be by his side. Philippe talks to an old friend who was working for British intelligence in 1949 and explores who might have been after Otto and why.
A story of life, love and a curious death told by writer and barrister, Philippe Sands. A cold war mystery that reveals shadowy forces at work and consequences that stretch across generations.</description></item><item><title>The Ratline – Ep.5: La Forza del Destino | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550061/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Midnight. Rome. 1949. Otto arrives in the eternal city, penniless, homeless, searching for a way out to Argentina. He's also unwittingly found himself in the middle of a battle between East and West. He finds employment and makes a trip out of the city to the countryside.
The Ratline is a story of a curious death, political intrigue, spies, Nazi hunters, shadowy forces in the Vatican and a son grappling with the sins of his father.</description></item><item><title>The Ratline – Ep.4: Where's Otto? | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550062/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550062/</guid><description>Podcast Description The war is over and Otto has disappeared. Whilst his friends are committing suicide or being tried for mass murder Otto has escaped high into the mountains with the help of a young SS soldier. Meanwhile Charlotte is working on getting him out of Austria.
A story of life, love and a curious death told by writer and barrister, Philippe Sands. A cold war mystery that reveals shadowy forces at work and consequences that stretch across generations.</description></item><item><title>The Ratline – Ep.3: A lot going on in Lemberg | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550063/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Whilst Charlotte Wachter and her children spend the summer in Zell am See, Otto is in Lemberg overseeing the 'Grosse Aktion' - the mass deportation of Jews to concentration camps.
The Ratline is a story of a curious death, political intrigue, spies, Nazi hunters, shadowy forces in the Vatican and a son grappling with the sins of his father. Producer: Gemma Newby
Sound Design: Neil Churchill
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Ratline – Ep.2: Meet The Wachters | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550064/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550064/</guid><description>Podcast Description In episode two of the Ratline we meet the Wachters, Otto and Charlotte and chart their ascent to power. Otto's job takes the family to Krakow and on to Galicia, where he makes some dubious decisions, and Horst continues to maintain his father's innocence. The Ratline is a story of a curious death, political intrigue, spies, Nazi hunters, shadowy forces in the Vatican and a son grappling with the sins of his father.</description></item><item><title>The Ratline – Ep.1: Secrets in the Castle | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550065/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Philippe Sands investigates the mysterious disappearance of senior Nazi, Otto Wachter, who was indicted for mass murder. The Ratline is a story of a curious death, political intrigue, spies, Nazi hunters, shadowy forces in the Vatican and a son grappling with the sins of his father. In episode one of this ten part series we travel to a castle outside Vienna to meet an old man who believes his Nazi father was murdered, and a voice from the past offers up clues to how it might have happened.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to Intrigue: The Ratline | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550066/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 13:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550066/</guid><description>Podcast Description A story of love, denial and a curious death presented by Philippe Sands. Hear the first episode on 18 Sept 2018.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Murder in the Lucky Holiday Hotel - Episode 5 | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550067/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550067/</guid><description>Podcast Description The series finale reveals who benefitted from the murder of a British man in China. The continuing true story of death, sex and Chinese elite politics
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Murder in the Lucky Holiday Hotel - Episode 4 | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550068/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550068/</guid><description>Podcast Description A spectacular show trial exposes the lavish lifestyle of China’s elite. The continuing true story of death, sex and elite politics in China.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Murder in the Lucky Holiday Hotel - Episode 3 | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550069/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550069/</guid><description>Podcast Description The action picks up as Neil Heywood arrives in Chongqing, where an "iron-blooded" police chief holds sway. The continuing true story of death, sex and elite politics in China.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Murder in the Lucky Holiday Hotel - Episode 2 | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550070/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550070/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’ve met the mayor’s wife. Now, meet the mayor, “the main man” who takes this story to the national stage. The continuing true story of death, sex and elite politics in China.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Murder in the Lucky Holiday Hotel - Episode 1 | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550071/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550071/</guid><description>Podcast Description A true story of death, sex and elite politics in China
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Welcome to Intrigue: Murder in the Lucky Holiday Hotel | Intrigue</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2767550072/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2017 15:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2767550072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to this new BBC podcast. The first episode will be published on 17 Feb 2017.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>