<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Very Scary People on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/very-scary-people/</link><description>Recent content in Very Scary People on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 08:00:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/very-scary-people/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>S2 Ep.7: Ken vs. Barbie | Very Scary People</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9397780015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 08:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9397780015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Paul Bernardo finally gets his day in court and the trial becomes a national spectacle. With limited physical evidence of murder, it’s Karla’s word again his. Host Donnie Wahlberg takes us through the nearly 5-month trial that captivated all of Canada and the aftermath of the violent saga of the Ken and Barbie Killers.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep.6: Tammy Homolka | Very Scary People</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9397780014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 08:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9397780014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Now that long sought-after video tapes are finally in the hands of the police. Karla has one final, shocking confession that leads investigators to revisit the night of her little sister Tammy’s untimely death. It turns out, Tammy’s death wasn’t an accident.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep.5: The Videotapes | Very Scary People</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9397780013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 08:00:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9397780013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Law enforcement gain a very helpful tip. They tirelessly search Karla and Paul’s little pink house for video tape evidence that would prove all of their suspicions and be enough to convict Paul of murder. As the investigation develops, it turns out that Karla isn’t as innocent as she’s let on. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep.4: The DNA Sample | Very Scary People</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9397780001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9397780001/</guid><description>Podcast Description A long-shelved DNA sample in the case of the Scarborough Rapist is finally tested. The sample matches Paul Bernardo. And after a physically violent dispute between Karla and Paul that sends Karla to the hospital, the police get more details about just how monstrous Paul can be. The police start to zero in on Paul for the murders of Leslie and Kristen. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep.3: Kristen French | Very Scary People</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9397780002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 07:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9397780002/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Saint Catharine’s community is rattled by a tragedy of their own. Sixteen-year-old, Kristen French, goes missing while walking home from school. The case quickly draws national attention and sparks a massive search effort. Eerie similarities are found between Kristen’s case and another teenage girl, Leslie Mahaffy, who was murdered just a year earlier.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep.2: Call 911 | Very Scary People</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9397780003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 07:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9397780003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Paul Bernardo is questioned by police after receiving multiple anonymous tips in response to a composite sketch of the Scarborough Rapist published in the local newspaper. At the same time, he’s falling in love with Karla Homolka and spending time with her family in the quiet town of St. Catharines. During their first holiday together, tragedy strikes close to home, her sister is found dead. Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep.1: Blond Hair Blue Eyes | Very Scary People</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9397780004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 07:00:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9397780004/</guid><description>Podcast Description A beautiful young couple, Karla Homolka and Paul Bernardo, are getting married on the shores of Lake Ontario in the suburbs of Toronto, Canada. Meanwhile, in the neighboring town of Scarborough, locals are gripped with fear and the police are at a loss: a serial rapist is at large, showing no signs of stopping. Host Donnie Wahlberg traces the perpetrator&amp;rsquo;s steps, only to find them leading back to the blond-haired blue-eyed groom.</description></item><item><title>Introducing Very Scary People: The Ken and Barbie Killers | Very Scary People</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9397780005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 07:00:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9397780005/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the late-80s and early 90s, the quaint suburbs of Toronto, Canada were blind-sided by an unprecedented flurry of violent crimes: a serial rapist on the loose and young girls vanishing… only to later discover their dead bodies, dismembered.&amp;nbsp; As separate investigations developed, police across the region followed leads pointing to a young, blond-haired blue-eyed duo.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Over seven episodes, host Donnie Wahlberg traces the twisted path of Paul Bernardo and Karla Homolka – a couple from Toronto that appeared loving and wholesome but had everybody fooled.</description></item><item><title>S1 Ep.6: Everyone Loves A Good Ghost Story | Very Scary People</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9397780006/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9397780006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Found guilty of killing his parents and siblings in their home, Ron DeFeo Jr. is sentenced to six counts of second-degree murder. But the convicted killer finds new fame in prison. Back in Amityville, the story of the gruesome massacre at 112 Ocean Avenue is taking on a life of its own. Host Donnie Wahlberg untangles the story of how the Dutch colonial home that was once a bloody crime scene becomes a permanent piece of horror &amp;mdash; and pop culture &amp;mdash; history.</description></item><item><title>S1 Ep.5: The People v. Ronald DeFeo Jr. | Very Scary People</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9397780007/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9397780007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nearly a year after the grisly Amityville murders, Ron &amp;ldquo;Butch&amp;rdquo; DeFeo Jr.'s fate would rest in the hands of a New York jury. But even in front of a judge, Ron Jr. was a chameleon; his story continued to evolve. One conflicted juror recounts the disturbing trial while host Donnie Wahlberg considers the question: Will the inconsistencies in Ron Jr.'s story spare him from life behind bars?
To learn more about how HLN protects listener privacy, visit cnn.</description></item><item><title>S1 Ep.4: The Confession | Very Scary People</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9397780008/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9397780008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amityville detectives shift all their attention to a single suspect in the murders of the DeFeo family: the oldest son, Ron DeFeo Jr. Following hours of intense interrogation, the sole surviving family member breaks. But Ron Jr.'s confession dredged up new details, complicated questions, and more secrets.
To learn more about how HLN protects listener privacy, visit cnn.com/privacy
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S1 Ep.3: Mob Ties | Very Scary People</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9397780009/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9397780009/</guid><description>Podcast Description As police continue their search for the killer of the DeFeos in Amityville, they discover the family's connections to organized crime. Host Donnie Wahlberg reveals how these mob ties came to light. It's a turning point in the case which brings police one step closer to their top suspect.
To learn more about how HLN protects listener privacy, visit cnn.com/privacy
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>S1 Ep.2: Meet The DeFeos | Very Scary People</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9397780010/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9397780010/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the community reels from the shocking DeFeo murders, residents pack an Amityville church to mourn the loss of the family. Host Donnie Wahlberg dives deep into DeFeo history, only to find out that this picture-perfect family had very violent secrets.
To learn more about how HLN protects listener privacy, visit cnn.com/privacy
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S1 Ep. 1: Small Town Murder | Very Scary People</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9397780011/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9397780011/</guid><description>Podcast Description After Ron DeFeo Jr. finds his parents and younger siblings dead in their Amityville, New York, home, police begin to search for the killer. Host Donnie Wahlberg and local journalist Joel Martin revisit that horrific evening in 1974, the crime scene and the investigation &amp;mdash; all in hopes of answering a question heavy on residents' minds: &amp;ldquo;Who would murder an entire family in the dead of night?&amp;rdquo;
To learn more about how HLN protects listener privacy, visit cnn.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Very Scary People | Very Scary People</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9397780012/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 21:25:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9397780012/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1974, a mass murder shook the sleepy waterfront town of Amityville, New&amp;nbsp;York. One November night, police found the DeFeo family shot dead, face&amp;nbsp;down in their beds. Only one survived: Ron DeFeo Jr., the eldest son with a&amp;nbsp;troubled past. In this six-part series, host Donnie Wahlberg untangles the dark&amp;nbsp;and complicated story of what happened that&amp;nbsp;night, and&amp;nbsp;unearths how&amp;nbsp;these&amp;nbsp;grisly murders sparked an infamous haunted tale.
Starting March 18, 2022
To learn more about how HLN protects listener privacy, visit cnn.</description></item></channel></rss>