<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Today Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-today-podcast/</link><description>Recent content in The Today Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:01:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-today-podcast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Esther Rantzen on a Christmas she did not expect to see | The Today Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3173720017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3173720017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dame Esther Rantzen is a broadcasting legend, responsible for some of the most famous moments in television history. She blazoned a trail for women in the media and has and has made a huge impact with her charity campaign work.
Today she is continuing to make headlines for her battle with stage-four lung cancer. In a remarkably candid interview with Amol and Nick, she reflects on her career and opens up about the impact the disease has had on her life.</description></item><item><title>Is Putin in danger of winning in Ukraine? | The Today Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3173720001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 18:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3173720001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ukraine is back in the news with Vladimir Putin holding his first press conference since the outbreak of war. But in the last few weeks the story has fallen from the top of the news agenda – with many of The Today Podcast listeners emailing to ask why.
Amol and Nick explain – and talk to Yale University historian Professor Timothy Snyder, one of the world’s leading experts in Russian and Ukrainian history.</description></item><item><title>Sunk! Is Sunak’s Tory Party over? | The Today Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3173720002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3173720002/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been a bruising 24 hours for Rishi Sunak including a ministerial resignation, emergency prime ministerial press conference and a former home secretary now firmly on manoeuvres. Amol and Nick discuss the Today programme’s exclusive interview with that former home secretary, Suella Braverman, and analyse how much trouble Sunak is now in. Will there be a leadership challenge?
As he’s shoring up his leadership the former prime minister Boris Johnson is trying to secure his legacy at the Covid Inquiry.</description></item><item><title>Why Generation Rent are so angry | The Today Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3173720003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 17:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3173720003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Private rents are soaring, homes to rent are in steep decline, house building has stalled. No wonder young people are full of rage about their chances of getting onto the housing ladder.
On this week’s podcast Amol and Nick take a deep dive into what’s going wrong with housing in the UK – and what can be done to fix it.
They’re joined by Angela Rayner, Labour’s deputy leader, who will be tasked with fixing the housing crisis if Labour win the next general election.</description></item><item><title>Are these tax cuts for real? | The Today Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3173720004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 17:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3173720004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who’s right? Are these really the biggest tax cuts since the 1980s? Or are we paying more tax than ever? Or might both things be true? Amol and Nick look through the headlines of a complicated Autumn Statement and ask whether these tax cuts are real.
They talk to former chancellor Ken Clarke about economic credibility, and they examine the tax-and-spend dividing lines between Labour and the Conservatives ahead of the election.</description></item><item><title>James May: On Top Gear, tea and driverless cars | The Today Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3173720005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 06:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3173720005/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this extra edition of The Today Podcast, James May talks to Amol and Nick about Top Gear, tea and driverless cars, as he is announced as one of this year's Today programme guest editors.
James, who is one of the presenters of The Grand Tour and a former presenter of Top Gear, will take the editorial reins and make a programme with the Today team this Christmas and he's got some interesting ideas about what he would like to explore.</description></item><item><title>Revolting! How much trouble are Sunak and Starmer in? | The Today Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3173720006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 07:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3173720006/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's been a week of turmoil in British politics culminating in the government losing its Rwanda case then taking on the Supreme Court – and Labour losing ten from its frontbench following a mass rebellion over Gaza.
There’s plenty for Amol and Nick to get stuck into this week on The Today Podcast as they assess the political landscape and ask, how much trouble are Rishi Sunak and Keir Starmer in?</description></item><item><title>David Cameron In, Suella Braverman Out | The Today Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3173720007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3173720007/</guid><description>Podcast Description This morning on the Today programme the news of the sacking Suella Braverman broke and we heard the surprise announcement that former Prime Minister David Cameron would be the Foreign Secretary.
In this emergency episode of The Today Podcast Amol and Nick discuss Rishi Sunak’s reshuffle.
Former Education Secretary Baroness Nicky Morgan, former Northern Ireland Secretary Theresa Villiers MP and former Deputy Prime Minister Lord Heseltine are all on hand to give their take on where this leaves the Conservative Party.</description></item><item><title>The Politics of Protest: Suella Braverman vs the police | The Today Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3173720008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 17:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3173720008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why did the Home Secretary write a newspaper column that puts her on a collision course with both the UK’s most senior police officer… and seemingly the prime minister?
In this week’s podcast Amol and Nick look at the politics of protest – and what exactly Suella Braverman is trying to achieve by taking on the police, ahead of a proposed march through London on Armistice Day calling for a ceasefire in Gaza.</description></item><item><title>Covidshambles: The human cost of chaos in No 10 | The Today Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3173720009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 02:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3173720009/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been an explosive week of evidence at the Covid inquiry. Government by WhatsApp and chaotic scenes at Downing Street. Amol and Nick discuss how badly the UK handled Covid and whether a different approach would have fundamentally altered the response and outcomes of the pandemic. Joining them in The Today Podcast studio is Louise Casey, who spent nearly 20 years in the civil service and who has run a range of inquiries, .</description></item><item><title>Your Questions Answered | The Today Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3173720010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 06:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3173720010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who decides which presenter does which interview on BBC Radio 4's Today programme? Does it create any tensions? In a busy newsroom how do you work out the facts?
Amol and Nick answer these listener questions and others in this bonus edition of The Today Podcast.
If you would like a question answering, get in touch by sending us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 4346 or email us Today@bbc.</description></item><item><title>What hope for peace? | The Today Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3173720011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3173720011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amol and Nick turn their attention this week to what conditions will need to be reached before Israelis and Palestinians are able to sit down with each other in search of a lasting settlement.
They speak to Yossi Beilin and Hiba Husseini, who have spent decades negotiating peace – finding their hopes dashed each time but becoming friends with each other in the process.
And they look at what’s happened at the Covid Inquiry and what’s coming up next week.</description></item><item><title>What Is This War Really About? | The Today Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3173720012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3173720012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amol and Nick discuss how the war in Israel and Gaza shows two competing versions of history. They look at what’s at stake and why it matters. They are joined in The Today Podcast studio by historian Niall Ferguson to discuss how critical a moment this is for the region and wider world. Episodes land every Thursday. Subscribe to The Today Podcast to get Amol and Nick's take on the biggest stories of the week.</description></item><item><title>Horror in Israel and Gaza - What next? | The Today Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3173720013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3173720013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Listen to Amol and Nick reflect on the Israel and Gaza conflict as they talk about what it might mean for the wider world. They talk to Martha, who’s spent much of this week presenting Radio 4’s Today from Jerusalem. The former chief of MI6, Sir Alex Younger is in ‘The Today Podcast’ studio giving his take on intelligence failures in the region and discussing his fears for what will happen next.</description></item><item><title>I cried after presenting my first Today programme | The Today Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3173720014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3173720014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amol and Nick are two of the BBC’s most experienced journalists. In this bonus episode of The Today Podcast they talk through their first day presenting Radio 4’s Today.
They remember the emotion of those first mornings as well as their favourite moments on the UK’s most influential radio news programme.
Also: find out what happens when a guest oversleeps and why Nick found himself running between Downing Street and a studio when Today was on air.</description></item><item><title>Can Rishi Sunak win it for the Tories? | The Today Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3173720015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 02:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3173720015/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Today Programme’s got the only interview with the prime minister recorded after his conference speech. What sort of a week has it been for Rishi Sunak and the Conservatives? Join Amol Rajan and Nick Robinson as they ask whether Rishi Sunak can lead his party to a 5th electoral victory and give their take on a strange week in politics.
Jane Green, professor of politics at Oxford University is in The Today Podcast studio with the latest polling and writer Armando Iannucci joins us to talk about the weirdness of party conferences and that time he nearly got a story on the Today programme.</description></item><item><title>Introducing The Today Podcast | The Today Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3173720016/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 15:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3173720016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Introducing The Today Podcast. A new weekly podcast from the team behind the UK's most influential radio news programme. Join Amol, Nick and guests every Thursday as they give their take on the biggest stories of the week, with insights from behind the scenes at Radio 4's Today. The first episode of The Today Podcast drops on October 5th. Subscribe on BBC Sounds. Get in touch by sending us a message or voice note via WhatsApp to +44 330 123 4346 or email Today@bbc.</description></item></channel></rss>