<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ologies with Alie Ward on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/ologies-with-alie-ward/</link><description>Recent content in Ologies with Alie Ward on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 16:30:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/ologies-with-alie-ward/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Quasithanatology (NEAR-DEATH EXPERIENCES) with Bruce Greyson | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860365/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 16:30:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860365/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tunnels of light. Unconditional love. Visions of dead aunts. And a lot of questions. What happens when you die… or almost die? GOOD QUESTION. Dr. Bruce Greyson chats about about brain activity during death, accounts from patients, out of body experiments, time dilation, the Swiss Alps, deathbed visions, accidental morgue visits, neurotransmitters, party drugs, religion vs. spirituality, and what matters most in life. As a world-renowned and respected psychiatrist and neurobiologist, he’s sought out answers for four decades and shares what we know – and don’t know – about the border of alive and unalive.</description></item><item><title>Smologies #33: SCORPIONS with Lauren Esposito | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860364/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860364/</guid><description>Podcast Description Scorpions: the victims of undue shade. A handful of people on planet Earth have a PhD in scorpions and Dr. Lauren Esposito is one of them. She spills the beans on how venom works, what&amp;rsquo;s up with the blacklight glow effect, how dangerous they really are, what all the movies get wrong, the best names for scorpions, where she&amp;rsquo;s traveled to look under rocks, where a scorpion&amp;rsquo;s butt is, if scorpions dance (SPOILER: YES), what good mothers they are, and how big they used to be millions of years ago.</description></item><item><title>Syndesiology (CONNECTIONS) with James Burke | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860363/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 04:03:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860363/</guid><description>Podcast Description He’s the guy pointing to a NASA launch behind him, in the most legendary shot in television history. He’s a science historian and Apollo Program correspondent. He’s the creator, host, and writer of the long-running program “Connections.” He is a science communication hero to millions and a global treasure. He is James Burke, and he chats about how connected historical events are, and how connection between humans is vital.</description></item><item><title>Audiobook Mixtape 3: Gift Ideas from the Ologists’ Brains | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860362/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860362/</guid><description>Podcast Description You like Ologists. Ologists write books. You like books, so let’s dive into a new, curated sampler platter from your favorite guests’ books.. Fill your ears with dark carnivals, boney catacombs, Rocky Mountain bears and wolves, flies you should love, maggots that make you beautiful, fungus that might be evil, why you should not care what other people eat, queer dolphins, invisible moose, monkey facts, fitness/mental health tips, and how to save money at the salon.</description></item><item><title>Smologies #32: CLOUDS with Rachel Storer | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860361/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860361/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cumulus! Lenticular! Venti sugar-free stratocumulus stratiformis translucidus undulatus! Those light and fluffy things that hang overhead weigh thousands of pounds and form under all kinds of conditions. Cloud doctor and nephologist Dr. Rachel Storer chats about why she loves clouds, the different varieties of them, what makes it rain, whether sailors delight at red skies at night, why clouds are never square and where we can find diamond rain.</description></item><item><title>Abstract Mathematology (UH, IS MATH REAL?) with Eugenia Cheng | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860360/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 08:08:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860360/</guid><description>Podcast Description Math wants to be friends. Let mathematician, author and Abstract Mathematologist Dr. Eugenia Cheng introduce you to a secret world: the artsy and emotional side of math. Dr. Cheng helps answer the age-old and (recently viral) question, “IS MATH REAL?” We chat about Fibonacci sequences, golden ratios, common core, loving thy neighbor, slide rules vs. calculators, imaginary numbers, the nature of zero, infinite cookies, and more. Turns out that math can change your relationships and permeate your every thought.</description></item><item><title>Road Ecology (ROAD KILL) with Ben Goldfarb | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Deer in headlights! Alligators in crosswalks! A possum in the oven? If you love wildlife, this is a must-listen to avoid killing critters with your car. Ben Goldfarb wrote the book on road kill and we chat about: wildlife crossings, skunk smells, moose impacts, ocelot facts, what to do if you see roadkill, how to avoid making more of it, and whether it&amp;rsquo;s okay to pick up a dead thing.</description></item><item><title>Smologies #31: INDIGENOUS COOKING with Mariah Gladstone | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860002/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dig in for a bite-sized episode about how native foods aren’t just a part of a past, but an essential and exciting aspect of the future. We talk flower bulbs, acorns, sunflower butter popcorn, frybread debates, mushroom foraging tips, corn magic, puffball mythology, decolonized diets, Instapots and – most importantly – food sovereignty with the WONDERFUL Indigikitchen cooking show host and environmental scientist Mariah Gladstone.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Garology (LONG CUTE ANCIENT PATIENT BOOPABLE NIGHTMARE FISH) Encore for GAR WEEK with Solomon David | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860003/</guid><description>Podcast Description November 6-12 is GAR WEEK! What is a gar, you ask? Picture: A long snout. Hundreds of teeth. Scales that could slice you. Should we fear it? Should we hug it? One of the world’s most passionate and knowledgeable experts on this ancient, mysterious fish joins to make you fall in love with these slimy longbois. Dr. Solomon David is affable, charming, enthusiastic and absolutely shameless when it comes to fish puns.</description></item><item><title>Neuroparasitology (NATURE ZOMBIES) with Matt Simon | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860004/</guid><description>Podcast Description What’s on your mind? ZOMBIES. The planet is full of mind-controlling foes, and “Plight of the Living Dead” author Matt Simon researched deep and traveled the world to document tales of fungus-controlled zombie ants, bellies and brains full of worms, wasp bunkers, decapitated ants, brutal stings, hapless cockroaches, the attraction of light, moonlit skinny dipping, and the philosophy of where I stop and you begin. The two of us also discuss the Last of Us, of course.</description></item><item><title>Smologies #30: SPIDERWEBS with Randy Lewis | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Invisible but stronger than steel. Complex architectural marvels. Things that stick to your face. Spiderwebs are much more than just Halloween decor or something to feather dust from your corners. Spider silk expert Dr. Randy Lewis of Utah State University not only coined the word &amp;ldquo;spidroin&amp;rdquo; for the proteins comprising the many types of silk, but he is considered one of the foremost experts on the wonders of spiderwebs.</description></item><item><title>Teratology (MONSTERS) with W. Scott Poole | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 00:02:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Frankenstein’s Monster! Hungry ghosts! Moaning bloodsuckers! Goat draining goblins. Babadooks. Gorilla-whales. Slasher films. Body horror… and what these folk stories, films, and fandoms have to do about our hopes and fears. Also yes, you can watch monster movies as a job. Just ask the wonderfully charming and deeply informed Dr. W. Scott Poole, College of Charleston professor and author of “Monsters in America,” who teaches multiple courses on history and monster lore.</description></item><item><title>Pomology (APPLES) with Susan K. Brown | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Green, yellow, striped, red, shiny, russet. Tart, sweet, sour, crunchy. Big, small, wild, heirloom, cultivated. How will you like them apples? Very much, once you hear all about the fascinating backstory of how an apple got into your lunch with one of the world’s finest pomologists and geneticists, the incredibly knowledgeable and charming Dr. Susan K. Brown, a professor at Cornell University&amp;rsquo;s AgriTech division. Fill your baskets with apple picking tips, genetic mash ups, taste test requirements, DNA trivia, compost treasures, maggot babies, the animal dung that changed history, how to have your own orchard, the sweet taste of science redemption, the loudest apple crunch on record, and what you’re actually tasting when you enjoy this feat of breeding.</description></item><item><title>Smologies #29: PUMPKINS with Anne Copeland | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860008/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860008/</guid><description>Podcast Description PUMPKIN PUMPKIN! Not only a thing to scream while passing a patch, but also the name of the book by author and human delight Anne Copeland. Yes, she&amp;rsquo;s so charmed by pumpkins that she dedicated a whole book to exploring their folklore, history, planting protocol, care, and cooking. Alie stops by her house in the rural hamlet of Yucaipa, California to chat about everything from creation myths surrounding pumpkins to the secret medicinal properties of pipitas, loving pumpkins (warts and all), and the big flimflam Anne needs the world to know about the pumpkin origin story.</description></item><item><title>Witchology (WITCHES &amp; WITCHCRAFT) Part 2 with Fio Gede Parma | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860009/</guid><description>Podcast Description More witches! History! Lore! Wardrobes! Movie trivia! And some advice from your elders? Part 2 is here with the wonderful, informed, and charming writer, speaker, spirit-worker, witch, and witchologist, Fio Gede Parma, who has most recently authored the book “The Witch Belongs to the World.” We chat cats, commercialization, witch trials, environmentalism, fashion, hallucinogenic tinctures, broomstick legends, sex positive witchery, celebrity witches, science history, cosmological ghost theories, and what to do if you think you might be a witch.</description></item><item><title>Witchology (WITCHES &amp; WITCHCRAFT) Part 1 with Fio Gede Parma | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860010/</guid><description>Podcast Description IT’S HERE. Witches. Not just a witch expert, but also a witch. Author Fio Gede Parma has been a practicing witch and highly respected writer, speaker and teacher, and they cover witch history, different types of witches, intersectional witchcraft, forest covens, teen movies, witch trials, witch fashion, midnight myths, lunar pratfalls, spells, cheerful nudists, awkward Uber rides and more. Also: how does one… become a witch?
And just a warning: we touch on some stigmas and physical and emotional harm suffered by those observing religions considered fringe.</description></item><item><title>Smologies #28: AGING with Caleb Finch | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860011/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860011/</guid><description>Podcast Description How long can we live? How much of aging is genetics vs. environment? How old are your cells? What can we learn from the world’s oldest people? World-renowned aging expert and biogerontologist Dr. Caleb &amp;ldquo;Tuck&amp;rdquo; Finch takes a quick break from his prolific research at USC to answer Alie&amp;rsquo;s sometimes basic questions about everything from molecules to Blue Zones.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Benthopelagic Nematology (DEEP SEA WORMS) with Holly Bik | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Weird little mouths! Hairy skin tubes! Demon nematodes! Antarctic explorer and Nematologist Dr. Holly Bik charms us into loving deep sea (benthopelagic) worms in a way you never thought possible. We also cover tiny worm brains, the smell of Antarctic mud, first-generation Ph.Ds, the research workhorse C. Elegans, deep sea mining machines, moisturizers, submersibles and more with a worm lady who has literally traveled to the ends of the Earth to ask: what’s in that mud?</description></item><item><title>Gustology (TASTE) with Gary Beauchamp | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sweet! Salty! Umami? What’s up with MSG? Why do you like your coffee black? Come down to flavortown and let’s talk tongues. Gustologist Dr. Gary Beauchamp is a chemosensory scientist and an expert in taste. We chat about tastebud flim-flam, celebrity grade hot wings, MSG research, excitotoxins, weaning off sugar, the worst soup on the market, what countries have salt restrictions, why you lost your taste with Covid, how much taste is smell, artificial sweeteners, acquiring a taste for foods, and how a sweet tooth may affect your booze consumption.</description></item><item><title>Cosmology (THE UNIVERSE) Part 2 Encore with Katie Mack | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Mack returns with a new introduction and updates on… listener questions! The universe, dimensions, asteroid bags and cosmic vertigo with the amazing Astro Katie, AKA Dr. Katie Mack. Part 1 was a primer on all things cosmological, from particle physics to black holes, so listen to that first then hop to this episode to get all your questions answered.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Smologies #27: MARS with Jennifer Buz | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860015/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Red Planet. A mysterious dusty orb millions of miles away. Our emergency escape bunker. Alie sits down with Dr. Jennifer Buz to talk about what Mars’s DEEEEAL is, why we send rovers there, the poetry of the moon Phobos, Martian sunsets and whether we could landscape Mars to look like a golf course. Jennifer is maybe the chillest areologist on this planet and an absolute gem.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cosmology (THE UNIVERSE) Part 1 Encore with Katie Mack | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stars. Black holes. THE GAWDANG UNIVERSE. Astrophysicist and cosmologist Katie Mack (@astrokatie) re-introduces us to this 2017 episode along with some bonus updates on astrophysics, her career, and the book she’s published since we last heard from her. Katie also tells us her most embarrassing moments as a cosmologist, debunks some physicist myths and gives us the nuts + bolts of everything form particle physics to gravitational waves and existential mysteries.</description></item><item><title>LIFE ADVICE Encore: For anyone who is tired &amp; needs some hacks | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alie takes a teeny tiny break from her vacation to reintroduce you to this laid back, super helpful fan favorite episode. Listen in for: Pomodoro timers! Bullet journals! Apps, tips, tricks and philosophies. Also: the most mellow episode ever, recorded late at night in a guest room. Like a cozy duvet of wisdom, this one is full of life hacks for remaining productive &amp;amp; healthy during distracting times. I asked Ologites their best strategies for keeping their brains less burdened and organizing everything from schedules to leftovers to sock drawers.</description></item><item><title>Smologies #26: POOP with Rachel Santymire | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860018/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yep. Here it is. A kid-friendly episode on… poop. Camel poop. Rhino poop. Dog poop. Cat poop. Your poop. The charming and informative Dr. Rachel Santymire &amp;ndash; aka Dr. Poop &amp;ndash; has a background in animal physiology and endocrinology and is elbow deep in dung as a research director at the Lincoln Park Zoo. Dr. Poop sits down with Alie to talk turds and why some critters like to chow down on their own (or others’), the stinkiest poopers, good smelling poop, how getting curious about poop can help save a species, and why the Lincoln Park Zoo has 17 freezers full of dookie.</description></item><item><title>Etymology (WORD ORIGINS) Encore with Helen Zaltzman | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860019/</guid><description>Podcast Description The brilliant and dazzling Helen Zaltzman pops in with some new asides in this encore episode of Ologies. Helen, host of the podcasts The Allusionist, Veronica Mars Investigations and Answer Me This, and a person who technically for a living researches the origins of language and thus is an etymologist, visits Alie&amp;rsquo;s apartment to chat about various word origins, gender in language, the Bible a.k.a. The Oxford English Dictionary, origins of the filthiest slang, emoji decoding, mediocrity, step parents, babies wearing glasses, Greek kimonos, the romance of languages and the fundamental truth that language is always changing whether you want it to or not.</description></item><item><title>Diabetology (BLOOD SUGAR) Part 2 Encore with Mike Natter | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860020/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wrapping up our Diabetology 2 parter encore, diabetic diabetologist and wonderful person Dr. Mike Natter, MD is back with a little introduction covering some stuff that wasn&amp;rsquo;t on the radar back in 2019, like what&amp;rsquo;s the deal with this Ozempic stuff you&amp;rsquo;ve heard about, and then Natter from the past goes on to answer all of your questions about blood sugar, the cost of insulin, pancreas transplants, keto, glucagon, how exercise can save your life, his most meaningful interactions with patients, pudding theft, and the best place to cry at work.</description></item><item><title>Diabetology (BLOOD SUGAR) Part 1 Encore with Mike Natter | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 07:12:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Mike Natter hosts this encore episode of Ologies (hosted by Alie Ward), it&amp;rsquo;s a classic 2 parter: Diabetology about the happy, moody-, sweaty-, unconscious-, and possibly even homicidal-making sugar in our blood. In this episode, Dr. Mike Natter dishes about how blood sugar works, what insulin does, and how prevalent diabetes is in all of its various forms. Also: keto vs. vegan, hypoglycemia, cyborg organs, owl hoots, gestational diabetes, type 1 vs.</description></item><item><title>Minisode: Dadward Takes a Break | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Listen, kids&amp;hellip; give your father a break, okay?
Sponsors of Ologies
Transcripts and bleeped episodes
Become a patron of Ologies for as little as a buck a month
OlogiesMerch.com has hats, shirts, masks, totes!
Follow @Ologies on Twitter and Instagram
Follow @AlieWard on Twitter and Instagram
Editing by Mercedes Maitland of Maitland Audio Productions and Jarrett Sleeper of MindJam Media and Mark David Christenson
Transcripts by Emily White of The Wordary</description></item><item><title>Neurotechnology (AI + BRAIN TECH) with Nita Farahany | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Machine poets. ChatGPT fails. Neurological surveillance. Brain implants that treat depression. Is it scary? Cool? Let’s firehose some questions at Duke Law professor, neuro and bioethicist, author and TED speaker Dr. Nita Farahany. She explains the history of AI, the dawn of chatbots, what’s changed recently, the potential for good, the possible perils, how different lawmakers are stepping in, and whether or not this is scary dinner party conversation.</description></item><item><title>Sciuridology (SQUIRRELS) with Karen Munroe | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 05:23:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Flying squirrels. Fox squirrels. Giant squirrels. Tiny ones. Grey ones. Black ones. Fluorescent ones? Alie is losing her mind talking to dream guest and Sciuridologist, Dr. Karen Munroe. This Baldwin Wallace University professor has studied squirrels for decades and addresses where they sleep, how many babies they have, if they bite each other’s junk, how they find their acorns, Marvel movies, birdfeeder drama, imported squirrels, melanistic morphs, world domination, fistfights with birders, the rarest squirrel, the best place for squirrel tourism and more.</description></item><item><title>Molecular Neurobiology (BRAIN CHEMICALS) Encore with Crystal Dilworth | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860025/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi! I’ve been in the hospital with pneumonia! But enjoy this banger of an encore about: Serotonin! Dopamine! Norepinephrine! Neurotransmitters: what&amp;rsquo;s their deal? Dr. Crystal Dilworth, aka Dr. Brain, stops by to have a spirited discussion about how chemical messengers change our moods and behaviors. We chat about depression, anxiety, what chemicals drive us to get off the couch, how antidepressants work, ADHD, addiction, the microbiome, new habits, quitting smoking, starting meditation, Oreos vs.</description></item><item><title>Smologies #25: LIGHTNING with Chris Giesige | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 23:41:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860026/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a kid-friendly episode on … thunder and lightning: very, very frighteningly interesting! Wildfire researcher and lightning scientist Chris Giesige answers questions about thunderclaps and lightning flashes in a laid back way that will put him at the top of your Fulminologist list. He explains everything from clouds to positive and negative charges, the link between lightning scientists and firefighters, volcanic lightning, ice particle mosh pits, how many gigawatts in a lightning strike, and how to enjoy a storm without getting zapped.</description></item><item><title>Curiology (EMOJI) Part 2 with Various Emoji Experts | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860027/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 08:46:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860027/</guid><description>Podcast Description The thrilling conclusion of all-things-emoji! Eggplants, peaches, jumping ska dudes, gray hearts, family emojis, what NOT to text your Southern Italian friends, yellow hands, red hair, the birth of the smiley face and how to celebrate World Emoji Day on July 17 with Emojipedia founder Jeremy Burge, designer Jennifer Daniel, and the world’s first emoji translator (and current Emojipedia editor-in-chief) Keith Broni.
Listen to Part 1 first, of course.</description></item><item><title>Curiology (EMOJI) Part 1 with Various Emoji Experts | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860028/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 06:58:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Thumbs up? Thumbs down. Skulls of joy. And so many expressions of pain and comfort. This, my babies, is the -ology that sparked this whole podcast. Curiology means “writing with pictures” but will certified emoji experts agree that they are curiologists? Listen in for behind-the-scenes drama, origin stories, stats on usage, trends and global context with Emojipedia founder Jeremy Burge, designer Jennifer Daniel, and the world’s first emoji translator (and current Emojipedia editor-in-chief) Keith Broni.</description></item><item><title>Field Trip: Birds of Prey and Raptor Facts | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860029/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 16:22:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Grab your stuff and hop in our van full of weirdos to check out Boise Idaho’s finest attraction: a 580 acre preserve of land that is absolutely flush with raptors who could eat your eyeballs. We’re back with another field trip episode, this time visiting The Peregrine Fund’s World Center For Birds of Prey in Boise, Idaho. We got a tour from Vice President of the Peregrine Fund Dr.</description></item><item><title>Smologies #24: SHIPWRECKS with Chanelle Zaphiropoulos | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860030/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 23:54:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ahoy matey, we’ve we’ve brought ye another ensmol’d episode of Ologies (which just means cleaned of filth and cut for brevity) this time on: Shipwrecks. We get to talk with maritime archaeologist and wreck nerd Chanelle Zaphiropoulos about her experiences with Shipwrecks, treasure, carbon dating, admirals worth admiring, ancient technology recovered from the depths of history, The Bermuda Triangle, and generally life as an underwater wreck detective.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Native Melittology (INDIGENOUS BEES) with Krystle Hickman | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860031/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 04:07:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Honeybees get all the attention, but native bees are the underbugs to root for. Photographer, author, and National Geographic Explorer Krystle Hickman shows us the wonders of indigenous bees through her lens focused on conservation of bees and their habitats. She covers their lifecycles, tunnels, turrets, fuzzy butts, frat house cuddling, and sexual dimorphism. We also chat about taxonomic fisticuffs, bee hotels, the mustard blight, monocultures, the teeniest livestock, and how to appreciate and photograph all of the marvels you’ve been overlooking.</description></item><item><title>Pectinidology (SCALLOPS) with Samantha Lynch | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860032/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 08:52:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860032/</guid><description>Podcast Description They clap. They swim. They have dozens of eyes and 2 million babies. They are scallops. Pectinidologist Dr. Samantha Lynch climbs aboard to share stories of theft on the brackish seas, gossip about scallops vs. oysters, ponderings on Disney bras, months without Rs, bay scallops, sea scallops, filter feeders, shellfish volunteering, curious baby bivalves, seagrass, red tides, and free buffets. We also check in with James Beard Award-nominated chef Miles Thompson who offers cooking tips (with a fair warning for vegetarians.</description></item><item><title>Smologies #23: MAMMALS with Danielle N. Lee | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860033/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 07:35:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here we are with the smol (shorter, cleaner, kid-friendly) version of another Ologies classic, in this case: Mammals. You’re one. Your dog is one. So are giant rats. What do we have in common? I promise you’ll find out the answer from the incredible Southern Illinois University professor, researcher, science communicator and mammalogist Dr. Danielle N. Lee as she joins us to chat about everything from nature’s parenting styles, mysteries of the platypus, how the dinosaurs affected mammal evolution, the origin of the word mom, and how we’re all in this together.</description></item><item><title>Fire Ecology (WILDFIRES &amp; INDIGENOUS FIRE MANAGEMENT) Mega Encore with Gavin Jones &amp; Amy Christianson | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860034/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 06:36:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Once again: the world is on fire. As wildfires burn across Canada and their smoke pours down the continent, we thought it would be a good time to encore these Fire Ecology episodes. First, Dr. Gavin Jones brings the heat talking about what fire is, how hot it burns, fire trends, tinderboxes, lots and lots of forest fire flim-flam, tolerant wombats, Angelina Jolie movies, cunning pine cones, thick bark, Indigenous fire stewardship and more.</description></item><item><title>Black American Magirology (FOOD, RACE &amp; CULTURE) with Psyche Williams-Forson | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860035/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 10:09:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860035/</guid><description>Podcast Description What’s the difference between Southern cooking and “soul food?” Is there a correct type of mac and cheese? And whose business is it what you eat? (Hint: no one’s). Culinary historian, scholar of African American life and culture critic Dr. Psyche Williams-Forson is a professor at University of Maryland College Park and department chair in the Department of American Studies. She also authored the books “Eating While Black: Food Shaming and Race in America” and “Building Houses out of Chicken Legs: Black Women, Food, and Power.</description></item><item><title>Field Trip: A Hollywood Visit to the Writers Guild Strike Line | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860036/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 00:25:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in, we’re going to the Valley to talk to cool, funny screenwriters about &amp;hellip; Artificial intelligence-drafted scripts! Trillion-dollar companies pretending they’re broke! Emmy-nominated writers with side hustles! Teamster bosses dropping mics! What an exciting time to gossip about Hollywood… labor unions! Listen, we all love watching our Programs and laughing, learning and loving. But things are getting WEIRD behind the scenes, and the Writers Guild of America is on strike, showing up in picket lines in front of movie and TV studios.</description></item><item><title>Acaropathology (TICKS &amp; LYME DISEASE) Updated Mega Encore with Neeta Pardanani Connally &amp; Andrea Swei | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860037/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860037/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s 2-for-1! Ticks AND Lyme: together in one helpful, disgusting, gossipy, empowering episode. This pair of episodes is about tiny, thirsty ticks and the diseases they spit into you is wall to wall wisdom from Dr. Neeta Pardanani Connally of the West Connecticut State University Tick Lab and Dr. Andrea Swei of SFSU’s Swei Lab cover how to remove a tick, if you should spray your yard and with what, how landscaping affects tick exposure, why Lyme Disease is spreading, the Lone Star Tick rolling into town, how to protect your pets and why the CC ruined poppyseed muffins.</description></item><item><title>Invisible Photology (INVISIBILITY CLOAKS) with Greg Gbur | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860038/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 17:12:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Invisibility cloaks. Transparent frogs. Stealth bombers. Gorilla mischief. Theoretical optical physicist and Invisible Photologist Dr. Greg Gbur joins Alie to chat about light, illusions, secret technology, science fiction inspiration, terrible camouflage, great movies, historical mishaps, and even a few great household life hacks – and why you should go read a book on your porch. Perhaps his book, Invisibility: The History and Science of How Not To Be Seen.</description></item><item><title>Stem Cell Biology (CELLS MAKING CELLS) with “Science Sam” aka Samantha Yammine | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 10:41:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860039/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do our bodies build our bodies? What does a stem cell look like? How do they know what to do? What diseases could stem cells cure? And why is Canada such a hot place for research? Dr. Samantha Yammine – known by many as Science Sam – is a stem cell biologist and science communicator and takes us back to the discovery of stem cells, chats ethical questions, spotting scams, cloning, gene-edited babies, helping your body heal faster and what advancements are being made, albeit by slowly growing in a dish.</description></item><item><title>Smologies #22: REPTILES &amp; AMPHIBIANS with David Steen | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860040/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 22:52:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860040/</guid><description>Podcast Description This shorter, kid-safe edit of the classic Herpetology episode features frilly gills, frog tornadoes, legless lizards, and reasons to appreciate snakes. Also, why you shouldn’t kiss one. Dr. David Steen is a beloved herpetologist and wildlife conservationist and his answers are full of facts and flim-flam busters.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Delphinology Part 2 (DOLPHINS) with Justin Gregg | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860041/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wow. It gets weirder. Military dolphins, dolphins on drugs, sensory deprivation, deciphering dolphin language, the search for alien life, and more with the affable and knowledgeable Delphinologist Dr. Justin Gregg. Should you cuddle a dolphin? Can one kill you? Should you hire dolphins as midwives? Why do they follow boats? And what’s Drake got to do with it?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Delphinology Part 1 (DOLPHINS) with Justin Gregg | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Giant brains! Communication mysteries! Infamous sensuality! Dolphins are here to blow your relatively tiny mind with their squeaks, clicks, cliques, history, lore, zany evolutionary path, psychedelic experiences, and so much more. Learn why some dolphins are pink, why NASA poured cash into groovy research, what it’s like to touch a dolphin, if they can learn to speak English, their mating strategies, captivity, and the researchers that made our culture obsessed with them.</description></item><item><title>Field Trip: My Butt, a Colonoscopy Ride Along &amp; How-To | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860043/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 04:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Come check out my butt with me! 1 in 16 people in the U.S. will have colon cancer, and 0 in 16 want to talk about getting a camera up your guts to check things out. I am one of them, but after losing loved ones to colon cancer – and staring down the barrel of my first-ever colonoscope — I recorded tips, tricks, taste tests, foggy drug hazes, bar room advice, and finally my surprising results.</description></item><item><title>Chickenology Part 2 (HENS &amp; ROOSTERS) with Tove Danovich | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 04:15:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860044/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re back for Part 2! If you missed Part 1, start there for the chicken basics and then come back for the weird stuff like chickens eating chickens, why chickens bother laying unfertilized eggs, rooster gossip, fairy eggs, nest abominations, bird grief, beak accessories, soft burbling chicken sounds, spicy chicken feed, safe corners of the internet, multicolored eggs and the big questions: SHOULD YOU GET A CHICKEN OR WHAT.</description></item><item><title>Chickenology Part 1 (HENS &amp; ROOSTERS) with Tove Danovich | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860045/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 18:06:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yes, Chickenology is a real word. And we have questions. Such as: should you get a chicken?! Chicken-haver and author of “Under the Henfluence” Tove Danovich stops in to recall how her casual backyard chicken experiment turned into an obsession, a lifestyle, and then a book. We chat about junglefowl, chicken competitions, egg prices, chicken statues, bird personalities, coop logistics, avian flus, shell hues, earlobes, live chicken cams, and more on this Part 1.</description></item><item><title>Smologies #21: SLEEP with Chris Winter | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860046/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 07:27:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860046/</guid><description>Podcast Description A G-rated, kid-safe Smologies edit all about getting your Zzzzzs. Neurologist and somnologist Dr. W. Chris Winter is an expert on sleep, and since his first interview, he’s released a book called “The Rested Child” all about sleep and kiddos! So parents, kids and anybody else can dive in to learn about different sleep stages, what sleep does to the brain, insomnia, ideal bedtime conditions, brain performance and how doctors often overlook pediatric sleep disorders.</description></item><item><title>Domicology (ABANDONED BUILDINGS, RECYCLED HOUSES &amp; GHOST TOWNS) with Rex LaMore | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860047/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 06:48:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860047/</guid><description>Podcast Description What’s inside that boarded up house? Should you explore an abandoned mall? A vacant factory? And how much of an old house ends up in a landfill? The founder of Domicology, Dr. Rex LaMore of Michigan State University’s Center for Community and Economic Development, is an expert on these things and answers any possible question you might have, from ghost towns to hidden house notes, arson, recycling wood, stealing metal and how to leave a better housing situation for future generations.</description></item><item><title>Chronobiology (CIRCADIAN RHYTHMS) Encore + 2023 Updates with Katherine Hatcher | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860048/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 16:40:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ahh, Daylight Savings Time: does it mess up your brain? What time should you go to bed? Are you sleeping enough? Is shift work really that bad? How dark is dark enough? The wonderful and hilarious Dr. Katherine Hatcher got her PhD in hormones, sleep cycles and circadian rhythms, and helps Alie dissect her terrible sleep habits. We also chat about a tiny magical area in our brains that acts as your body&amp;rsquo;s Big Ben.</description></item><item><title>Smologies #20: FISHES with Chris Thacker | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860049/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 06:23:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ichthyology is not easy to say, but fish are easy to love. Dr. Chris Thacker will get you so thrilled to stare into a pond or look up pictures of silvery sea serpent-looking fish friends.
Hilariously charming fish expert and LA County Natural History Museum Curator of Ichthyology, Dr. Thacker took Alie to a basement full of several million jars of fish to chat about the worst fish husbands, the weirdest mating behaviors, the scariest fish, the nicest fish, the tiniest fish, how they breathe, how you can help reverse global warming, and whether you should pee in wetsuits.</description></item><item><title>Detroitology (DETROIT) with Aaron Foley | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860050/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 20:57:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why an episode on Detroit?! It’s got a great story. Standalone, this episode is a fascinating look at a metropolis that swelled and thrived during the auto boom, then declined, and is navigating a rocky rebirth of sorts. Aaron Foley was Detroit’s first official City Storyteller and wrote the book “How to Live In Detroit Without Being a Jackass.” I’ve wanted to have him on Ologies for five years, and we finally sat down to talk about MoTown, car culture, square pizza, $1000 houses, gentrification, urban infrastructure, underground salt mines, amusement park slides, Diana Ross, emerging rappers, and the city’s abandonment issues.</description></item><item><title>Field Trip: An Airport Full of Neuroscientists | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860051/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 19:36:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860051/</guid><description>Podcast Description I’m at the airport and there are hundreds of brain scientists everywhere. So I swallowed my dignity/anxiety and approached strangers about the neuroscience they do. The result is a bushel of info on cravings, sleep, consciousness, addiction, dopamine, monogamy, Ozempic, toxins in your brain and so much more with: Georgia Kirkpatrick, Isabella Montana, Dr. Marissa Co, Chancey Garrett, Noah Millman, Pique Choi, Dr. Barbara Sorg and Elizabeth Plunk. Oops, we just made a bunch of new friends.</description></item><item><title>Environmental Toxicology (POISONS + TRAIN DERAILMENT) with Kimberly K. Garrett | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860052/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 09:10:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chemical spills, historical disasters, water quality, airborne toxic events, clear gasses, White Noise, dead fish, dark clouds, chemistry tests, trench coats, PFAS, phthalates, and the Ohio train derailment that plumed vinyl chloride into the skies of a small Ohio town. The lovely and informative Environmental Toxicologist Dr. Kimberly K. Garrett works at the intersection of chemical safety, public health and environmental justice — and she has cool science tattoos.</description></item><item><title>Melaninology (SKIN/HAIR PIGMENT) with Tina Lasisi | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860053/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 02:22:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Skin color! Hair texture! Biological anthropology! The incredibly informed and infectiously funny Dr. Tina Lasisi joins to chat sunscreen, ashiness, redheads, light skin, dark skin, in-between skin, beards, UVAs, UVBs, shower habits, cultural colloquialisms, vitiligo, melasma, medical math, ocher, freckles and more. Dr. Lasisi is about to become your new favorite science communication and internet friend. Also: sunscreen, people.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Scotohylology (DARK MATTER) with Flip Tanedo | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860054/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 10:53:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860054/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s invisible. It’s mysterious. It’s all around us – and no one knows what it is. Let’s have a fun existential crisis by pondering Dark Matter! The world’s most affable and endearing theoretical particle physicist, Dr. Flip Tanedo of UC Riverside, makes the Large Hadron Collider, Higgs bosons, and neutrinos make sense. Also: Star Trek, space ghosts, vintage insults, supernovas and more. You’ll leave with a newfound wonder and the desire to read physics journals for the secrets of life.</description></item><item><title>Laryngology Part 2 (VOICE BOXES) with Ronda Alexander | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860055/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 10:57:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Part 2 is here! Pull up a seat for singing techniques, baby talk, baritones, whistle notes, stroke recovery, vibrato, Julie Andrews, crying jags, throat singing, accents and much more with your new favorite Laryngologist, Dr. Ronda Alexander. We just… we love her so much.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Laryngology Part 1 (VOICE BOXES) Ronda Alexander | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860056/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 21:52:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Voices! Singing! Anxiety busters! Breathing! The absolutely magnetic, charismatic Laryngologist and surgeon Dr. Ronda Alexander makes her long-awaited Ologies debut to chat about why we sound the way we do, hormones and voices, Elvis accents, opera singing, kid voices, turning back time vocally, coughing, sleep apnea, acid reflux, vocal fry, Mariah and more in this stellar two-parter. Come back next week when we answer so many burning questions.</description></item><item><title>Aperiology (MACRO PHOTOGRAPHY) Encore with Joseph Saunders | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860057/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 09:25:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lights! Cameras! Arachnids! And lizards and bees and beetles. Macro photography is like magic: curved glass gives an entirely new take on the world, from dust on a cricket’s brow to a curious mantid stare to the elegant symmetry of spider whiskers. Joseph Saunders is an Oklahoma-based wildlife photographer whose larger-than-life photos of bugs and reptiles will make you realize just how little we appreciate the creatures on our window sills and skittering up our porches.</description></item><item><title>Oneirology Part 2 (DREAMS) with G. William Domhoff | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860058/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 17:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Part 2 is here: Lucid dreaming! Teeth falling out! Medications and dreaming! The source of creativity! Even how to clean your brain. Dr. G. William Domhoff has studied dreams for decades and returns to answer an absolute deluge of questions with his wisdom and aplomb. By the end, you’ll know to sleep better, why it’s important, how to relax like a fish, if cheese alters your subconscious, why your dog flaps their paws during naps, and rejoice about a freshly discovered part of the brain.</description></item><item><title>Oneirology Part 1 (DREAMS) with G. William Domhoff | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860059/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 02:38:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860059/</guid><description>Podcast Description WHY do we dream? What do dreams mean? What parts of our brain are working after-hours? We sought out UC Santa Cruz researcher and professor Dr. G. William Domhoff, a world expert on the topic, for this dream-come-true episode. Learn about historical dream research, dream researchers collect dream reports, how neurodivergence affects dreaming, why you should set an alarm to go to bed, how remembering dreams can help solve problems, and more about REM myths!</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode: Secrets, Advice + Ask-Me-Anything | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860060/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 01:53:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860060/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a weird rambling bonus episode for the lonely week between the holidays and New Years! I thought I’d serve up a mellow hang full of secrets, a retrospective of the things that kept me relatively sane this past year, life hacks, science-backed ways to improve your mood, and a jaunty Q&amp;amp;A from Patrons. It’s not a normal episode, but just a little hello and check-in from your internet dad.</description></item><item><title>Smologies #19: EVOLUTION with John McCormack | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860061/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 08:32:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Another G-rated edit of a classic! This Smologies with Dr. John McCormack of Occidental College is all about evolution, Darwinism, birds, bacteria, natural selection and how our mutations can be our greatest strengths. Also: breaking down terms like genetic drift and Linnaean taxonomy and why Charles Darwin had to face haters under his own roof. (For the adult version, the full-length episode is linked below.) Follow John McCormack on Twitter or the Moore Lab of Zoology on Instagram Full length (not classroom-friendly) episode + tons of science links here A donation went to: BirdNet.</description></item><item><title>P-22: The Life &amp; Death of an L.A. Cougar with Miguel Ordeñana &amp; Beth Pratt | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860062/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 08:26:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Very special episode for a very special cat. The day after the legendary Los Angeles mountain lion P-22 took his last breath, we talked with Natural History Museum wildlife biologist Miguel Ordeñana about his decade-long study of P-22 after discovering him in Griffith Park. Beth Pratt of #SaveLACougars and the National Wildlife Federation also shares how P-22 fueled her passion for saving this species from extinction — and we hear what one animal meant to millions of Angelenos.</description></item><item><title>Meteorology (WEATHER &amp; CLIMATE) with Marshall Shepherd | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860063/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 10:25:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bomb cyclones! Polar vortices! Atmospheric rivers! And rained out barbecues. One of the world’s leading Meteorologists, Dr. Marshall Shepherd – a former NASA scientist and current Professor of Geography and Atmospheric Sciences at the University of Georgia – is here to field a downpour of questions. We chat about percentages in forecasts, hail, sleet, storm chasing, heatwaves, fluid dynamics, TV weather people, climate change delayism and his favorite weather-themed movies.</description></item><item><title>Enigmatology (WORD PUZZLES) with David Kwong | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860064/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Crosswords! Puzzles! Wordles! Magic? Ah yes, world-renowned Enigmatologist David Kwong drops in to chat about the intersection of sleight of hand and brain games, covering everything from Scrabble strategies to how to get away with a surprise party unsuspected. Also: crosswords and dementia, how puzzles are like hot sauce, a secret group of Hollywood magicians, his most clever clues, cryptic crosswords, international slang, Wordle’s many derivatives, and how to get over your intimidation of all those empty squares.</description></item><item><title>Special Ep: Mycology (MUSHROOMS) Tom Volk Memorial Encore | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860065/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 03:03:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860065/</guid><description>Podcast Description In celebration of Dr. Tom Volk’s life: Mushrooms! Psilocybin! Humongous fungus! Black mold! Foraging! The incredibly charming and warm Dr. Tom Volk, world-renowned mushroom expert, welcomes Alie into his office to dive deep into the underground world of fungal enthusiasts and touch on pathogens and medicinal therapies. Dr. Volk himself was a heart transplant patient, and shared how his life had been changed since a donor saved it. Also: Alie holds his old heart in her hands.</description></item><item><title>Indigenous Pedology (SOIL SCIENCE) with Lydia Jennings | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860066/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 14:23:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Soil! Dirt! Earth. Dr. Lydia Jennings, aka Native Soil Nerd, breaks down the stuff under our feet and explains everything from mining to why soil can be different colors. Also: medicine from microbes, giving back to the land after extractive processes, collecting samples in urban rivers, elders’ ecological knowledge, planting hot Cheetos, potting soil mysteries, lung fungus, the smell of rain and why gardening makes you happy. Oh and running hundreds of miles for your science.</description></item><item><title>Smologies #18: FEASTS with Katherine Spiers | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860067/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 05:46:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kid-friendly and quick! It’s another Smologies G-rated cut of a classic episode. Loosen your belts and tuck a napkin under your chin because feasting season is here. Katherine Spiers &amp;ndash; journalist, food anthropologist, editor of HowtoEatLA.com and host of the culinary history podcast Smart Mouth &amp;ndash; lets Alie belly up for a buffet of questions about winter gatherings, Thanksgiving myths, green bean casseroles, the hazards of deep frying, holy eels and more.</description></item><item><title>Bryology (MOSS) Encore with Dr. Robin Wall Kimmerer | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860068/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860068/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s November and you need chill vibes. And Native American Heritage Month is the perfect time to encore this classic. World-renowned author, botanist, Indigenous ecology professor and bryologist Dr. Robin Wall Kimmerer, author of “Gathering Moss” and “Braiding Sweetgrass,” talks about her passion for moss. Cozy up for the most beautifully doled-out information about hidden worlds, overlooked mysteries, botanical drama, forests in miniature, Native peoples’ uses for moss and philosophies about science and ecology.</description></item><item><title>Discard Anthropology (GARBAGE) with Robin Nagle | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860069/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 21:34:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Landfills! Treasures in the trash! Corporate conspiracies! Composting! An instantly classic conversation with the incredibly knowledgeable, frank and wonderful Dr. Robin Nagle of New York University’s Liberal Studies! She is a clinical professor, author, TED speaker and former New York City sanitation worker and truly the best person on Earth to trash talk with. We cover what you can and can’t actually recycle, sticky mustard bottles, drugs in the trash, Swedish Death Cleaning, mobsters and landfills, Bitcoin in the dump, the future of garbage and exactly how screwed we are.</description></item><item><title>Smologies #17: FLAGS with E. Tory Laitila | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860070/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 07:22:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860070/</guid><description>Podcast Description A kid-friendly, shortened version of our classic episode on …flags! E. Tory Laitila, a textile expert who has also handled Honolulu&amp;rsquo;s flag protocol, gives the skinny on the oldest flags, skull and crossbone Jolly Rogers, his favorite state flag, Scandinavian simplicity, the hardest flags to draw, who designed our modern American flag and how you too can have &amp;hellip; fun with flags all year round.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Vampirology (VAMPIRES) Part 2 with Jeff Holdeman | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860071/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 07:46:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Start with Part 1 for all the folkloric history, superstition, and Dracula basics. And then this Part 2 has vampire finches, fang straws, vegan bloodsuckers, threshold invites, horniness, grain alcohol, garlic breath, psychic vampires and all our questions answered by Dr. Jeff Holdeman, professor and Vampirologist in Indiana University’s Slavic and East European Languages and Cultures department. Also: I think you should write a novel.
Part 1: alieward.com/ologies/vampirology</description></item><item><title>Vampirology (VAMPIRES) Part 1 with Jeff Holdeman | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860072/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:13:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fangs! Capes! Undead bloodlust! Are vampires soul-draining ghouls or a hot prom date? No better person to ask than Indiana University professor of Slavic and East European Languages and Cultures,&amp;quot; Dr. Jeff Holdeman, who teaches the course “The Vampire in European and American Culture.” In Part 1, it’s a deep dive into the HISTORY. Jeff breaks down the folkloric purpose of vampire stories and how they morphed into novels and hit the silver screen.</description></item><item><title>Smologies #16: INSECTS with Lila Higgins | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860073/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 23:57:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860073/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;re back with another shorter, cleaner, edition of an Ologies classic, today it&amp;rsquo;s all the way back from Episode 11: INSECTS, just straight up buuuugs. Quite likely Alie&amp;rsquo;s favorite subject ever with an ologist who quite likely also dramatically shifted her life. That would be Lila Higgins, with passion more powerful than a Goliath Beetle&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;especially large slicey mandibles&amp;rdquo; . We cover a lot of ground, from dinosaur bugs, to why wasps are so problematic, and even why it&amp;rsquo;s totally fine to kiss a cockroach.</description></item><item><title>Metropolitan Tombology (PARIS CATACOMBS) with Erin-Marie Legacey | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860074/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 07:45:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Let’s get spooky. Venture below Parisian streets and into the catacombs: hundreds of miles of subterranean tunnels housing millions of human skeletons, some fashioned into sculpture. Alie tracked down Dr. Erin-Marie Legacey – author of “Making Space for the Dead,” professor of French history and one of the world’s foremost experts on this eerie place. We chat about everything from miasmas to sinkholes, boggling cemetery history, smells, skulls, hidden chambers, (very) underground parties, and how we view our bodies post-life.</description></item><item><title>FIELD TRIP: I Go France and Learn Weird French Stuff | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860075/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 04:39:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Consider this an audio postcard from my first vacation in 13 years. I travel a lot for my other job (as a science correspondent on Innovation Nation for CBS) so I am out of practice on jet-setting for the sake of pure fun. But Jarrett’s family was headed to France so we cashed in some points and tagged along. Join me for some weird stuff I googled on the road, from pastry wars to royal cosplay, wax death masks, angry mobs, filming locations, things you can’t collect in a park and eat, how to get along with French waiters, what to do if a loved one starts sobbing in public, one of the best ways to see Paris, cider that tastes like flowers, a theme park with a hidden agenda, and the fall fashion trends that were confusingly ubiquitous.</description></item><item><title>5th Anniversary Special! Xylology (LUMBER) with Jeff Perry | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860076/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 21:36:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860076/</guid><description>Podcast Description What’s the customary 5th Anniversary gift? Apparently… WOOD! So we wrangled our favorite sawmill owner/operator of LA’s Angel City Lumber, Jeff Perry – who rescues downed street trees from the chipper and turns them into beautiful planks, boards, stumps and chonks. We cover everything from forest management to 2x4s, wood grain, burls, bog logs, sawdust, tree disease, asparagus tips, salvaged lumber, kiln drying, Westward expansion, Indigenous forest management, cedar whiff, and how working with wood changes your relationship to death.</description></item><item><title>Geology (ROCKS) Part 2 with Schmitty Thompson | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860077/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 06:25:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860077/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re back! Listen to Part 1 first, then hit this follow-up with your favorite geologist Schmitty Thompson, who answers listener questions a-plenty. Such as: What is a geode? Are crystals in gift shops even real? Where’s the best place to look at rocks? Is ice a rock? Plus: rock puns, favorite rocks, best and worst rock names, long hikes, imposter syndrome, lab-grown diamonds, fossilized trees, space rocks, lead poisoning, and puns.</description></item><item><title>Smologies #15: FAMILY TREES with Stephen Hanks | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860078/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 02:20:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860078/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a shorter, swear-free version of the wonderful Genealogy episode with author Stephen Hanks &amp;ndash; who teaches genealogy classes in Portland, Oregon and has contributed to PBS genealogy documentaries. We chat histories, mysteries, memories and families, plus what ignited his passion for learning about his own history. Also: how to find your family through census records, county archives, and death certificates; which DNA tests he’s taken; our most recent common ancestor; and whether or not he wears a detective cape.</description></item><item><title>Geology (ROCKS) Part 1 with Schmitty Thompson | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860079/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 09:07:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860079/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is a rock? How big is a boulder? Why are they pretty and heavy? It’s rock talk with a true enthusiast, the charming and beloved Geologist Schmitty Thompson. Schmitty walks us through different types of rocks, minerals, geological formations, roadside wonders, countertop crystals, stone skipping, and why you should stare lovingly into a pit of gravel. There were so many listener questions, we had to make this a two-parter people.</description></item><item><title>Oreamnology (MOUNTAIN GOATS ARE NOT GOATS) with Julie Cunningham | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860080/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 07:34:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mountain goats are not goats. And there’s only one living species, Oreamnos americanus. WHAT?? Montana-based wildlife biologist and Oreamnologist Julie Cunningham counts mountain goats from helicopters, traps and tests them for science, and spends even her off days searching for them on mountaintops. We cover their population, sensual mating habits, the feel of their wool, pungent goatwhiff, tips for hikers and how these animals defy gravity scaling near-vertical cliffs.</description></item><item><title>Diplopodology (MILLIPEDES &amp; CENTIPEDES) with Dr. Derek Hennen | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860081/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 01:49:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860081/</guid><description>Podcast Description How many legs? Why so many legs? What&amp;rsquo;s a millipede versus a centipede? And again WHY SO MANY LEGS. We have just the guy for that: Diplopodologist Dr. Derek Hennen. As a person who’s spent over a decade sorting through leaf litter and naming scores of new species, Derek is truly a champion for the multi-limbed little critters. If you liked what Casey Clapp brought to Dendrology, get ready to appreciate millipedes like you never thought you would.</description></item><item><title>Critical Ecology (SOCIAL SYSTEMS + ENVIRONMENT) with Suzanne Pierre | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860082/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 18:24:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860082/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do societal structures affect the planet? Why should we get to know our neighbors? What’s the ecological price we pay for … stuff? Yep, there’s an -ology for that. We chat with the founder of Critical Ecology: biogeochemist, National Geographic Explorer, researcher and plant nerd, Dr. Suzanne Pierre. Dr. Pierre’s Critical Ecology Lab is involved with research on the biomes of former plantations, air pollution, agricultural runoff, and even asking questions about wildfire science and the prison system.</description></item><item><title>Thanatology — NEW Interview (GRIEF &amp; MOURNING) with Cole Imperi + tips for Going Through It | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860083/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860083/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you have a physical body, or know someone who does, this episode is for you! Hello, we’re all going to die. And we’re probably all going to lose someone we love. Thanatologist Cole Imperi has become a dear friend and on July 17, 2022 we pulled up a street corner in LA to chat about what she’s been up to and how to cope with the loss of a loved one.</description></item><item><title>Thanatology (DEATH &amp; DYING) Updated Encore with Cole Imperi | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860084/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 06:16:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860084/</guid><description>Podcast Description As I round out my bereavement leave following your beloved Grandpod’s passing, we’re serving up a special updated Encore of an episode and an Ologist who changed my life. Hoooo boy. We get all up in death and dying&amp;rsquo;s business and to my shock, it&amp;rsquo;s not a bummer. Confront and perhaps OVERCOME existential anxiety as we discuss not only the science of death but the nature and goddang beauty of life.</description></item><item><title>Cheloniology (SEA TURTLES) Encore with Camryn Allen | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860085/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 07:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hope you dug tortoises because we’re back, shellin’ out the good stuff, with this week’s encore of sea turtles, so get ready to become wildly obsessed with them. Cheloniologist Dr. Camryn Allen met up with Alie on a tropical island (ok, in a hotel room on a tropical island) to chat about flipper slappings, turtle rodeos, nesting BBs, current surfing, endangered statuses, field work, sleeping under water, world records, boopable noses, male:female ratios, mind-boggling navigation, what you can do to help them, and the many mysteries that still remain.</description></item><item><title>Testudinology (TORTOISES) Encore with Amanda Hipps | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860086/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 23:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860086/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;re bringing back one shell of an episode with today&amp;rsquo;s encore. What&amp;rsquo;s a tortoise? What&amp;rsquo;s a turtle? Why do they live so dang long? What&amp;rsquo;s up with their junk? Wildlife biologist and testudinologist Amanda Hipps studies gopher tortoises and dishes about turtle nomenclature, cliques, dicks, behavior, burrows, evolution, habitats and more. If you don&amp;rsquo;t dig tortoises yet, you&amp;rsquo;re about to fall deep into a turtle tunnel in love with them.</description></item><item><title>Zymology (BEER) Encore with Quinton Sturgeon | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860087/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 05:52:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nothin&amp;rsquo; like crackin&amp;rsquo; open a cold one with the Ologites, amirite? If you like booze, you&amp;rsquo;ll love&amp;hellip; fungus! Alie goes Rogue and takes a field trip to a brewery in Newport, OR where she smells vats of bubbling beer slop and learns about the microorganisms that are the workhorses of the brewing industry. Learn about yeasts, how beer is made, the hardest part about being a beer maker, the thick history of beer, some home brewing tips and also a nugget about bungholes.</description></item><item><title>Personality Psychology (PERSONALITIES) Encore with Simine Vazire | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860088/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 07:39:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860088/</guid><description>Podcast Description A few personal updates from your internet dad and then … WHO ARE WE? This one is a banger, folks. Personality researcher &amp;amp; psychology professor Dr. Simine Vazire dishes about introverts, extroverts, self-esteem, sociopaths, neuroticism, conscientiousness, Buzzfeed quizzes, yearbook inscriptions, trusting people, screwing up your kids, acting like your parents, changing personality traits through therapy or medication and astrology being put to the test. Also, Alie finds out what kind of dog she is.</description></item><item><title>Smologies #14: ALIENS with Kevin Peter Hand | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860089/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 07:26:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860089/</guid><description>Podcast Description A Smologies kid-friendly version of… ALIENS! EXTRATERRESTRIALS! MARTIANS! The phenomenal Dr. Kevin Peter Hand of NASA&amp;rsquo;s Jet Propulsion Laboratory dishes on the oceans of distant moons, methane rivers, ice crusts, the James Webb Space Telescope findings, what might be out there, aliens, what elements a planet needs to sustain life, and how finding extraterrestrial microbes would change the way we see life on this here tiny blue dot in space.</description></item><item><title>Lutrinology (OTTERS) with Chris J. Law | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860090/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 08:22:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860090/</guid><description>Podcast Description YOU’RE NOT READY. But it’s time. Otters. Sea otters. River otters. Big beefy otters. Tiny otters. Giant river otters. Otters chasing you down the street. Dr. Chris J. Law, a professional Lutrinologist, shares tales about coastal vs. inland otters, otter terrorism, magical teeth, lustrous fur, rock pockets, kelp naps, otter terrorism, cautionary motherhood, toxic relationships, hand holding and why otters make you trust them, despite the fact that you should perhaps not trust an otter.</description></item><item><title>SUMMERSODE: Balmy Vibes &amp; Seasonal Factoids with various Ologists | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860091/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 23:45:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860091/</guid><description>Podcast Description I NEEDED TO MAKE THIS, OKAY? I needed to get excited about summer wonders. So we toiled over the ultimate Summersode. Kick back for a compilation of snorkeling tips, shark statistics, firefly safaris, constitutional law questions, the science of makeouts, appreciation for hornets, horniness for foraging, cabins, campfires, crevice checking, jellyfish tips, bear safety, the importance of handwritten memories and actual scientific advice on how to find joy amid difficult conditions.</description></item><item><title>Smologies #13: CORALS with Shayle Matsuda | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860092/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 02:30:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Another kid-safe, short episode of Smologies! What IS a coral? Where do they grow and what do they eat and why are they so pretty? What kind of tools do coral scientists use? Why are they so many colors? And what is bleaching? Will changing your sunscreen save coral reefs? The wonderful and charming Cnidariologist Dr. Shayle Matsuda took time out of his busy schedule during a coral spawning event to chat about how magical and beautiful coral can be and why reef health is important.</description></item><item><title>Dipterology (FLIES) with Bryan Lessard | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860093/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 20:46:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860093/</guid><description>Podcast Description DO NOT YOU SKIP THIS ONE. Listen. Give flies a chance. Everyone loves a bee, but meanwhile flies are out here with all kinds of bodies and adaptations, inhabiting the least inhabitable lands, pollinating your future lunch, shimmering in rainbows, having lifelong love affairs, and burrowing in your back to eat your flesh. It’s a wild world and Australian Dipterologist Dr. Bryan Lessard creaks open a door to a wonderland of fly facts.</description></item><item><title>Gorillaology (GORILLAS) with Tara Stoinski | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860094/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 06:52:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fresh new episode! Gorillas. These chest-beating, salad-munching, communal living, thick-furred beauties have so many surprises for you. (Don&amp;rsquo;t get this confused with the earlier Primatology episode because this is all new and zeros in on two species of critically endangered ape!) Gorillaologist (IT’S A WORD) Dr. Tara Stoinski has been a gorilla scientist for nearly 3 decades and dishes on everything from fieldwork in cloudy mountains to dick facts, forest farts, banana flim-flam, the intersection of animal conservation and community investment, night-time nesting, grief, what those big teeth are for, gorilla musk, the legacy of primatologist Dr.</description></item><item><title>Somnology (SLEEP) Part Two Encore with Dr. W. Chris Winter | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860095/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 05:01:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you listened to Part 1 yet? No? Go on, git. Here&amp;rsquo;s a link to it! Go do that.
Now if you have, this Part 2 is a bonanza of problem solving from neurologist and somnologist Dr. W. Chris Winter. He&amp;rsquo;ll cover: if you should be taking sleep supplements or pills, sleep talking, apnea, why sleepiness makes us hungry, narcolepsy, the difference between insomnia and sleep deprivation, how to lucid dream, the dangers of shift work and some tactics to lull yourself to dreamland without any medications.</description></item><item><title>Smologies #12: EATING BUGS with Julie Lesnik | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860096/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 06:39:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bugs are cool! But are they lunch? Entomophagy Anthropologist Dr. Julie Lesnik is an expert on bug eating and enthusiastically explains how much more sustainable – and tasty? &amp;ndash; it is than other types of animal proteins. We talk about the human past, present and future of ingesting insects, from grasshopper tacos to ant omelettes, cricket wedding cakes, humane bug slaughter, water conservation, arthropod allergies, and the cultural biases that are literally killing us.</description></item><item><title>Somnology (SLEEP) Part One Encore with Dr. W. Chris Winter | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860097/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 08:05:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Birds do it. Bees do it. Why the hell can&amp;rsquo;t we do it? Called &amp;ldquo;The Sleep Whisperer,&amp;rdquo; neurologist and sleep specialist Dr. W. Chris Winter joins for an updated encore of the thrilling 2-parter about why we need sleep, the ideal amount of it, what sleep does to the brain, insomnia, sleep stages, ideal bedtime conditions, and even the historical lore around sleep paralysis. Next week, we&amp;rsquo;ll answer listener questions about everything from sleeping pills to brain performance to insomnia cures to apnea to sleepwalking to parenthood and shift work.</description></item><item><title>Conotoxinology (CONE SNAIL VENOM) with Joshua Torres &amp; Sabah Ul-Hasan | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 05:28:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Predatory. Sneaky. Deadly. Lifesavers? You think you don’t care about cone snails. But that’s about to change. Conotoxinologists Dr. Sabah Ul-Hasan and Dr. Joshua Torres study these spiral-shelled hunters of the sea. Why all the fuss? Because their venom – and the microbes that live in it — may hold medical magic that can help us solve problems related to pain and insulin and much more. Also: how long can you live after a cigarette snail strikes you?</description></item><item><title>Urology (CROTCH PARTS) with Fenwa Milhouse | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860099/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 08:06:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860099/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’ve done Nephrology, Gynecology, and Phallology — but nothing prepared us for this. Penis implants. Road trip pees. Kegels. Bidets. Squirting. UTIs. Clitoral flim-flam. Elephant bladders. Everyone’s favorite Urologist, Dr. Fenwa Milhouse, makes chatting about the uh, juicy stuff effortless and easy. Like peeing should be. She humbly describes herself as a crotch plumber, but she’s so much more: a surgeon, a mentor and an inspiration.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Acoustic Ecology (NATURE RECORDINGS) with Eddie Game | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860100/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 03:28:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Insects humming. Birds squawking. Chainsaws buzzing? What does the rainforest sound like? Or the oceans outside of port cities? Is the world getting louder? And what can recording devices detect that our ears – especially mine, Alie’s – can’t? Acoustic Ecologist Dr. Eddie Game of the Nature Conservancy has asked conservation questions over decades of work in 20 countries, and even though his microphone for this interview sucked, his stories and wisdom are a pleasure to hear.</description></item><item><title>Classical Archaeology (ANCIENT ROME) Encore with Darius Arya | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860101/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 08:08:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860101/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you LIVE for drama, you will LOVE dead Romans. Wars, backstabbing, opulence and uprisings: a little something for everyone. Classical Archeologist and TV host Dr. Darius Arya is back for an encore of this 2018 classic to dish about priceless garbage piles, lead poisoning, ancient political scandals, pottery graveyards, unearthing sculptures, tomb discoveries, what&amp;rsquo;s under European cities, and how Roman society was a little like America these days.</description></item><item><title>Teuthology (SQUIDS) Encore with Dr. Sarah McAnulty | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860102/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 08:36:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860102/</guid><description>Podcast Description THE SQUIDMOBILE HAS ARRIVED. Get in losers; we’re talking cephalopods. Yes, she drives a vehicle with squid all over it and encourages people to text her, and we have this encore episode to prove it. The world&amp;rsquo;s most impassioned squid nerd, Sarah McAnulty, gets locked in a basement with Alie to talk about cephalopods, alien DNA, camouflage, invisibility cloaks, why cute things make us bonkers, terrible mating strategies, cute and clever ones and why she is so charmed by squid.</description></item><item><title>Environmental Microbiology (TESTING WASTEWATER FOR DISEASES) with Amy Kirby | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860103/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 19:46:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Oh boy. This episode may seeeeem crappy but it is certainly not a waste of your time. We’re not kidding, while the episode is of course wonderful, mostly thanks to our wonderful guests, it is also certainly about poopy wastewater and what we can all learn from it. About those terrific guests: we mostly speak with Dr. Amy E. Kirby, Ph.D., MPH of the frickin’ CDC (yes, that CDC) about the National Wastewater Surveillance System or NWSS.</description></item><item><title>Echinology (SEA URCHINS &amp; SAND DOLLARS) with Rich Mooi | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860104/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 23:13:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860104/</guid><description>Podcast Description The hedgehogs of the sea: echinoids are spiky, spiny, pokey, be-toothed, venomous, mysterious, gorgeous evolutionary marvels. And Dr. Rich Mooi of the California Academy of Arts &amp;amp; Sciences is one of their biggest champions. Come stroll through the offices for a face-to-face encounter with this infectious expert. We talk sand dollars, uni, doves of peace, fire urchins, kelp forests, tiny hats, butt placement, foot eyes and how to find your niche, even if it’s miles below the surface on a rotting log.</description></item><item><title>Carnivorous Phytobiology (MEAT-EATING PLANTS) with Hali’a Eastburn | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860105/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 01:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Flesh hungry plants. The world’s fastest hunters. Botany with brains? Seymour, it’s time to feed because we’re doing meat-eating plants with conservation ecologist and carnivorous phytobiologist, Hali’a Eastburn. Can a Venus Fly Trap digest human flesh? Do frogs think of pitcher plants as home or hell? How fast is a bladderwort? Are scientists anesthetizing plants? Why exactly DID they name a fly trap after the goddess of love? Also: homicidal plant tattoos, nature’s grossest vending machines, and what plants are most goth with a pair of real #bogbitches.</description></item><item><title>LIFE ADVICE: For anyone who is tired &amp; needs some hacks | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860106/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 06:49:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pomodoro timers! Bullet journals! Apps, tips, tricks and philosophies. Also: the most mellow episode ever, recorded late at night in a guest room. Like a cozy duvet of wisdom, this one is full of life hacks for remaining productive &amp;amp; healthy during distracting times. I asked Ologites their best strategies for keeping their brains less burdened and organizing everything from schedules to leftovers to sock drawers.
In quick 5 chapters: Your Hot Bod Needs This Home is Where the Hard Is Wrestling with Father Time Tricking Your Brain to Trick Your Brain Emo Stuff</description></item><item><title>Smologies #11: SNAILS &amp; SLUGS with Jann Vendetti | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860107/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 07:24:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860107/</guid><description>Podcast Description The SMOL version of an ep about smol precious creatures, we&amp;rsquo;re talkin&amp;rsquo; slimy little angels with bellies for feet&amp;hellip; literally! That&amp;rsquo;s what gastropod means! We&amp;rsquo;ve got Dr. Jann Vendetti of the Natural History Museum of LA County to talk with Alie about snail-based beauty products, escargot, urban snails, thousands and thousands of teeth, and whether or not you should adopt a rabbit-sized pet snail.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ferroequinology (TRAINS) Encore with Matt Anderson | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860108/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 01:11:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trains. Locomotives. Choochoos. Bullet trains. Hyperloops. Subways. How fast can they go? How did they change American history? Why do people love them? What should we do with all that abandoned track? Can you marry a train? What&amp;rsquo;s it like to shovel coal into a steam engine?
Alie went off the rails at the Henry Ford Museum in Dearborn, Michigan talking to an official ferroequinologist and curator Matt Anderson &amp;ndash; who confessed to some youthful railroad mischief, delivered a succinct slice of U.</description></item><item><title>Part 2: Attention-Deficit Neuropsychology (ADHD) with How to ADHD, Black Girl Lost Keys, Jahla Osborne + more | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860109/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 04:26:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Did Part 1 leave you informed and now you need a pep talk? Get ready for an absolute banger of an episode with 5 experts: René Brooks of BlackGirlLostKeys.com, TEDTalk speaker and How to ADHD YouTuber Jessica McCabe and neuroscientist Jahla Osborne of University of Michigan. What is it like to get diagnosed? How do you know which medication – if any – is right for you? Why is there such a spike in ADHD diagnoses during the pandemic?</description></item><item><title>Part 1: Attention-Deficit Neuropsychology (ADHD) with Russell Barkley | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860110/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:29:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Focus. Productivity. Relationships. Distraction. Neurodiversity. How do you know if you have ADHD? How can you get others to understand your ADHD brain? What are your treatment options and how can they help? In Part 1, we talk racing thoughts, brilliant brains and the causes and effects of Attention-Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder with the world’s leading expert, Dr. Russell Barkley who is A BIG DEAL. Psychologist, retired professor of clinical psychiatry, author and speaker, Dr.</description></item><item><title>Cycadology (RARE PLANT DRAMA) with Nathalie Nagalingum | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860111/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 04:34:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gather round fellow nerds, you’re about to learn about the wildest not a fern not a bush not a cactus plant you never knew you never knew about: CYCADS. These endangered ancient plants have been around for 270 million years, give or take, and now they’re some of the most valuable vegetation in the world. Come along to learn about these uncomfortably sexy gymnosperms and the international crimes people do to steal them.</description></item><item><title>Carnivore Ecology (LIONS, TIGERS, &amp; BEARS) with Rae Wynn-Grant | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860112/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 05:04:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ah, charismatic megafauna! Teeth, claws, fur, hibernation, bear hugs, hiking, cougar attacks, nature preserves, and living your childhood dreams with Alie’s longtime -ologist crush, Dr. Rae Wynn-Grant. The large carnivore ecologist, researcher and TV presenter tells us all about her field work, what it’s like to stuff a baby bear in your coat, how carnivore plasma may one day save your life, balancing a few different stellar careers at once and the launch of her own PBS podcast, Going Wild.</description></item><item><title>Myrmecology (ANTS) Encore with Dr. Terry McGlynn | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860113/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 11:28:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860113/</guid><description>Podcast Description You have ants. We all have ants, but do we KNOW ants? Get ready for cult-leader queens, bullet ant stings, kitchen pest hacks, the dynamics of a billion-sister megacolony. Dr. Terry McGlynn sits down to have a BIG discussion about itty-bitty creatures in this encore because I was out of town seeing my family and just needed a week off. Learn about tropical ants, urban ants, how they walk on water, which ones are picky eaters, which ones make weird sounds, what ant movies are bunk, and some help-help takeaways.</description></item><item><title>Smologies #10: BODY HEAT with Shane Campbell-Staton | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860114/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 11:20:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bundle up for a smol, classroom-friendly episode with Princeton University evolutionary biologist and Thermophysiologist Dr. Shane Campbell-Staton. You’ll learn about everything from heat tolerance to frostbite, anti-freeze woodfrogs to icy alligators, why some people run hot, why your toes run cold, how a fever is like a honeybee, how geography influences our body composition, why mammoths are big, and why you should grab your hat before running out the door.</description></item><item><title>Indigenous Cuisinology (NATIVE COOKING) with Mariah Gladstone of Indigikitchen | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860115/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 08:07:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shoving elk into a dorm room freezer. The wildest tasting rice. Flower bulbs, acorn whoopie pies, frybread debates, mushroom foraging tips, corn magic, puffball mythology, decolonized diets, squash lasagna, bison harvests, small worlds, Instapots and – most importantly – food sovereignty with the WONDERFUL Indigikitchen cooking show host, environmental scientist Mariah Gladstone, who reminds us all that native foods aren’t a part of a past, but an essential and exciting aspect of the future.</description></item><item><title>Screamology (LOUD VOCALIZATIONS) with Harold Gouzoules | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860116/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 02:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860116/</guid><description>Podcast Description I scream, you scream, we all scream for… a brand new, screaming hot episode of Ologies. Be warned slaps the top of this ep you can fit so many screams in this bad boy. (Seriously though, there’s a lot of screaming in this episode, it’s probably not the one to gently fall asleep to.) What kinds of screams you ask? We got birds, foxes, caterpillars, movie stars, children, James Bond?</description></item><item><title>Bovine Neuropathology (HEADBUTTING) with Nicole Ackermans | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860117/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 09:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Slamming heads together to impress someone: why does this happen? Let’s ask Dr. Nicole Ackermans, whose current job involves receiving sheep heads and painstakingly counting damaged neurons from headbutting concussions. The Neuropathology episode last week gives all the concussion basics, but this one turns the microscope away from accidents and points it right at intentional behaviors in nature, from bighorn sheep to musk oxen, goats, woodpeckers, and some other animals that will freak you out.</description></item><item><title>Smologies #9: GAMING with Jane McGonigal | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860118/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 08:13:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Games! Play! Fun! Addiction? Flim-flam? From the origins of tabletop classics to the future of VR, Dr. Jane McGonigal answers our burning questions. This video game developer, TED speaker and bestselling author is an expert on how playing &amp;ndash; and especially video games &amp;ndash; can motivate, soothe and connect us. Will video games turn your child into a future car thief? How do they make you stronger? How much is too much?</description></item><item><title>Neuropathology (CONCUSSIONS) with Mary Alexis Iaccarino | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860119/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 05:16:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi, last week I fell down a flight of stairs. Then I went to the hospital. Then I emailed Dr. Mary Alexis Iaccarino, a Harvard Medical School professor and specialist in rehabilitation from traumatic brain injuries. I asked her all about what happens during a concussion, when to be worried, how long it takes to heal, when a person should get their ass to a hospital, what a brain scan can tell us about a head injury, what it CAN’T tell us about a head injury, if you can fall asleep after a head injury, and the differences between mTBI, TBI, SRC, CTE and even ATGATT.</description></item><item><title>Raccoonology (PROCYONIDS) with A Gaze of Raccoonologists | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860120/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 01:48:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here we go: SIX more raccoon experts, because one episode is not enough for the wonders of these terrific trash bandits. Revel in the raccoon love and hear about presidential pets, neuronal density, why raccoonologists walk out on the job, their fabled intelligence, how Aesop&amp;rsquo;s Fables factor into raccoonology, and the comfort of the male gaze?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Procyonology (RACCOONS) with Suzanne MacDonald | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860121/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 13:59:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tiny hands! Round rumps! Chaos! Compost! Delicious garbage and sweet faces make raccoons as mysterious as they are adored. World class raccoon expert, psychologist and animal behaviorist Dr. Suzanne MacDonald of Toronto’s York University explains tree sleeping, brain worms, cartoon raccoons, queer icons, whether you should keep one as a pet and also: some of the best career and life advice from midnight gremlins eating chicken bones in your driveway.</description></item><item><title>Smologies #8: HAGFISH with Tim Winegard | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860122/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 09:58:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who doesn&amp;rsquo;t love a floppy, slime-filled, hot dog shaped creature of the deep sea? On this Smologies (It&amp;rsquo;s like if Ologies were more Smol) we return to our conversation with Tim Winegard, a professional hagfishologist (YES IT&amp;rsquo;S A WORD) at Chapman University, and he dishes on the world&amp;rsquo;s slimiest treasures. You&amp;rsquo;re gonna learn about things like why you don&amp;rsquo;t always need a spine and how special ketchup is and, of course, lots and lots about mucus.</description></item><item><title>Genicular Traumatology (BAD KNEES) with Kevin Stone | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860123/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 09:46:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860123/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do your knees feel? How do YOU feel about your knees? Buckle up to better your relationship with what some listeners call their most hated and contentious joint. Globally-lauded orthopedic surgeon Dr. Kevin Stone agreed to sit on a porch and explain everything from cracking to popping, patellas to tendons vs ligaments, cartilage donuts, physical therapy, self-surgery, joint juices, sporty injections, cadaver tissues, pig legs, if weight has any effect on knee health, types of arthritis, bionic body parts, and if knees are really out to get us.</description></item><item><title>Audiobook Mixtape 2: Gift Ideas from the Ologists’ Brains | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860124/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 02:23:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860124/</guid><description>Podcast Description From crisp cider to blistering lava, life advice, climate solutions, the comforts of venison stew, cockroaches in orbit, UFO culture, social justice, dongs, worms, wasps, fireflies, bear orgies, makeouts, disasters, the deep ruts of the patriarchy, and desperate horny bugs. This second-ever “Audiobook Mixtape” has it all. So if you’re near a fireplace but have no book, or haven’t started holiday shopping (like your dear old Dadward VonPodcast) let this casserole of literary snippets serve as a refresher of favorite episodes, a teaser for ones you haven’t heard or just a gentle nudge toward a bookshop.</description></item><item><title>Smologies #7: CATS with Mikel Delgado | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860125/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 06:31:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860125/</guid><description>Podcast Description CATS! Kittens. Tigers. Purring. Toys. Litterboxes. We cover it all in this abridged and G-rated Felinology version for Smologites, or just anyone who doesn’t want to listen to swearing with their science. Professional cat behavior expert Dr. Mikel Delgado dishes on domestication, cats on leashes, why they want to sit on your laptop, how to play with cats the right way, if tigers make biscuits, and so much more.</description></item><item><title>Forensic Ecology (NATURE DETECTIVE) with Tiara Moore | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860126/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 04:22:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yep &amp;ndash; it’s detective work! But instead of crime scenes, environmental scientist, marine biologist and Forensic Ecologist Dr. Tiara Moore travels the world to sample the sea and the soil looking for the ghosts of larvae past, whispers of frog spit, fungal traces in loamy soil, and the unseen forces that lead to algal blooms and toxic tides. She also is the CEO of #BlackInMarineScience week, which is NOW: Nov.</description></item><item><title>Booster Coronasode: Shots &amp; Holidays with Vaccine Infodemiologist Jessica Malaty Rivera | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860127/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 11:15:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860127/</guid><description>Podcast Description You’re six to ten times LESS likely to catch COVID-19 if you’re vaccinated, and thus less likely to infect others. Great! But what about breakthrough cases? Who’s at risk for them? How many folks haven’t gotten vaccinated? Should pregnant people get the ol’ jab, what might happen with transmission rates in 2022, yearly booster questions, the ethics of vaccine distribution, myocarditis, Long COVID, quarantine fatigue and essentially whether the holidays are a good idea.</description></item><item><title>Smologies #6: WOLVES with Bridgett vonHoldt | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860128/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 07:27:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wolf howls, wolf packs, wolf history and more! November 23 is the dog appreciation holiday Wolfenoot so we’re dishing up a puppy-sized and kid-friendly Smologies with lupinologist and Princeton professor Dr. Brigette vonHoldt. Learn about wolf populations, canine family dynamics, Game of Thrones direwolves, if wolves howl at the moon, myths and truths about alphas, and how you can help our lupine friends.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tiktokology (THE TIKTOK APP) with Hank Green | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860129/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 06:44:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who’s on it? What’s on it? And why does the interface feel like you’re on a prank show? Scicomm host, vlogger, author, internet friend, and TikTok-maker Hank Green stops in to chat about learning the language of the algorithm, dopamine, duets, data concerns, idealized selves, self-expression, mental health, authenticity,work/ life boundaries. And just a bunch of milk.
Follow Hank at TikTok.com/@hankgreen1, Twitter.com/HankGreen, https://www.instagram.com/hankgreen/ Alie Dadward aka me on TikTok https://www.</description></item><item><title>Dolorology (PAIN) with Rachel Zoffness | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860130/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860130/</guid><description>Podcast Description PAIN. What is it? Where does it come from? And how can we hurt less? Which hurts more, a kidney stone or heartache? Why does chronic pain persist? Can we turn down our pain dials? To answer these huge questions, pain psychologist Dr. Rachel Zoffness enthusiastically explains the brain, pain and how to retrain it. She is an unabashed neuronerd and a ray of hope in a field that is misunderstood, neglected and under-explained.</description></item><item><title>Teuthological Ludology (ACTUAL SQUID GAMES, NOT THE TV SHOW) with Sarah McAnulty | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860131/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 02:53:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Boy howdy&amp;hellip; Squid games. We know we weren&amp;rsquo;t the only ones watching Squid Game and thinking, &amp;ldquo;Do squid play games?&amp;rdquo; Hence we combined the study of squids (teuthology) and games (ludology) to make Teuthological Ludology with everyone&amp;rsquo;s favorite squid expert: Dr. Sarah McAnulty from the 2018 Teuthology episode. We reunited on mic to discuss things like shapeshifting, flirtatious trickery, living fishing lure, siphon squirts, weird things found in shark stomachs, and cephalopods who are downright dicks to fish.</description></item><item><title>Smologies #5: VETERINARY BIOLOGY with Vernard Hodges &amp; Terrence Ferguson | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860132/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 21:56:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860132/</guid><description>Podcast Description At long last: an episode dedicated to veterinary medicine! Dr. Terrence Ferguson &amp;amp; Dr. Vernard Hodges have been friends for nearly 30 years and have co-owned their rural Georgia veterinary clinic, Critter Fixers, for over 20 years. The two wonderful buddies talk about getting accepted into vet school, caring for spiders &amp;amp; camels &amp;amp; lizards &amp;amp; toads &amp;amp; kittens &amp;amp; doggos, the weirdest things they’ve extracted from animal tummies, if our pets love us back, keeping kidneys healthy, grain-free diets, what to do if your (Alie’s) dog is plumping up by a few pounds, what they wish animal owners knew, when it’s time to let go vs.</description></item><item><title>Taphology (GRAVESITES) with Robyn S. Lacy | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860133/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 06:21:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bidding farewell to the sweetest and spookiest month, we traipse past graves with archeologist, conservator and Taphologist Robyn Lacy. What’s the difference between a graveyard and a cemetery? Is it wrong to picnic in one? And can tombstone scrubbing help the world and soothe your living soul? Plus, font trends on headstones, old-timey gravestone emojis, a coffin-within-a-coffin, the best epitaphs and knowing the difference between slate, marble, and granite monuments.</description></item><item><title>Kinetic Salticidology (DANCING SPIDERS) with Sebastian Echeverri | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860134/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 07:41:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chiropterology Part 2 (BATS) Encore with Merlin Tuttle | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860135/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 22:22:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860135/</guid><description>Podcast Description PART 2: The stunning conclusion of a 3-hour gab session about frickin&amp;rsquo; bats with America&amp;rsquo;s favorite chiropterologist, Dr. Merlin Tuttle. Learn about bat conversations, their close friendships, surprising dongs, where they keep their nipples, how to go bat spotting after the sun sets, more myths and misconceptions about bat danger, perhaps the grossest thing Merlin has ever put in his mouth, how to hang up a bat house for maximum bat party funtimes, the latest on white nose syndrome and how it feels to get slapped by a bat.</description></item><item><title>Chiropterology (BATS) Encore with Merlin Tuttle | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860136/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 22:15:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860136/</guid><description>Podcast Description “People fear most what they understand least.&amp;quot; Words of wisdom from explorer/American treasure/bat expert, Dr. Merlin Tuttle. As your internet dad/host takes care of her surgically recuperating husband this week, we revisit her visit to Austin. In 2019, Alie headed to the bat capital and sat down with the legendary chiropterologist to discuss wild field stories and close calls and caves and comebacks and bat chatter and what a bat actually is and how big they get and what&amp;rsquo;s up with their smushy noses, why folks are so frightened by them, the evolution of flight, echolocation, getting a bat out of your house, how they sleep upside down, which ones guzzle blood, and the latest on white nose syndrome &amp;ndash; which is not a drug problem.</description></item><item><title>Corvid Thanatology (CROW FUNERALS) Encore with Kaeli Swift | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860137/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 04:41:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Crows have funerals? CROWS HAVE FUNERALS. The inky black bird with the big brain warns and maybe mourns around their fallen friends and Dr. Kaeli Swift is here to tell us all about it. As an avid wildlife researcher and corvid specialist, she&amp;rsquo;s observed death behaviors that will shock you to your bones and ruffle your hackles &amp;ndash; while somehow also making you cry about peanuts. Also: so much inspiration to keep being yourself and to work hard toward what you love.</description></item><item><title>Pyrotechnology (FIREMAKING) with Ellery Frahm | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860138/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 11:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860138/</guid><description>Podcast Description Grab your fire extinguisher and hang on to your eyebrows, we’re building FIRES today. Now, this is pyrotechnology in the anthropological sense; the kind covered in hair metal concert venue liability insurance will have to wait for another day, no no, these are the kind your ancestors made. Get ready for sharp rocks, hairy jello, sooty caves, glowing coals, iron sparks, burnt feet, wolf skulls, fluffy fungus, molten metal, ember tending and more with Yale anthropologist and pyrotechnologist, Dr.</description></item><item><title>Opossumology (O/POSSUMS) with Lisa Walsh | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860139/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 08:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teeth. Tails. Concentric nipples. This not-at-all-rodent has the distinction of being North America’s sole marsupial and so Alie hunted down lauded Opossumologist Dr. Lisa Walsh and launched an absolute torrent of giddy questions. How many ticks do they really eat, can we keep them as pets, how do we all convincingly feign death, opossum vs. possum, fingerprints, orphaned babies, the best possum jokes, the worst ones, venom immunity, bifurcated dongs, space portal vageens, being equally ugly and adorable, the rise of the memes, why we scream at our own asses, and more.</description></item><item><title>Ciderology (DELICIOUS APPLE BEVERAGE) with Gabe Cook | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860140/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 02:35:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860140/</guid><description>Podcast Description How ya like them apples?! Well, liquified. And fermented. Author, podcaster, cider-maker and globally lauded beverage historian Gabe Cook, aka The Ciderologist, is an enthusiastic champion of this tragically overlooked drink, and he joins with a bushel full of facts, well-spun yarns and tasting tips. Belly up for a foaming glass of friendly competition, bucolic farmhouses, DIY cider tips, film flam busters, cider recommendations from a pro, and a little ASMR.</description></item><item><title>Eudemonology (HAPPINESS) with Laurie Santos | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860141/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860141/</guid><description>Podcast Description HAPPINESS RESEARCH, straight up. What is happiness? How do our circumstances affect happiness? Why is the word “gratitude” kinda cringey? What can we do to feel better? Should we feel guilty for feeling happy? When is positivity “toxic?” Yale cognitive scientist, Eudemonologist, and host of The Happiness Lab podcast Dr. Laurie Santos chats about how scientists measure human happiness and what their research has shown helps achieve it, even during the worst of times.</description></item><item><title>Spesh Ep: Drawdown Design Project with C. Andrew Hall | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860142/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 07:04:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Art meets science! Problems meet solutions! Climate change meets … hope? In this atypical episode, things get casual as hell as Alie sits down to talk about the Drawdown Design Project: an illustration non-profit started by filmmaker, Emmy-nominated television editor and longtime friend Andy Hall. When he’s not having to edit Alie on Innovation Nation, Andy is the founder and creative director of the Drawdown Design Project, which commissioned some of the world’s most sought-after artists to illustrate climate solutions outlined by Drawdown.</description></item><item><title>Is Your Carbon Footprint BS?: How to Save a Planet takes over Ologies | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860143/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 05:24:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Ayana Elizabeth Johnson. You loved her Oceanology episode and now she is in your feed to address everyone’s agonizing internal question: IS MY CARBON FOOTPRINT BS?! I don’t drop a lot of podcast episodes into my precious Ologies feed, but this topic was so wonderfully covered by Dr. Johnson and co-hot Alex Blumberg that I had to do it. And as a bonus, stay tuned for Wednesday’s episode between me and my old friend C.</description></item><item><title>Smologies #4: BEES with Amanda Shaw | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860144/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 07:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860144/</guid><description>Podcast Description YA LIKE BEES? You will &amp;ndash; after this short, edited-for-all-ages Smologies cut of our classic Melittology episode featuring President of the Urban Beekeepers Association, Amanda “Mandy” Shaw. We chat about honeybees vs. native ones, hives vs. nests, honey, how to become a beekeeper, social structures, why a queen becomes a queen, how to keep Mason bees as outdoor pets, if you should eat honey to deal with seasonal allergies, and why planting some flowers could make you and the bees pretty happy.</description></item><item><title>Indigenous Fire Ecology (GOOD FIRE) with Amy Christianson | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860145/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 07:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cultural burns. Prescribed blazes. A healthy forest. What exactly is “good fire?” Let’s ask Indigenous fire scientist Dr. Amy Christianson, who is a co-host of the podcast &amp;hellip;Good Fire. This wonderfully generous and informed scholar took a quick break from her Canadian wilderness vacation to fill me in on Indigenous history, collaborations between Western science &amp;amp; First Nations elders, Aboriginal thoughts on cultural burns, flim-flam, evacuations, snowmelt, hunting strategies, land stewardship, happy trees, climate strategies, and the social science behind wildfire education.</description></item><item><title>Fire Ecology (WILDFIRES) with Gavin Jones | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860146/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860146/</guid><description>Podcast Description As Smashmouth said, “My world’s on fire, how ‘bout yours?” Why yes, Mr. Mouth, it is, indeed, on fire. As so many of us around the globe are sharing in this burning sensation, what better time than now to sit down and fire off a lot of questions at Fire Ecologist, Dr. Gavin Jones. We talk about what fire is, how hot it burns, fire trends, tinderboxes, lots and lots of forest fire flim-flam, tolerant wombats, Angelina Jolie Movies, cunning pine cones, thick bark, Indigenous fire stewardship and more.</description></item><item><title>Smologies #3: TOADS with Priya Nanjappa | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860147/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 06:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ohaaay another edited-down, classroom-friendly Smologies! About&amp;hellip; toads! Are they frogs? Do they have arms? What do they eat? How long do they live? What’s with the warts? Amphibian enthusiast Priya Nanjappa joins with a toadally awesome episode that will change the way you crouch down and shake hands with your tiny backyard grumpa.(And for the full version with NSFW stories, the link is below.)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Systems Biology (MEDICAL MATHEMATICS) with Emily E. Ackerman | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860148/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 21:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Biological mysteries solved with numbers! Graphs! Patterns! Data points! Systems biology! You never knew it existed, yet it’s keeping us alive. Systems Biologist Dr. Emily E. Ackerman join to chat about why the field appealed to her, how her work shifted during the pandemic, why she wants to scream at Excel sometimes, how computing might replace specific types of animal testing, accessibility in STEM, the immune system, why she loves being a disabled scientist and advocate, the ethics of CRISPR, and some really nice guy named Doug.</description></item><item><title>Lampyridology (FIREFLIES) aka Sparklebuttology with Sara Lewis | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860149/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 08:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860149/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re BACK! With a fresh new episode to light up your life and butt. World renowned firefly expert Dr. Sara Lewis of Tufts University joins to share her love of a bug that many think is merely a mythological delight. Learn how these tiny animals illuminate the night, the dos and don’ts of firefly observation, how to take good firefly photos, femme fatales, pink glowworms, secret languages, artificial lights, what’s up with their population numbers, why Western states can chill out with their lightning bug envy, and how you can ensure the world stays aglow with these beloved bugs.</description></item><item><title>Smologies #1: THE MOON with Selenologist Raquel Nuno | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860151/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 02:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Introducing… SMOLOGIES. Smaller, shorter, G-rated episodes cut from your favorite classics. Listen to Smologies in classrooms, around people whose language is squeaky clean, and in safe-for-work settings. You get bite-sized info in a jiffy, and I get to reserve my filthy language for our longer, regular episodes that drop on Tuesdays. In this episode, planetary geologist Raquel Nuno chats about when the moon formed, what its made of, how moon phases work, gravity, conspiracy theories debunked, the far side of the moon, lunar caves and why she pulls out the telescope to stare at the sky every night.</description></item><item><title>Smologies #2: DINOSAURS with Paleontologist Michael Habib | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860150/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 02:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yes, a double dose of short, all-ages episodes to launch Smologies! We cleaned up the full version and polished it into a safe-for-work digest of dinosaur facts and tales from a paleontologist with Dr. Michael Habib. Learn about the economics of a dino dig, his favorite beasts, cloning from amber samples, which museum dinos are real vs. fakes, Jurassic Park flimflam and more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Elasmobranchology (MORE NEW SHARK STORIES) with MISS_Elasmo Shark Scientists | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860152/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 08:25:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lemon sharks! Goblin sharks! Bonnet sharks! Whale sharks! And &amp;hellip;sawfish? WE NEEDED A BIGGER BOAT. One shark episode was not enough, during this: The Week of the Shark. Sure, Alie just got married a few days ago, but that doesn’t mean we can’t throw together this bundle of wonder with a few of the incredible researchers from Minorities in Shark Science. Get ready to befriend Jaida Elcock, Jasmin Graham, and Amani Webber-Schultz as they spin yarns about wild field stories, explain why they love sharks, debunk common flim flams, quote favorite shark flicks, and make sure appreciate the stunning diversity and evolution of these ancient creatures.</description></item><item><title>Selachimorphology (SHARKS) Encore with Chris Lowe | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860153/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 23:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860153/</guid><description>Podcast Description SHAAAARKS. Leading shark researcher Dr. Chris Lowe dishes about bad shark PR, behind-the-scenes Jaws trivia, his thoughts on Sharknado, surfing safety, immune system marvels, cannibal twins, shark personalities, sea sex, and knife teeth in this, an encore-but-refreshed episode with your newly married pod-dad. Alie learns that sharks are not the ocean&amp;rsquo;s a-holes but true evolutionary marvels who suffer from sensationalized reputations and sometimes inside-out butts. Listen up as a science primer during this, the holy Week of the Shark.</description></item><item><title>Matrimoniology (MARRIAGE) Encore with Ben Karney | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860154/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 07:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860154/</guid><description>Podcast Description A special encore as your dad hastily preps to wed your podmom, Jarrett. Refresh your brain about your heart, then stay tuned for a new secret at the end.
Love! Romance! Intimate relationships! Marriage! Divorce! Remarriage! Clowns! This episode has it all. The wonderfully warm Dr. Benjamin Karney of the UCLA Marriage lab has been studying romance and intimate relationships for 20 years and sits down to chat about being single and the mechanisms behind finding a partner, what behaviors foster intimacy, why some couples stay together vs.</description></item><item><title>UFOlogy (UNEXPLAINED AERIAL PHENOMENA) with Sarah Scoles and Kate Dorsch | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860155/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 23:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860155/</guid><description>Podcast Description UFOs are real. Straight up. There are unidentified objects flying around — but does that mean they’re aliens? Two experts in the research and culture of Unexplained Aerial Phenomena (UAPs) &amp;ndash; science journalist/author Sarah Scoles and Dr. Kate Dorsch, a scholar in the History and Sociology of Science &amp;ndash; joined Alie moments after Friday’s breaking news of the Pentagon’s UAP report. Strap in for “tic tacs,” space rocks, black triangles, fighter pilot sightings, Roswell, abduction trends, secret military missions, surprising conclusions, and the -ologists’ own wacky field experience researching UFOs … and the people obsessed with hunting town the truth.</description></item><item><title>Spheksology (WASPS) with Eric Eaton | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860156/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wasps!? Don’t even THINK of skipping this one, my beautiful chickens. You’re about to change your outlook on the most maligned winged sky babies, and we are delighted that author, bug dude, and spheksologist Eric Eaton is about to change your mind and fill your heart with respect and appreciation. Hunker down for fig critters, bejeweled zombie queens, bug corsets, underdogs, BBQ tips, gardening secrets, stinger myths and snack vaults.</description></item><item><title>Quarantinology (UM, WHAT HAPPENS NOW?) with Various Ologists | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860157/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 12:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860157/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lifted restrictions! Discarded masks! Vaxxing &amp;amp; relaxing! Parties. Variant confusion. FOMO while also dreading events. Worry about strangers. Grief for a cancelled year. WHAT’S HAPPENING HERE? We’ve got you covered. As infection rates go down and restrictions lift in the U.S., you may feel: relieved, overjoyed, nude without a mask, guilty about surviving, conflicted about gatherings, or mourning a loss. We gathered a small army of experts to chat about historical quarantines and recovery periods, vaccine rates, economic projections, the mental state of healthcare workers and the grief that can follow an historical event.</description></item><item><title>Wildlife Ecology (FIELDWORK) with Corina Newsome | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860158/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 11:07:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860158/</guid><description>Podcast Description Human-sucking mud holes. Beautiful birdsongs. Early mornings. Eyeball gnats. Stunning vistas. The long-awaited episode with ornithologist Corina Newsome is finally here and we talk all about the day-to-day-realities of being a Wildlife Ecologist. She dishes about working in zoos, getting her masters, housing for grad students, nest checking, birding apps, camera traps, #BlackBirdersWeek, and more. She is hilarious, informative, and dedicated to her work in avian conservation and truly has the best laugh.</description></item><item><title>Phallology (PENISES) with Emily Willingham | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860159/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 08:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dongs. Schlongs. Peters. Intromittent organs. Gamete cannons. Biologist, gonad researcher, and Phallologist Dr. Emily Willingham joins to chat about peckers big and small, plain and fancy, barbed, coiled, colossal, pickled, and efficient. Also on the agenda: how the pressures of masculinity affect self-image, what actually contributes to a partner’s pleasure, what can cause willies to go wonky (and how to get back on track,) life beyond the binary, and sensual turtles.</description></item><item><title>Pinnipedology (SEALS &amp; WALRUSES) with Luis A. Hückstädt | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860160/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 08:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860160/</guid><description>Podcast Description Seals. Sea lions. Walruses. Walrus dongs. Classic Ologies. We sit down with Luis A Hückstädt, PhD and talk about blubber, ocean currents, psychedelic teeth, whisker tech, receding ice, boops, snoots, barks, butt nubbins and whether or not that one seal from the video actually felt bashful about getting that fish cake? Or was it a sea lion? Which is which? Spoiler: you’ll find out in this episode of Ologies: Pinnipedology.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Feed Drop: Implicit Bias on the REAL GOOD podcast | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860161/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 04:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860161/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ohulloh! This is not your regular Ologies episode (which will come on Tuesday per usual.) It’s actually not an Ologies episode! This is a fun little bonus GUEST podcast we&amp;rsquo;re dropping in our feed. Real Good is a show that started during the beginning of COVID to highlight different non-profits helping with the pandemic — but soon revealed that many problems that became so acute during quarantine had existed in people&amp;rsquo;s lives for a long time prior.</description></item><item><title>Foraging Ecology (EATING WILD PLANTS) with @BlackForager, Alexis Nikole Nelson | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860162/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 10:11:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860162/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mustard gossip. Knotweed recipes. Cow parsnips. Serviceberry appreciation. Hogweed warnings. Dead man’s fingers. The incredibly knowledgeable and entertaining Alexis Nikole Nelson a.k.a. @BlackForager walks us through Foraging Ecology with a ginormous bushel of tips &amp;amp; tricks for finding edibles at all times of the year, from blossoms to fungus. Belly up for some invasive snacks, elusive mushrooms, magnolia cookies, mugwort potatoes, violet cocktails, foraging guides, weed trivia and tips to avoid poisonous berries.</description></item><item><title>Biomineralogy (SHELLS) with Robert Ulrich | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860163/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 03:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bones. Shells. Reefs. Teeth. Biomineralogy. The wonderful UCLA geochemist Rob Ulrich answers a giant pile of questions such as: How do crystalline structures materialize out of thin air and water? How do squishy animals make such hard shells? What’s the difference between a shell and an exoskeleton? What’s the noise you hear when you listen to a seashell? What’s up with ocean acidification? How do you keep a fiddle leaf tree alive?</description></item><item><title>Speech Language Pathology (TALKING DOGS... AND PEOPLE) with Christina Hunger | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860164/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 06:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860164/</guid><description>Podcast Description Talking dogs. Rolled Rs. That dangly thing in the back of your throat. Speech impediments. Alternative forms of communication. And talking cats. World famous speech pathologist by day, dog whisperer also by day, Christina Hunger MA, CCC-SLP joins us to talk about what those letters after her name mean, helping people literally find their voice, AAC (Augmentative and Alternative Communication), different types of language and communication, and how she applied the same principles to gift her dog with the ability to emotionally manipulate her.</description></item><item><title>Maritime Archaeology (SHIPWRECKS) with Chanelle Zaphiropoulos | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860165/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 06:35:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shipwrecks. Treasure. Sunken planes. Scuttled submarines. New life forming around old machinery. There’s an -ology for that &amp;ndash; just ask Maritime Archaeologist and wreck nerd Chanelle Zaphiropoulos. This absolutely charming and passionate scuba diver, history buff and antiquities scholar dishes about pirates, warships, admirals worth admiring, and ships ranging in size from water taxis to the Costa Concordia and Titanic. Also world record diving stats, war graves, how owning a fountain pen can be egregious and why a Midwestern coal barge from the 1970’s is worthy of weeping over.</description></item><item><title>Proptology (THEATER &amp; FILM PROPS) with Jay Duckworth | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860166/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 23:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860166/</guid><description>Podcast Description Real skulls. Fake pistols. Vegan steaks. Onstage bonfires. Cursed productions. Industry secrets and more with the world’s most lovable and beloved prop master, Professor Jay Duckworth aka @Proptologist on TikTok. A veteran of stage and screen and now an adjunct professor at Pace University, Jay chats about props vs. wardrobe vs. set design, how he keeps tracks of the thousands of items used to make a set feel real, what it was like to work on Hamilton from the very beginning, a prop master’s tool belt, design heroes, the importance of art &amp;ndash; and sanitation workers &amp;ndash; and why you should always carry a Moleskein notebook.</description></item><item><title>Ursinology Part 2 (BEARS) with Thea Bechshoft, Lana Ciarniello, Drew Hamilton, Wes Larson, Tsalani Lassiter &amp; Danielle Rivet | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860167/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 11:46:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Because one bears is not enough bears, SIX more ursinologists join to answer your questions about polar bear fur, monogamy, that scene from &amp;ldquo;The Revenant&amp;rdquo; and more. Five chapters of bear life, from mindblowing mating strategies to how bears get from point A to B, media portrayals of these beautiful beasts and how to save them. Also: do bears want you to sing to them? Bear biologists and conservationists Dr.</description></item><item><title>Ursinology (BEARS) with Chris Morgan | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860168/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 06:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Grizzlies. Pandas. Black bears. Chonkers. The episode you’ve begged for with scientist, explorer, and Ursinologist Chris Morgan. Why are bear ears so cute? What’s up with hibernation? How do you play nice with bears? What is it like to hug them? How creepy is Teddy Ruxpin? Panda patterns, fat bear competitions, tooth nubbins, land “bridges,” camping tips and more with host of “The Wild” podcast and your new favorite bedtime story teller.</description></item><item><title>Oology (EGGS) Encore + Bonus Material with John Bates | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860169/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 05:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860169/</guid><description>Podcast Description This encore includes tons of previously cut and never-before-heard bonus material (and maybe an eggregious number of sidenotes) about how perfect and weird eggs are. The biggest eggs! The smallest eggs! The people arrested for stealing the most eggs! Oologist Dr. John Bates gives Alie a tour of the egg vault at the Field Museum of Chicago and it was a barrage of beautiful sights and shocking facts about bird butts.</description></item><item><title>Fanthropology Pt. 2 (FANDOM) with Meredith Levine | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860170/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 08:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860170/</guid><description>Podcast Description PART 2 with legit professional Fanthropologist Meredith Levine. In this thrilling conclusion, we take Patreon questions and address stans vs. fans, cults and fandom, how fan fiction circumvents the studio system, how showrunners feel about fan suggestions, fangirling, fanboying and a novel term for that plus a bonus tables-are-turned interview about your weird dad’s favorite stuff. Fanthroplogy: a riveting field. Once again, WHO KNEW? Meredith did. Listen to Part 1 here: alieward.</description></item><item><title>Fanthropology (FANDOM) with Meredith Levine | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860171/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 17:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860171/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why does some music give us butterflies? Why do we loooove certain comic books, social media accounts or TV characters? What story does your toothpaste tell? Legit professional Fanthropologist Meredith Levine is a fount of fandom knowledge and we chat all about everything from cosplay to K-Pop, Star Wars, Frasier, Trekkies, fan-fic, how influencer culture works, the algorithms, and how loving what we love is a form of self-care.</description></item><item><title>Nephrology (KIDNEYS) with Samira Farouk | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860172/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 22:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860172/</guid><description>Podcast Description What’s in pee? Should you donate a kidney to a stranger? Which hurts worse: childbirth or kidney stones? Why are some kidneys the size of footballs? March is World Kidney Month and before you shrug it off: 15% of adults have chronic kidney disease &amp;ndash; and most don’t even know it. This episode could save a life. Transplant Nephrologist Dr. Samira Farouk chats about how nephrology is for cool kids, how transplant chains work, legends about bathtubs filled with ice, how dialysis works, where nephrology ends and urology begins, how much water you should drink and why kidney punches aren’t allowed in boxing.</description></item><item><title>Cicadology (CICADAS) with Gene Kritsky | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860173/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 02:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860173/</guid><description>Podcast Description They are numerous. They are patient. They are COMING for the United States in droves this spring: They are cicadas. The Cicada guy Dr. Gene Kritsky joins to chat all about the annual cicadas you may see every summer vs. the periodical ones that cycle through the states in broods of giant numbers. Learn how they survive underground for decades, what they are doing down there, all about their lifecycle, who eats them and why, plus get inspired to take a cicada safari, download Cicada Safari, and appreciate their sexually desperate songs, which can be as loud as an ambulance.</description></item><item><title>Gluteology (BUTTS) with Natalia Reagan | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860174/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 09:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860174/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yes, an entire episode on butts. Primatologist and anthropologist Natalia Reagan joins to chat about the caboose: why do we have butts? Why do we like butts? How do we appreciate ours even more? She drops knowledge on bidets, wiping, twerking, the mystical field of Rumpology, how our derrieres have our back, plus butt dimples, and crack formations. Also: some personal revelations and getting back on your feet after a curveball.</description></item><item><title>Molecular Biology (PROTEINS + SCIENCE COMMUNICATION) with Raven “The Science Maven” Baxter | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860175/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 11:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860175/</guid><description>Podcast Description This one’s got it all: teeny tiny cellular factories, obscure trivia, historical gossip, sick beats, mitochondrial relevancy, viral popularity, a backstory that with charm you to death, sports cars, lab coats, smelly vats, Space Camp and mysteries of the brain. Raven The Science Maven has a background in molecular biology and is getting her Ph.D in Science Communication and shares stories from both disciplines, while Alie generally does her best to suppress high pitched noises of excitement.</description></item><item><title>Carobology (NOT-CHOCOLATE TREES) with Megan Lynch | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860176/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 03:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860176/</guid><description>Podcast Description You might only know carob as not-chocolate, which is a tragedy of its disco-era branding. This tough, gnarly, drought-resistant plant is the real-life Giving Tree, explains passionate Carobologist Megan Lynch. Dripping with leathery banana-shaped legume pods, this tree quietly dots suburban streets but has kept people alive through wars and famines, can feed livestock, makes beautiful furniture, and might cure ailments from neurodegenerative diseases to the dark depths of your irritable bowels.</description></item><item><title>Economic Sociology Pt. 2 (MONEY/FREAKONOMICS) with Steven Levitt and Anna Gifty Opoku-Agyeman | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860177/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 06:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860177/</guid><description>Podcast Description Part 2 is here! Gamestop, #stonks, Universal Basic Income, how to incentivize things that are good for us, whether or not kids should have an allowance, Trekonomics and more. Economist, professor and “Freakonomics” co-author Steven Levitt joins to chat about everything from being cheap and what decision making costs our minds to the worth of the Amazon rainforest. Rising economics star and Harvard Fellow Anna Gifty Opoku-Agyeman graces us with her thoughts on the subreddit WallStreetBets, how we measure the health of the economy, dealing with bullies, and Gossip Girl.</description></item><item><title>Economic Sociology Pt. 1 (MONEY/FREAKONOMICS) with Anna Gifty Opoku-Agyeman and Steven Levitt | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860178/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 08:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860178/</guid><description>Podcast Description Choices! Trade-offs! Money! How much should you save? And how much should stimulus checks be? Don’t be scared by the term “economics,” especially since it doesn’t end in -ology. This 2-part Economic Sociology bonanza addresses the behavior that motivates the fiscal systems of the world, from avocado toast to retirement funds. Economist, professor and “Freakonomics” co-author Steven Levitt joins to chat about why we learn too much of the wrong math and how everything from marriage to dinner parties involves little choices rooted in economic principles.</description></item><item><title>Bilharziology (BLOOD FLUKES) with Anouk N. Gouvras | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860179/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 09:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860179/</guid><description>Podcast Description A LOST EPISODE! Three years in the making, this interview features vials of vile creatures, worm drama, febrile hallucinations, spooning, and unfortunate snacks. It has waited a long time to meet you, so let’s get weird, take a trip back to summer of 2017 &amp;ndash; before Ologies existed &amp;ndash; and unearth one of the very first, never-before-heard interviews. Alie absolutely bungles her way through a chat with Dr. Anouk Gouvras, a London-based parasitologist studying the flatworms that cause schistosomiasis.</description></item><item><title>Urban Rodentology (SEWER RATS) with Bobby Corrigan | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860180/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 20:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860180/</guid><description>Podcast Description RATS: They love pizza. They invade taquerias at midnight. They scurry. They cuddle. They outsmart. They inspire movies that inspire musicals. Proving that not just woodsy megafauna can be charismatic, rats have lives we would never suspect. Globally-lauded Urban Rodentologist Dr. Robert Corrigan, or Bobby if you like, has been studying these animals in their big-city ecosystem for decades and he is a wonder-filled joy. Learn about rats’ origin story, the difference between a rat and a mouse, where they live, their preferred “food dialects,” and how to (hopefully humanely) keep one out of your house &amp;ndash; or car?</description></item><item><title>Vaccine Infodemiology (COVID-19 IMMUNITY) with Jessica Malaty Rivera | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860181/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 20:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860181/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Coronasode we’ve been waiting for! Vaccines. Finally. But what does this mean? As a Vaccine Infodemiologist and science communication lead for The COVID Tracking Project, Jessica Malaty Rivera specializes in infectious disease epidemics and the surge of misinformation that accompanies them. The very first human trials of the COVID-19 vaccine occurred in March 2020, and Alie asks Jessica one million questions about the differences between the two available vaccines, rollout schedules, herd immunity, mRNA, vaccine hesitancy, mutated virus strains, picnics, vision boards, the post-holiday spike, how history can influence current vaccine rates, whether you should wipe down your groceries and more.</description></item><item><title>Part 2: Dendrology (TREES) with Casey Clapp -- UPDATES + NEW INTERVIEW | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860182/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 07:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860182/</guid><description>Podcast Description Part 2 of a very special duo! The fresh catch-up interview to learn what the world’s most charming and enthusiastic tree expert, Casey Clapp, has been up to since his 2018 episode aired. He’s been busy. Listen to hear if he’s gotten more pine cone tattoos, what other trees he hates, which ones he gives 10/10, musical blunders, winter pagan traditions, and why trees may play a huge role in his personality.</description></item><item><title>Part 1: Dendrology (TREES) with Casey Clapp -- Encore | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860183/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860183/</guid><description>Podcast Description Part 1 of a very special duo: Do trees have feelings? How do they talk? How old can they get? Are there any tree stories that will make me cry? Spoiler: YES. This episode aired in May 2018 and is worth a revisit, especially since Part 2 is a brand new 2020 interview with possibly the world&amp;rsquo;s most enthusiastic tree expert, J. Casey Clapp. Learn about his many tree tattoos, new additions to those tattoos, how roots communicate to each other, &amp;ldquo;crown shyness,” social media shyness and the mental health benefits of tree proximity.</description></item><item><title>Scorpiology (SCORPIONS) with Lauren Esposito: Encore Presentation | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860184/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860184/</guid><description>Podcast Description This specific episode was cited in The New Yorker this week, so we’re giving it an encore refresh with bonus material and a 2020 update from Dr. Esposito herself!
Scorpions: the victims of undue shade. If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever wanted to impress a date with weird facts THIS IS THE EPISODE FOR YOU. A handful of people on planet Earth have a PhD in scorpions and Dr. Lauren Esposito is one of them.</description></item><item><title>Garology (LONG CUTE ANCIENT PATIENT BOOPABLE NIGHTMARE FISH) with Solomon David | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860185/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860185/</guid><description>Podcast Description A long snout. Hundreds of teeth. Scales that could slice you. What is a gar and should we fear it? Should we hug it? One of the world’s most passionate and knowledgeable experts on this ancient, mysterious fish joins to make you fall in love with these slimy longbois. Dr. Solomon David is affable, charming, enthusiastic and absolutely shameless when it comes to fish puns. Slip into some hip waders and jump in the muck to learn all about a creature that &amp;ndash; despite decades of mudslinging &amp;ndash; is not a gar-bage fish.</description></item><item><title>Space Archaeology (SPACE JUNK) with Alice Gorman | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860186/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 05:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860186/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gaze into the cosmos and wonder at broken satellites, retired rockets and shattered contraptions. Archaeologist Dr. Alice Gorman is a leading expert on orbital debris and chats about what’s up there, how it got there, and how to get it down. Strap in to hear about everything from Sputnik to sports cars, flaming garbage bonking us, alien clutter, collision potential, the most adorable space rubbish, cosmic burials and how one does this type of archeology without boarding a rocket.</description></item><item><title>Alligator Ecotoxicology (GATOR POISONS) with Laura Kojima | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860187/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 07:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860187/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alligators, crocodiles and … a shut-down nuclear weapons plant? The excitement never ends when you’re Laura Kojima, an Alligator Ecotoxicologist. A longtime reptile cheerleader, Laura has passion to match some truly bananas stories about field work, tail smacks, gator jaws, mercury levels, swamp boats, and crocodilian evolution, overbites, and locomotion. Her incredible work keeps people &amp;ndash; and the gators &amp;ndash; safer in toxic waters and she recalls her favorite alligator bite and the one animal that sent her to the hospital.</description></item><item><title>Awesomeology (GRATITUDE) with Neil Pasricha | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860188/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860188/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gratitude: what’s the deal? Does it really make us happier? Even when the world seems terrible? Or is being appreciative a bunch of hokey flim-flam? Author Neil Pasricha started a blog of 1000 Awesome Things in 2008 and it led him down rabbit holes looking into the science of gratitude and how to better survive some really tough times. Learn about your new morning ritual, how much of happiness is genetically determined, why you should sniff a tree, honeymoon drama, simple appreciation, singing while making dinner, the gambles you take while scrolling, and how your brain means well &amp;ndash; but can make you miserable on purpose.</description></item><item><title>Biological Anthropology (APE SEX) with Lara Durgavich | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860189/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 09:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860189/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sexy apes: you’re one of them. And Biological Anthropologist Dr. Lara Durgavich joins to chat about everything from monogamy to PMS, male birth control pills, freezers of orangutan urine, imposter syndrome and testosterone, how the Pope makes you buy more tampons, which species has better sex, pancakes vs. boners, and boobs as a life preserver. It’s wall to wall gonad gossip and just may change the way you see yourself, you hairy, horny beautiful beast.</description></item><item><title>Indigenous Fashionology (NATIVE CLOTHING) with Riley Kucheran | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860190/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 08:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860190/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fashion! Trends! Not really! This lively chat with Riley Kucheran, an Assistant Professor of Design Leadership at Ryerson University’s School of Fashion, covers everything from the history of industrialized clothing manufacture to current Indigenous designers he loves, political statements through beadwork, Indigenous art markets, and a dissection of Coachella headdresses. From Biigtigong Nishnaabeg Nation, Riley also describes his experiences climbing the corporate ladder in the fashion retail world vs.</description></item><item><title>Pedagogology (SCIENCE COMMUNICATION) with Bill Nye | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860191/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 23:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860191/</guid><description>Podcast Description BILL NYE. That’s right. Bill Freakin’ Nye sits down to get grilled by your Dadward (that’s me, Alie) all about Pedagogology, the art and science of science communication. How did the modern day hype man of facts and wonder get his start? What does he love about his job? What are the most important elements of spreading knowledge? WHICH TIE IS HIS FAVORITE TIE? We chat about everything from comedy to TV crews, what he thinks about when he goes for walks, taking risks to follow your dreams, advice from Carl Sagan, tackling climate change, what makes him optimistic and … how to be the next Bill Nye.</description></item><item><title>Cucurbitology (PUMPKINS) Encore with Anne Copeland | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860192/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860192/</guid><description>Podcast Description HERE IS SOME SAFE, COZY COMFORT: a platter of pumpkins. We have a new episode up this week: Desairology (MORTUARY MAKE-UP) but if that&amp;rsquo;s toooo spooky: This 2019 Cucurbitology episode is an Ologies all-time favorite. Also? It helped launch sweet, sweet Anne Copeland’s book to the top of the seasonal cookbook charts last year. “Pumpkin, Pumpkin!” is not only a thing to scream while passing a patch, but also the name of author and human delight Anne Copeland&amp;rsquo;s gourd opus.</description></item><item><title>Desairology (MORTUARY MAKE-UP) with Monica Torres | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860193/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 02:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860193/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happens when you die? Cosmically, no one knows. But cosmetically, Desairologist Monica Torress knows everything. This friendly Phoenix funeral director shares her secrets for giving the dearly departed the greatest glam on their “special day.” She chats practical preservation techniques, spooky questions, her influences, the newest make-up lines, formaldehyde, mourning and grief, and how to make sure you look like you &amp;ndash; or Dolly Parton &amp;ndash; when your loved ones say their goodbyes.</description></item><item><title>Anthropodermic Biocodicology (HUMAN LEATHER BOOKS) with Megan Rosenbloom &amp; Daniel Kirby | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860194/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 02:54:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860194/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anthropodermic bibliopegy is a long, fancy way of saying “HUMAN SKIN BOOKS” and the study of confirming or debunking them is … Anthropodermic Biocodicology. For this skin-crawling, history-trawling Spooktober episode, we chat with the absolutely wonderful and charming medical librarian and expert of books bound in human skin, Megan Rosenbloom. Also on the line: analytical chemist Dr. Daniel Kirby, who discusses how books are tested to confirm if they are, in fact, human leather.</description></item><item><title>Forest Entomology (CREEPY CRAWLIES) with Kristen Wickert | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860195/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 23:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860195/</guid><description>Podcast Description Spooktober continues with … CrEePy cRawLies. And dark woods and solo hiking and Forest Entomologist Dr. Kristen Wickert a.k.a. KayDubs the Hiking Scientist. We chat about everything from Moth Man to chubby caterpillars to spiderwebs to fungus. She tells us how to look for big beautiful moths, what footwear is best for hitting the trail, which bugs to kill and which to cheer on, how to deal with mosquitos in your yard and ticks in your pants and why the woods feel like home.</description></item><item><title>Condorology (CONDORS &amp; VULTURES) with Jonathan C. Hall | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860196/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 19:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860196/</guid><description>Podcast Description To kick off SpooOoktober, we’re looking at huge birds that DEVOUR DEATH: the giant, majestic and critically endangered California condor. Condorologist Dr. Jonathan C. Hall’s work helps monitor populations, tracks flight data, and keeps tabs on how well this small population is rebounding after going extinct in the wild in 1987. We chat carcasses, wingspans, beaks, bald heads, and more. By the end, you’ll want to gaze at the skies hoping for a sighting.</description></item><item><title>Political Sociology (VOTER TURNOUT &amp; SUPPRESSION) with Mindy Romero | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860197/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 06:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860197/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you need fuel to get excited about voting: here it is. How low is U.S. voter turnout? And why? Are mail-in ballots safe? Should you vote early? How has voter suppression worked in the past &amp;ndash; and the present &amp;ndash; to skew elections? Oooh, buckle up as the wonderful Dr. Mindy Romero, a Political Sociologist and founding director of USC’s Center for Inclusive Democracy, chats about what drives us to the polls, what keeps us away, how to celebrate election day, and why every single vote actually does matter.</description></item><item><title>Fulminology (LIGHTNING) with Chris Giesige | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860198/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 05:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860198/</guid><description>Podcast Description Thunder and lightning: very, very frighteningly interesting! Wildfire researcher and lightning scientist Chris Giesige answers questions about thunderclaps and lightning flashes in a laid back way that will put him at the top of your Fulminologist list. He explains everything from clouds to positive and negative charges, volcanic lightning, fire tornadoes, getting struck by lightning, fractal scars, sprites, elves, how many gigawatts in a lightning strike, and how to enjoy a storm without getting zapped.</description></item><item><title>Mammalogy (MAMMALS) with Danielle N. Lee | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860199/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860199/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mammals: you’re one. Your dog is one. So are giant rats. What do we have in common? Nipples. The incredible Southern Illinois University professor, researcher, science communicator and mammalogist Dr. Danielle N. Lee joins to chat about everything from nature’s parenting styles to hairy bellies, milk glands, nip counts, how a meteor paved the way for our existence, her favorite mammals and the mysteries of the platypus. An episode years in the making, Alie barely keeps her cool as Dr.</description></item><item><title>Cervidology Part 2 (DEER) with Rhiannons Jakopak &amp; Kirton | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860200/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 04:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860200/</guid><description>Podcast Description The spirited, laughy chatter with a duo of deer scientists named Rhiannon continues in the thrilling conclusion with Part 2. Buckle up for listener questions addressing everything from social structure to hunting to Chronic Wasting Disease to how not to hit a deer with your car. Also the weirdest animal fact Alie has ever learned in the history of Ologies. Soul-rattling. And if you missed Part 1, circle back and catch up to learn all about ungulates and deer and moose and elk and fawns and … some Stevie Nicks trivia and Welsh mythology for good measure.</description></item><item><title>Cervidology (DEER) Part 1 with Rhiannons Kirton &amp; Jakopak | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860201/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 06:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860201/</guid><description>Podcast Description What IS a deer? And an elk? And a moose? And a Rhiannon? One thing they all have in common: cervidology. Buckle up for some spirited, laughy chatter with a duo of deer scientists. They dish all about Welsh mythology and their field trips into the remote, gorgeous wilderness. They’ll explain what to do if you find a fawn, if you should feed backyard deer, what deer population numbers are like, hunting, ungulates, being a first-generation scientist and more.</description></item><item><title>Dasyurology (TASMANIAN DEVILS) with Jarrah Dale | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860202/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860202/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tasmanian devils! Quolls! Carnivores! Wait … what is a quoll? In what will become an instant-favorite new episode, Dasyurologist and Australian critter scientist Jarrah Dale joins from Down-Down Under to discuss his work at Oxford University studying the ecology of misunderstood boofy bush babes. Alie learns about everything from the Tasmanian landscape to Looney Toons to flim flam, karaoke shrieking, wallaby standoffs, the most Australian afternoon ever, Tim Tam slams, moms with the munchies, teat shortages, Tassie tumors that are shrinking populations, and more.</description></item><item><title>Oceanology (THE OCEAN) with Ayana Johnson: Encore Presentation | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860203/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860203/</guid><description>Podcast Description With some fresh updates, ocean and policy expert Dr. Ayana Johnson guests in an encore presentation of a fan favorite episode. Hear updates from her, learn about her new podcast “How to Save a Planet,” and what she’s been up to since this episode originally aired in 2018. Are plastic straws really that bad? What&amp;rsquo;s the oldest message in a bottle? Any scuba vs. snorkel strategies? Does sunscreen kill coral?</description></item><item><title>Experimental Archaeology (OLD TOOLS/ATLATLS) with Angelo Robledo | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860204/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 21:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860204/</guid><description>Podcast Description Spears! Sharp rocks! Ancient blades, bows and arrows and &amp;hellip;atlatls? What’s an atlatl? Experimental Archaeologist and decades-long ancient tool enthusiast Angelo Robledo is as passionate as an ologist can get. You likely have never heard of an atlatl, but by the end of the episode you’ll be carving one out of old lumber. Also covered: early axes, Indigenous traditions of Central and South America, ancient graffiti, tales of field work, archeology heroes, what to do if you find artifacts on a hike, and the physics of how far you can lob ancient weaponry, plus: the World Atlatl Association.</description></item><item><title>Toxinology (JELLYFISH VENOM) with Anna Klompen | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860205/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 20:54:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860205/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jellyfish stings: what are they and why do they hurt? And who studies them? Toxinologist Anna Klompen, that’s who. Speaking from her lab in Kansas, surrounded by jellies, the self-described professional jellyfish nerd invites us into her scientific Polyp Parlor to chat about barbs, neurotoxins, quick sting fixes, panty hose, the deadliest jellies, the harmless ones, pee, her favorite moments in science and the species that have her heart forever.</description></item><item><title>Medusology (JELLYFISH) with Rebecca Helm | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860206/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 07:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860206/</guid><description>Podcast Description What even is a jellyfish?! How do they eat? What are they made of? Can we eat them? Your new favorite Medusologist, Dr. Rebecca Helm, is a ray of human sunshine in the depths of the deep sea. Truly one of the finest biology conversations you may ever hear. Get ready for PacMan ghosts, pet jellyfish, the biggest and smallest jellies, new band names, live medusas, secret formulas to incite jellyfish puberty, and the lengths that she will go to to see a jelly bloom.</description></item><item><title>Minisode: Listeners Interview Alie | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860207/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 17:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860207/</guid><description>Podcast Description Update! This episode posted on Tuesday per usual, then somehow un-published itself! Weird. Harrumph!
It’s been a rough week for ol&amp;rsquo; Dadward VonPodcast, including a technical difficulty that left her behind, so she asked listeners if they would rather have a bizzaro minisode that involved a 30-40 minute rant about raw tomatoes or an AMA, and guess what: here’s both, sort of. There was quite a bit of rambling an editing to make it a minisode, but we hope you enjoy.</description></item><item><title>Aperiology (MACRO PHOTOGRAPHY) with Joseph Saunders | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860208/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 05:12:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860208/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lights! Cameras! Arachnids! And lizards and bees and beetles. Macro photography is like magic: curved glass gives an entirely new take on the world, from dust on a cricket’s brow to a curious mantid stare to the elegant symmetry of spider whiskers. Joseph Saunders is an Oklahoma-based wildlife photographer whose larger-than-life photos of bugs and reptiles will make you realize just how little we appreciate the creatures on our window sills and skittering up our porches.</description></item><item><title>Agnotology (IGNORANCE) with Robert Proctor | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860209/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 09:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860209/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yes, there is an -ology for that. Dr. Robert Proctor is a Stanford professor of the History of Science and co-edited the book “Agnotology: The Making &amp;amp; Unmaking of Ignorance,” having coined the word 30 years ago. We chat about everything from the true evils of tobacco marketing, to the sugar lobby, to racial injustice, horse vision, the psychology of the Flat Earther movement, which countries have the highest rates of climate denial, empathy, how to navigate difficult conversations and why it&amp;rsquo;s critical to dismantle the systems of willful ignorance, starting locally.</description></item><item><title>Bryology (MOSS) with Dr. Robin Wall Kimmerer | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860210/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860210/</guid><description>Podcast Description An instant classic. You’ll listen on repeat as world-renowned author, botanist, Indigenous ecology professor and bryologist Dr. Robin Wall Kimmerer talks about her passion for moss. Cozy up for the most beautifully doled-out information about hidden worlds, overlooked mysteries, botanical drama, forests in miniature, Native peoples’ uses for moss and philosophies about science and ecology. Dr. Kimmerer, author of “Gathering Moss” and “Braiding Sweetgrass,” will change the way you see mosses forever, will inspire you to wear a loupe on a rope, and will soothe your soul with her beautiful voice and prose.</description></item><item><title>Neuroendocrinology (SEX &amp; GENDER) Part 2 with Daniel Pfau | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860211/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 22:30:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860211/</guid><description>Podcast Description The wonderful neuroscientist and endocrinology researcher Dr. Daniel Pfau is back for Part 2 to answer listener mail about how hormones affect our moods, the variation of gender expression, queer lizards, how a strict gender binary is harmful to entire populations, hormone replacement therapy, hormones in sports, gender dysphoria, additional info on the Gender Unicorn and more. They remain just charming and kind and this episode will help you further understand just how many ways there are to be human.</description></item><item><title>Neuroendocrinology (SEX &amp; GENDER) Part 1 with Daniel Pfau | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860212/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 09:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860212/</guid><description>Podcast Description How many genders are there? How do you know if you’re queer? Is sexual orientation biological, and if so, how? The amazing Michigan State University neuroscientist and endocrinology researcher Dr. Daniel Pfau joins to share their path in academia finding the perfect research, understanding their own genderqueer identity, what animals in nature exhibit queer behavior, how hormones influence the brain, how important it was for them to find community and why the gender binary isn’t a good fit for a lot of people.</description></item><item><title>Very Special Episode: BlackAFinSTEM with various Ologists | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860213/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 19:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860213/</guid><description>Podcast Description The most ologists in one Ologies. And maybe my favorite episode ever. #BlackBirdersWeek was such a force that we wanted to keep the energy going by spotlighting not one, but 30 ologists. You’re about to meet 30 new science heroes who are @BlackAFinSTEM and chatting about electric fish snouts, urban birds, falcons, lizards, crocodiles, economics, carnivores, sea turtles, porcupine noses, butt breathing, Ivory Towers, microaggressions, and how being an ally is a learning process we can all get better at.</description></item><item><title>Pelicanology (PELICANS) with Juita Martinez | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860214/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 04:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860214/</guid><description>Podcast Description Spine mysteries, saggy sacs, limericks, flim flam, flags, #BlackBirdersWeek, sandals, divebombs, porcupine espionage, ice cream sandwiches and more! The warm and wonderful pelicanologist Juita Martinez studies these glorious dinosaurs and shares fieldwork stories, what it’s like to hold a floofy baby sea bird, what she loves about being in nature and resources for undergrads interested in becoming scientists. We also chat about birding and the amazing visibility campaign launched by BlackAFinSTEM, which is hosting online events this week to open the discussion about how racism affects Black naturalists, scientists, hikers and any other people of color who want to enjoy the outdoors.</description></item><item><title>Oikology (DECLUTTERING) with Jamie &amp; Filip Hord + Joe Ferrari | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860215/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 08:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860215/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why does clutter happen? How can we get rid of it and how will it affect us psychologically if we do? Buckle up for an episode that will lift your spirits and quite possibly change your life. We all have unfolded piles of laundry, that closet we don’t want to open, a tornado of papers on our desk that seems impossible to sort through. Enter: Oikology, the science of keeping things contained.</description></item><item><title>Planariology (VERY COOL WORMS, I PROMISE) with Oné Pagán | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860216/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 05:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860216/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who cares about flatworms? Guess what: you do. Planarian expert Dr. Oné Pagán shares his infectious enthusiasm for the teeny tiny ribbons of flesh that are helping scientists understand addiction, limb regeneration, stem cells, immortality and maybe aliens though probably not aliens. You’re about to be obsessed. We discuss where to find planarians, serendipitous science, taking risks in life, how these worms regrow themselves when they are cut into 279 pieces, marine flatworms, penis fencing, multipurpose mouth tubes, the Unabomber and more.</description></item><item><title>Coronasode: Virology Update (COVID-19) with Shannon Bennett &amp; Mike Natter | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860217/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 20:46:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860217/</guid><description>Podcast Description What kind of masks should you wear? How many people have had COVID-19 and don’t know? Do antibody tests work? When will we have a vaccine? Is it okay to picnic? Will there be a second wave? You need updates and we’ve got ologists. The wonderful Dr. Shannon Bennett from the first Virology episode joins us again, as well as New York City physician Dr. Mike Natter from the Diabetology episode.</description></item><item><title>Architectural Technology (COMPUTER PROGRAMMING) with Iddris Sandu | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860218/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 08:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860218/</guid><description>Podcast Description Iddris Sandu is only 22, but his life story is already legendary. This Architectural Technologist learned to program at the age of 11 and has worked with everyone from Kanye West to Nipsey Hussle to Space X. We talk coding, web design, holograms, and how programming works and what languages should you learn and why it&amp;rsquo;s important. The designer and entrepreneur also shares his creative process, favorite programming languages, philosophies on future technology and why empathy matters in life and in design.</description></item><item><title>Nassology (TAXIDERMY) with Allis Markham | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860219/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 19:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860219/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glass eyes! Pelts! Antlers! Hides! Bones! Tanning! Hilarious, charming and globally celebrated taxidermist Allis Markham chats about her passion for preserving animals for museums and institutions. She’s won multiple awards for her artful poses and meticulous work as an ethical taxidermist. With her flair for vintage styling, is perhaps the most elegant badass on planet Earth. Learn the process of making museum taxidermy, her favorite pieces she’s ever made, the best diorama halls, how to DIY it at home, the dos and don’ts of picking up roadkill, why she’s not a fan of &amp;lsquo;crap taxidermy&amp;rsquo; and if &amp;hellip;humans could theoretically be &amp;hellip; stuffed.</description></item><item><title>Penguinology (PENGUINS) with Tom Hart | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860220/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 19:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860220/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do penguins have flippers or wings? Why do they waddle? Do they really mate for life? What’s up with pebble gifts? Are they squishy or dense? And why why why are they so cute? April 25th is World Penguin Day and there’s never been a better time to sit down with renown Penguinologist Dr. Tom Hart, a research fellow with Oxford University. We chat all about life on Antarctica, how he counts colonies, how you can help him count colonies, what penguins smell like, behaviors he’s witnessed, and why he does NOT find penguins cute.</description></item><item><title>Gastroegyptology (BREAD BAKING) with Seamus Blackley | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860221/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 22:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860221/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sourdough starters! Ancient yeasts! Why we need/knead dough! And why you don&amp;rsquo;t need to buy a starter to start. Polymath, particle physicist, inventor of the Xbox, and truly delightful fermentation nerd Seamus Blackley joins to chat about his kitchen adventures resurrecting dormant yeasts from 4,000 Egyptian baking vessels, plus wild yeasts, the infuriating myth of “yeast scarcity,” the beauty of everyday objects, the debt we owe our ancestors, the joy of getting to know your dough plus tons of tips for newbie and experienced bakers.</description></item><item><title>Philematology (KISSING) with Robin Dunbar | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860222/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 09:29:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860222/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why do we kiss? What makes a good kiss or a bad kiss? How many microbes do we exchange? Is it good for us? One of the world’s most accomplished researchers on kissing, social behavior and relationships, Dr . Robin Dunar of Oxford University reluctantly agrees to be interviewed and explains how kissing may have evolved, how discos are research labs and friends are people you can invite yourself to have a beer with.</description></item><item><title>Plumology (FEATHERS) with Allison Shultz | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860223/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860223/</guid><description>Podcast Description Plumage! Sexy dances! Feather heists! Possible holographic disco birds? Natural History Museum of LA ornithology curator Dr. Allison Shultz is a professional plumologist aka feather expert. We visit the museum’s collection of rare specimens and chat about everything from fossilized dinosaur feathers to silent owl flight to furry bird legs to why pigeons are so loud, peacock tails, down parkas, quill pens, heavy metal flautists, feather thieves, pigments, flight feathers, Vantablack, if you can eat feathers and why birdwatching is like seeing tiny purple raccoons zoom overhead.</description></item><item><title>Lepidopterology (BUTTERFLIES &amp; MOTHS) — Encore Presentation with Phil Torres | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860224/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 06:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860224/</guid><description>Podcast Description Since we just put out the &amp;ldquo;All (Washed) Hands on Deck&amp;rdquo; episode on Sunday, we figured a happy Springtime encore about fluttery, colorful cuties was in order &amp;ndash; with a few new updates and asides. Because &amp;hellip; Butterflies are gross. Yes they are delightful and beautiful and part of any idyllic picnic-scape but lepidopterologist, TV host and jungle explorer Phil Torres is here to gossip about how shamelessly disgusting our favorite bugs actually are.</description></item><item><title>Coronasode: All (Washed) Hands on Deck -- How to Help Yourself &amp; Others Right Now with Dr. Michael F. Wells | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860225/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 20:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860225/</guid><description>Podcast Description CALLING ALL OLOGISTS: If you’re a scientist who wants to help with the COVID-19 pandemic &amp;ndash; boy howdy have we got an episode for you. Dr. Mike Wells, a neurobiologist at Harvard University and the Broad Institute, knows we need tests in the U.S. and is coralling all the wonderful scientists willing to pitch in. He explains how testing for the SARS CoV-2 virus works, what other countries are doing, and even the book that inspired him to pursue science.</description></item><item><title>Veterinary Biology (CRITTER FIXING) with Dr. Vernard Hodges &amp; Dr. Terrence Ferguson | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860226/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860226/</guid><description>Podcast Description At long last: an episode dedicated to veterinary medicine! Dr. Terrence Ferguson &amp;amp; Dr. Vernard Hodges have been friends for nearly 30 years and have co-owned their rural Georgia veterinary clinic, Critter Fixers, for over 20 years. The two wonderful buddies talk about getting accepted into vet school, caring for spiders &amp;amp; camels &amp;amp; lizards &amp;amp; toads &amp;amp; kittens &amp;amp; doggos, the weirdest things they’ve extracted from animal tummies, if our pets love us back, keeping kidneys healthy, grain-free diets, what to do if your (Alie’s) dog is plumping up by a few pounds, what they wish animal owners knew, when it’s time to let go vs.</description></item><item><title>Coronasode: Virology (COVID-19) with Dr. Shannon Bennett + various ologists | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860227/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 07:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860227/</guid><description>Podcast Description Folks, it’s a megasode. Not one, but 4 ologists. “Coronavirus” is on everyone’s lips &amp;ndash; and some people’s hands &amp;ndash; but what is it? Where did it come from? How does it spread? How dangerous is it? What should we do? Who’s most at risk? Was it biowarfare? Do bats spread it? Should you wear a mask? Can we still smooch our dogs on the face? Do we need to doomsday prep?</description></item><item><title>Scatology (POOP) with Rachel Santymire | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860228/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 06:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860228/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yep. Here it is. Let’s dive right in &amp;hellip; to poop. Hippo poop. Ferret poop. Octopoop. Dogs. Cats. Yours. The charming and informative Dr. Rachel Santymire &amp;ndash; aka Dr. Poop &amp;ndash; has a background in animal physiology and endocrinology and is elbow deep in dung as a research director at the Lincoln Park Zoo. Dr. Poop sits down with Alie to talk turds and how she uses poo to determine the health and stress of wild and captive animals, plus: poop vs.</description></item><item><title>Volitional Psychology (PROCRASTINATION) with Dr. Joseph R. Ferrari | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860229/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 10:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860229/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Everyone procrastinates, but not everyone is a procrastinator,” quoth Dr. Joe Ferrari, a charming, hilarious expert on the subject. The research psychologist, author and DePaul University professor sits down for a truly delightful exploration of why we procrastinate, how prevalent it is, when it becomes harmful, some myths about procrastination, why it’s similar to gambling, how decision-making can feel paralyzing, how to trust your own abilities, and most importantly &amp;ndash; what to do if you’re a chronic procrastinator.</description></item><item><title>Cryoseismology (ICEQUAKES) with Celeste Labedz | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860230/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 18:45:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860230/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glaciers: Where are they? What are they made of? What happens when chunks splinter off into the sea? There are ICEQUAKES? CalTech Cryoseismologist Celeste Labedz sometimes wears a cape with her snowpants and spends part of her career shooting explosions into giant chunks of ice and recording the seismic activity, analyzing the rivers that flow through glaciers, and keeping tabs on glacial melt. Also discussed: the most goth way to honor a glacier, and whether or not you should visit them IRL.</description></item><item><title>Genealogy (FAMILY TREES) with Stephen Hanks | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860231/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 10:26:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860231/</guid><description>Podcast Description Histories, mysteries, memories and families: it’s time to clamber up our ancestral trees. Author and genealogist Stephen Hanks &amp;ndash; who teaches genealogy classes in Portland, Oregon and has contributed to PBS genealogy documentaries &amp;ndash; sits down to chat about what ignited a passion for learning about his own history. Also: how to find your family through census records, county archives, death certificates and more, plus which DNA tests he’s taken, our most recent common ancestor, and how America can try to heal from its past.</description></item><item><title>Nephology (CLOUDS) with Rachel Storer | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860232/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 21:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860232/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cumulus! Lenticular! Venti sugar-free stratocumulus stratiformis translucidus undulatus! Those light and fluffy things that hang overhead weigh thousands of pounds and form under all kinds of conditions. Cloud doctor and nephologist Dr. Rachel Storer chats about why she loves clouds, the different varieties of them, weather modification, sun dogs, bad emojis, tornado chasing, flim flam, conspiracy theories, cloud tattoos and diamond rain. Also: the common factor in whoopee cushions, boob implants and your lunch.</description></item><item><title>Diabetology (BLOOD SUGAR) Part 2 with Dr. Mike Natter, MD | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860233/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 20:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860233/</guid><description>Podcast Description Diabetic diabetologist and wonderful person Dr. Mike Natter, MD is back to answer all of your questions about blood sugar, the cost of insulin, pancreas transplants, keto, glucagon, how exercise can save your life, his most meaningful interactions with patients, pudding theft, and the best place to cry at work. Also: why you should always keep frosting in your purse.
This episode is swear-free and okay for all ages, and a bleeped version of Diabetology Part 1 can be found at this link.</description></item><item><title>Diabetology (BLOOD SUGAR) Part 1 with Dr. Mike Natter, MD | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860234/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 07:49:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860234/</guid><description>Podcast Description Your blood sugar can make you happy, moody, sweaty, unconscious and possibly even homicidal. In this episode, Dr. Mike Natter dishes about how blood sugar works, what insulin does, and how prevalent diabetes is in all of its various forms. Also: keto vs. vegan, hypoglycemia, cyborg organs, owl hoots, gestational diabetes, type 1 vs. type 2 and &amp;hellip; does Gwyneth drink her own pee? Also: the emotional side of the disease and how to help those in your life who are diabetic.</description></item><item><title>Bisonology (BUFFALO) with various bisonologists | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860235/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 01:33:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860235/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bison bison! Not just something to holler into the sky, but also the scientific name for North America&amp;rsquo;s majestic wild bovines that once roamed the plains in the tens of millions. What&amp;rsquo;s up with their humps? On what occasion do they wear capes? What noises do they make? How many are out there? What are the best ways to help them? In this special episode, you get 4x the usual number of ologists as we talk to archeologist Dr.</description></item><item><title>Futurology (THE FUTURE) with Rose Eveleth | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860236/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860236/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;The future&amp;rsquo;s not ours to see&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; OR IS IT? Professional futurologist Rose Eveleth &amp;ndash; host of the podcast Flash Forward &amp;ndash; endures all kinds of breathless questions from Alie about shiny metal and implanted microchips and biohacking and population density curves and flying cars and equality and utopias and the Jetsons and technology and nuclear fusion and whether or not our phones are spying on us and if we should have kids or dogs.</description></item><item><title>Fearology Pt. 2 (FEAR) with Mary Poffenroth -- Encore Presentation | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860237/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860237/</guid><description>Podcast Description FEAR. Anxiety. Stress. Dread. It&amp;rsquo;s all the same dang thing, as it turns out. Biologist and fear expert Mary Poffenroth is back to answer your questions in Part 2 of the encore presentation that&amp;rsquo;s been one of the most helpful interviews of ol&amp;rsquo; Alie Ward&amp;rsquo;s life. Learn how super successful people approach fear, Mary’s scariest hour, plus answers to all of your questions about night terrors, self-spookery, sharks&amp;rsquo; bad PR image to how likely it is that a snake will bite your butt.</description></item><item><title>Fearology Pt. 1 (FEAR) with Mary Poffenroth -- Encore Presentation | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860238/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860238/</guid><description>Podcast Description Every day, your brain tries to save your life by being terrified. Thanks, brain! Also, calm the f*ck down, brain. In 2018, Alie hunted down Mary Poffenroth, an expert in the biological and sociological causes/effects of fear &amp;ndash; and it is riveting. This December, Time Magazine named Ologies a top podcast and recommended this episode specifically. Plus it just so happens that there was an administrative snafu with the podcast network and we&amp;rsquo;re not supposed to have new episodes for two weeks, so enjoy this encore of a truly life changing episode.</description></item><item><title>Audiobook Mixtape: Gift Ideas from the Ologists’ Brains | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860239/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 01:23:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860239/</guid><description>Podcast Description Need holiday gift ideas? GET BOOKS. This episode is like an audiobook… but also a mixtape? It&amp;rsquo;s got a little bit of everything, from cozy cabin tales to dark caves to our own reflections, how your atoms will be recycled, New Year’s resolutions, cat training, dog rescues, battling past demons, aging, the apocalypse, crime TV and even Egyptian boobytraps. Alie has wanted to deliver excerpts from ologists’ books for over a year but she let them pile up for an even bigger compilation.</description></item><item><title>Chronobiology (CIRCADIAN RHYTHMS) with Katherine Hatcher | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860240/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 08:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860240/</guid><description>Podcast Description What time should you go to bed? Are you sleeping enough? Is Daylight Savings good for us? Is shift work really that bad? How dark is dark enough? Katherine Hatcher, who studies hormones, sleep cycles and circadian rhythms, helps Alie dissect her terrible sleep habits and talks about a magic tiny area in our brains that acts as your body&amp;rsquo;s Big Ben. By the end of the episode, you&amp;rsquo;ll be in footie pajamas eager to change your whole life.</description></item><item><title>Phonology (LINGUISTICS) with Nicole Holliday — Encore Presentation | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860241/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860241/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alie is delirious with the flu, so it’s an encore presentation of a favorite episode. If you slept on this when it first aired, get into Phonology now. Vocal fry. Code switching. Black Twitter. Valley girls. Culture vultures. WE&amp;rsquo;RE TALKING ABOUT TALKING. Alie battles traffic to sit down with linguistics professor Dr. Nicole Holliday about intonational phonology: how tones and pitch help us bond with others and construct identities.</description></item><item><title>Quantum Ontology (WHAT IS REAL?) with Adam Becker | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860242/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 05:35:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860242/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is anything real? How many universes are there? Do we know what dark matter is all about? Is everything a simulation being run by a quantum computer through a wormhole from a future era? Is the answer to everything really &amp;hellip; 42? The affable and charming astrophysicist, author and philosopher of tiny particles Dr. Adam Becker pulls up a seat. And Alie has an existential crisis or two as they discuss the drama, intellectual battles and drunken debates of science past, and the hope that a new era of thinkers will figure out what exactly is going on in the world.</description></item><item><title>Lupinology (WOLVES) with Bridgett vonHoldt | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860243/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 19:44:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860243/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wolf howls, wolf packs, wolf pups and more! As the holiday Wolfenoot approaches, lupinologist and Princeton professor Dr. Brigette vonHoldt sits down to talk about her research looking at everything from wolf populations to modern dog behavior, canine family dynamics, Game of Thrones direwolves, Yellowstone wolfies, the ecological impact of predators, if wolves howl at the moon, myths and truths about alphas, the wolf movie she refuses to see, how dog and human genetics are similar, and how you can help our lupine friends.</description></item><item><title>Molecular Neurobiology (BRAIN CHEMICALS) with Crystal Dilworth | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860244/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 09:24:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860244/</guid><description>Podcast Description Serotonin! Dopamine! Norepinephrine! Neurotransmitters: what&amp;rsquo;s their deal? Dr. Crystal Dilworth, aka Dr. Brain, stops by to have a spirited discussion about how chemical messengers change our moods and behaviors. We chat about depression, anxiety, what chemicals drive us to get off the couch, how antidepressants work, ADHD, addiction, the microbiome, new habits, quitting smoking, starting meditation, Oreos vs. cocaine, SSRIs vs. SNRIs, what it&amp;rsquo;s like to hold a human brain in your hands and if she would donate hers to science.</description></item><item><title>Chiropterology Part 2 (BATS) with Merlin Tuttle | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860245/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 05:01:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860245/</guid><description>Podcast Description PART 2: The stunning conclusion of a 3-hour gab session about frickin&amp;rsquo; bats with America&amp;rsquo;s favorite chiropterologist, Dr. Merlin Tuttle. Learn about bat conversations, their close friendships, surprising dongs, where they keep their nipples, how to go bat spotting after the sun sets, more myths and misconceptions about bat danger, perhaps the grossest thing Merlin has ever put in his mouth, how to hang up a bat house for maximum bat party funtimes, the latest on white nose syndrome and how it feels to get slapped by a bat.</description></item><item><title>Chiropterology (BATS) Part 1 with Merlin Tuttle | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860246/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 10:13:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860246/</guid><description>Podcast Description “People fear most what they understand least.&amp;quot; Words of wisdom from explorer/American treasure/bat expert, Dr. Merlin Tuttle. Alie headed to the bat capital of Austin and sat down with the legendary chiropterologist to discuss wild field stories and close calls and caves and comebacks and bat chatter and what a bat actually is and how big they get and what&amp;rsquo;s up with their smushy noses, why folks are so frightened by them, the evolution of flight, echolocation, getting a bat out of your house, how they sleep upside down, which ones guzzle blood, and the latest on white nose syndrome &amp;ndash; which is not a drug problem.</description></item><item><title>Demonology (EVIL SPIRITS) with Alyssa Beall | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860247/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 07:24:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860247/</guid><description>Podcast Description Demons, spooky spirits, devils, fallen angles, hungry ghosts: every culture has them. And West Virginia University Religious Studies professor, demonologist and history buff Dr. Alyssa Beall runs down how humans have used myths and stories to explain the feelings that make our hairs stand up and our stomaches sink. Is possession a mental illness? Are demons pranksters from hell? Is your baby evil or just cranky? And why do we like to be scared and poke at the line between life and death?</description></item><item><title>Spidroinology (SPIDERWEBS) with Randy Lewis | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860248/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 07:35:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860248/</guid><description>Podcast Description Invisible but stronger than steel. Complex architectural marvels. Things that stick to your face. Spiderwebs are much more than just Halloween decor or something to feather dust from your corners. Spider silk expert Dr. Randy Lewis of Utah State University not only coined the word &amp;ldquo;spidroin&amp;rdquo; for the proteins comprising the many types of silk, but he is considered one of the foremost experts on the wonders of spiderwebs.</description></item><item><title>Cucurbitology (PUMPKINS) with Anne Copeland | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860249/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 20:44:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860249/</guid><description>Podcast Description PUMPKIN PUMPKIN! Not only a thing to scream while passing a patch, but also the name of author and human delight Anne Copeland&amp;rsquo;s gourd opus. Yes, she&amp;rsquo;s so charmed by pumpkins that she dedicated a whole book to exploring their folklore, history, planting protocol, care, and cooking. On a lark, Alie stops by her house in the rural hamlet of Yucaipa, California to chat about everything from creation myths surrounding pumpkins to Anne&amp;rsquo;s favorite recipes, how to make a pumpkin last longer on your porch, the secret medicinal properties of pipitas, why humans might need to go bananas on Halloween, how to propose via pumpkin, and the big flimflam Anne needs the world to know about the pumpkin origin story.</description></item><item><title>Osteology (SKELETONS/BODY FARMS) with Daniel Wescott | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860250/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 00:22:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860250/</guid><description>Podcast Description Let&amp;rsquo;s dig right into Spooktober with &amp;hellip; BONES. You&amp;rsquo;re a steak-covered skeleton and it&amp;rsquo;s nothing to fear. The amazingly kind and committed osteologist Dr. Daniel J. Wescott of Texas State University&amp;rsquo;s famed Forensic Anthropology Research Center sits down &amp;ndash; surrounded by skulls and femurs and ribs &amp;ndash; and chats about how bones are formed, how they break, why they might hurt when the weather changes, what CSI gets wrong, how long it takes a body to decompose, looking for isotopes in found remains, cast iron coffins, skeleton myths, body donation, and more.</description></item><item><title>Phenology (FALL/SEASONS) with Libby Ellwood | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860251/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 23:05:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860251/</guid><description>Podcast Description The seasons are a-changin&amp;rsquo;! It&amp;rsquo;s sweater weather in both hemispheres and seasonal researcher and expert Phenologist Dr. Libby Ellwood weighs in with amazing information about why fall smells so good, why leaves change color, why we like to cronch them, historical records of blossoms and twigs, bird migrations, Daylight Savings, seasonal mythbusting, pumpkin spice vs. apple cider, the best temperature to wear sweaters, why the Halloween aisle springs up in summer and how global temperature shifts affect the whole food web.</description></item><item><title>Potterology Part 2 (WIZARD SCIENCE) with Rebecca Lai | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860252/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 21:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860252/</guid><description>Podcast Description UPDATE: since this episode was first released, J.K. Rowling has said and written some deeply transphobic sentiments and for this, Alie no longer stans nor supports her. So in listening to this episode, let&amp;rsquo;s marvel at the -ologist herself and her love of Chemistry and remember that feminism is intersectional and trans women are women, and trans folks are welcome and beloved in the Ologies universe.
PART 2: Your questions answered by Dr.</description></item><item><title>Potterology Part 1 (WIZARD SCIENCE) with Rebecca Lai | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860253/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860253/</guid><description>Podcast Description UPDATE: since this episode was first released, J.K. Rowling has said and written some deeply transphobic sentiments and for this, Alie no longer stans nor supports her. So in listening to this episode, let&amp;rsquo;s marvel at the -ologist herself and her love of Chemistry and remember that feminism is intersectional and trans women are women, and trans folks are welcome and beloved in the Ologies universe.
Accio: ALL YOUR DREAMS COMING TRUE.</description></item><item><title>Vexillology (FLAGS) with E. Tory Laitila | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860254/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 04:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860254/</guid><description>Podcast Description Flags! How long have we flown them? Will you get arrested for stomping on one? Which ones are cute and which are fugly? Which colors don&amp;rsquo;t we see on flags and why? How did all this flag etiquette originate? E. Tory Laitila, a textile expert who also handles Honolulu&amp;rsquo;s flag protocol, gives the skinny on how to dispose of a flag, flags and conspiracy theories, history of the Pride flag, the oldest flags, which state flag needs a makeover the hardest, how to store flags, who designed our modern American flag and how you too can have &amp;hellip; fun with flags all year round.</description></item><item><title>Paleontology (DINOSAURS) Encore Presentation with Michael Habib | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860255/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 08:41:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860255/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s a trip back in time to a baby podcast! Hear the humble beginnings of Ologies as your Ol&amp;rsquo; Dadward takes a week to celebrate her parents&amp;rsquo; 50th wedding anniversary. This encore presentation of Paleontology &amp;ndash; complete with new bells, whistles, intro and a fresh secret or two at the end &amp;ndash; will remind you of the wonders of dino digs. Dr. Michael Habib of the beloved Natural History Museum of Los Angeles County answers questions such as: Did Ross Gellar ruin being a paleontologist?</description></item><item><title>Disasterology (DISASTERS) with Samantha Montano | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860256/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 01:11:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860256/</guid><description>Podcast Description Floods, earthquakes, tsunamis, tornados, explosions, hurricanes, oil spills, bombings, BAD THINGS: Why do they happen? What can we do to prepare? What is a disaster vs. a catastrophe? Who makes it their life&amp;rsquo;s work to go help? Professional Disasterologist and Emergency Management expert Dr. Samantha Montano sits down to talk about disaster movies, the addiction of helping others, the aftermath of Hurricane Katrina and the floods, looting, doomsday prepping, keeping calm under pressure, climate change, governmental budgets, cathedrals vs.</description></item><item><title>100th Episode: Best Life Advice from Ologists + 100 More Ologies | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860257/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 08:18:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860257/</guid><description>Podcast Description ONE HUNDRED EPISODES, kiddos. From slimy hagfish coils on the ocean floor to the outer reaches of space. Into our brains and out a bird butt and beyond. Ol&amp;rsquo; Dadward reflects on the past 100 episodes by distilling the 5 best peptalk lifehack self-helpy pieces of advice she&amp;rsquo;s learned from making Ologies for the last nearly two years. Also: a list of 100 potential more episodes and what&amp;rsquo;s cooking for the next few weeks.</description></item><item><title>Saurology (LIZARDS) with Earyn McGee | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860258/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 07:53:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860258/</guid><description>Podcast Description Saurologist and professional lizard scientist Earyn McGee visits Alie to go on a little lizard hunt, then they hunker down to chat about everything from tiny chameleons to drooling dragons, venomous thiccbois, legless lizards, geckos’ antigravity grip, festering dragon mouths, gila monster sightings, close encounters with lions, tangles of snoozy lizards, virgin births, and blood shooting from eyeballs. We also discuss Earyn’s wildly popular #FindThatLizard Twitter game and she gives us all some sound advice on social anxiety and how to succeed in literally any field or ambition.</description></item><item><title>Graphology (HANDWRITING/FORGERY) with Sylvia Kessler | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860259/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 03:05:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860259/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is it weird to have different handwritings? How do you forge ancient documents? What pen should you use to write checks? Who is the greediest person in American history? Forensic document examiner Sylvia Kessler met up with Alie in the back of a Nebraska office store to chat about penmanship, ransom notes, court cases, self-expression, and we very lightly touch on the fringe -ology that uses handwriting to analyze personalities and how Barnum knew best when it comes to carnival &amp;ldquo;magic.</description></item><item><title>Cnidariology (CORAL) with Shayle Matsuda | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860260/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 06:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860260/</guid><description>Podcast Description Will changing your sunscreen save coral reefs? What even IS a coral? Where do they grow and what do they eat and why are they so pretty? Is it reefs or reeves? The wonderful and charming coral biologist and cnidariologist Shayle Matsuda of the Hawaii Institute of Marine Biology/UH Mānoa takes time out of his busy schedule during a coral spawning event to chat about how magical and beautiful coral can be and why reef health is important.</description></item><item><title>Disinfectiology (BLEACH) with Evan Rumberger | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860261/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 23:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860261/</guid><description>Podcast Description It lives under your sink and may have saved your life but… WHAT THE FUNK IS BLEACH? Hot off of a beaker-laden lab tour, Alie chats with Dr. Evan Rumberger, a bleach scientist, about his work, his history, what bleach IS, what it turns into, and how to appreciate this household staple. Also: what exactly is in swimming pools and how to tie-dye shirts when you’re goth. This was part of a partnership with Clorox, but Alie thought the chemistry was cool enough to share with Ologites.</description></item><item><title>Nomology Part 2: (THE CONSTITUTION): Let's read the whole friggin thing. | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860262/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 03:31:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860262/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever read every word of The U.S. Constitution? You don&amp;rsquo;t have to, because ol&amp;rsquo; Dadward here is about to read it into your ears and give little sidenotes to make sure we both understand it.
This episode is a follow up to Nomology with law professor Franita Tolson, so start there for the basics and learn why knowing your rights and using your voice can change the future.</description></item><item><title>Nomology (THE CONSTITUTION) with Franita Tolson | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860263/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 21:23:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860263/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you&amp;rsquo;ve never read The Constitution, you&amp;rsquo;re like most of us. What does it even say?! Most Americans aren&amp;rsquo;t law scholars, which is why we sat down with a Dean of USC&amp;rsquo;s Gould School of Law, Professor Franita Tolson, to have her give us the crib sheet on the most important document in the free world. What&amp;rsquo;s up with the amendments? What are the articles? What does it mean to be an American?</description></item><item><title>Cabinology (CABINS) with Dale Mulfinger | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860264/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 16:36:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860264/</guid><description>Podcast Description Log cabins, woodsy getaways, A-frame cuties, cottages, tiny homes, lake houses: WE GET INTO IT. World famous Minnesota architect, author, professional cabinologist and human delight Dale Mulfinger sits down to discuss everything from what makes a cabin a cabin, to why we bond better surrounded by wood, Scandinavian hygge-ness, where to situate windows, cabin history, horror flicks and vacation activities. Alie sits there starry-eyed and stammers a bunch because she&amp;rsquo;s so excited.</description></item><item><title>Disease Ecology (LYME/TICK-BORNE ILLNESSES) with Andrea Swei | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860265/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 08:26:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860265/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lyme Disease! Powassan virus! That Lonestar tick meat allergy! Paralysis ticks! Acarology taught us all about the eight-legged villains that aim for our crevices, but Disease Ecologist Dr. Andrea Swei offers a deep dive under the skin to learn more about what nasties a tick can give us. We chat a whole bunch about Lyme Disease: its prevalence, testing, treatment, which animals carry it, “chronic Lyme” vs. post-treatment Lyme.</description></item><item><title>Island Ecology (ISLANDS) with Andy Kraemer | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860266/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 08:34:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860266/</guid><description>Podcast Description What IS an island? How do birds and plants and mammals GET there? Why do we like going to islands? Dr. Andy Kraemer studies how life populates and survives on hunks of remote rock and chats all about the Galapagos Islands &amp;ndash; where he does his research. We address the smallest island in the world, the largest, some bananas biological adaptations, Darwin&amp;rsquo;s finchy mistakes, some nude people and a Baroness who got caught up in a homicide scandal, and shrinking skeletons.</description></item><item><title>Acarology (TICKS) with Neeta Pardanani Connally | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860267/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 09:45:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860267/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ticks: They’re tiny. They’re thirsty. They’re drooling vectors of various illnesses and they want nothing more than to cuddle up to your darkest crevices. In the episode, learn how to remove a tick, if you should spray your yard and with what, how landscaping affects tick exposure, why Lyme Disease is spreading, the Lone Star Tick rolling into town, how to protect your pets and why the CC ruined poppyseed muffins.</description></item><item><title>Psychological Traumatology (PTSD &amp; STRESS) with Nicholas Barr | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860268/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 08:15:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860268/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happens to the brain under extreme stress? Why do past traumas haunt us? What kind of therapies work for veterans? And what can we do in day-to-day life to be more resilient to adverse experiences? Traumatologist and social worker Dr. Nicholas Barr has studied PTSD in veterans and homeless youth and explains how traumas affect the rest of our lives and how to bounce back by getting a little help.</description></item><item><title>Behavioral Ecology (REPRODUCTIVE TRADEOFFS) with Amy Worthington | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860269/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 08:39:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860269/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why do we bone? Why should we have kids? When should we have kids? Crickets might answer all these questions. Dr. Amy Worthington of Creighton University in Omaha, Nebraska studies &amp;ldquo;life history tradeoffs:&amp;rdquo; when to allocate resources to reproduction versus preserving your own health. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re an insect ghosting a buster mate or a millennial waiting to have kids until the economy gets better, you may learn a thing or two about whether having kids is worth it.</description></item><item><title>BONUS Minisode: Preview of Alie on Bill Nye's "Science Rules!" | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860270/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 07:57:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860270/</guid><description>Podcast Description Announcement: BILL NYE HAS A PODCAST. And Alie&amp;rsquo;s his first guest. Bill Nye’s on a mission to change the world, one phone call at a time and yer ol’ Dadward VonPodcast is first in the chair helping field questions. Yes she is freaking out about this and yes you should listen. In “Science Rules!,&amp;quot; he tackles the curliest questions on just about anything in the universe with his signature knowledge and affability.</description></item><item><title>Mycology (MUSHROOMS) with Tom Volk | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860271/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 08:44:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860271/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mushrooms! Psilocybin! Humungous fungus! Black mold! Foraging! The incredibly charming and warm Dr. Tom Volk, world-renown mushroom expert, welcomes Alie into his office to dive deep into the underground world of fungal enthusiasts and touch on pathogens and medicinal therapies. Dr. Volk himself is a heart transplant patient, and shares how his life has been changed since a donor saved it. Also: Alie holds his old heart in her hands.</description></item><item><title>Bufology (TOADS) with Priya Nanjappa | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860272/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 19:00:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860272/</guid><description>Podcast Description Toaaaaads! Friend or foe? Dive into a toad hollow with bufologist and charming human Priya Nanjappa, who is a wealth of knowledge and a font of affection for toads. Which toads are the biggest, the most poisonous, the history of the cane toad, toad licking, orgies with pythons, mating calls, evolution, wart film flam, witch myths , toad abodes and more. This episode will change the way you crouch down and shake hands with your tiny backyard grumpa.</description></item><item><title>Minisode: All of My Secret Travel Trips + Some Updates | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860273/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 17:22:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860273/</guid><description>Podcast Description THAT&amp;rsquo;S RIGHT IT&amp;rsquo;S A MINISOHDA FROM MINNESOHDA. On the last stop of a six-state Midwest tour interviewing -ologists for future episodes, your ol&amp;rsquo; Dadward Von Podcast was going to serve up a re-run this week. HOWEVER, I love you all too much and instead I recorded a solo episode in my rental car of the best travel tips I&amp;rsquo;ve amassed from the last decade of being on the road.</description></item><item><title>Addictionology (ADDICTION) with Erin Parisi | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860274/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 17:14:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860274/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;Addiction doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be a bummer!,&amp;rdquo; quoth addictionologist Erin Parisi, who has some uplifting and hopeful tales from her professional life. But content warning: it&amp;rsquo;s definitely not a day in the park. Tune in for some info on alcohol dependence, smoking, opiates, behavioral addictions, how addiction can futz with your reward systems, some sobering statistics, what we can learn from rat parties, how childhood experiences can set the stage for substance dependence later, how many people are in recovery, what to do if a friend or loved one seems to have a problem, how to tell if you might have a problem, enjoying your grandpa&amp;rsquo;s casserole, cuddling babies and more.</description></item><item><title>Hagfishology (HAGFISH) with Tim Winegard | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860275/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 14:06:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860275/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hagfish: these floppy hot dogs of the deep sea deserve our undying respect. Tim Winegard is a professional hagfishologist (YES IT&amp;rsquo;S A WORD) at Chapman University, and he dishes on the world&amp;rsquo;s slimiest treasures. Prepare to hear about swift escapes, spellbinding clots of slime, patchy backstories, aphrodisiacs, outlasting extinction events, why you don&amp;rsquo;t always need a spine, eating your way out of a dead whale, and &amp;ndash; like a slippery messiah &amp;ndash; turning water to slime.</description></item><item><title>Scorpiology (SCORPIONS) with Lauren Esposito | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860276/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 05:57:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860276/</guid><description>Podcast Description Scorpions: the victims of undue shade. If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever wanted to impress a date with weird facts THIS IS THE EPISODE FOR YOU. A handful of people on planet Earth have a PhD in scorpions and Dr. Lauren Esposito is one of them. She spills the beans on how venom works, what&amp;rsquo;s up with the blacklight glow effect, how dangerous they really are, what all the movies get wrong, the best names for scorpions, where she&amp;rsquo;s traveled to look under rocks, where a scorpion&amp;rsquo;s butt is, if scorpions dance or make out (SPOILER: YES), what good mothers they are, how big they used to be millions of years ago and how &amp;ndash; technically speaking &amp;ndash; they are not poisonous.</description></item><item><title>FIELD TRIP: How to Change Your Life via the Natural History Museum of LA | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860277/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 09:28:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860277/</guid><description>Podcast Description After last week&amp;rsquo;s heavy episode, Alie takes a little break with a Field Trip to one of her favorite places, the Natural History Museum of LA County. Hop in her pocket to hear about singing trees, hungry harpy eagles, architectural antelopes, crows that know your car, a pelt vault, sea serpents, willow huts, why Alie started loitering around in a vest, her personal list of must-see hidden exhibits, &amp;ldquo;Secrets from the Vault,&amp;rdquo; her new live series for First Fridays in April and June, plus excerpts from the NHM&amp;rsquo;s new book, Wild LA: Explore the Amazing Nature in and Around Los Angeles &amp;ndash; and how volunteering could quite possibly change your life.</description></item><item><title>Victimology (CRIME VICTIMS) with Callie Rennison | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860278/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 05:39:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860278/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a world saturated with CSI spinoffs and true crime documentaries, we look at a criminology subset focusing not on the pathology of the killers, but on the victims of crime: their experiences, vulnerability, survival rates, statistics, trauma, and recovery. In the least goofy episode to date, the brilliant and warm professional victimologist Dr. Callie Rennison of the University of Colorado chats about resources, historical changes of perspective, gender&amp;rsquo;s role in victimization and how people of color and Native populations are at a tragically higher risk for violent victimization.</description></item><item><title>Astrobiology (ALIENS) with Kevin Peter Hand | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860279/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 06:14:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860279/</guid><description>Podcast Description ALIENS! EXTRATERRESTRIALS! MARTIANS! Let&amp;rsquo;s. Get. Into. It. The phenomenal Dr. Kevin Peter Hand of NASA&amp;rsquo;s Jet Propulsion Laboratory dishes on the oceans of distant moons, methane rivers, E.T., ice crusts, what might be out there, the timeline of possibly finding them, ghosts, aliens, dark matter, if we should fear making contact with intergalactic beings, if the government is hiding alien secrets, how finding extraterrestrial microbes would change the way we see life on this here tiny blue dot in space.</description></item><item><title>Ludology (VIDEO GAMES) with Jane McGonigal | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860280/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 09:53:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860280/</guid><description>Podcast Description Video games! Tabletop games! IRL role-play gaming! The &amp;hellip; lottery? Dr. Jane McGonigal is a video game developer, TED speaker, bestselling author and total badass with a deep knowledge of how games &amp;ndash; and especially video games &amp;ndash; can motivate, soothe and connect us. We talk about everything from Monopoly to dance offs, Fortnite, vintage Atari, VR, the challenge of Dark Souls, the sweetness of League of Legends, how Tetris can get you through rough times and the health issue that caused Dr.</description></item><item><title>Etymology (WORD ORIGINS) with Helen Zaltzman of The Allusionist Podcast | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860281/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 08:32:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860281/</guid><description>Podcast Description The brilliant and dazzling Helen Zaltzman, host of The Allusionist podcast and person who technically for a living researches the origins of language and thus is an etymologist, visits Alie&amp;rsquo;s apartment to chat about various word origins, gender in language, the Bible a.k.a. The Oxford English Dictionary, origins of the filthiest slang, emoji decoding, mediocrity, step parents, babies wearing glasses, Greek kimonos, the romance of languages and the fundamental truth that language is always changing whether you want it to or not.</description></item><item><title>Thermophysiology (BODY HEAT) with Shane Campbell-Staton | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860282/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 18:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860282/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode, and Dr. Shane Campbell-Staton, are a true joy. The UCLA professor, host of the Biology of Superheroes Podcast and Thermophysiologist talks about big animals vs. little ones, lizard storms, dinosaur blood, hibernating bears, why you sweat in your sleep, antifreeze frogs, miracle hamsters, why different people run at very different temperatures, how comic books influence the way he sees science, learning how his brain works and some time management hacks that he uses as a professor and host of an amazing podcast.</description></item><item><title>Personality Psychology (PERSONALITIES) with Simine Vazire | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860283/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 08:50:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860283/</guid><description>Podcast Description WHO ARE WE? Personality researcher &amp;amp; psychology professor Dr. Simine Vazire dishes about introverts, extroverts, self-esteem, sociopaths, neuroticism, conscientiousness, Buzzfeed quizzes, yearbook inscriptions, trusting people, screwing up your kids, acting like your parents, changing personality traits through therapy or medication and astrology being put to the test. Also, Alie finds out what kind of dog she is.
Dr. Simine Vazire on Twitter
This week&amp;rsquo;s donation was made to improvingpsych.</description></item><item><title>Matrimoniology (MARRIAGE) with Ben Karney | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860284/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 14:52:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860284/</guid><description>Podcast Description Love! Romance! Intimate relationships! Marriage! Divorce! Remarriage! Clowns! This episode has it all. The wonderfully warm Dr. Benjamin Karney of the UCLA Marriage lab has been studying romance and intimate relationships for 20 years and sits down to chat about being single and the mechanisms behind finding a partner, what behaviors foster intimacy, why some couples stay together vs. splitting up, some bananas proposals, wedding budgets, how parenting affects marriage, historical problems with matrimony and his own experiences with marriage and divorce.</description></item><item><title>Biogerontology (AGING) with Caleb Finch | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860285/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 08:17:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860285/</guid><description>Podcast Description How long can we live? How much of aging is genetics vs. environment? What does oral hygiene have to do with brain health? What causes Alzheimer’s? How do turtles and naked mole rats live so long? Are there any proven strategies for living a longer life? What&amp;rsquo;s up with whiskey and eggs? World-renowned aging expert and biogerontologist Dr. Caleb &amp;ldquo;Tuck&amp;rdquo; Finch takes a quick break from his prolific research at USC to answer Alie&amp;rsquo;s sometimes stupid questions about everything from molecules to movies.</description></item><item><title>Cheloniology (SEA TURTLES) with Camryn Allen | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860286/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 09:32:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860286/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you think you like sea turtles, get ready to become wildly obsessed with them. Cheloniologist Dr. Camryn Allen met up with Alie on a tropical island (ok, in a hotel room on a tropical island) to chat about flipper slappings, turtle rodeos, nesting BBs, current surfing, endangered statuses, field work, sleeping under water, world records, boopable noses, male:female ratios, mind-boggling navigation, what you can do to help them, and the many mysteries that still remain.</description></item><item><title>Testudinology (TORTOISES) with Amanda Hipps | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860287/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 10:48:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860287/</guid><description>Podcast Description What&amp;rsquo;s a tortoise? What&amp;rsquo;s a turtle? Why do they live so dang long? What&amp;rsquo;s up with their junk? Wildlife biologist and testudinologist Amanda Hipps studies gopher tortoises and dishes about turtle nomenclature, cliques, dicks, behavior, burrows, evolution, habitats and more. If you don&amp;rsquo;t dig tortoises yet, you&amp;rsquo;re about to fall deep into a turtle tunnel in love with them.
Follow Amanda Hipps on Instagram or Twitter
This week&amp;rsquo;s donation was made to AlongsideWildlifeFoundation.</description></item><item><title>Snow Hydrology (SNOW &amp; AVALANCHES) with Ned Bair | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860288/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 07:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860288/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s tiny! It&amp;rsquo;s beautiful! It&amp;rsquo;s cold! It can kill you. Snow and avalanche expert Dr. Ned Bair meets up on a bench during a layover to chat about the beauty of snowflakes, the best ammo for snowball fights, firing cannons at mountainsides, avalanche flam-flam, the dangers of snow patrolling, a lifesaving goat-antelope, the best and worst ski movies and a mentor that changed his life. Also: bomb cyclones and some tips on excavating your car.</description></item><item><title>Felinology (CATS) with Mikel Delgado | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860290/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860290/</guid><description>Podcast Description We love them. We live with them. We are mystified by them. Alie hunted down professional cat behavior expert Dr. Mikel Delgado who dishes on everything from toilet training to feral taming to neonatal kittens to cats eating our dead bodies to domestication, toxoplasmosis, litter box strategies, cats on leashes, why they want to sit on your laptop, how to play with cat toys the right way, why cats drool, if tigers make biscuits, catnip stupors and so much more.</description></item><item><title>Minisode: Ologies Upgrades &amp; Changes for 2019 | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860289/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860289/</guid><description>Podcast Description A few things are changing in the world of Ologies and I just wanted to take a few minutes in this bare-bones minisode to lay &amp;rsquo;em out. Transcripts and bleeped versions will be available in the next month or two, donations are going to specific Ologist-chosen charities per episode, and finally, Ologies puts on big pants and has sponsors. Will I call you and talk to you about a bra?</description></item><item><title>Entomophagy Anthropology (EATING BUGS AS SUSTAINABLE PROTEIN) with Julie Lesnik | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860291/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 03:42:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860291/</guid><description>Podcast Description DO YOU CARE ABOUT THE APOCALYPSE? Okay cool. No matter what your diet, get this episode in your ears. Entomophagy Anthropologist Dr. Julie Lesnik &amp;ndash; an enthusiastic expert on bug eating &amp;ndash; breaks down the human past, present and future of insect cuisine for our surging population. If you&amp;rsquo;re considering cutting back on meat, or if you&amp;rsquo;re a vegan helping others explore more sustainable options, Dr. Lesnik will get you pumped as hell for changing mindsets.</description></item><item><title>Ornithology (BIRDS) Encore Presentation with James Maley | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860292/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2018 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860292/</guid><description>Podcast Description Birds! Horned screamers! Winged pirates! Just in time for the Audubon&amp;rsquo;s winter Christmas Bird Count (which goes until Jan. 5) here is an encore presentation of an early episode. Professional bird-person and all around cool dude James Maley joins Alie to talk about bird mating, monogamy, the cult of ornithology, absurd birds, parrots that are smarter than your friends&amp;rsquo; kids, a surprising fact about owl ears and history&amp;rsquo;s most tragically zealous bird nerds.</description></item><item><title>Mixology (COCKTAILS) with Matthew Biancaniello | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860293/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 08:06:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860293/</guid><description>Podcast Description Foraging, infusing, shaking, stirring: this one&amp;rsquo;s got it all. How do you make weird, fancy drinks at home? How much booze should you buy for a party? What drinks do bartenders hate to make? How can you avoid a hangover? What are the best mocktails? Famed bar chef and mixologist Matthew Biancaniello tours Alie through Malibu fire aftermath and talks about his boggling backstory, why he doesn&amp;rsquo;t go out much, the secret formula to making good drinks and why you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be afraid to be weird.</description></item><item><title>Selenology (THE MOON) with Raquel Nuno | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860294/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 03:53:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860294/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are we crazier during a full moon? What is the Moon made of? Can we move to the Moon? Was the Moon landing a hoax? What&amp;rsquo;s up with all those craters? Planetary geologist and selenologist Raquel Nuno loves the Moon and sits down to answer approximately 1 million of Alie&amp;rsquo;s shameless questions. Gaze into the sky with newfound understanding and appreciation for our glowing buddy in the sky. Also: a burst bladder and a drunk moose.</description></item><item><title>Classical Archaeology (ANCIENT ROME) with Darius Arya | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860295/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 04:35:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860295/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you LIVE for drama, you will LOVE dead Romans. Wars, murders, opulence and uprisings: a little something for everyone. Classical Archaeologist and TV host Dr. Darius Arya dishes about priceless garbage piles, lead poisoning, ancient political scandals, pottery graveyards, unearthing sculptures, tomb discoveries, what&amp;rsquo;s under European cities, and how Roman society was a little like America these days. But also a lot different. And what we can learn from it.</description></item><item><title>Microbiology (GUT BIOME) with Elaine Hsiao | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860296/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 04:54:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860296/</guid><description>Podcast Description LOVE YOUR GUTS. 90% of your serotonin is made in your guts and you have hundreds of trillions of friends clinging to you at all times. Microbiologist Dr. Elaine Hsiao is a total badass who runs her own lab investigating the role of the gut biome in behaviors. She sat down to chat about anxiety, depression, elusive fecal transplants, autism, epilepsy, kombucha promises, autoimmune disorders, probiotics and more. Alie fanned out pretty hard and asked all of the questions about how your beloved, simmering insides affect your brain.</description></item><item><title>Grateful-ology (GRATITUDE) is not totally a real word | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860297/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860297/</guid><description>Podcast Description A (perhaps) much-needed refresher course on last year&amp;rsquo;s gratitude minisode. As a friend of a friend&amp;rsquo;s hairdresser once said: &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s hard to be hateful with a plateful of grateful.&amp;rdquo; Is it? In this pre-holidays quickie episode, Alie is grumpy as hell and decides to research the neuroscience of gratitude. Does it work? Who&amp;rsquo;s studying it? Does she need to buy a journal? Find out how jotting down things you don&amp;rsquo;t hate on the back of a receipt or opening a secret Twitter account may be worth more than whatever you get in your office Secret Santa exchange.</description></item><item><title>Food Anthropology (FEASTS) with Katherine Spiers | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860298/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 05:05:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860298/</guid><description>Podcast Description Loosen your belts and tuck a napkin under your chin because feasting season is here. Katherine Spiers &amp;ndash; journalist, food anthropologist and host of the wondrous culinary history podcast Smart Mouth &amp;ndash; lets Alie belly up for a buffet of questions about winter gatherings, Thanksgiving myths, stuffed peacocks, green bean casseroles, potato backstories, Friendsgivings, the hazards of deep frying, the eels of Jesus, some stuffing horrors and more.</description></item><item><title>Eschatology (THE APOCALYPSE) with Phil Torres | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860299/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 04:03:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860299/</guid><description>Podcast Description Doomsday. The apocalypse. The End. Join scholar, author and professional existential risk philosopher Phil Torres for a surprisingly jovial romp through different &amp;ldquo;Oops we&amp;rsquo;re screwed&amp;rdquo; scenarios that will lead to the destruction of the planet or extinction of our species. (Not to be confused with lepidopterologist/butterfly man, Phil Torres.) Find out where we&amp;rsquo;re at on Ye Olde Doomsday clock, if any of us should have babies, if AI will destroy us, pop-cultural Antichrists, Black Mirror, simulations, technology as friend or foe, why voting matters (lookin’ at you, America) and how to remain chill in the face of doom.</description></item><item><title>Corvid Thanatology (CROW FUNERALS) with Kaeli Swift | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860300/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 01:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860300/</guid><description>Podcast Description Crows have funerals? CROWS HAVE FUNERALS. The inky black bird with the big brain warns and maybe mourns around their fallen friends and Dr. Kaeli Swift is here to tell us all about it. As an avid wildlife researcher and corvid specialist, she&amp;rsquo;s observed death behaviors that will shock you to your bones and ruffle your hackles &amp;ndash; while somehow also making you cry about peanuts. Also: so much inspiration to keep being yourself and to work hard toward what you love.</description></item><item><title>Somnology (SLEEP) Part 2 with Dr. W. Chris Winter | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860301/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860301/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you listened to Part 1 yet? No? Go on, git. Go do that.
Now if you have, this Part 2 is a bonanza of problem solving from neurologist and somnologist Dr. W. Chris Winter. He&amp;rsquo;ll cover: if you should be taking sleep supplements or pills, sleep talking, apnea, why sleepiness makes us hungry, narcolepsy, the difference between insomnia and sleep deprivation, how to lucid dream, the dangers of shift work and some tactics to lull yourself to dreamland without any medications.</description></item><item><title>Somnology (SLEEP) Part 1 with W. Chris Winter | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860302/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 05:41:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860302/</guid><description>Podcast Description Birds do it. Bees do it. Why the hell can&amp;rsquo;t we do it? Called &amp;ldquo;The Sleep Whisperer,&amp;rdquo; neurologist and sleep specialist Dr. W. Chris Winter joins Alie for a thrilling 2-parter about why we need sleep, the ideal amount of it, what sleep does to the brain, insomnia, sleep stages, ideal bedtime conditions, and even the historical lore around sleep paralysis. Next week, we&amp;rsquo;ll answer listener questions about everything from sleeping pills to brain performance to insomnia cures to apnea to sleepwalking to parenthood and shift work.</description></item><item><title>Surgical Oncology (BREAST CANCER) with Donna-Marie Manasseh | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860303/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 03:06:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860303/</guid><description>Podcast Description (Bonus: I bleeped any curse words so you can share this episode with your kids and your grandma.)
Yes, October is Breast Cancer Awareness month but Dr. Donna-Marie Manasseh spends 12 months a year as a tumor hunter, saving lives. She is brilliant, uplifting, hilarious and a hero, quite honestly. She sat down in her Brooklyn office to talk about prevention, diagnosis, prognosis, when to get screened, what to do if you feel something weird, how to look forward to mammograms, how men can help family members stay informed, self-care and how she unwinds.</description></item><item><title>Ologiesology with Alie Ward (1-Year Anniversary Episode) | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860304/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 00:42:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860304/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ever wanted to know how an episode of Ologies is made? Are you curious to learn about your host Alie Ward’s journey into science communication and beyond? If you need to know how Dad Ward does it all each week, this episode is for you.
Become a patron of Ologies for as little as a buck a month: www.Patreon.com/ologies
OlogiesMerch.com has hats, shirts, pins, totes!
Follow @Ologies on Twitter or Instagram</description></item><item><title>Functional Morphology (ANATOMY) with Joy Reidenberg | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860305/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 01:59:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860305/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ever poked at roadkill? Watched videos of whales exploding? Drooled over a curio cabinet full of claws &amp;amp; bones? Peered into a jar with a pickled toad? Then this one is for you. Arguably the world&amp;rsquo;s most famous comparative anatomist (and pretty-much-also functional morphologist) Dr. Joy Reidenberg pulls up a chair at Mt. Sinai Hospital to talk about her fascinating backstory, exploding whales, taxidermied chipmunks, dead toadfish, animal&amp;rsquo;s weird anatomy and its function and how it might help human health.</description></item><item><title>Myrmecology (ANTS) with Terry McGlynn | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860306/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 01:43:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860306/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cult-leader queens. Bullet ant stings. Kitchen pest hacks. The dynamics of a billion-sister megacolony. Dr. Terry McGlynn sits down to have a BIG discussion about itty-bitty creatures. Learn about tropical ants, urban ants, how they walk on water, which ones are picky eaters, which ones make weird sounds, what ant movies are bunk, and some self-help takeaways. Also: sniffing your relatives before deciding to kill them.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Egyptology (ANCIENT EGYPT) with Kara Cooney | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860307/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 03:46:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860307/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a decade of fandom, Alie finally meets famed Egyptologist Dr. Kara Cooney &amp;ndash; and forgets her equipment. They meet again for a spirited history lesson on ancient Egypt: the pyramids, the monarchs, the dynasties, the cats, the corpses, the curses. Kara also lays out the history of female kings and their parallels to modern Western politics, what it&amp;rsquo;s like to talk to a mummy, and why we should stop overworking.</description></item><item><title>Conservation Technology (EARTH SAVING) with Shah Selbe | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860308/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 00:50:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860308/</guid><description>Podcast Description THIS IS UPLIFTING, I PROMISE. And it might just make you switch careers. As a bookend to last week&amp;rsquo;s Oceanology episode, Conservation Technologist Shah Selbe chats about saving the planet with some well-intentioned technology. Wind turbines, solar cars, and all the ways in which sensors, drones, recycled smartphones and real-time data reporting can help conserve species, spaces and communities that are threatened. Hear inspiring tales of travel, art, adventure and putting engineering to good use from a former rocket-science turned professional do-gooder.</description></item><item><title>Oceanology (OCEANS) with Ayana Johnson | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860309/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 01:03:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860309/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are plastic straws really that bad? What&amp;rsquo;s the oldest message in a bottle? Any scuba vs. snorkel strategies? Does sunscreen kill coral? Can we reverse ocean warming in our lifetime? In a conversation with ocean and policy expert Dr. Ayana Johnson, Alie struggles with finding a balance between the wonders and the bummers. For the first 15-20 minutes, learn weird ocean trivia, why we love the sea, and facts about the ocean&amp;rsquo;s depths and beauty.</description></item><item><title>Ferroequinology (TRAINS) with Matt Anderson | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860310/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 00:06:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860310/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trains. Locomotives. Choochoos. Bullet trains. Hyperloops. Subways. How fast can they go? How did they change American history? Why do people love them? What should we do with all that abandoned track? Can you marry a train? What&amp;rsquo;s it like to shovel coal into a steam engine?
Alie went off the rails at the Henry Ford Museum in Dearborn, Michigan talking to an official ferroequinologist and curator Matt Anderson &amp;ndash; who confessed to some youthful railroad mischief, delivered a succinct slice of U.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Minisode: Kalology -- Your Letters | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860311/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 00:25:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860311/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a companion to Kalology (BEAUTY STANDARDS) Alie reads your thoughts about appearance and beauty culture in this, a bonus minisode. You wrote in about how make-up is a creative outlet, how beauty standards can be an oppressive time suck, about hairy pits and culture clashes, money burdens, appearances in different professions, trans and non-binary perspectives, and what you wish the next generation did differently. Y&amp;rsquo;all made Ol&amp;rsquo; Ward tear up more than once, and it&amp;rsquo;s an honor to share your stories.</description></item><item><title>Kalology (BEAUTY STANDARDS) with Renee Engeln | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860312/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 00:24:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860312/</guid><description>Podcast Description We love it. We hate it. BEAUTY CULTURE.
Looking good can make us feel decorated, empowered and more confident &amp;ndash; but why?
And why are certain groups subtly told to &amp;ldquo;make-up&amp;rdquo; for their appearance?
What&amp;rsquo;s the line between self-care and oppression?
Psychologist and beauty-researcher Dr. Renee Engeln shines a huge bright floodlight on the sometimes ugly machinery of the billion-dollar beauty and &amp;ldquo;fitness&amp;rdquo; industry. This is an episode for make-up lovers, haters and the millions of us confused about being both at once.</description></item><item><title>Oology (EGGS) with John Bates | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860313/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 03:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860313/</guid><description>Podcast Description The biggest eggs! The smallest eggs! The people arrested for stealing the most eggs! Oologist Dr. John Bates gave Alie a tour of the egg vault at the Field Museum of Chicago and it was a barrage of beautiful sights and shocking facts about bird butts. Get ready for speckly eggs, falcon tales, delicate treasures, pigeon mysteries, modern research with old artifacts, Easter bullshit, and whether or not you can hatch chickens from grocery store eggs.</description></item><item><title>Ophthalmology (EYES) with Reid Wainess | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860314/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 04:07:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860314/</guid><description>Podcast Description 75% of adult Americans have wonky vision of some kind, your host included. Longtime pal and real-life eye surgeon, Dr. Reid Wainess answers all the questions that you never bring up during appointments. He and Alie chat about how eyes are just little cameras in your skull, glasses vs. contacts, Lasik, why we cry, some boggling ER stories, how marijuana effects eyeballs, floaters, cataracts, eye color, dogs in goggles and more.</description></item><item><title>Epidemiology (DISEASES) with 'This Podcast Will Kill You's' Erins Welsh &amp; Allmann-Updyke | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860315/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860315/</guid><description>Podcast Description TWO epidemiologists-named-Erin &amp;ndash; and hosts of the stellar This Podcast Will Kill You &amp;ndash; chat with Alie about historical horror stories, THE plague, cholera cocktails, flu shots, tick bombs, milkmaids, witch trials and more as they share their infectious enthusiasm for disease ecology. How much should you wash your hands? What&amp;rsquo;s the best way to flirt with a stranger on a bus? Why are people scared of vaccines? What conspiracy theory enthralls Alie?</description></item><item><title>Selachimorphology (SHARKS) with Chris Lowe | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860316/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860316/</guid><description>Podcast Description SHAAAARKS. Leading shark researcher Dr. Chris Lowe dishes about bad shark PR, behind-the-scenes Jaws trivia, his thoughts on Sharknado, surfing safety, immune system marvels, cannibal twins, shark personalities, sea sex, and knife teeth. Alie learns that sharks are not the ocean&amp;rsquo;s sociopaths but true evolutionary marvels who suffer from sensationalized reputations and sometimes inside-out butts. Listen up as a science primer during this, the holy Week of the Shark.</description></item><item><title>Malacology (SNAILS &amp; SLUGS) with Jann Vendetti | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860317/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860317/</guid><description>Podcast Description Crazy dongs! Gardening tips! Snail-based beauty products! Weather the LA heatwave and slug along with Dr. Jann Vendetti of the Natural History Museum of LA County as she gossips with Alie about some sensual slug lovemaking, Gold Rush lore, urban snails, beer bingeing and why you should stop and high five (high one?) a gastropod for evolving into such an interesting critter. Also: should you adopt a rabbit-sized pet snail?</description></item><item><title>Areology (MARS) Part 2 with Jennifer Buz | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860318/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 06:05:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860318/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last week we got a big thicc primer on ol&amp;rsquo; Mars, that dusty desert doomsday cabin millions of miles away. This week, Alie continues the conversation with areologist Dr. Jennifer Buz and asks your Patreon questions about whether we could landscape Mars to look like a golf course, what a water balloon fight on Mars would be like, and if people in Jennifer&amp;rsquo;s lab quote science fiction. Plus we hear directly from Kim Staney Robinson on the moral quandaries of inhabiting the red planet and explore the question: &amp;ldquo;Why is Elon Musk so horny for Mars?</description></item><item><title>Areology (MARS) Part 1 with Jennifer Buz | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860319/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 08:55:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860319/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Red Planet. A mysterious dusty orb millions of miles away. Our emergency escape bunker. Alie sits down with Dr. Jennifer Buz to talk about what Mars’s DEEEEAL is, why we send rovers there, good science fiction, so-so science fiction, double egg yolks, the poetry of the moon Phobos and some of the best science dreams perhaps ever recorded. Jennifer is maybe the chillest areologist on this planet and an absolute gem.</description></item><item><title>MINISODE: Aestaology (SUMMER) should be a word | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860320/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 04:39:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860320/</guid><description>Podcast Description Melons. Fire. Waterfights. It&amp;rsquo;s finally summer and Alie&amp;rsquo;s into it. So with this solo mini-ep, learn about a few ologies that are not real but should be such as aestaology (summer) &amp;amp; hydropolemology (waterfights). Also discussed: a few ologies that are in fact real, like cucurbitology (melons), pyrotechnology (humans chillin&amp;rsquo; and grillin&amp;rsquo; around a fire) and lampyridology (fireflies.) Just a little buffet o&amp;rsquo; facts to get you excited about summer.</description></item><item><title>Deltiology (POSTCARDS) with Donna Braden | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860321/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 05:47:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860321/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why were postcards invented and why do they still exist? Why do we lie to people and say our lives are better than they are? Alie stopped into the Henry Ford Museum in Dearborn, Michigan and talked to curator of 40 years, Donna Braden, about her work with the postcard collections &amp;ndash; as well as her musings about how emotions impact memory, why Americans love to hit the open road and what the biggest postcard you&amp;rsquo;re allowed to mail is.</description></item><item><title>Rhinology (NOSES) with John Craig | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860322/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 07:50:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860322/</guid><description>Podcast Description Allergies. Nose jobs. Smell nostalgia. Street drugs. Septum piercings. Snoring. Hang on to your faces because Dr. John Craig goes deep and shares why he&amp;rsquo;s so passionate about rhinology. You&amp;rsquo;ll have a whole new relationship with your whiffer, appreciating what happens behind your nas-holes and coming away with some strategies to combat hay fever, Afrin addiction plus: a very legal substitute for illegal party drugs. Also: why you may want to shove a crayon into your nose.</description></item><item><title>Phonology (LINGUISTICS) with Nicole Holliday | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860323/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860323/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vocal fry. Code switching. Black Twitter. Valley girls. Culture vultures. WE&amp;rsquo;RE TALKING ABOUT TALKING. Alie battles traffic to sit down with linguistics professor Dr. Nicole Holliday about intonational phonology: how tones and pitch help us bond with others and construct identities. Inspired in part by former President Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s masterful linguistic variability, Dr. Holliday&amp;rsquo;s work focuses on how language is used in the crossing and construction of racial/ethnic boundaries.</description></item><item><title>Cynology (DOGS) with Brandon McMillan | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860324/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 05:57:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860324/</guid><description>Podcast Description Your best friend is a hairy beast and that&amp;rsquo;s something to celebrate. This episode is a little different in tone and let&amp;rsquo;s just say GOOD LUCK NOT CRYING, SUCKERS. Alie sits down with &amp;ldquo;Lucky Dog&amp;rdquo; host Brandon McMillan, who cares more about saving shelter mutts than he does about the 3 Daytime Emmys he&amp;rsquo;s won for doing it. Learn about his Hollywood drama-worthy backstory that led to being one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most celebrated dog trainers, plus how to calm anxious pups, breeders vs.</description></item><item><title>Lepidopterology (BUTTERFLIES) with Phil Torres | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860325/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860325/</guid><description>Podcast Description Butterflies are gross. Yes they are delightful and beautiful and part of any idyllic picnic-scape but lepidopterologist, TV host and jungle explorer Phil Torres is here to gossip about how shamelessly disgusting our favorite bugs actually are. Learn their secrets, their mating habits, how they turn themselves into goo and then into another creature, what moth os the most goth, what flowers to plant to attract them, the scariest thing about the jungle and what it feels like to help discover new species.</description></item><item><title>Trichology (HAIR) with Valerie Horsley | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860326/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 06:17:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860326/</guid><description>Podcast Description Peach fuzz. Chin hairs. Mammalian ponytails. WHY DO THEY HAPPEN. Yale researcher and associate professor Dr. Valerie Horsley stops by California to chat with Alie about the nature of hair and why it grows in the wrong places, the causes and remedies for hair loss, the grossest museum ever, and why we love and hate and need our hair as animals. Also: Dr. Horsely&amp;rsquo;s decision to run for office and Alie&amp;rsquo;s disgusting confessions, per usual.</description></item><item><title>Dendrology (TREES) with J. Casey Clapp | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860327/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860327/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do trees have feelings? How do they talk? How old can they get? Are there any tree stories that will make me cry? Spoiler: YES. Possibly the world&amp;rsquo;s most enthusiastic tree expert, J. Casey Clapp, shows Alie his many tree tattoos, explains how roots communicate to each other, addresses &amp;ldquo;crown shyness&amp;rdquo; and schools Alie on the mental health benefits of tree proximity. Also: banana facts and Casey f*cking hates apples.</description></item><item><title>Fearology Pt. 2 (FEAR) with Mary Poffenroth | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860328/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860328/</guid><description>Podcast Description FEAR. Anxiety. Stress. Dread. It&amp;rsquo;s all the same dang thing, as it turns out. Biologist and fear expert Mary Poffenroth is back for Part 2 of what has been one of the most helpful interviews of ol&amp;rsquo; Alie Ward&amp;rsquo;s life. Learn how super successful people approach fear, Mary’s scariest hour, plus answers to all of your questions about night terrors, self-spookery, sharks&amp;rsquo; bad PR image to how likely it is that a snake will bite your butt.</description></item><item><title>Fearology Pt. 1 (FEAR) with Mary Poffenroth | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860329/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860329/</guid><description>Podcast Description Every day, your brain tries to save your life by being terrified. Thanks, brain! Also, calm the f*ck down, brain. Alie hunted down Mary Poffenroth, an expert in the biological and sociological causes/effects of fear and it is riveting. This real life FEAROLOGIST (which is a real word) talks about how fear is literally killing you, the difference between stress and fear, how to get along with your co-workers, friends, or partner better, and how to talk to your brain when it has needlessly pulled the fire alarm.</description></item><item><title>Radiology (X-RAY VISION) with Varshana Gurusamy | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860330/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860330/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey, kiddo, it&amp;rsquo;s what&amp;rsquo;s INSIDE that matters &amp;ndash; like your guts and bones and squishy brain and intestines and stuff. Meet Dr. Varshana Gurusamy: diagnostic radiology resident, Texan and amazing person with great stories. You&amp;rsquo;ll learn the difference between an MRI and an ultrasound, between a CT scan and a CAT scan and why you should not put big things in orifices that you might not be able to retrieve them unaided.</description></item><item><title>Evolutionary Biology (DARWINISM) with John McCormack | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860331/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 06:57:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860331/</guid><description>Podcast Description Celebrate your lucky mutations with an episode about natural selection, agonizing boat trips, redemption stories, olde timey inter-family marriages, how much money you can make playing videos games, finch beaks, whether or not cave men are kinda hot and how to live on a small island with your soulmate. Evolutionary biologist and the director of the Moore Lab of Zoology, John McCormack, chats about all things evolution and gives Alie a new appreciation for how genetic blips can be hidden strengths.</description></item><item><title>Gynecology (NETHER HEALTH) with Philippa Ribbink | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860332/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 04:04:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860332/</guid><description>Podcast Description Let&amp;rsquo;s get intimate with the mechanics of nether parts via a frank chat with the calmest, coolest gyno in Portland, Dr. Philippa Ribbink. She visited Alie&amp;rsquo;s weird hotel to chat about vaginas (vs. vulvas), self-care, mental health, imposter syndrome, trans care, childbirth, body image, the accuracy of assault statistics, grooming, hygiene and more. NO QUESTION WAS TOO DELICATE, FOLKS.
Language alert: In considering the inclusion of trans women, I opted for the use of the term &amp;ldquo;women&amp;rsquo;s health&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;women&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; as gynecology is currently (yet antiquatedly) defined.</description></item><item><title>Zymology (BEER) with Quinton Sturgeon | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860333/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 04:05:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860333/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you like booze, you&amp;rsquo;ll love&amp;hellip; fungus! Alie goes Rogue and takes a field trip to a brewery in Newport, OR where she smells vats of bubbling beer slop and learns about the microorganisms that are the workhorses of the brewing industry. Learn about yeasts, how beer is made, the hardest part about being a beer maker, the thick history of beer, some home brewing tips and also a nugget about bungholes.</description></item><item><title>Melittology (BEES) with Amanda Shaw | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860334/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860334/</guid><description>Podcast Description BEES! Hives, honey, and how to keep them as outdoor pets. Meet melittologist and President of the Urban Beekeepers Association, Amanda Shaw. She and Alie cozy up in a weird hotel in Portland to chat about honeybees vs. native ones, how to become a beekeeper, social savagery that rivals Game of Thrones, if you should eat honey to deal with seasonal allergies, what happens in the drone zone (hint: boning) and how we can SAVE THESE FRIGGIN BEES.</description></item><item><title>Museology (MUSEUMS) with Ronnie Cline | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860335/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860335/</guid><description>Podcast Description Museums! Mummies! Paintings! Hot dogs! Alie sits down with her dear internet friend and museologist Ronnie Cline, who manages 30,000 artifacts over 22 California State Park Museums. Get the hot gossip about behind-the-scenes museum life, vintage ghosts, following your dreams, changing the tone of history and the time Alie ruined a 16th Century Dutch portrait. Also: why Jack London is your new dead celebrity crush.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Gizmology (ROBOTS) with Simone Giertz | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860336/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2018 05:24:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860336/</guid><description>Podcast Description YouTube&amp;rsquo;s Sh*tty Robots machine-maker, very funny human being, professional tinkerer and potential astronaut Simone Giertz hops in Alie&amp;rsquo;s car to hang out in a sketchy Hollywood alley and chat. Topics covered: the definition of a robot, artificial intelligence, the gateway to her thirst for engineering power, plastic animals, and topless grandmas.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mythology (STORYTELLING) with John Bucher | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860337/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860337/</guid><description>Podcast Description Superhero movies. Bastardized fairy tales. The psychology of celebrity. Star Wars. And yes, some ancient Greek and Roman myths. Professional mythologist and screenwriting consultant John Bucher spins some yarns and unravels some mysteries behind what makes a good story, and why we so desperately need them. Also: rethinking your own life&amp;rsquo;s narrative and gaining a greater appreciation for Elvira. Trust me.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Teuthology (SQUIDS) with Sarah McAnulty | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860338/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 07:21:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860338/</guid><description>Podcast Description Squids. Cuttlefish. Octopusseseses. The world&amp;rsquo;s most impassioned squid nerd, Sarah McAnulty, gets locked in a basement with Alie to talk about cephalopods, alien DNA, camouflage, invisibility cloaks, why cute things make us insane, terrible mating strategies, cute and clever ones and why she is so charmed by squid. Also addressed: Philly accents and the Kraken.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sexology (SEX) with Shan Boody aka Shannon Boodram | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860339/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 08:51:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860339/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sex. Sex. Sex. Sex. Also sex. Buckle up, Ologites, because clinical sexologist and author Shannon Boodram (known for her sex educational YouTube channel ShanBoody) chats with Alie about sexual identity, how a friggin&amp;rsquo; vagina works, how to get over slumps, love languages, monogamy vs. open relationships, dating in the wake of #metoo, some fun with prostate orgasms, foot fetishes and why relationships can be like pizza. Then at the very very end Alie talks about the weirdest sex dream she&amp;rsquo;s ever had SORRY.</description></item><item><title>Gelotology (LAUGHTER) with Lee Berk | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860340/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860340/</guid><description>Podcast Description The. Study. Of. Laughter. It exists, and it&amp;rsquo;s called gelotology. In one of the oddly more somber episodes, Alie sits down with Dr. Lee Berk, a doctor who is &amp;ldquo;serious about laughter&amp;rdquo; and has dedicated decades to hunting down how humor affects the body. Learn about what makes a joke a joke, the science behind happiness, why you laugh when you&amp;rsquo;re nervous, if comedians are naturally depressed or if that&amp;rsquo;s a myth, and why some people get paid to tickle rats.</description></item><item><title>Ichthyology (FISHES) with Chris Thacker | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860341/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860341/</guid><description>Podcast Description ALL. ABOUT. FISH. Hilariously charming fish expert and LA County Natural History Museum Curator of Ichthyology, Dr. Christine Thacker, sits down with Alie in a basement full of several million jars of fish to chat about the worst fish husbands, the weirdest mating behaviors, the scariest fish, the nicest fish, the tiniest fish, how they breathe, how you can help reverse global warming, and whether you should pee in wetsuits.</description></item><item><title>Herpetology (SNAKES, FROGS, ETC.) with David Steen | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860342/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860342/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sea turtles, frog storms, Indiana Jones trivia, the triumph of will that was Snakes on a Plane, plus dissembling your anti-sneck feelings with Dr. David Steen. Learn more about what makes a herp a herp, the unfortunate etymology behind the ology, and why you&amp;rsquo;ll be a rebel by loving snakes. A great episode for those who want to conquer their fears with science and logic, and also who grew up romping around and turning over logs.</description></item><item><title>Sports &amp; Performance Psychology (ANXIETY &amp; CONFIDENCE) with Sari Shepphird | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860343/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860343/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sweaty palms before a date. Racing heart during a presentation. Needing a diaper while delivering a wedding toast. We&amp;rsquo;ve all been there. On the heels of New Year&amp;rsquo;s resolutions, sports &amp;amp; performance psychologist Dr. Sari Shepphird explains confidence vs. performance anxiety, the origins of perfectionism, how much social media is too much, self-sabotoage and also dishes on strategies that athletes use to perform under pressure. Also: why you should holler the F word when you&amp;rsquo;re nervous, why being authentic is always the best policy and the perils of professional darts.</description></item><item><title>Hematology (BLOOD) with Brian Durie | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860344/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860344/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bloooood. In this special episode, Alie sits down with Scotsman and hematologist Dr. Brian Durie to talk about blood: what it is, and what can go wrong. As an oncologist, Dr. Durie is a leading researcher in multiple myeloma, a disease that&amp;rsquo;s deeply affected Alie&amp;rsquo;s family. So learn about what&amp;rsquo;s in your blood and how doctors are finding new cures and therapies for the people diagnosed with blood cancers.</description></item><item><title>Glycobiology (CARBS) with Michelle Dookwah | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860345/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 12:30:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860345/</guid><description>Podcast Description Carbohydrates: no longer just for your piehole. Stuff some knowledge into your ears with sugar scientist Michelle Dookwah and learn how your cells use carbs to communicate, the whys behind your winter cravings, the hot goss on the keto diet, and how much sugar you should really be eating. Also: B-movies about biology and the weirdest thing Alie ate today.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cosmology PART 2 with Katie Mack | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860346/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860346/</guid><description>Podcast Description Listener questions! The universe, dimensions, asteroid bags and cosmic vertigo with the amazing Dr. Katie Mack. Part 1 was a primer on all things cosmological, from particle physics to black holes, so listen to that first then hop to this episode to get all your questions answered.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cosmology (THE UNIVERSE) with Katie Mack, Part I | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860347/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860347/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stars. Black holes. THE GAWDANG UNIVERSE. Astrophysicist and cosmologist Katie Mack (@astrokatie) joins to tell us her most embarrassing moments as a cosmologist, to debunk some physicist myths and give the nuts + bolts of everything form particle physics to gravitational waves and existential mysteries. Walk away with cocktail party comprehension of everything from the itty-bitty quarks that make you to the neutron stars banging together across the cosmos.</description></item><item><title>Entomology (INSECTS) with Lila Higgins | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860348/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 02:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860348/</guid><description>Podcast Description Buuuugs. We cover perhaps Alie&amp;rsquo;s favorite ology ever with an ologist who changed her life. Meet Lila Higgins: the self-professed &amp;ldquo;bug geek&amp;rdquo; with passion more infectious than a glassy winged sharpshooter mouth. (That will make sense later.) We talk about clowns in the forest, badgers, Hare Krishnas, solitary bugs vs. social ones, why wasps are such dicks and why it&amp;rsquo;s totally fine to kiss a cockroach and eat a cricket.</description></item><item><title>Minisode: Grateful-ology is not a real word... | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860349/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860349/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a friend of a friend&amp;rsquo;s hairdresser once said: &amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s hard to be hateful with a plateful of grateful.&amp;rdquo; Is it? In this pre-holidays quickie episode, Alie is grumpy as hell and decides to research the neuroscience of gratitude. Does it work? Who&amp;rsquo;s studying it? Does she need to buy a journal? Find out how jotting down things you don&amp;rsquo;t hate on the back of a receipt or opening a secret Twitter account may be worth more than whatever you get in your office Secret Santa exchange.</description></item><item><title>Cosmetology (GLAM/GROOMING) with Alysha Sherri Marcantonio | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860350/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 07:51:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860350/</guid><description>Podcast Description Skin care! Beard care! History! Grooming! Men&amp;rsquo;s concealer! Make-up! And most importantly: what is self-confidence and where does it come from? The incredibly charming Alysha Marcantonio has been Alie&amp;rsquo;s make-up artist for years and stepped in the booth to dish about HOW IN THE HECKERS she always has perfect skin (Alysha, not Alie), what it&amp;rsquo;s like to hear all the gossip on set, creature prosthetics vs. glam squad and why beauty truly does come from the inside.</description></item><item><title>Ornithology (BIRDS) with James Maley | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860351/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 12:22:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860351/</guid><description>Podcast Description Birds! Horned screamers! Winged pirates! Professional bird-person and all around cool dude James Maley joins Alie to talk about bird mating, monogamy, the cult of ornithology, absurd birds, parrots that are smarter than your friends&amp;rsquo; kids, a surprising fact about owl ears and history&amp;rsquo;s most tragically zealous bird nerds. If you love birds, you&amp;rsquo;ll be at home. If a bird did you dirty, you&amp;rsquo;ll open your heart and learn to love again.</description></item><item><title>Thanatology (DEATH &amp; DYING) with Cole Imperi | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860352/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 12:18:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860352/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hoooo boy. We&amp;rsquo;re all up in death and dying&amp;rsquo;s bizness and to Alie&amp;rsquo;s shock, it&amp;rsquo;s not a bummer. Confront and perhaps OVERCOME existential anxiety as we discuss not only the science of death but the nature and goddamn beauty of life. Everything from burial methods, the latest in eco funerals, what a funeral director hates most, how gnomes die, and how to regret less. Meet your new favorite thanatologist and oddly, get the guts to be the you you want to be.</description></item><item><title>Minisode: Fall Ologies! ... Fallogies? | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860353/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 20:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860353/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s hot and Alie is nostalgic for fall. So here&amp;rsquo;s a mini episode on the world&amp;rsquo;s best autumn ologies to cozy up your week. Considerate blood bats, pumpkin hacks, leaf phenology, and &amp;hellip; Real. Life. Zombies.
alieward.com/ologies
Instagram.com/ologies
Twitter.com/ologiespod
OlogiesMerch.com
Music by Nick Thorburn
Support the show: http://Patreon.com/ologies
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Horology (WATCHES) with Cameron Weiss | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860354/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 05:04:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860354/</guid><description>Podcast Description Million-dollar watches, World War II&amp;rsquo;s role in watchmaking, and how much caffeine a watchmaker drinks. Twenty-something horologist Cameron Weiss also dishes about mechanical vs. quartz, little tiny springs, patience, S-Town and the history of timekeeping. Also we address rap lyrics and some existential boolsheet.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Gemology (CRYSTALS &amp; GEMS) with Kelly Sitek | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860355/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 12:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860355/</guid><description>Podcast Description Professional gemologist Kelly Sitek talks about adventures in mining, the chemical composition of different gems, breaks down the test taking process for gemology and gives advice on haunted stones. We also spill some tea on cultured pearls and address the psychology and neurological merits of crystals/the placebo effect. Whether you are a staunch skeptic or all about woo-woo, you may end up shoving a crystal down your pants just for good luck.</description></item><item><title>Paleontology (DINOSAURS) with Michael Habib | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860356/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 07:50:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860356/</guid><description>Podcast Description Did Ross Gellar ruin being a paleontologist? What&amp;rsquo;s the hot goss on dino feathers? How did some dinos have four wings and which costs more: a used sedan or a dinosaur? Featuring guest Michael Habib of the Natural History Museum of LA County. Also covered: why Alie used to feel meh about dinos (DON&amp;rsquo;T JUDGE) and the realities of cloning. Oh and penis implants.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Primatology (MONKEYS &amp; APES) with Kate Gilmore | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860357/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860357/</guid><description>Podcast Description Settle in with Alie Ward and guest Kate Gilmore, a professional primatologist and lead keeper of the great apes and Old World monkeys at the Los Angeles Zoo. Learn about chimpanzee mating, why zookeepers don&amp;rsquo;t wear FitBits, primate DRAAAMA, the erroneous philosophy behind truck nuts and what happens in the middle the night at the zoo. Also get some good info on primate conservation and how to be a friend to orangutans.</description></item><item><title>Volcanology (VOLCANOES) with Jess Phoenix | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860358/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860358/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this first episode of Ologies, Alie Ward chats with volcanologist Jess Phoenix who also happens to be running for Congress. Learn how hot magma is, how volcanoes are formed, how screwed the Pacific Northwest is, what thrills Jess about volcanoes, and what to do if surrounded by horse bandits. Also: some valuable information about haunted lava tubes.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 0 | Ologies with Alie Ward</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9981860359/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 05:12:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9981860359/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedy podcaster and science correspondent Alie Ward asks smart people dumb questions to learn about their professional obsessions.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>