<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Criminal on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/criminal/</link><description>Recent content in Criminal on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 09:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/criminal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Episode 248: The Questions I’m Asking | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530261/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530261/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we meet “Genius Grant” winner Andrea Armstrong. In 2019, she started the Incarceration Transparency Project to identify and make public how many people were dying behind bars in Louisiana. The project also documents conditions inside the state’s prisons and jails – what Andrea Armstrong calls “secretive spaces of confinement.” She’s said: “Too often, the how and why a person in prison dies is kept secret from everyone, including the person’s family.</description></item><item><title>Episode 247: Send Her to the Island | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530001/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530001/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a young woman showed up at a boarding house in Manhattan, she said her name was Nellie Brown – but that was all she seemed to remember about herself. Soon, people became scared of her. Someone went to the police: &amp;ldquo;I want you to take her quietly.&amp;rdquo; Stacy Horn&amp;rsquo;s book is Damnation Island: Poor, Sick, Mad, and Criminal in 19th-Century New York. Travis Russ&amp;rsquo; upcoming play is The Gorgeous Nothings.</description></item><item><title>Episode 246: The Kit | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530002/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530002/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the early 1970s, Marty Goddard was worried about the high rates of sexual assault in Chicago. She learned from police that evidence from sexual assault cases often wasn’t collected properly — or at all. “They said, ‘We don’t get evidence.’ And this really kicked everything off.” Criminal is going back on tour in February! We’ll be telling brand new stories, live on stage. You can even get meet and greet tickets to come and say hi before the show.</description></item><item><title>Episode 245: Masterpiece | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530003/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530003/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the 1950s poodles were all the rage — one tabloid even reported that when a girl “makes the big time she traditionally acquires 3 things — minks, gems, and a poodle.” But one poodle in particular put the breed on the map. His name was Masterpiece… and police in 13 states knew exactly what he looked like. This episode originally aired in 2018. To listen to more family-friendly episodes of Criminal and This is Love, check out our playlist here.</description></item><item><title>Episode 244: Fine Art and Meat Cleavers | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530004/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530004/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1913, museums and art galleries in London received a memo from the police. It told them to be careful when they let in visitors – women might try to attack the art. Criminal is going back on tour in February! We’ll be telling brand new stories, live on stage. You can even get meet and greet tickets to come and say hi before the show. Tickets are on sale now at thisiscriminal.</description></item><item><title>Episode 243: The Liverpool Exchange | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530005/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530005/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the 1980s, Liverpool was having what journalists called a heroin epidemic. The chairman of a local organization where people would go for drug counseling told a reporter, “We are on the brink of complete catastrophe.” Then a small group of people decided to try something. Maia Szalavitz’s book is Undoing Drugs: How Harm Reduction Is Changing the Future of Drugs and Addiction. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Episode 242: Interrogation Room | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530006/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530006/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a 17-hour-long interrogation, a woman confesses to a murder. But then, evidence surfaces proving that she can’t have actually done it – and that it was a false confession. Today, we’re looking at what goes on in an interrogation room – and hear a recording from inside. Maurice Chammah and the Marshall Project released a 6-part podcast series about James Holland and Larry Driskill – it’s called “Smoke Screen: Just Say You’re Sorry.</description></item><item><title>Episode 241: How to Sell a Haunted House | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530007/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530007/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1989, Helen Ackley decided to sell her old Victorian house in Nyack, New York. It didn’t go as planned. The house became the center of a case that’s referred to as “The Ghostbusters ruling.” This episode was originally released in 2020. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.com/CriminalShow. Criminal is going back on tour in February!</description></item><item><title>Episode 240: The Spy | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530008/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jack Barsky was a college student in 1970 when the KGB knocked on the door of his dorm room to inquire about his plans after college. “I was told to broaden my knowledge of culture, of literature, of music, to become a well-educated person who could operate in higher strata of society.” Jack Barsky wrote a book about his life. It’s called Deep Undercover: My Secret Life and Tangled Allegiances as a KGB Spy in America.</description></item><item><title>Episode 239: Chesa, Kathy, and David | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530009/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kathy Boudin and David Gilbert were once members of the radical activist group the Weather Underground. In 1981, they helped members of the Black Liberation Army rob a Brink’s armored car at the Nanuet National Bank. Their son, Chesa Boudin, was 14 months old at the time. He spent his childhood visiting his parents in prison. Criminal is going back on tour in February! We’ll be telling brand new stories, live on stage.</description></item><item><title>Jiminy Crickets | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here&amp;rsquo;s a little preview of what we’re making over on Criminal Plus! We’re having a lot of fun making these bonus episodes. In each one, Criminal co-creator Lauren Spohrer and I take your questions and talk about what’s happening behind the scenes – and anything else that comes up. Recently we’ve talked about the only time I’ve ever stopped an interview, unusual gift ideas, Lauren’s love of sheet cakes, how to fall asleep, and some unwelcome guests in my studio.</description></item><item><title>Episode 238: The Confession, Part 2 | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530011/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530011/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode continues where Episode 237 leaves off. 17 years after he shot a man, Trevell Coleman walked into a police station and tried to turn himself in. He’d never been a suspect in the case, and had kept the secret for years. He also never knew if the man had lived or died — but after turning himself in, he finally found out. Criminal is going back on tour in February!</description></item><item><title>Episode 237: The Confession, Part 1 | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530012/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trevell Coleman signed with Bad Boy Records in 1998. He made it onto the Billboard charts, and was called “the latest protege of rap’s royal family.” But there was something from his past he hadn’t told anyone about – and he couldn’t let it go. Criminal is going back on tour in February! We’ll be telling brand new stories, live on stage. You can even get meet and greet tickets to come and say hi before the show.</description></item><item><title>Phoebe vs. Oyster | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530013/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re coming up on 10 years of Criminal. In the past decade, we&amp;rsquo;ve loved taking the show all over the country - including the time I ate a bad oyster in San Francisco and almost didn&amp;rsquo;t make it on stage. It means a lot to us, to be together with you in person - so we&amp;rsquo;re excited to be doing it again soon. This February, we&amp;rsquo;ll be coming to Seattle, San Francisco, Los Angeles, St.</description></item><item><title>Episode 236: Under the Crabapple Tree | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530014/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530014/</guid><description>Podcast Description On September 16, 1922, a reverend and a choir singer were found dead under a tree. Between their bodies was a stack of love letters. When police began investigating the murders, tabloid reporters did too, and rumors about the case began to spread quickly. We have some exciting news – Criminal is going back on tour! We can’t wait to see you. Presale tickets are available at 12 pm ET today for Criminal Plus members.</description></item><item><title>Episode 235: The Newsroom | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff German was a reporter for over 40 years in Las Vegas. He spent his life covering the mafia, corruption, and murder. In 2022, he was found killed outside his home. His colleagues at the Las Vegas Review-Journal tried to figure out why he had died—and if his death had anything to do with his work. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice.</description></item><item><title>Episode 234: The Séances | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530016/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1916, two British soldiers were held captive in a remote prisoner-of-war camp. People said the camp was escape-proof. One day, one of the soldiers received a postcard from his aunt in England, suggesting they try experimenting with a Ouija board. When reports of ghosts started circulating around the camp, the two soldiers had an idea. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice.</description></item><item><title>Episode 233: Iceland Noir | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530017/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Iceland is one of the most peaceful countries in the world, but people there love to read about crime. Even the Prime Minister of Iceland has written a crime novel. We stopped by her office to ask why. Prime Minister Katrín Jakobsdóttir and Ragnar Jónasson&amp;rsquo;s book is Reykjavík. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.</description></item><item><title>The Other Phoebe Judge | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530018/</guid><description>Podcast Description A preview of what we’re making over on Criminal Plus! Hear me and Criminal co-creator Lauren Spohrer taking your questions, telling stories, and talking with other producers and special guests. We’re having a lot of fun making these bonus episodes. When you sign up for Criminal Plus, you’ll also get ad-free listening on all of the shows we make, access to an exclusive merch store, and more. If you sign up as a Premium member, you’ll also get to attend virtual live events—like our first one, coming up on Thursday, August 24.</description></item><item><title>Episode 232: Wolf 10 | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530019/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530019/</guid><description>Podcast Description In April of 1995, wildlife biologists flew small airplanes over Yellowstone National Park, looking for two missing wolves. “They’re just gone. And that’s implausible because wolves don’t just disappear.” Thomas McNamee’s book is The Killing of Wolf Number Ten. This episode was originally released in 2020. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.</description></item><item><title>Episode 231: The Nurse | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530020/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530020/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Amy Loughren started working as a nurse at Somerset Medical Center, she did everything she could to hide the fact that she had a heart condition. And then, another nurse named Charles Cullen discovered Amy’s secret. He told her that he would keep it, but she didn’t know that he was keeping his own secret too. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice.</description></item><item><title>Episode 230: The Perfectionists | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530021/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530021/</guid><description>Podcast Description A story about religion, sex, an assassination, and silverware. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.com/CriminalShow. Sign up for Criminal Plus to get behind-the-scenes bonus episodes of Criminal, ad-free listening of all of our shows, members-only merch, and more. Learn more and sign up here. Listen back through our archives at youtube.</description></item><item><title>Episode 229: A Glamour and a Mystery | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530022/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the summer of 1917, 16-year-old Elsie Wright took a photograph of her 9-year-old cousin, Frances Griffiths. It was the first photograph she’d ever taken — and it became the source of a mystery that lasted for most of the 20th century. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.com/CriminalShow. Sign up for Criminal Plus to get behind-the-scenes bonus episodes of Criminal, ad-free listening of all of our shows, and members-only merch.</description></item><item><title>Episode 228: Roll of the Dice | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530023/</guid><description>Podcast Description The UNABOM investigation was one of the longest manhunts in American history - it lasted for 18 years starting in 1978. Before the FBI started investigating Ted Kaczynski, they looked into a number of suspects, including a group of friends who loved playing Dungeons &amp;amp; Dragons. This episode is part of the podcast Project Unabom. Listen to the entire series on Apple Podcasts: https://apple.co/Project_Unabom. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Episode 227: The Bodies in the Bog | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530024/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530024/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the summer of 1984, a local newspaper reporter outside of Manchester, England, got a tip from the police. A foot had been found in a nearby bog. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.com/CriminalShow. Sign up for Criminal Plus to get behind-the-scenes bonus episodes of Criminal, ad-free listening of all of our shows, and members-only merch.</description></item><item><title>Episode 226: The Prison Newspaper | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530025/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530025/</guid><description>Podcast Description A little over sixty years ago, there were 250 prison newspapers being published on a regular basis. Today, there are 26. We visit Nash Correctional Institution in North Carolina to meet Phillip Vance Smith, II, the editor of The Nash News. Learn more about the American Prison Newspapers digitization project here. Listen to more of Fresh Air’s interview with Angolite editor Wilbert Rideau here. Special thanks to Terry Gross and Fresh Air, which is produced at NPR member station WHYY and distributed by NPR.</description></item><item><title>Episode 225: The Impersonator | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530026/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mary Jones could sing just like Aretha Franklin. One night, a James Brown impersonator saw her perform at a Motown tribute show - and thought he could take her on tour and trick audiences into believing she was the real Queen of Soul. Jeff Maysh tells the story. Learn more in Jeff Maysh’s piece for Smithsonian Magazine, “The Counterfeit Queen of Soul.” Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Episode 224: Al Capone, Eliot Ness, and Cleveland’s Torso Murderer | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530027/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530027/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1934, a man collecting driftwood along the Lake Erie shore found a human torso on the beach. No one could figure out what had happened. Over the next several years, more bodies were discovered. Eventually, a coroner assembled something he called the “Torso Clinic” to work on the case. It was made up of about 30 people – doctors, professors, police officers, and a young Prohibition agent named Eliot Ness.</description></item><item><title>Episode 223: The Unknown Woman | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530028/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530028/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a toymaker and a doctor teamed up to make the world’s first CPR doll, they decided to make the doll’s face look like one specific woman – a woman who they thought had drowned. People call her l’Inconnue de la Seine, or the Unknown Woman of the Seine. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.</description></item><item><title>Episode 222: The Paramedics | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530029/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530029/</guid><description>Podcast Description As recently as 1965, if you had a medical emergency, the people who showed up at your door would be volunteer firefighters, police officers, or undertakers with a hearse. Today, the story of how a group of Black men from Pittsburgh changed that. Kevin Hazzard’s book is American Sirens: The Incredible Story of the Black Men Who Became America&amp;rsquo;s First Paramedics. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice.</description></item><item><title>Episode 221: Lavender Scare | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530030/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Helen James grew up in a military family — her great-great-grandfather fought in the Civil War, her father in WWI, and her uncles in WWII. So when she enlisted in 1952, she felt like she belonged. Shortly after, she realized she was being watched. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.</description></item><item><title>Episode 220: Shipwrecked | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530031/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530031/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s an old sailors’ saying about the ocean at the southernmost part of the world — “below 40 degrees latitude, there is no law; below 50 degrees, there is no God.” David Grann brings us the story of what happened when five British warships set off on a secret mission to steal a ship filled with treasure. They’d have to sail around the very bottom of South America — at 56 degrees south.</description></item><item><title>Episode 219: A Mysterious Bank | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530032/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530032/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the late 1870s, a woman named Sarah Howe started a bank just for single women called the Ladies’ Deposit Company. She asked new customers to tell their friends about the bank rather than advertising in newspapers, and she promised she could almost double their money. Today, the story of the woman running a Ponzi scheme before Charles Ponzi was even born. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Episode 218: "Did we get it right?" | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530033/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530033/</guid><description>Podcast Description “What we ask jurors to do is to just absorb all this trauma and just to keep on absorbing it and not process it with anyone. Just hold it in and hold it in and hold it in.” A look at what happens during and after a trial – and how some courts are trying to help jurors. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice.</description></item><item><title>Episode 217: The Juror | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530034/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530034/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2008, Sven Berger was chosen to serve on the jury for a murder trial. He says the sentence that he and his fellow jurors handed down “felt like a mistake right away.” Sven talked about what happened next on the podcast Heavyweight, and today, we’re sharing that episode with you. Maurice Chammah originally reported on Sven’s story for The Marshall Project. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Episode 216: The Magdalene Laundries | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530035/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530035/</guid><description>Podcast Description When she was 14 years old, Elizabeth Coppin was sent to a place called Peacock Lane in Cork, Ireland. It was a laundry business run by a Catholic order of nuns. Elizabeth noticed bars on its windows. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.com/CriminalShow. Listen back through our archives at youtube.</description></item><item><title>Episode 215: The Somerton Man | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530036/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530036/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1948, two horse jockeys were riding on a beach in Australia when they came across a man lying in the sand. There was a partially smoked cigarette resting on his jacket. He was well dressed, with a striped tie and polished shoes. And he was dead. No one could figure out who he was. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice.</description></item><item><title>Episode 214: Palace of Justice – A Conversation with Benjamin Ferencz | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530037/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530037/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Benjamin Ferencz was 27 years old, he prosecuted his very first trial. It&amp;rsquo;s been called the largest murder trial in history, with more than one million victims. There were 22 defendants, each of them high-ranking members of Nazi Germany’s death squad. Benjamin Ferencz died last Friday, April 7, at the age of 103. He was the last surviving prosecutor from the Nuremberg trials. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re sharing our conversation from 2018.</description></item><item><title>Episode 213: The Most Wonderful Terrible Person | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530038/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530038/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Debra Miller woke up on October 8th, 1964, she was expecting to see a black Volkswagen in her family’s driveway. Instead, she saw a police car. “And I knew my father was dead.” Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.com/CriminalShow. Listen back through our archives at youtube.com/criminalpodcast. We also make This is Love and Phoebe Reads a Mystery.</description></item><item><title>Episode 212: The Fasting Cure | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530039/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530039/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1911, two sisters traveled to Seattle to meet a &amp;ldquo;doctor&amp;rdquo; named Linda Hazzard. The sisters didn’t seem very sick, but when they arrived, Dr. Hazzard told them they didn’t have a moment to lose – they needed to begin her treatment right away. A few months later, one of the sisters wrote a letter to her old governess. “I am wonderfully better in fact,” she said, “getting stronger by leaps.</description></item><item><title>Episode 211: Crazy Eddie | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530040/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530040/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the 1980s, the discount electronics chain store Crazy Eddie was so famous, its commercials were parodied on &amp;ldquo;Saturday Night Live.&amp;rdquo; So when the family business began selling its company shares on Wall Street — making millions — nobody questioned its success. Gary Weiss’ book is Retail Gangster: The Insane, Real-Life Story of Crazy Eddie. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice.</description></item><item><title>Episode 210: Out of the Box | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530041/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530041/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1964, one of the best javelin throwers in Australia traveled to England to see if he could qualify for the Olympics. But, because of an injury, he didn’t make the team - and he couldn’t afford a plane ticket home. So he came up with an idea while working a cargo job at Heathrow Airport: “I saw them shipping animals. And I thought, well, if the dogs can survive it, I could.</description></item><item><title>Episode 209: An Impossible Crime, Part 2 | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530042/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530042/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode continues where Episode 208 leaves off. In 2001, Daniel Taylor wrote a letter from prison to a reporter at the Chicago Tribune named Steve Mills. Steve Mills spent months investigating before publishing a detailed examination of Daniel’s case as part of a series called “Cops and Confessions.” Daniel told us, “To have someone finally say that they believed me changed my whole life.” Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Episode 208: An Impossible Crime | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530043/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Daniel Taylor was 17 years old when he was arrested for a 1992 double homicide in Chicago. But Daniel had an alibi. He was in jail at the time of the murders. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.com/CriminalShow. Listen back through our archives at youtube.com/criminalpodcast. We also make This is Love and Phoebe Reads a Mystery.</description></item><item><title>Episode 207: Novak v. City of Parma | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530044/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530044/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2016, a man named Anthony Novak created a parody Facebook page of his local police department. &amp;ldquo;I just thought, &amp;lsquo;That would be funny.&amp;rsquo;&amp;rdquo; About a month later, he was arrested. Novak is now petitioning the Supreme Court, and The Onion submitted an amicus brief in support of his case. Their brief is written as a parody of an amicus brief. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice.</description></item><item><title>Episode 206: The Feather Lady | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530045/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530045/</guid><description>Podcast Description On October 4, 1960, Eastern Airlines Flight 375 took off from Boston’s Logan airport, and then, two minutes later, it crashed. 62 people died. Investigators couldn&amp;rsquo;t figure out what had happened, and they decided to ask a scientist working at the Smithsonian for help. Roxie Laybourne&amp;rsquo;s investigation helped launch a whole new field of science that changed aviation and forensics. Special thanks to the Smithsonian Institution Archives for letting us share audio of Roxie Laybourne.</description></item><item><title>Episode 205: Sunset Mesa | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530046/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Debbie Schum waited a long time to receive the cremated ashes of her friend, LoraLee Johnson. When she did, she felt relieved to finally take them home with her. But then, she got a call from the FBI. We first aired this episode in 2020. Earlier this month, Megan Hess and Shirley Koch were sentenced for their crimes. We&amp;rsquo;ve included updates about the case in this version of the episode.</description></item><item><title>Episode 204: They Came for the Judges | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530047/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530047/</guid><description>Podcast Description When the Taliban took control of Afghanistan in August of 2021, they unlocked the prisons and freed prisoners, some of whom sought revenge on the women judges who convicted them. We speak with some of the judges in today’s episode. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: apple.co/CriminalShow. Listen back through our archives at youtube.</description></item><item><title>Episode 203: Dog in the Bed, Cat in the Bag, Camel on the Golf Course | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530048/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stories of animals really going for it. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: Apple.co/CriminalShow. Listen back through our archives at youtube.com/criminalpodcast. We also make This is Love and Phoebe Reads a Mystery. Artwork by Julienne Alexander. Check out our online shop. Episode transcripts are posted on our website. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Episode 202: Across the Atlantic | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530049/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530049/</guid><description>Podcast Description In February of 1910, members of the Music Hall Ladies Guild in London received a strange letter from their treasurer – a singer who went by the name Belle Elmore. It said that she suddenly had to travel to the United States, and that she was resigning from her position. Several weeks later, at the Music Hall Ladies Guild fundraising ball, Belle&amp;rsquo;s husband arrived with a date. And she was wearing Belle&amp;rsquo;s brooch.</description></item><item><title>Episode 201: The Tylenol Murders | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530050/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530050/</guid><description>Podcast Description On September 29, 1982, Adam Janus suddenly collapsed in his home outside of Chicago. He died within hours. Later that same day, in the same house, his brother also collapsed — then his sister-in-law. All three of them had been healthy. Nobody could figure out what was going on. Stacy St. Clair and Christy Gutowski reported an investigative series looking back on the Tylenol murders for the Chicago Tribune.</description></item><item><title>Episode 200: We Interrupt This Program | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530051/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530051/</guid><description>Podcast Description On a Saturday night, in February 1949, the music programming on one of the most popular radio stations in Quito, Ecuador, was interrupted with an urgent news bulletin: strange objects in the sky that looked like large disks with bright lights were using a powerful ray to destroy a nearby city. And they were heading right for Quito. Thanks to Lisette Arévalo for sharing her tape and her reporting.</description></item><item><title>Episode 199: Ghostwatch | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530052/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530052/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Halloween night, in 1992, an unusual television special aired on the BBC. Nobody expected what happened next. “The technicians were looking up at the big screen in the lobby, saying to each other, ‘My God, what&amp;rsquo;s going on in Studio One?&amp;rsquo;” Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.com/CriminalShow. We also make This is Love and Phoebe Reads a Mystery.</description></item><item><title>Episode 198: The Hammersmith Ghost | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530053/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530053/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the winter of 1803, residents outside of London reported strange encounters with a ghost. Some said it looked like Napoleon Bonaparte, or a horse without a head. Others said the ghost breathed fire and smoke. By Christmas, there was a “full-scale phantom panic.” Shortly after the New Year, one man decided he’d stop the ghost once and for all. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice.</description></item><item><title>Episode 197: Mantrap | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530054/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ed and Bertha Briney’s unoccupied farmhouse was reportedly broken into 50 times over 10 years. They put up “No Trespassing” signs, repeatedly complained to sheriffs in two different counties, nailed doors shut, and boarded up windows - but nothing worked. So they decided to try something else. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.</description></item><item><title>Episode 196: Hungryland | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530055/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530055/</guid><description>Podcast Description In March of this year, a biologist working in a nature preserve in Florida saw an alligator swimming along a canal with something in its mouth. When she looked closer, she realized it was a human arm. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.com/CriminalShow. We also make This is Love and Phoebe Reads a Mystery.</description></item><item><title>Episode 195: The Procedure | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530056/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530056/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1967, a very unlikely group of individuals gathered to quietly break the law and help facilitate abortions. They established a phone number. When you called it, a recording of a woman&amp;rsquo;s voice would tell you what to do next. Who was behind this number? The Clergy Consultation Service, an underground network of ministers and rabbis who wanted to help people access safe abortions in a time before it was legal.</description></item><item><title>Episode 194: The Divorce Colony | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530057/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530057/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode picks up where Episode 193 left off. We suggest you listen to them in order. Blanche Molineux visited her husband while he was in prison for murder to keep up what she called the “ghastly pretense.” But eventually, she couldn’t keep it up anymore, and bought a train ticket to a place called &amp;ldquo;The Divorce Colony.&amp;rdquo; April White’s book is The Divorce Colony: How Women Revolutionized Marriage and Found Freedom on the American Frontier.</description></item><item><title>Episode 193: A Ring and a Bottle | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530058/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530058/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1895, Blanche Chesebrough moved into a small apartment in Gramercy Park, in New York City. She brought a portrait of her parents, a vase for flowers, and her piano. She later said, “music had been my one absorbing interest,” and that she wasn’t interested in getting married. But eventually, she agreed to anyway. When she returned home from her honeymoon, she learned her husband was suspected of murder.</description></item><item><title>Episode 192: The Devil’s Hole Pupfish | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530059/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530059/</guid><description>Podcast Description There is a cave in the middle of the Mojave Desert called Devil&amp;rsquo;s Hole. It&amp;rsquo;s home to a small iridescent blue fish, called the Devil&amp;rsquo;s Hole pupfish - and you can&amp;rsquo;t find them anywhere else in the world. There are fences, cameras, and motion sensors for security. In 2016, three men rammed the fences and broke in. We need your help. We are conducting a short audience survey to help plan for our future and hear from you.</description></item><item><title>Episode 191: The Sailor's Teeth | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530060/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530060/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1982, forensic dentists examined the teeth of thousands of sailors stationed on an aircraft carrier called the USS Carl Vinson in Newport News, Virginia. It’s been called “the largest dental dragnet likely in U.S. history.” Chris Fabricant’s book is Junk Science and the American Criminal Justice System. We need your help. We are conducting a short audience survey to help plan for our future and hear from you.</description></item><item><title>Episode 190: Day In, Day Out | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530061/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530061/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Laura Coates decided to become a prosecutor in Washington, D.C., she was told that the job would be “human misery.” She says she remembers thinking, “If there&amp;rsquo;s one person in the justice system who could do something about human misery, surely, it&amp;rsquo;s the powerful prosecutor.” After four years, she quit. Laura’s book is Just Pursuit: A Black Prosecutor’s Fight For Fairness. We need your help. We are conducting a short audience survey to help plan for our future and hear from you.</description></item><item><title>Episode 189: The Doctors | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530062/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530062/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2018, we talked with three of America’s most experienced trauma surgeons about what happens when someone is shot. We wanted to spend some time with that conversation again this week. Special thanks to Dr. Amy Goldberg, Dr. David Spain, and Dr. Ronald Stewart. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.</description></item><item><title>Episode 188: John &amp; Trooper | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530063/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530063/</guid><description>Podcast Description For 10 years, Detective John Reilly and his horse Trooper were the only mounted team assigned to Central Park. They rode the same route every day. John says Trooper didn’t like change. “If you changed the route, he got mad.” And then in 2019, they both retired at the same time.
Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.</description></item><item><title>Episode 187: 427 Emails | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530064/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pontiac Correctional Center is a maximum security prison in the small town of Pontiac, Illinois. It’s the oldest in the state - founded in 1871 - and has a reputation for being one of the most violent. There is a guard at Pontiac who some staff praise for being tough and having their backs. But other staff and people in the prison say she is known for abuse. In 2019, she was investigated by the Department of Corrections and State Police.</description></item><item><title>Episode 186: The Magpie | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530065/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530065/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Shigeru Yabu was 9 years old, he and his family were incarcerated at Heart Mountain Internment Camp, along with thousands of other Japanese and Japanese American families. One day, Shigeru discovered a baby magpie that had fallen out of its nest. He named her Maggie. “That bird walked up my arm all the way to my shoulder, and we looked at each other, eye to eye.” Shigeru Yabu’s book is Hello Maggie!</description></item><item><title>Episode 185: The Princess | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530066/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530066/</guid><description>Podcast Description One night in 1817, a woman appeared in the village of Almondsbury, in England. No one could figure out who she was. But everyone wanted to solve the mystery.
Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.com/CriminalShow. We also make This is Love and Phoebe Reads a Mystery. Artwork by Julienne Alexander.</description></item><item><title>Episode 184: Ransom | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530067/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Miles Hargrove was in his sophomore year of college when he got a phone call that his father had been kidnapped.
Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.com/CriminalShow. We also make This is Love and Phoebe Reads a Mystery.
Artwork by Julienne Alexander. Check out our online shop. Episode transcripts are posted on our website.</description></item><item><title>Episode 183: Breaking into the F.B.I. | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530068/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530068/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1971, a woman visited an F.B.I. office in Pennsylvania. She identified herself as a college student interested in learning about opportunities for women in the F.B.I. None of that was true. She was there “to see whether there were security alarms before we could decide if we could break in.”
Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.</description></item><item><title>Episode 182: The Midnight Slider | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530069/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530069/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2013, a small boat called The Midnight Slider was found floating empty in the waters off of Isle Madame in Nova Scotia. &amp;ldquo;Murder is not something that occurs in this neck of the woods very often,&amp;rdquo; says Jake Boudrot, editor of the The Reporter, &amp;ldquo;There&amp;rsquo;s always been a tradition of taking care of families, watching out, looking out for one another.&amp;rdquo; Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Episode 181: Pappy, Another Round | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530070/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530070/</guid><description>Podcast Description When it comes to Kentucky bourbon, Pappy Van Winkle is among the most exclusive. You can’t get it unless you’re exceptionally lucky, exceptionally wealthy, or willing to break the law. The Pappy frenzy has the police, bartenders, and even the Van Winkle family themselves wringing their hands. According to the Distilled Spirits Council of the United States, sales of the most expensive American whiskeys have basically doubled since 2016, when we first looked into Pappy Van Winkle.</description></item><item><title>Episode 180: The Boycott | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530071/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530071/</guid><description>Podcast Description 15 years after the Supreme Court ruled that school segregation was unconstitutional in Brown v. Board of Education, many schools across the South were still segregated. Some school districts actively blocked desegregation. North Carolina passed legislation authorizing tuition grants to white private schools, sometimes called &amp;ldquo;segregation academies.&amp;rdquo; Members of the KKK held rallies in North Carolina, describing desegregation as &amp;ldquo;anti-Christian&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;communistic.&amp;rdquo; When the Federal government pressured school boards to comply or lose their funding, many responded by shuttering Black schools and assigning Black students to formerly all-white schools.</description></item><item><title>Episode 179: A Splendid Newfoundland, Cursing Birds, and the Fashion Fox | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530072/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stories of animals really going for it. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.com/CriminalShow. We also make This is Love and Phoebe Reads a Mystery. Artwork by Julienne Alexander. Check out our online shop. Episode transcripts are posted on our website.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 178: "The experiment requires that you continue." | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530073/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Please continue. 2. The experiment requires that you continue. 3. It is absolutely essential that you continue. 4. You have no other choice, you must go on. Gina Perry&amp;rsquo;s book is Behind the Shock Machine: The Untold Story of the Notorious Milgram Psychology Experiments. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.</description></item><item><title>Episode 177: Palace of Justice | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530074/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530074/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Benjamin Ferencz was 27 years old, he prosecuted his very first trial. There were 22 defendants, each of them high-ranking members of Nazi Germany’s death squad. The entire world was watching. Today, we take a look at the Nuremberg trials and their role in defining international law after World War II. This episode originally aired in 2018—this version includes an update with Benjamin Ferencz, who celebrated his 101st birthday earlier this year.</description></item><item><title>Episode 176: The Red Flag | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530075/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530075/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2006, a man named William Ramsey went to the Mayo Clinic in Jacksonville, Florida for a life-saving liver transplant. It was a success, and so when his health started to decline after the procedure, doctors couldn&amp;rsquo;t figure out why. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.com/CriminalShow. We also make This is Love and Phoebe Reads a Mystery.</description></item><item><title>Episode 175: Ghost Racket Crusade | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530076/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530076/</guid><description>Podcast Description The story of two famous friends — Sir Arthur Conan Doyle and Harry Houdini — and the disagreement that ended their friendship: can we speak to the dead? Read Rose Mackenberg&amp;rsquo;s essays in Tony Wolf&amp;rsquo;s book, Houdini&amp;rsquo;s Girl Detective: The Real-Life Ghost-Busting Adventures of Rose Mackenberg. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.</description></item><item><title>Episode 174: The Loves | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530077/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530077/</guid><description>Podcast Description “There is something he hasn’t been telling me and I’m about to find out what it is.” Bobby and Cheryl Love’s book is The Redemption of Bobby Love: A Story of Faith, Family, and Justice. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.com/CriminalShow. We also make This is Love and Phoebe Reads a Mystery.</description></item><item><title>Episode 173: Family Money | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530078/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530078/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Beverley Schottenstein’s husband Alvin died, she and her children sold their stake in his family’s business, worth an estimated 90 million dollars. Family relationships got complicated. It was hard to know who to trust. And what happened next surprised everyone. Beverley told us, “I was floored.” Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.</description></item><item><title>Episode 172: Roselle and Michael | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530079/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael Hingson was on the 78th floor of the North Tower of the World Trade Center on September 11, 2001. He says the first indication that something was wrong was the sound of a muffled explosion. Then the building began to tilt, and he felt the floor drop like an elevator. But Michael Hingson didn’t panic because his guide dog, Roselle, was calm. Michael Hingson’s book is Thunder Dog.</description></item><item><title>Episode 171: Sealand | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530080/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today&amp;rsquo;s episode begins with rock &amp;amp; roll and ends with royalty. When bands like the Rolling Stones and the Beatles were becoming popular, they weren&amp;rsquo;t played much on the radio in England. The BBC controlled the airwaves at the time, and some listeners described its music offerings as &amp;ldquo;square.&amp;rdquo; So aspiring DJs packed up their record collections, got in boats, and sailed past the territorial limits of the UK, where they set up pirate radio stations in the sea—sometimes on abandoned WWII sea forts.</description></item><item><title>Episode 170: Ian Manuel | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530081/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530081/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;The phone rang and rang and a lady picked up on the other end and I still remember the operator saying, &amp;lsquo;You have a collect call from Ian for Debbie. Will you accept the charges?&amp;rsquo; And I remember Debbie saying, &amp;lsquo;Yes, I accept.&amp;rsquo; And I just remember blurting out, &amp;lsquo;Ms. Baigrie, I just called to wish you and your family a merry Christmas and to apologize for shooting you.</description></item><item><title>Episode 169: Masquerade | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530082/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530082/</guid><description>Podcast Description The story of a cryptic children’s book, a real-life treasure hunt, and its very mysterious winner: “He refused to be on camera. It’s just his voice. His wife even asks that they disguise his voice, but she asks too late. The interview is already happening. And she faints.” Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.</description></item><item><title>Episode 168: 48 Hours, Part 2 | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530083/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530083/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode picks up where Episode 167 left off. We suggest you listen to them in order. When Aaron Quinn called the Vallejo police to report that his girlfriend Denise Huskins had been kidnapped, and went into the station for questioning, a detective told Aaron that he didn&amp;rsquo;t believe him. When Denise was released after being held captive for about 48 hours, police didn&amp;rsquo;t believe her either. It soon became clear that the police viewed Denise and Aaron as suspects, not victims.</description></item><item><title>Episode 167: 48 Hours | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530084/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530084/</guid><description>Podcast Description “I think it was around 3:00 a.m., and that’s when I heard a strange man’s voice waking me from sleep.” This is part one of a two-part episode. Listen to part two in our next episode. Denise Huskins and Aaron Quinn’s book is Victim F. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.</description></item><item><title>Episode 166: On Fire | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530085/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530085/</guid><description>Podcast Description On November 12th, 2012, the Accomack County volunteer fire departments got a call. An abandoned house had suddenly gone up in flames. And then, just hours later, a second fire was reported. Then a third. Over the next few months, there would be a lot more fires—nearly 90 in all. It was all anyone could talk about in Accomack. Someone was burning down the entire county. Monica Hesse&amp;rsquo;s book is American Fire: Love, Arson, and Life in a Vanishing Land.</description></item><item><title>Episode 165: Unfit | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530086/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530086/</guid><description>Podcast Description In August 1934, Ann Cooper Hewitt was having lunch with her mother when she suddenly felt pain in her abdomen. When she went to the doctor, he told her she would have to have her appendix removed. He never examined her abdomen. She later told papers that when she woke up from surgery, she heard a nurse saying that Ann “didn’t suspect a thing.” Audrey Clare Farley&amp;rsquo;s book is The Unfit Heiress: The Tragic Life and Scandalous Sterilization of Ann Cooper Hewitt.</description></item><item><title>Episode 164: Sanctuary | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530087/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530087/</guid><description>Podcast Description After 32 years in the United States, José Chicas was told he had to leave. He bought a plane ticket to El Salvador, but then a local church offered another option. Special thanks to Jackie Metivier. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.com/CriminalShow. We also make This is Love and Phoebe Reads a Mystery.</description></item><item><title>Episode 163: The Ghoul of Grays Harbor | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530088/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530088/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Pacific Northwest was said to be terrorized by a serial killer in the early 20th century. Bodies were floating to the surface of the Chehalis and Wishkah Rivers. A local police chief told reporters that he believed that they were dealing with “the greatest murderer of the age.” But the real story was a lot more complex. It’s about myth-making and working conditions, The Sailors&amp;rsquo; Union of the Pacific, and a man named William Gohl (often called Billy Gohl) who angered the wealthiest and influential people in town: “They saw him as a thorn in their side and as a person who needed to be removed.</description></item><item><title>Episode 162: I Fought the Law | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530089/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530089/</guid><description>Podcast Description The song “I Fought the Law” by the Bobby Fuller Four reached number 9 on the Billboard Charts in the week of March 12, 1966. Just months later, Bobby Fuller was found dead. The mystery of what happened to him has been called “the rock and roll version of John F. Kennedy’s assassination.” We speak with Miriam Linna and Dalton Powell. We made a special playlist of music discussed in this episode.</description></item><item><title>Episode 161: Only in Hollywood | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530090/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530090/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Joan Borsten married actor Oleg Vidov, also known as “the Soviet Robert Redford,” he introduced her to beautiful Soviet animations created in Moscow’s Soyuzmultfilm studio, like Hedgehog in the Fog, by Yuri Norstein. Joan and Oleg eventually acquired the rights to distribute the films outside of the former Soviet Union. One day, Joan realized someone was undercutting their business, and she devised a very Hollywood solution. We talk with Joan Borsten, Andre Violentyev, and former FBI Special Agent and current private investigator, Jake Schmidt.</description></item><item><title>Episode 160: Hot Lotto | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530091/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530091/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2010, a $16.5 million Hot Lotto ticket was sold at a gas station in Des Moines, Iowa. At first, no one showed up to claim the prize. And then, a series of lawyers tried to claim the money on behalf of a client they would not name. Things got stranger, and eventually investigators uncovered what has been called the biggest lottery fraud in U.S. history. We speak with Iowa’s state Auditor, Rob Sand, and with Ed Stefan, who spent years working at the Multi State Lottery Association.</description></item><item><title>Episode 159: Spiritual Developments | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530092/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530092/</guid><description>Podcast Description One Sunday afternoon, a man named William Mumler decided to take a self portrait. He said he was alone in the photography studio, but as the photograph developed he saw something very strange—the image of someone else, sitting beside him. Mumler’s “spirit photograph” was championed by advocates of Spiritualism, who saw it as evidence that the living could communicate with the dead. Mumler began to host portrait sessions in his studio, for a hefty fee.</description></item><item><title>Episode 158: "If it ever happens, run." | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530093/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530093/</guid><description>Podcast Description “What I recall most is the way that she grabbed my wrist and, shaking a bit, she said over and over again, ‘If it happens, run. Don’t let that happen to you. Run. If it ever happens, run.’” It was years before Cynthia Brown understood what her great-grandmother, Athalia Howe, was talking about. Athalia Howe grew up in Wilmington, North Carolina in the late 1890s. At the time, Wilmington was called “the freest town in the country” for Black people, and by 1898, Black men had become integral in Wilmington’s government.</description></item><item><title>Episode 157: The Short Life of Qandeel Baloch | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530094/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Qandeel Baloch grew up in a conservative village in Pakistan called Shah Sadar Din, a place where it was shocking to see a woman swimming outdoors. She ran away from home, changed her name from Fouzia Azeem, auditioned for Pakistan Idol, and eventually became “Pakistan’s first social media star.” By 2015, she was reported to be one of the 10 most Googled people in Pakistan. As she became more famous, Qandeel Baloch also became more controversial.</description></item><item><title>Episode 156: Sister Helen | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530095/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530095/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1982, Sister Helen Prejean was invited to write a letter to a man on death row in Louisiana’s Angola State Prison named Elmo Patrick Sonnier. She told us, “I thought that all I was going to be doing was writing letters. And lo and behold, two years later, I am in that execution chamber.” She’s now 81, and has been present at the executions of six men. Sister Helen’s book, Dead Man Walking, is about her time as a spiritual advisor to Elmo Patrick Sonnier and Robert Lee Willie.</description></item><item><title>Bears on Ice | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530096/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530096/</guid><description>Podcast Description A day in the life of the town of Kalispell, Montana. Thanks very much for listening this year, and happy New Year. Read about other days in the Flathead Beacon&amp;rsquo;sPolice Blotter. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.com/CriminalShow. We also make This is Love and Phoebe Reads a Mystery. Artwork by Julienne Alexander.</description></item><item><title>Episode 155: Cannonball | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530097/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530097/</guid><description>Podcast Description With Covid-19 shutdowns, people have been taking advantage of quiet highways to drive as fast as they can from New York City to Redondo Beach, California. They’re trying to break records set in an unofficial and secretive race called the “Cannonball.” Car and Driver Magazine editor Brock Yates came up with the idea for the race, and described it as a “balls-out, shoot-the-moon, rumble.” He also wrote the screenplay for the 1981 movie based on the race, “Cannonball Run,” which starred Burt Reynolds, Farrah Fawcett, and Roger Moore.</description></item><item><title>Episode 154: The Night of the Party | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530098/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530098/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Nathan Myers and Clifford Williams were charged with the murder of Jeanette “Baldie” Williams in Jacksonville, Florida on May 2, 1976, neither of them were worried they would be convicted. They had dozens of witnesses that could confirm that they had been at a party when the shots were fired. But during their trial, not a single one of those witnesses was asked to testify. The prosecution’s entire case rested on the testimony of a woman named Nina Marshall, who&amp;rsquo;d been in bed with Jeannette Williams at the time of the shooting.</description></item><item><title>Episode 153: The Max Headroom Incident | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530099/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530099/</guid><description>Podcast Description One Sunday night in November 1987, something very odd happened in the middle of the WGN nine o’clock news in Chicago. Sportscaster Dan Roan had been talking about the Chicago Bears, when the screen suddenly went black. Then a person appeared, dancing back and forth in front of a moving striped background, and wearing a mask. The mask was the face of a fictional character from 1985 named Max Headroom, who was supposed to be the world’s first computer generated TV host.</description></item><item><title>Episode 152: The Clearwater Monster | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530100/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Early one morning in 1948, a phone call woke up the police chief in the small town of Clearwater, Florida. The caller said he’d seen something strange at the beach. Residents woke up that morning to find an odd set of footprints in the sand, and a rumor began circulating that Clearwater Beach had a sea monster. The rumor spread so wide, it caught the attention of a biologist in New York named Ivan Sanderson.</description></item><item><title>Episode 151: The Many Lives of Michael Malloy | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530101/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530101/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1932, a group of men in a speakeasy in Prohibition-era New York City hatched a plan — to take out life insurance on a loner named Michael Malloy, and make his death look like an accident. They thought it would be easy money. But Michael Malloy would become known as the man who just wouldn’t die. Simon Read’s book is On the House: The Bizarre Killing of Michael Malloy.</description></item><item><title>Episode 150: 76th and Yates | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530102/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530102/</guid><description>Podcast Description On May 8, 2013, a man named Timothy Jones was arrested in Chicago. He says it wasn’t until he got to the police station that he found out that he was being charged with murder. He didn’t even know someone had died. Earlier that day, a woman named Jacqueline Reynolds had been driving through the intersection of 76th and Yates Boulevard when she was hit and killed by a police car.</description></item><item><title>Episode 149: Dr. Parkman is Missing | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530103/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530103/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the mid-1800s, Harvard Medical School had a reputation for being a “den of body snatchers.” And then, in November 1849, the school’s most prominent supporter, Dr. George Parkman, went missing. He was last seen walking into the medical school building. Several days later, a janitor, named Ephraim Littlefield found something strange in the lab of faculty member Dr. John Webster. Paul Collins’ book is Blood &amp;amp; Ivy: The 1849 Murder That Scandalized Harvard.</description></item><item><title>Episode 148: Errol Morris | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530104/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Early in his career, Errol Morris read about a shocking series of alleged insurance crimes in a small town in Florida, which some referred to as “Nub City.” There were allegations that men and women were mutilating themselves &amp;ndash; removing hands and feet &amp;ndash; in order to exploit accidental dismemberment clauses in insurance policies, and collect money. It was very difficult to prove that these injuries were intentional and not accidental.</description></item><item><title>Episode 147: Kids on the Case | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530105/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530105/</guid><description>Podcast Description The summer after Jessica Maple finished 6th grade, she found out that her great-grandmother’s house had been burglarized. So, 12-year-old Jessica got out her notebook, looked for fingerprints, and decided she would conduct her own investigation. This week, four stories of kids who cracked the case. We speak with 10-year-old Griffin Steele, Griffin’s dad Shane Steele, his mother Carol Steele, and his brother, Jackson. Logan Hultman, age 10, and his mother Alyssa Hultman share a story about helping out.</description></item><item><title>Episode 146: Ten Doors | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530106/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tim Jenkin was a member of the ANC (African National Congress). The organization had been declared unlawful in South Africa, seen by the white minority as a threat to public order. In 1978, Tim Jenkin was charged under South Africa’s Terrorism Act for disseminating anti-apartheid material and sentenced to 12 years in prison. Just before he was convicted, someone gave him a book called Papillon, by Henri Charrière, which he said “was really a manual of escape.</description></item><item><title>Episode 145: How to Sell A Haunted House | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530107/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530107/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1989, Helen Ackley decided to sell her old Victorian house in Nyack, New York at 1 Laveta Place. It didn’t go as planned. There were stories of ghosts, and the house became the center of a case that’s referred to as “The Ghostbusters ruling.” The judicial opinion read: “as a matter of law, the house is haunted.” We speak to Mark Kavanagh, Cynthia Kavanagh, Richard Ellis, University of Chicago law professor Lior Strahilevitz, and Randall Bell, who specializes in real estate damage economics.</description></item><item><title>Episode 144: Looking Out | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530108/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530108/</guid><description>Podcast Description People incarcerated in California’s San Quentin State Prison aren’t allowed to have pets — but some people, like Ronell Draper, have found ways to work around that. Meet Ronell Draper, also known as “Rauch,” plus Ear Hustle’s Nigel Poor and Earlonne Woods join Phoebe to talk about the impact of Covid-19 at San Quentin. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice.</description></item><item><title>Episode 143: Knock and Announce | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530109/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530109/</guid><description>Podcast Description “I didn’t do what they said I did. And it was like, I don’t know how to disprove the police. I mean, it’s my word against theirs. I don’t really stand a chance.” In 2015, the 15th Circuit Drug Enforcement Unit in South Carolina gave a confidential informant $100 to buy marijuana from Julian Betton. And then they broke down his door. Officers David Belue, Chris Dennis, and Frank Waddell shot at Julian an estimated 29 times.</description></item><item><title>Episode 142: Robert Smalls | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530110/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530110/</guid><description>Podcast Description On May 13, 1862, in Charleston, South Carolina, a man named Robert Smalls took command of a Confederate ship called The Planter and liberated himself and his family from enslavement. As they passed the Confederate-held Fort Sumter, Robert Smalls was said to have saluted it with a whistle, and then added an extra one, “as a farewell to the confederacy.” Robert Smalls’ great-great-grandson, Michael Boulware Moore, tells the story.</description></item><item><title>Episode 141: It Looked Like Fire | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530111/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530111/</guid><description>Podcast Description On August 10th, 2014, one day after 18-year-old Michael Brown was shot and killed by Officer Darren Wilson in Ferguson, Missouri, Edward Crawford went to his first protest. “The people, you know, I guess they were out there to be heard,” Ed told us. We also speak with Robert Cohen of the St. Louis Post-Dispatch. We first released this episode in 2015—this version includes an update. This episode contains references to police brutality.</description></item><item><title>Episode 140: Cowboy Bob | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530112/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530112/</guid><description>Podcast Description In May 1991, a bank robber walked into a bank in Irving, Texas, and without speaking handed the teller a note that read, “This is a bank robbery. Give me your money. No marked bills or dye packs.” Witnesses reported that the robber was wearing a cowboy hat and a brown leather jacket. And then it happened again. And again. But when FBI agents finally got a lead, they discovered that robber wasn’t who they expected at all.</description></item><item><title>Episode 139: Learning How to Forgive | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530113/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530113/</guid><description>Podcast Description “I’ve been teaching law for almost 40 years. And I recently realized we don’t really teach people in law school about the tools of forgiveness that are built into the legal system.” Today, we’re talking with Harvard law professors Dehlia Umunna and Martha Minow about when and how the law should forgive. Martha Minow’s latest book is When Should Law Forgive. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice.</description></item><item><title>Episode 138: Starlight Tours | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530114/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530114/</guid><description>Podcast Description In January 2000, the bodies of two First Nations men were found frozen in a remote area of Saskatoon, Canada. It was a place where nobody walked, especially in the winter. And then, a man named Darrell Night came forward and said he had been dropped off by police on the outskirts of town, but he had made it back alive. We speak with former police officer Ernie Louttit and reporter Dan Zakreski about the deaths of Neil Stonechild, Lawrence Wegner, and Rodney Naistus, and “starlight tours” within the Saskatoon Police Service.</description></item><item><title>Episode 137: Wolf 10 | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530115/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530115/</guid><description>Podcast Description In April of 1995, wildlife biologists flew small airplanes over Yellowstone National Park, looking for two missing wolves. “They’re just gone. And that’s implausible because wolves don’t just disappear.” The missing wolves were two of 14 that had been brought down from Canada in an attempt to reestablish the wolf population in Yellowstone. Not everyone supported the Yellowstone Wolf Project—including a man named Chad McKittrick. We speak with Thomas McNamee and Joe Fontaine.</description></item><item><title>Looking for Wolves | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530116/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 18:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our other show, This is Love, is coming back on April 1. All new stories, about animals and the wild, and what happens when we take time to look around us.
Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Artwork by Julienne Alexander.
Check out our online shop. Criminal is a proud member of Radiotopia from PRX. Please review us on Apple Podcasts!</description></item><item><title>Phoebe Reads a Mystery | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530117/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 14:38:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Phoebe reads Agatha Christie’s first novel, The Mysterious Affair at Styles. For more, visit Phoebe Reads a Mystery on its own feed. Apple: https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/phoebe-reads-a-mystery/id1503921457 Spotify: https://open.spotify.com/show/4aqOirMxxorVMFcVRvDusi RSS: http://feeds.feedburner.com/PhoebeReadsAMystery
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 136: La Brea Dave | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530118/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sgt. David Mascarenas was the Dive Supervisor for the Los Angeles Police Department. He’s been diving his whole life, and prides himself on never refusing a dive, no matter how treacherous. At least until the summer of 2013, when a murder investigation led him into the unusually murky waters of the La Brea tar pits. We first spoke with Sgt. Mascarenas in 2015. This week, we’re adding to the story with information about the crime he couldn’t tell us before.</description></item><item><title>Episode 135: 527 Lime Street | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530119/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Just before midnight on October 15, 1990, police arrived at 527 Lime Street in Jacksonville, Florida to find the small wood-frame house on fire. A man named Gerald Lewis was standing in the front yard. He said there were people inside the house. What happened next was so unusual that it changed the way we think about arson. We speak with attorney Frank Ashton and fire investigator John Lentini about the Lime Street case and why it was so important.</description></item><item><title>Episode 134: Call Russ Ewing | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530120/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530120/</guid><description>Podcast Description “The police had surrounded the house. They had been there for quite a while. They didn’t want to try to rush the house because they thought he might kill one of the innocent people. But after waiting for a long time, I asked the police: ‘Let me see if I can talk to the guy.&amp;rsquo;” For decades, TV news reporter Russ Ewing stood beside more than 100 people—at their request—as they surrendered to the police.</description></item><item><title>Episode 133: Red Hair, Gold Car | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530121/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530121/</guid><description>Podcast Description One day Adam Braseel got a phone call from his mother. She said that a man in Grundy County, Tennessee had been murdered, and the police thought Adam had something to do with it. Adam was charged with and convicted of the murder of Malcolm Burrows and assault against Rebecca Hill and Kirk Braden, despite there being no physical evidence against him. And then, 8 years later, Judge Justin Angel ordered a new trial.</description></item><item><title>Episode 132: Herrin Massacre | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530122/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530122/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the spring of 1922, the United Mine Workers of America announced a national strike. And then, that summer in Herrin, Illinois, 23 people were murdered over two days. Men, women, and children came out of their houses to watch, and in some cases, to take part in the violence. Scott Doody’s book is Herrin Massacre. Special thanks to the Special Collections Research Center at Southern Illinois University, Carbondale, and Matt Gorzalski, and to John Griswold, who wrote Herrin: The Brief History of an Infamous American City.</description></item><item><title>Episode 131: Sunset Mesa | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530123/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Debbie Schum waited a long time to receive the cremated ashes of her friend, LoraLee Johnson, from Sunset Mesa Funeral Directors in Montrose, Colorado. When she did, she felt relieved to finally take them home with her. But then, she got a call from the FBI. It turned out that the owner of the funeral home, Megan Hess, and her parents Shirley and Alan Koch had been operating a body brokering business—without permission from anyone.</description></item><item><title>Episode 130: Who's There | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530124/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Crime Blotter: “The Learning Center on Hanson Street reports a man across the way stands at his window for hours watching the center, making parents nervous. Police ID the subject as a cardboard cutout of Arnold Schwarzenegger.” Today, we’re looking at mistakes and misunderstandings. Like when Nate Roman returned home one evening to find his Marlborough, Massachusetts home mysteriously clean, and when 82-year-old Willie Murphy dealt with a home intruder in her own way.</description></item><item><title>Phoebe, Judge Me | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530125/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530125/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are trying something different.
Have a question for Phoebe? You can call into our voicemail at (919) 697-8231.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 129: Panic Defense | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530126/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530126/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1995, two men filmed an episode of the daytime talk show, The Jenny Jones Show. A few days later, one of the men was dead. The shooter later claimed he’d committed the murder “in a panic that he was being falsely accused or identified as a gay person.” We speak with Cynthia Lee, Carsten Andresen, and Paul Howard about so-called “gay panic” and “trans panic” defenses, and we discuss the murders of Scott Amedure, Islan Nettles, Larry King, Ahmed Dabarran, and Matthew Shepard.</description></item><item><title>Episode 128: Deep Breath | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530127/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 15:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530127/</guid><description>Podcast Description World-class biathlete Kari Swenson was on an afternoon trail run in the mountains near Big Sky, Montana in July 1984 when two men blocked her path. They were Don and Dan Nichols, a father and son pair who later became known as the “mountain men.” This story was produced by 30 for 30 Podcasts from ESPN, and reported by Bonnie Ford. Find more at 30for30podcasts.com. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Episode 127: The Reverend | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530128/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530128/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1977, a man named Robert Burns went to a funeral and shot someone, in the head, in front of 300 people. He didn’t deny it, and his lawyer, Tom Radney, didn’t deny it. Burns told a police officer: “I had to do it. And if I had to do it over, I’d do it again.” The man he’d shot was Willie Maxwell, and everyone knew who Willie Maxwell was.</description></item><item><title>Episode 126: A New Kind of Life | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530129/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530129/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1930, a Cuban woman named Elena de Hoyos went to the hospital in Key West, Florida. She had a bad cough, and her family was afraid she had Tuberculosis. She met a German x-ray technician named Carl Von Cosel who claimed he could save her, using unusual methods he’d invented himself. But on October 25, 1931, Elena de Hoyos died. “Count Von Cosel,” as he called himself, wrote that a strange new kind of life began for him.</description></item><item><title>Episode 125: The Less People Know About Us | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530130/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530130/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPOILER WARNING: Please listen to Episode 51: Money Tree before you listen to this one. Three years ago, we spoke with Axton Betz-Hamilton about discovering that her identity had been stolen as a child. When she found out who had stolen it, everything changed. We spoke with Axton again a couple of weeks ago. She said that since our last conversation she’s been conducting an investigation, going back to the very beginning of her own life, and reconsidering every memory.</description></item><item><title>Episode 124: A Bucket, a Mop, and a Sledgehammer | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530131/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530131/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a crime occurs, or when someone dies, the police aren’t responsible for cleaning up. That’s not their job. The coroner takes the body, the police conduct their investigation, and then everyone leaves. But the blood, and the rubber gloves, and the uneaten food in the refrigerator are all left behind. Sandra Pankhurst didn’t like imagining that. So she decided to clean it up. She became a crime scene cleaner.</description></item><item><title>Episode 123: Mrs. Sherlock Holmes | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530132/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530132/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1917, 18-year-old Ruth Cruger disappeared. She’d last been seen getting her ice skates sharpened in the motorcycle shop of a man named Alfredo Cocchi. Newspapers reported that she probably ran off with a boyfriend, and New York police said that there were no clues to go on. But an investigator named Grace Quackenbos Humiston decided that she would do whatever it took to find her. She became known as “Mrs.</description></item><item><title>Episode 122: Professor Quaalude | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530133/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530133/</guid><description>Podcast Description John Buettner-Janusch was one of the first Americans to study lemurs. He held prestigious faculty positions at Yale, Duke and NYU, before surprising everyone with a series of increasingly bizarre crimes. Peter Kobel&amp;rsquo;s Book is The Strange Case of the Mad Professor. You can learn more about lemurs at The Duke Lemur Center, which Peter Klopfer and John Buettner-Janusch founded together.
﻿Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice.</description></item><item><title>Episode 121: Off Leash | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530134/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530134/</guid><description>Podcast Description “I never did anything wrong. I never had a speeding ticket. I think I just saved all my stuff up for just one thing.” This week, we speak with Toby Dorr – better known as the Dog Lady of Lansing Prison. She started the Safe Harbor Prison Dogs program in 2004, and that’s how she met John Maynard.
Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice.</description></item><item><title>Episode 120: The Tunnel | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530135/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530135/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the late 1800s, North Carolina was trying to build a railway system through the Western part of the state. In December of 1882, something went wrong. The Raleigh News and Observer called it “too horrible to chronicle without a shudder.” We speak with Gary Carden, George Frizell, and Al Fisher about the Cowee Tunnel disaster. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice.</description></item><item><title>Episode 119: He's Still Neutral | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530136/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan Stevenson has lived in Oakland’s Eastlake neighborhood for 40 years. He says crime has been an issue for as long as he can remember, but he isn’t one to call the police. He’s a pretty “live and let live” kind of guy. Or he was. Before he finally got fed up and took matters into his own hands. We update one of our favorite episodes about “the Buddha of Oakland” with news and additional interviews, including a chat with Kurt Kohlstedt from 99% Invisible about other creative community interventions, including parklets and Guerrilla gardening.</description></item><item><title>Episode 118: Stowaway | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530137/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530137/</guid><description>Podcast Description One day in 1969, Paulette Cooper decided to see what she could get away with. Learn more about Paulette Cooper on her website. Here’s her 1969 Cosmopolitan piece about stowing away onboard the SS Leonardo da Vinci. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.com/CriminalShow. We also make This is Love and Phoebe Reads a Mystery.</description></item><item><title>Episode 117: The Lake | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530138/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530138/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amanda Hamm and her boyfriend Maurice LaGrone drove to Clinton Lake one night in 2003. The next day, DeWitt County Sheriff Roger Massey told a local newspaper, “We don’t want to blow this up into something that it’s not. But on the other side, we’ve got three children who are dead. None of us know exactly what happened.” If you’d like to learn more about the case, Edith Brady Lunny has written a book, along with Steve Vogel, called The Unforgiven.</description></item><item><title>Episode 116: Jessica and the Bunny Ranch | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530139/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530139/</guid><description>Podcast Description In our last episode we spoke Cecilia Gentili, a trans Latina who worked for many years as an undocumented sex worker. Today, we get two more views of sex work in America. We speak with a high-end escort in New York City, and take a trip to one of the only legal brothels in the country – the Moonlite Bunny Ranch, where we speak with Alice Little. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Episode 115: Cecilia | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530140/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530140/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Cecilia Gentili was growing up in Argentina, she felt so different from everyone around her that she thought she might be from another planet. “Some of us find our community with our own family and some of us don’t.” Today, Cecilia runs a policy reform organization called Trans Equity. She’s active in efforts to decriminalize sex work in New York, and to repeal SESTA-FOSTA.
Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Episode 114: Philip and Becky | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530141/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530141/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Philip Benight met Becky Golden, they made a promise to stick together, no matter how bad things got. Read Ann Neumann&amp;rsquo;s reporting in Harper&amp;rsquo;s: https://harpers.org/archive/2019/02/going-to-extremes-elderly-assisted-suicide-caregivers/. Her book is The Good Death: An Exploration of Dying in America. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.com/CriminalShow. We also make This is Love and Phoebe Reads a Mystery.</description></item><item><title>Episode 113: Hostage | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530142/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530142/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the summer of 1973, Clark Olofsson and Jan-Erik Olsson robbed the Kreditbanken in Stockholm’s Norrmalmstorg town square. They held four people hostage for six days. Swedish psychiatrist and criminologist Nils Bejerot coined the term “Stockholm Syndrome” to describe the response of the hostages. Bank robber Clark Olofsson told us, “It was fun.” Special thanks to Terence Mickey of the podcast Memory Motel, for allowing us to share audio from his interview with Kristin Enmark.</description></item><item><title>Episode 112: The Mail | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530143/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530143/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode contains adult content. Please use discretion. When Sarah Garone was 13 years old, she received something very strange in the mail. She didn&amp;rsquo;t know who it was from, or why they would have sent it. And then it happened again. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.com/CriminalShow. We also make This is Love and Phoebe Reads a Mystery.</description></item><item><title>Episode 111: Silvon Simmons | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530144/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530144/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2016, Silvon Simmons was shot in the back by police officer Joseph Ferrigno. The Rochester Police Department said Silvon fired first, and charged him with attempted aggravated murder of a police officer. “My first instinct, to be honest, was they shot this guy and now there’s a coverup.” - Liz Riley, Special Assistant Public Defender, Monroe County Public Defender’s Office.
Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice.</description></item><item><title>Episode 110: Baby Snatcher | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530145/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Georgia Tann of Memphis, Tennessee bragged that she had a rigorous selection process that matched the perfect child with the perfect home. Barbara Raymond&amp;rsquo;s book is The Baby Thief.
Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.com/CriminalShow. We also make This is Love and Phoebe Reads a Mystery. Artwork by Julienne Alexander.</description></item><item><title>Episode 109: Homewrecker | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530146/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530146/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s one thing to get into an argument with a stranger on Facebook. It&amp;rsquo;s another thing to try to ruin that stranger&amp;rsquo;s life. In 2015, Re/Max realtor Monika Glennon discovered how far a stranger would go, when she found herself on a website called “She’s a Homewrecker.”
Special thanks to Kashmir Hill, at Gizmodo. https://gizmodo.com/when-a-stranger-decides-to-destroy-your-life-1827546385
For a transcript of this episode, send an email to transcripts@thisiscriminal.com with the episode name and number.</description></item><item><title>Episode 108: The Numbers | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530147/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530147/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Fannie Davis and her family moved to Detroit in the mid-1950s, they hadn&amp;rsquo;t prepared themselves for how hard it would be. They had trouble finding steady work. So, Fannie found a way to take care of her family. She started small, but built a robust and lucrative operation… a business that a lot of people knew about but no one talked about.
Bridgett Davis&amp;rsquo; book is The World According to Fannie Davis: My Mother&amp;rsquo;s Life in the Detroit Numbers.</description></item><item><title>Episode 107: The Widow and the Winchester | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530148/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530148/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Sarah Winchester&amp;rsquo;s husband died, she inherited millions from the family business: the manufacture of the famous Winchester Rifle. A medium reportedly told Sarah that she would be haunted by the victims of that rifle unless she used her fortune to build a house, and never stop building. That&amp;rsquo;s exactly what she did.
Pamela Haag’s book is The Gunning of America: Business and the Making of American Gun Culture.</description></item><item><title>Episode 106: Linda | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530149/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530149/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a suburb outside of Salt Lake City, a 69-year-old woman named Linda Gillman hired a man named Christian Olsen to do some repairs on her condo. After months of working together, Linda Gillman asked for Christian’s help with a different sort of project.
For a transcript of this episode, send an email to transcripts@thisiscriminal.com with the episode name and number. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice.</description></item><item><title>Episode 105: Protection | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530150/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530150/</guid><description>Podcast Description John &amp;ldquo;Sonny&amp;rdquo; Franzese was once described as &amp;ldquo;largely responsible for the glamorization of the Mafia over the past century.” He&amp;rsquo;d been active in the Colombo crime family since the 1960s. And then, when he was 93, he was given an 8-year sentence. The evidence that helped convict him came from the last person he expected to wear a wire.
For a transcript of this episode, send an email to transcripts@thisiscriminal.</description></item><item><title>Episode 104: Witness | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530151/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530151/</guid><description>Podcast Description We speak to a Gerald Shur who has given thousands of people new names, told them where they would live, and warned them they could never go back home. Today, we take a look into the founding of the Witness Protection Program.
For more, check out Gerald Shur&amp;rsquo;s book, WITSEC.
For a transcript of this episode, send an email to transcripts@thisiscriminal.com with the episode name and number. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode: The Bark | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530152/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530152/</guid><description>Podcast Description A story about Steve Hutton, a police constable in England, who decided to do things a little differently.
For a transcript of this episode, send an email to transcripts@thisiscriminal.com with the episode name and number. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Artwork by Julienne Alexander.
Check out our online shop. Criminal is a proud member of Radiotopia from PRX. Please review us on Apple Podcasts!</description></item><item><title>Episode 103: Get Out of My House | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530153/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530153/</guid><description>Podcast Description On a hot summer day in 1978, a group of friends started renovating an old house in a neighborhood in Atlanta called Little Five Points. The home belonged to Carmela Aliffi and her then-husband, Bear. Carmela and her friends were steaming wallpaper off of the walls when two strangers just walked in. One of them had a gun. Thanks to listener Jenna Alstad for writing in with her mother’s story.</description></item><item><title>This is Love: How to Live Forever | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530154/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our second podcast, This is Love, is back. We’re sharing this first episode with Criminal listeners - we hope you like it. If you want to hear more, subscribe to This is Love in Apple Podcasts or wherever you listen. Learn more at www.thisislovepodcast.com
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 102: Ride-Along | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530155/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530155/</guid><description>Podcast Description We spend the day in a police car in Austin, Texas.
For a transcript of this episode, send an email to transcripts@thisiscriminal.com with the episode name and number. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Artwork by Julienne Alexander.
Check out our online shop. Criminal is a proud member of Radiotopia from PRX. Please review us on Apple Podcasts! It’s an important way to help new listeners discover the show: iTunes.</description></item><item><title>Episode 101: The Fox | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530156/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530156/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode picks up where Episode 100 left off. We suggest you listen to them in order.
When Martin McNally met another plane hijacker in prison, they started coming up with a plan to escape&amp;hellip;using the very thing that got them there in the first place.
For a transcript of this episode, send an email to transcripts@thisiscriminal.com with the episode name and number. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Episode 100: Ten Thousand Feet in the Air | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530157/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530157/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the afternoon of June 23rd, 1972, Martin McNally walked into the St. Louis airport with a wig, a sawed-off rifle, and a plan.
For a transcript of this episode, send an email to transcripts@thisiscriminal.com with the episode name and number. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Artwork by Julienne Alexander.
Check out our online shop. Criminal is a proud member of Radiotopia from PRX.</description></item><item><title>I'm Phoebe Judge | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530158/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530158/</guid><description>Podcast Description Thanks for helping us celebrate 100 episodes!
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 99: Racehorse Haynes | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530159/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530159/</guid><description>Podcast Description There is nothing Richard &amp;ldquo;Racehorse&amp;rdquo; Haynes of Houston, Texas wouldn&amp;rsquo;t do to win a case. He’s widely considered to be one of the most exceptional criminal defense attorneys America has ever seen. He was notorious for pulling stunts in the courtroom. We speak with his son, Slade Haynes, and attorneys Charla Aldous and Chris Tritico about how Racehorse Haynes changed how they approach a jury.
Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Episode 98: The Doctors | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530160/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530160/</guid><description>Podcast Description Three of America&amp;rsquo;s most experienced trauma surgeons speak with us about what happens when someone is shot. This is an unfiltered look at the damage that gunshot wounds inflict upon the body. Special thanks to Dr. Amy Goldberg, Dr. David Spain, and Dr. Ronald Stewart.
Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.</description></item><item><title>Episode 97: Palace of Justice | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530161/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530161/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Benjamin Ferencz was 27 years old, he prosecuted his very first trial. There were 22 defendants, each of them high-ranking members of Nazi Germany&amp;rsquo;s death squad. The entire world was watching. Today, we take a look at the Nuremberg trials and their role in defining international law after World War II. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.</description></item><item><title>Episode 96: On the Run | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530162/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530162/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Tyler Wetherall was a kid, her mother and father packed up the family car and drove through the night. They were on the run from the FBI. And by the time she was 9, Tyler had learned how to communicate in codes, adapt to new countries, and to never reveal who or where her father was. Tyler Wetherall wrote about her time on the run in her book, No Way Home.</description></item><item><title>Episode 95: The Job | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530163/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Not long into his job as prison superintendent, Frank Thompson was asked to write the manual on lethal injection for the state of Oregon. Capital punishment had not been implemented in more than 30 years, and no one knew how to do it. Frank had to travel around the country learning how other states do it, and he asked his staff to practice. They simulated every step, including seating witnesses in the gallery, interacting with the press, and strapping each other to the gurney.</description></item><item><title>Episode 94: The Chase | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530164/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530164/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mark Roberts has attended almost every major sporting event in the world. And he&amp;rsquo;s been escorted off the field almost every time. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.com/CriminalShow. We also make This is Love and Phoebe Reads a Mystery. Artwork by Julienne Alexander. Check out our online shop. Episode transcripts are posted on our website.</description></item><item><title>Episode 93: Lavender Scare | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530165/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Helen James grew up in a military family — her great-great-grandfather fought in the Civil War, her father in WWI, and her uncles in WWII. So when she enlisted in 1952, she felt like she belonged. Shortly after, she realized she was being watched. Today we talk to one of the members of the U.S. Air Force impacted by a campaign to remove LGBTQI+ employees of the U.S. government in the 1950s.</description></item><item><title>Episode 92: Dementia Americana | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530166/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530166/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode picks up where Episode 91 left off. We suggest you listen to them in order. The early 20th century&amp;rsquo;s biggest murder trial, and a particular brand of &amp;ldquo;madness.&amp;rdquo; Visit thisiscriminal.com to see rare photographs from Harry Thaw&amp;rsquo;s trial. Cameras were not allowed in the courtroom, but Boston Globe photographer E.E. Bond snuck in a special camera, hidden in his vest and operated with a watch chain. Thanks to our friends at the Boston Public Library for allowing us to share them.</description></item><item><title>Episode 91: The "It" Girl | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530167/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530167/</guid><description>Podcast Description The story behind the face of New York&amp;rsquo;s Gilded Age. For more information, check out Paula Uruburu&amp;rsquo;s book, American Eve. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.com/CriminalShow. We also make This is Love and Phoebe Reads a Mystery. Artwork by Julienne Alexander. Check out our online shop. Episode transcripts are posted on our website.</description></item><item><title>Episode 90: Sharks | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530168/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530168/</guid><description>Podcast Description The U.S. Navy attempted to develop a shark attack repellant after many sailors were attacked during WWII. The first step was the formation of a &amp;ldquo;Shark Research Panel,&amp;rdquo; which led to what we have today: the International Shark Attack File. When someone is attacked by a shark, anywhere in the world, the investigation closely resembles police work. &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re not reinventing the wheel. There&amp;rsquo;s been no shortage of trial and error that went into police investigations and what we do follows,&amp;rdquo; says George Burgess, the world&amp;rsquo;s foremost shark attack investigator.</description></item><item><title>Episode 89: Shadowing Sheila | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530169/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530169/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPOILER WARNING: Please listen to our first episode about Sheila, Episode 88: Cold Case, before you listen to this one. This episode contains descriptions of violence and may not be suitable for everyone. Sheila Wysocki became a private investigator to try to help solve the murder of her college roommate, Angela Samota. She wasn&amp;rsquo;t planning on taking any other cases, but then the letters started coming. This week, we shadow Sheila and her colleagues as she investigates the unsolved murder of Lauren Agee.</description></item><item><title>Episode 88: Cold Case | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530170/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530170/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1984, Sheila Wysocki found herself helping the police investigate the murder of her college roommate, Angela Samota. Detectives asked her to help gather information, and even sent her out to dinner with the main suspect, a man named Russell Buchanan. But the case remained unsolved. 20 years later, Sheila Wysocki decided to investigate it herself. This episode contains descriptions of sexual assault and may not be suitable for everyone.</description></item><item><title>Episode 87: Casper, Wyoming | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530171/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530171/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Dovala has lived in Casper, Wyoming since he was 19. He’s worked all kinds of cases, first as a detective and later as sheriff, but a 1973 murder stays with him. This episode contains descriptions of sexual assault and may not be suitable for everyone. For more information, check out Ron Franscell&amp;rsquo;s book, The Darkest Night. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice.</description></item><item><title>Episode 86: Willie Bosket | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530172/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Before he was 10 years old, Willie Bosket had skipped school, started fires, picked pockets, and stolen a car. A psychiatrist at Bellevue called him the &amp;ldquo;saddest little boy she’d ever seen.” By the time he was 16 years old, he was known all over New York City as the “Baby-Faced Butcher.&amp;rdquo; His crimes led to the passing of the Juvenile Offender Act of 1978 and changed how juvenile offenders are punished all over the country.</description></item><item><title>Episode 85: The Manual | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530173/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530173/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1993, Mildred and Trevor Horn, along with their live-in nurse Janice, were found murdered in their Montgomery County home. A Maryland police spokesperson described the homicide investigation as the most &amp;ldquo;exhaustive and labor intensive&amp;rdquo; in the department&amp;rsquo;s history. And then homicide investigators found a strange manual titled Hit Man: A Technical Manual for Independent Contractors published by Paladin Press, and the case became national news. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.</description></item><item><title>A New Show from the Makers of Criminal: Episode 1 | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530174/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530174/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1971, David Alexander went for a run in Central Park and started talking to a stranger. For our first episode of This Is Love, a story about what&amp;rsquo;s possible when we bet everything on each other. We speak with David, Jody, and Julienne Alexander. Listen to other episodes of This is Love at https://thisislovepodcast.com/. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t already, please follow the show and review us on iTunes! https://apple.</description></item><item><title>Episode 84: Masterpiece | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530175/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530175/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the 1950s poodles were all the rage — one tabloid even reported that when a girl “makes the big time she traditionally acquires 3 things — minks, gems, and a poodle.” But one poodle in particular put the breed on the map. His name was Masterpiece&amp;hellip;and police in 13 states knew exactly what he looked like. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice.</description></item><item><title>This Is Love | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530176/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530176/</guid><description>Podcast Description Some spiders eat their young, and some eat their parents … love is never simple. From the makers of the award-winning podcast Criminal, This is Love investigates life’s most persistent mystery. Stories of sacrifice, obsession, and the ways in which we bet everything on one another. Listen to other episodes of This is Love at https://thisislovepodcast.com/. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t already, please follow the show and review us on iTunes!</description></item><item><title>Episode 83: The Mothers | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530177/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530177/</guid><description>Podcast Description There is a group in Durham, NC called &amp;ldquo;Parents of Murdered Children.&amp;rdquo; This week, we meet three of its members. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.com/CriminalShow. We also make This is Love and Phoebe Reads a Mystery. Artwork by Julienne Alexander. Check out our online shop. Episode transcripts are posted on our website.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode: Like a Page from a Book | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530178/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 19:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530178/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1892, a gruesome murder took place in a small fishing village in Argentina. The police had a suspect who would not confess. What happened next would change the way murders were investigated around the world. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.com/CriminalShow. We also make This is Love and Phoebe Reads a Mystery.</description></item><item><title>Episode 82: The Choir | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530179/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530179/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a child, Lawrence Lessig was a gifted singer. His church choir director encouraged him to attend a choir camp at a prestigious boarding school in New Jersey. He was so talented that the school invited him to stay and join their official choir. He sang at Carnegie Hall and toured the world. But it was what happened behind the scenes that would change his life forever. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Episode 81: Unexpected Guests | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530180/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Three mysteries we can’t stop thinking about. The first is about an impossible photo taken at a bed &amp;amp; breakfast in Etna, California. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.com/CriminalShow. We also make This is Love and Phoebe Reads a Mystery. Artwork by Julienne Alexander. Check out our online shop. Episode transcripts are posted on our website.</description></item><item><title>Episode 80: Photo, Hair, Fingerprint | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530181/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530181/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1988, a man in Hickory, North Carolina named Willie Grimes was sentenced to life in prison for raping and kidnapping a 69-year-old woman named Carrie Lee Elliot. He was convicted with evidence experts would later call “junk science.” It took him 24 years to convince someone to look at the evidence again. Special thanks to Chris Mumma of the North Carolina Actual Innocence Center. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Episode 79: Secrets and Séances | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530182/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530182/</guid><description>Podcast Description Helen Duncan was a famous medium who travelled around Britain in the 1940s performing séances. She claimed to speak to the dead, and even produce physical manifestations of their spirits. But when Helen Duncan seemed to know wartime secrets about the whereabouts of military ships, like the sunken HMS Barham, she caught the attention of MI5 and notable psychic investigator Harry Price. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Episode 78: The Botanist | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530183/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530183/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1993, Gerald Boggs of Steamboat Springs, Colorado was found dead in his home. He&amp;rsquo;d been burned with a stun gun, hit with a shovel, and shot several times. The victim&amp;rsquo;s wife, Jill Coit, was the primary suspect, but she had an alibi for the estimated time of death: she was camping with her boyfriend Michael Backus. Investigators were at a loss, and turned to two very unlikely people for help.</description></item><item><title>Episode 77: The Escape | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530184/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530184/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1962, brothers John and Clarence Anglin, along with fellow incarcerated person Frank Morris, managed to escape the one prison in America that was supposed to be inescapable: Alcatraz. Alcatraz is surrounded by icy waters, so the men would’ve needed a raft in order to escape the island. When no evidence of the raft or the three men was found, the FBI concluded that the men had drowned and closed their case.</description></item><item><title>Episode 76: The Big Lick | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530185/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530185/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Tennessee Walking Horse has a natural gait that&amp;rsquo;s famously smooth. And, if trained in a certain way, it can perform a walk that&amp;rsquo;s even more spectacular, called the Big Lick. But, there&amp;rsquo;s a secret behind how, exactly, these horses are trained to do the crowd-pleasing step they&amp;rsquo;re celebrated for; it’s called “soring” and it’s been outlawed since the 1970’s. Still, some horse trainers still use the practice today in order to compete in the Big Lick.</description></item><item><title>Episode 75: The Gatekeeper | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530186/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530186/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;I keep saying &amp;lsquo;where&amp;rsquo;s the body? Kill someone,&amp;rsquo;&amp;rdquo; Marilyn Stasio told us. She reads at least 200 crime novels a year to determine which are worthy of her prestigious &amp;ldquo;Crime Column&amp;rdquo; in the New York Times Book Review. We talk with her about crime as entertainment - and why people are so addicted to the genre that she can&amp;rsquo;t stay away from: &amp;ldquo;My fingers just itch when I see something that&amp;rsquo;s says &amp;lsquo;murder.</description></item><item><title>Episode 74: Catastrophe | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530187/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530187/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1993, more than 1,000 levees broke along the Mississippi River, flooding thousands of acres. Most of these cases were accidents due to the river rising well above its usual levels. But in West Quincy, Missouri, there was another culprit, James Scott. His crime? Knowingly causing a catastrophe by breaking the levee. But his motive was not what prosecutors expected. Thanks to Noam Osmand for the story. For more information, check out Adam Pitluk&amp;rsquo;s book, Damned to Eternity.</description></item><item><title>Episode 73: Carry A. Nation | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530188/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530188/</guid><description>Podcast Description At the turn of the century, Carry Nation was “America’s foremost lady hellraiser” and &amp;ldquo;the apostle of reform violence.” A radical member of the temperance movement, Carrie Nation was known for attacking saloons, bars, and pubs with a hatchet engraved with name. In her own words, she was &amp;ldquo;a bulldog running along at the feet of Jesus, barking at what He doesn&amp;rsquo;t like.&amp;rdquo; We liked her hatchet pins so much, we thought we’d try to make some of our own.</description></item><item><title>Episode 72: Bears, Birds, and Bones | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530189/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530189/</guid><description>Podcast Description As long as 2,500 years ago, Native Americans placed the bones of their dead in giant mounds of earth in the shape of animals. The Effigy Mounds National Monument in Iowa was created to protect one set of these - and the bones inside. But in 2011, a new superintendent, Jim Nepstad, discovered that the remains of 41 Native Americans had disappeared. In this episode, we use the term &amp;ldquo;Native American&amp;rdquo; because the story refers to legislation that uses that term.</description></item><item><title>Episode 71: A Bump in the Night | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530190/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530190/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amber Dawn was 20 when she moved into a one-bedroom apartment in Enumclaw, Washington. On her very first night, she began to notice strange sounds. And they didn&amp;rsquo;t stop. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.com/CriminalShow. We also make This is Love and Phoebe Reads a Mystery. Artwork by Julienne Alexander.</description></item><item><title>Episode 70: The Procedure | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530191/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530191/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1967, a very unlikely group of individuals gathered to help women quietly break the law and obtain an abortion. The first step was to call a phone number. A recording of a woman&amp;rsquo;s voice would tell you what to do next. Who was behind this number? The Clergy Consultation Service, an underground network of ministers and rabbis who wanted to help women access safe abortions. Today, they call themselves the Religious Consultation for Reproductive Choice.</description></item><item><title>Episode 69: Becoming Chief Brown | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530192/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530192/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shortly after David Brown was sworn in as the Dallas Chief of Police, his son shot and killed a police officer. Just before he retired as chief, 5 Dallas officers were shot and killed in what was said to be the deadliest attack for police officers since September 11th, 2001. Today on the show, we ask David Brown how he’s changed after 33 years of policing. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Episode 68: All the Time in the World | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530193/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530193/</guid><description>Podcast Description The “body farm” at Texas State University is a place almost no one is allowed to see, because it’s one of very few places in the world that deliberately puts out human bodies to decompose in nature. Forensic Anthropologists observe decomposition in order to help police officers discern when and how someone may have died. We asked if we could visit, and they agreed. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Episode 67: Milk Carton Kids | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530194/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530194/</guid><description>Podcast Description On a Sunday morning in 1982, in Des Moines, Iowa, Johnny Gosch left his house to begin his usual paper route. A short time later, his parents were awakened by a phone call – it was a neighbor — their paper hadn&amp;rsquo;t come. His would be the first face of a missing child ever printed on a milk carton. This story comes to us from reporter Annie Brown and our friends at 99% Invisible.</description></item><item><title>Episode 66: Bully | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530195/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530195/</guid><description>Podcast Description Skidmore, Missouri is a very small town. In the &amp;rsquo;70s, there was only one bar, one grocery store, and one bully. Ken McElroy was so ruthless and intimidating that even police officers looked the other way. He terrorized the town for decades, until they finally fought back. We spoke with Harry MacLean, author of In Broad Daylight. Special thanks to Chelsea Korynta. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Episode 65: The Kingfish | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530196/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530196/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1928, Huey P. Long became the youngest Governor in Louisiana’s history. He bragged that he bought lawmakers like “sacks of potatoes, shuffled ‘em like a deck of cards.” By the time he was 39 years old, he’d made his way to the U.S. Senate. And just a couple of weeks after his 42nd birthday, he was assassinated in the Capitol Building in Baton Rouge, Louisiana. Allegedly, a doctor named Carl Weiss shot him.</description></item><item><title>Episode 64: 420 | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530197/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 20:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530197/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Colorado Department of Transportation says the 420 mile markers on the state&amp;rsquo;s highways were stolen so often, they had to replace them with 419.99 mile markers. Many people know that &amp;ldquo;420&amp;rdquo; represents marijuana - hence the popularity of the mile markers - but very few know why. It&amp;rsquo;s not a police code, it&amp;rsquo;s not the number of chemical compounds in cannabis, and it&amp;rsquo;s certainly not Bob Marley&amp;rsquo;s birthday.</description></item><item><title>Episode 63: Rochester, 1991 | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530198/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530198/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kim Dadou says she wishes she had a nickel for every person who has asked why she didn&amp;rsquo;t leave her abusive boyfriend Darnell Sanders. The two dated for four years and Darnell Sanders was routinely violent. But in the middle of the night on December 17th, 1991, Kim Dadou’s entire life changed. This episode contains descriptions of physical violence against women. It may not be suitable for everyone. Please use discretion.</description></item><item><title>Episode 62: Wildin | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530199/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530199/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2014, 16-year-old Wildin Acosta left Olancho, Honduras and traveled toward the U.S. border. When he arrived, he turned himself in to border patrol agents. He was one of 68,541 unaccompanied minors who crossed the border into the U.S. that year. We spoke to Wildin Acosta shortly after Donald Trump’s inauguration, and after he had spent months in a detention center. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice.</description></item><item><title>Episode 61: Vanish | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530200/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530200/</guid><description>Podcast Description People have faked death to escape criminal convictions, debts, and their spouses. In 2007, a man named Amir Vehabovic faked his death just to see who showed up at the funeral (answer: only his mom). John Darwin faked his own death in a canoeing accident in the UK. And the ex-boyfriend of Olivia Newton John, Patrick Mcdermott, is rumored to have faked his death. It&amp;rsquo;s an appealing soap-opera fantasy, but actually disappearing requires an incredible amount of planning.</description></item><item><title>Episode 60: Finding Sarah and Philip | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530201/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530201/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2005, Teri Knight drove 650 miles on midwestern roads through Ohio, Indiana, Iowa and Illinois, pleading with the public to help her do what law enforcement and the FBI had not been able to: find the remains of her children Sarah and Philip Gehring. An Ohio woman named Stephanie Dietrich read about Teri Knight&amp;rsquo;s search in her local paper, and decided she would try to help. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Episode 59: In Plain Sight | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530202/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530202/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1849, abolitionist and attorney Wendell Phillips wrote: &amp;ldquo;We should look in vain through the most trying times of our revolutionary history for an incident of courage and noble daring to equal that of the escape of William and Ellen Craft; and future historians and poets would tell this story as one of the most thrilling in the nation&amp;rsquo;s annals, and millions would read it, with admiration of the hero and heroine of the story.</description></item><item><title>Episode 58: Walnut Grove | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530203/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530203/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2010, Michael McIntosh&amp;rsquo;s son was incarcerated at the Walnut Grove Youth Correctional Facility in the small town of Walnut Grove, Mississippi. One Sunday, Michael McIntosh went to visit his son and was turned away because, he was told, prison officials &amp;ldquo;did not know&amp;rdquo; where his son was. He spent the next six weeks searching for his son, only to find him in the hospital with severe injuries. And Michael McIntosh&amp;rsquo;s son wasn&amp;rsquo;t the only one who had been hurt at the facility.</description></item><item><title>Episode 57: Everyday Genius | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530204/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530204/</guid><description>Podcast Description To close out 2016, we&amp;rsquo;re bringing you two lighter stories of people exhibiting everyday genius under. . . unusual circumstances. Comedian Dave Holmes&amp;rsquo; story begins with an upsetting phone call from the IRS. Then we meet a Baton Rouge attorney with a story of wild resourcefulness at Louisiana State Penitentiary, also known as Angola. A word of caution, this episode contains language that may not be suitable for everyone.</description></item><item><title>Episode 56: Don't Let Me See You In The Whirl | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530205/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530205/</guid><description>Podcast Description Since 1938, a weekly African-American owned newspaper called The Evening Whirl has covered crime in St. Louis with a style all its own, using alliteration and rhyme, and often omitting the usual crime-reporting words like &amp;ldquo;accused&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;alleged.&amp;rdquo; The paper has been widely criticized for its casual approach to fact-checking and sensational writing style. But the paper&amp;rsquo;s owner, Anthony Sanders, who has been helping out with it since he was 18 years old, doesn&amp;rsquo;t have any plans to change it.</description></item><item><title>Episode 55: The Shell Game | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530206/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530206/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Magic Castle in Hollywood has been a private club for magicians since 1963, and its walls are lined with portraits of magicians past and present. Among them is a portrait of one of the earliest American organized crime bosses and conmen, Jefferson Randolph &amp;ldquo;Soapy&amp;rdquo; Smith. And though it may seem strange that this &amp;ldquo;mecca of magic&amp;rdquo; honors a criminal, Soapy&amp;rsquo;s legacy reveals just how blurry the line is between a delightful trick and a dirty one.</description></item><item><title>Episode 54: Melinda and Clarence | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530207/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530207/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPOILER WARNING: Please listen to Episode 53: Melinda and Judy before you listen to this one. Melinda Dawson found out on the same day in 1998 that her adoptive mother had been killed and that her own husband Clarence Elkins was being charged with the murder. He was convicted in 1999 and given two life sentences. Left alone with her two sons, no money, and no experience, Melinda set out to try and prove that he was innocent.</description></item><item><title>Episode 53: Melinda and Judy | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530208/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530208/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Melinda Dawson was seven years old, she learned that she was adopted under suspicious circumstances. As she got older and had children of her own, she tried to learn something about her biological parents. And when she went to the county courthouse and asked to see a copy of her birth certificate, she discovered that she was an unwitting participant in a traumatic history of a small town in Georgia where Dr.</description></item><item><title>Episode 52: The Checklist | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530209/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530209/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPOILER WARNING: Please listen to Episode 51: Money Tree before you listen to this one. While working on our last episode, we became curious about the nature of psychopathy &amp;ndash; how it is defined, and what to do if someone close to you meets the criteria of the Hare psychopathy test. We spoke with Dr. Ronald Schouten, author of Almost a Psychopath, and Jon Ronson, author of The Psychopath Test.</description></item><item><title>Episode 51: Money Tree | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530210/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530210/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Axton Betz-Hamilton was 11 years old, her parents&amp;rsquo; identities were stolen. At that time, in the early 90s, consumer protection services for identity theft victims were basically non-existent. So the family dealt with the consequences as best they could. But when Axton Betz-Hamilton got to college, she realized that her identity had been stolen, too. In fact, her credit score was in the lowest 2%. As she was working to restore her credit, she inadvertently discovered who had stolen the family&amp;rsquo;s identity: a woman named Pam Elliot.</description></item><item><title>Episode 50: This is Criminal | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530211/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2016 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530211/</guid><description>Podcast Description To celebrate Criminal&amp;rsquo;s 50th episode, we check in with some of our most memorable guests including Fran Schindler from Episode 17: &amp;ldquo;Final Exit,&amp;rdquo; Dan Stevenson from Episode 15: &amp;ldquo;He&amp;rsquo;s Neutral,&amp;rdquo; Corporal Scott Foster from Episode 29: &amp;ldquo;Officer Talon,&amp;rdquo; and Marian Tolan from Episode 18: &amp;ldquo;695-BGK.&amp;rdquo; Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.</description></item><item><title>Episode 49: The Editor | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530212/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530212/</guid><description>Podcast Description In November of 1988, Robin Woods was sentenced to sixteen years in the notoriously harsh Maryland Correctional Institution. In prison, Robin Woods found himself using a dictionary to work his way through a book for the first time in his life. It was a Mario Puzo novel. While many people become educated during their incarceration, Robin Woods became such a voracious and careful reader he was able to locate a factual error in Merriam Webster&amp;rsquo;s Collegiate Encyclopedia.</description></item><item><title>Episode 48: Eight Years | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530213/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2016 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530213/</guid><description>Podcast Description 2008 was an exciting time to be a Harry Potter fan. The final book, Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows, had been released. Movies were on the way. And author Melissa Anelli was at the center of it all, running a popular fan site called The Leaky Caldron and working on a book of her own, Harry, a History. Just as things couldn’t get better, Melissa Anelli received her first death threat.</description></item><item><title>Episode 47: Brownie Lady | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530214/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2016 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530214/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shortly after Meridy Volz moved from Milwaukee to San Francisco, she received a phone call from a friend asking her to take over a small bakery business. Meridy agreed to run the bakery, but she only wanted to sell one thing: pot brownies. Her brownies were a massive success, and soon she was making enough money to support three families. Meridy tells her story alongside her daughter, Alia Volz, who describes what it&amp;rsquo;s like when San Francisco&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;original brownie lady&amp;rdquo; is your mom.</description></item><item><title>Episode 46: Tiger | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530215/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530215/</guid><description>Podcast Description There are more tigers in captivity in America than wild tigers in the entire world. The exact number of captive tigers in this country isn&amp;rsquo;t known, because many of them live in people&amp;rsquo;s backyards or unaccredited zoos, and the legality of their ownership varies widely by state and even by circumstance. We travelled to Louisiana to see a 550-pound Siberian-Bengal tiger who lives at a truck stop. The owner, Michael Sandlin, has fought very hard to persuade Louisiana lawmakers he&amp;rsquo;s not a criminal.</description></item><item><title>Episode 45: Just Mercy | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530216/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530216/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a law student, Bryan Stevenson was sent to a maximum security prison to meet a man on death row. The man told Stevenson he&amp;rsquo;d never met an African-American lawyer, and the two of them talked for hours. It was a day that changed Stevenson&amp;rsquo;s life. He&amp;rsquo;s spent the last 30 years working to get people off of death row, but has also spent the final hours with men he could not save from execution.</description></item><item><title>Episode 44: One Eyed Joe | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530217/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530217/</guid><description>Podcast Description Not only was John Frankford a famous horse thief, he was also a notoriously good escape artist. People thought no jail was strong enough to keep him, but then in 1895 he was sentenced to Philadelphia&amp;rsquo;s Eastern State Penitentiary. At Eastern State, Frankford became the victim of a strange practice: the prison doctor, Dr. John Bacon, dissected his body and removed his brain. The Frankford case would just be one of many others in the region and would illuminate an underground cadaver network supplying medical schools across the state of Pennsylvania.</description></item><item><title>Episode 43: 39 Shots | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530218/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530218/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1979, a group of labor organizers protested outside a Ku Klux Klan screening of the 1915 white supremacist film, The Birth of a Nation. Nelson Johnson and Signe Waller-Foxworth remember shouting at armed Klansmen and burning a confederate flag, until eventually police forced the KKK inside and the standoff ended without violence. The labor organizers felt they&amp;rsquo;d won a small victory, and planned a much bigger anti-Klan demonstration in Greensboro, North Carolina.</description></item><item><title>Episode 42: The Finger | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530219/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530219/</guid><description>Podcast Description People have been giving each other &amp;ldquo;the finger&amp;rdquo; since Ancient Greece. The first documented use is said to be a photograph from 1886 in which the pitcher for the Boston Beaneaters extends his middle finger to the camera (ostensibly to the rival New York Giants). Even though it&amp;rsquo;s been around for so long, many still find the gesture offensive enough to try to bring criminal charges. Courts have ruled that &amp;ldquo;flipping the bird&amp;rdquo; is a form of speech protected by the First Amendment.</description></item><item><title>Episode 41: Open Case | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530220/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530220/</guid><description>Podcast Description Since 1965, there&amp;rsquo;s been an unsolved murder in Houston, Texas. The main suspect, Charles Rogers, managed to disappear and police were never able to find him. The case is still considered open. In 1997, a couple of forensic accountants named Hugh and Martha Gardenier decided to look into the murders, and were able to uncover evidence that the police missed. And now they think they&amp;rsquo;ve solved the mystery. They wrote a novel about their findings called The Ice Box Murders.</description></item><item><title>Episode 40: Pappy | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530221/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530221/</guid><description>Podcast Description When it comes to Kentucky bourbon, Pappy Van Winkle is among the most exclusive, according to food writer Brett Anderson. The bourbon is prized for its wheat base and special barrels for aging, handpicked by Julian Van Winkle III, the president of Old Rip Van Winkle Distillery. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter who you are or how much money you have &amp;ndash; you can&amp;rsquo;t get it unless you&amp;rsquo;re exceptionally lucky or willing to break the law.</description></item><item><title>Episode 39: Either/Or | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530222/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2016 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530222/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1983, three men were prepared to plead guilty to the violent sexual assault of Elizabeth Daniel in Anderson, South Carolina. Defense attorneys did not want their clients to go before a jury, so they arranged a plea deal. This left the sentencing in the hands of Judge C. Victor Pyle who gave the assailants a very controversial choice: undergo castration or serve 30 years in jail. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Episode 38: Jolly Jane | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530223/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530223/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane Toppan was born in Massachusetts in 1857. She attended the Cambridge Nursing School, and established a successful private nursing career in Boston. Said to be cheerful, funny and excellent with her patients, nothing about &amp;ldquo;Jolly Jane&amp;rdquo; suggested she could be &amp;ldquo;the most notorious woman poisoner of modern times” responsible for the death of at least 35 people. She would later be committed to the Taunton Insane Asylum. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Episode 37: Hastings | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530224/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530224/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2010, an eighth-grader brought a loaded gun to a middle school in Hastings, Minnesota. We speak with Jake Bullington and Emma Bolters, two students at the school, and Mark Zuzek, the principal, about the hours in lockdown. Read Jake Bullington&amp;rsquo;s essay, &amp;ldquo;Yeah, I&amp;rsquo;m Afraid of Guns.&amp;rdquo; Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.</description></item><item><title>Episode 36: Perfect Specimen | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530225/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530225/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 500-year-old Treaty Oak in Austin, Texas was once called &amp;ldquo;the most perfect specimen of a North American tree.&amp;rdquo; But in 1989, Austin&amp;rsquo;s city forester John Giedraitis realized that the Treaty Oak didn&amp;rsquo;t look so good, and began to wonder whether someone had intentionally tried to kill it. The Austin police were on the case, so when Paul Stedman Cullen was arrested for the criminal “mischief,” it was time to unearth what his motives for killing a tree could be.</description></item><item><title>Episode 35: Pen &amp; Paper | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530226/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2016 16:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530226/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a young woman in the 60s, Andy Austin talked her way into a job as a courtroom sketch artist in Chicago. She spent 43 years sketching everyone from disgraced governors to John Wayne Gacy, and says she only made someone look bad on purpose once. See Andy Austin&amp;rsquo;s sketches, including the one she made of Phoebe, on our website http://thisiscriminal.com/episode-35-pen-paper-1-22-2016/. Her book, Rule 53: Capturing Hippies, Spies, Politicians, and Murderers in an American Courtroom, is available here or here.</description></item><item><title>Episode 34: The Stay | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530227/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2016 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530227/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael Ross was the first person in Connecticut to be sentenced to death since 1960. He claimed that he wanted to die in order to atone for what he had done. One journalist spent twenty years trying to figure out whether or not his remorse was real. Learn more about Martha Elliot&amp;rsquo;s relationship with Michael Ross in her book, The Man in the Monster. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Episode 33: Deep Dive | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530228/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2015 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530228/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sgt. David Mascarenas is the Dive Supervisor for the Los Angeles Police Department. He&amp;rsquo;s been diving his whole life, and prides himself on never refusing a dive, no matter how treacherous. At least until the summer of 2013, when a murder investigation led him into the unusually murky waters of the La Brea tar pits. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice.</description></item><item><title>Episode 32: It Looked Like Fire | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530229/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2015 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530229/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ed Crawford had never been to a protest until he heard about the shooting of Michael Brown in Ferguson, Missouri. Robert Cohen, a staff photographer with the St. Louis Post Dispatch, ended up taking a photograph of Ed that would be seen around the world, and change both of their lives. To see the photos, visit http://thisiscriminal.com/episode-32-it-looked-like-fire-12-11-2015/. We released an update to this episode in June of 2020. Please find the updated story here: https://thisiscriminal.</description></item><item><title>Episode 31: American Dream | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530230/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530230/</guid><description>Podcast Description When we&amp;rsquo;re kids, we have ideas of what we want to be when we grow up &amp;ndash; movie star, doctor, astronaut. But what if we dream of being like Butch Cassidy, Jesse James, or John Dillinger? And what happens when you&amp;rsquo;re not a kid anymore but you&amp;rsquo;re still obsessed with becoming an outlaw? For Clay Tumey, this dream led him to commit a series of robberies in 2006. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Episode 30: The Agreement | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530231/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530231/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2005, Danny Egipciaco had the opportunity to participate in a robbery of a drug supplier&amp;rsquo;s stash house. He was told he&amp;rsquo;d take home between $100K-200K. In the end, the robbery never happened, so why has Danny spent the last ten years at Fort Dix Correctional Institution? Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.</description></item><item><title>Episode 29: Officer Talon | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530232/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2015 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530232/</guid><description>Podcast Description Corporal Scott Foster of the Hillsborough, NC Police Department worked closely with his K-9 partner, Talon, for many years. They located weapons and narcotics, tracked suspects through dark woods, and went home together after work. But when Talon was injured on the job and had to retire early, Corporal Foster was paired with a new dog and life got a lot more complicated. Watch Phoebe get attacked by a police dog: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Episode 28: P.D.I.D. | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530233/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2015 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530233/</guid><description>Podcast Description Patti Hammond Shaw is a transgender woman. She&amp;rsquo;s legally female on her birth certificate and driver&amp;rsquo;s license, and has been since 1993. But when she was arrested in 2009, male officers strip-searched her in front of male detainees, and held her overnight in a men&amp;rsquo;s cellblock. Patti Hammond Shaw hired a lawyer and fought back. Her case was instrumental in changing how the police process and detain transgender individuals in Washington, D.</description></item><item><title>Episode 27: No Place Like Home | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530234/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2015 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530234/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the early 90s, a wealthy magazine publisher was convicted of fraud and sentenced to 18 months in a minimum security prison in Louisiana. But white collar criminals weren&amp;rsquo;t the only people living there, and the other people inside had basically been forgotten about by the outside world, some of them for decades. Learn more about Neil White’s time at Carville in his memoir, In the Sanctuary of Outcasts.</description></item><item><title>Episode 26: Angie | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530235/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2015 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530235/</guid><description>Podcast Description In July of 2002, Philadelphia Homicide Detective Pat Mangold was called to the scene of a gruesome murder on the Schuylkill River. When he wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to determine the victim&amp;rsquo;s identity, he expected the case to remain unsolved. But then, out of the blue, a professional soccer player named Adam Bruckner inserted himself into the investigation, and became obsessed with solving the crime. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Episode 25: The Portrait | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530236/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2015 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530236/</guid><description>Podcast Description More than eighty years ago, a North Carolina family of nine posed for a Christmas portrait. Two weeks later, all but one of them had been shot dead. (See the portrait here.) Today, we bring you the story of the Lawson family of Stokes County. Thanks to Elephant Micah and Sarah Bryan for collaborating with us this month. Download Elephant Micah&amp;rsquo;s version of &amp;ldquo;Lawson Family&amp;rdquo; (along with their version of &amp;ldquo;Pearl Bryan&amp;rdquo;) on iTunes or Bandcamp.</description></item><item><title>Episode 24: Pearl Bryan | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530237/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530237/</guid><description>Podcast Description In February of 1896, a little boy discovered a woman&amp;rsquo;s headless body in a farmer&amp;rsquo;s field in Fort Thomas, Kentucky. No one knew who she was, or what had happened. Newspapers carried headlines like &amp;ldquo;Hunt for the Head&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Headless Horror.&amp;rdquo; Quickly, the crime scene became a tourist attraction and visitors traveled from all over to collect bloody souvenirs. The gruesome details were adapted into a popular song that&amp;rsquo;s been recorded dozens of times.</description></item><item><title>Episode 23: Triassic Park | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530238/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2015 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530238/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Petrified Forest National Park in Arizona has the largest collection of petrified wood in the world. The beautiful wood is more than 200 million years old, and visitors to the park often take a little piece home with them as a souvenir. But stealing the wood has serious consequences, both legal and, some say, supernatural. See photographs of the conscience letters and learn more about Ryan Thompson&amp;rsquo;s book here.</description></item><item><title>Episode 22: Ex Libris | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530239/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2015 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530239/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hundreds of thousands of dollars&amp;rsquo; worth of rare books have been disappearing across America since the late 90s, and haven&amp;rsquo;t resurfaced in the marketplace. They&amp;rsquo;ve just vanished, never to be seen again. But unlike most thieves, this thief is motivated by something more abstract and romantic than money, which makes him extremely difficult to catch. Today, we have the story of John Charles Gilkey. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Episode 21: Bloodlines | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530240/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2015 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530240/</guid><description>Podcast Description Julius Robinson had killed for revenge before, and so when his sister was brutally murdered in her sleep last year, he says he planned to &amp;ldquo;get&amp;rdquo; the killer. He felt like his family expected him to get revenge, because that&amp;rsquo;s what he&amp;rsquo;d always done, both in and out of prison. But when he learned that the killer was actually his 17-year-old nephew, he struggled against his family&amp;rsquo;s expectations and his own.</description></item><item><title>Episode 20: Gil From London | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530241/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530241/</guid><description>Podcast Description Karen Miller met a man named Gil Harper on Facebook. They started flirting. The flirtation grew more serious. Eventually, they planned to meet in real life. Gil would travel from London to meet Karen for her birthday. With his arrival just a few days away, Karen&amp;rsquo;s son scrambled to learn more about Gil&amp;rsquo;s identity. But trying to determine whether someone is who they say they are turned out to be a whole lot more confusing and dangerous than Chris imagined.</description></item><item><title>Episode 19: Mother's Little Helper | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530242/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2015 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530242/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sandie Alger is a 71-year-old woman with a very long rap sheet. She was in and out of prison throughout the 1960s, 70s, and 80s, and upped her game each time she got out. Prison, she says, is where you move &amp;ldquo;up the criminal ladder, just like the corporate ladder.&amp;rdquo; Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.</description></item><item><title>Episode 18: 695BGK | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530243/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530243/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode won a “Best Documentary” award at the Third Coast International Audio Festival. Police officer John Edwards was patrolling a quiet neighborhood in Bellaire, Texas when he saw an SUV driven by two young Black men, including Robbie Tolan. It was just before 2am on December 31, 2008. Edwards followed the SUV and ran the license plate number. When his computer indicated that the SUV was stolen, Edwards drew his gun and told the two men to get down on the ground.</description></item><item><title>Episode 17: Final Exit | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530244/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530244/</guid><description>Podcast Description No one disputes that it&amp;rsquo;s against the law to take another person&amp;rsquo;s life, but is it against the law to sit with someone and watch while they die by suicide? We meet an elderly woman named Fran Schindler who sneaks around the country as an &amp;ldquo;exit guide.&amp;rdquo; This is a live interview from Motorco Music Hall in Durham, North Carolina. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice.</description></item><item><title>Episode 16: Poster Boy | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530245/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2015 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530245/</guid><description>Podcast Description On July 17th, 1889, the residents of Clayton County, Iowa woke up to news of the worst crime in their history. A Civil War veteran John Elkins and his young wife Hattie had been murdered in their bed in a grisly attack. Their two children escaped to raise the alarm. But something was off. There were no suspects. There were no clues. To quote the local newspaper, the whole thing was “surrounded in a veil of mystery.</description></item><item><title>Episode 15: He's Neutral | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530246/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2015 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530246/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan Stevenson has lived in Oakland&amp;rsquo;s Eastlake neighborhood for 40 years. He says crime has been an issue for as long as he can remember, but he isn&amp;rsquo;t one to call the police on drug dealers or sex workers. He&amp;rsquo;s a pretty &amp;ldquo;live and let live&amp;rdquo; kind of guy. Or he was. Before he finally got fed up and took matters into his own hands. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Episode 14: The Fifth Suspect | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530247/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2015 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530247/</guid><description>Podcast Description In June 2014, authorities released information about a massive child pornography ring being conducted in North Carolina. Four suspects had already been arrested, and the police were asking the public for help finding a fifth suspect. But they didn&amp;rsquo;t need to look very hard &amp;ndash; the suspect, a man named Tommy Wall, was about to turn himself in, almost by accident. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice.</description></item><item><title>Episode 13: The Big Sleep | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530248/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2014 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530248/</guid><description>Podcast Description Raymond Chandler is often called the greatest American crime novelist, famous for murder mysteries like The Big Sleep and Farewell, My Lovely. He&amp;rsquo;s the subject of several biographies, and his correspondence and manuscripts are archived at Oxford. But something very, very important to Chandler had gotten lost. No one noticed until a pair of Chandler&amp;rsquo;s biggest fans, newlyweds in their seventies, Loren Latker and Annie Thiel, got on the case.</description></item><item><title>Episode 12: Break The Internet | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530249/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2014 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530249/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1999, most of America&amp;rsquo;s tech hysteria centered around Y2K. But at that same time, a teenager in Canada named Mike Calce was messing around in chat rooms, meeting hackers, and learning tricks. At 15, he decided to put his knowledge to the test. To push up against the Internet&amp;rsquo;s limits, and in some places, break them. In the end, he managed to pull off something no one had ever seen before.</description></item><item><title>Episode 11: I'm About To Save Your Life | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530250/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2014 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530250/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1977, a mild-mannered aeronautical engineer sideswiped a parked car in Compton, CA. When he stopped his car to survey the damage, a man named Leon Moore opened the driver-side door, shoved him over, and started driving. He said, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m about to save your life.&amp;rdquo; We talk to lawyer Stephanie Nally about a con that spanned decades. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice.</description></item><item><title>Episode 10: Dear Sheila | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530251/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2014 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530251/</guid><description>Podcast Description Working as a reporter for a TV station in New Hampshire, Kevin Flynn was covering the capture and arrest of a female serial killer named Sheila LaBarre. As he grew more and more obsessed with LaBarre’s story, Flynn decided to write her a letter. She wrote back. Their correspondence became flirtatious, and eventually he went to visit her in person. We talk with Kevin Flynn and Rebecca Lavoie. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Episode 9: That Crime Of The Month | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530252/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2014 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530252/</guid><description>Podcast Description What does it mean when a woman commits a crime and attributes her actions to PMS? We revisit the first use of the &amp;ldquo;PMS defense&amp;rdquo; in this country, back in 1981. What have we learned about the science of PMS since then? Last year, the American Psychiatric Association classified a form of PMS (Premenstrual dysphoric disorder, or PMDD) as a mental disorder in the DSM-V. How can the scientific community study severe premenstrual symptoms without perpetuating the utterly unscientific idea that menstruating women aren’t mentally competent or liable for crimes they commit?</description></item><item><title>Episode 8: Can't Rock This Boat | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530253/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 13:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530253/</guid><description>Podcast Description In March 1964, a 35-year-old African-American woman named Johnnie Mae Chappell was walking along the side of the road in Jacksonville, Florida. Four white men were driving around listening to the local race riots on the radio. They had a gun on the dashboard. As they passed Chappell, one of the men leaned out the car window and shot her to death. As the police investigated, evidence began to mysteriously disappear, making it impossible to punish the men who admitted to committing the crime.</description></item><item><title>Episode 7: J.R.R. Ziemba | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530254/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2014 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530254/</guid><description>Podcast Description Crime victims are often put under the same scrutiny as the accused. Not only for their version of events, but sometimes for how they look and talk, too. We meet a man whose trial hurt worse than his assault. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.com/CriminalShow. We also make This is Love and Phoebe Reads a Mystery.</description></item><item><title>Episode 6: We Lost Them | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530255/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530255/</guid><description>Podcast Description On April 13, 2014, former KKK member Frazier Glenn Cross pulled into a Jewish Community Center and ambushed William Corporon and his grandson Reat Griffin Underwood, killing both. He then killed another woman named Terri LaManno a short distance away. What does the family left behind do when they are thrust into a national spotlight? How do they figure out what to disclose and what should be private? Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Episode 5: Dropping Like Flies | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530256/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2014 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530256/</guid><description>Podcast Description Every year for the past few years, tens of thousand of flytraps have gone missing – from the wild, from gardens, from nurseries. And, really, nobody knows where they go. What’s cropped up in rural North Carolina is essentially a Venus Flytrap crime ring — with lackies, middle men, and a mysterious end buyer who’s perpetuating the market. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice.</description></item><item><title>Episode 4: Call Your Mom | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530257/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2014 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530257/</guid><description>Podcast Description There are plenty of things we don&amp;rsquo;t share with our mothers. Dark, sad things. Unless of course, you both speak the same dark language. Kathleen Vernon is a coroner in Albany County, Wyoming, the youngest ever, in fact. But she didn’t come to this preternatural curiosity just on her own; the business of death runs in the family. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice.</description></item><item><title>Episode 3: The Buck Stops Here | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530258/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530258/</guid><description>Podcast Description With the advent of the Inkjet printer, counterfeiting money became as simple as a trip to Staples. By the year 2000, there were 72 million of these homemade dollars in circulation. The real question is… who was behind them all? Today, we talk to a woman who “made” her own money. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice. Follow the show and review us on Apple Podcasts: iTunes.</description></item><item><title>Episode 2: Pants On Fire | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530259/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530259/</guid><description>Podcast Description For nearly a century we&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to read someone&amp;rsquo;s truthfulness by the way they act. Be it through machines, or our own intuition. The police have tried. The FBI has tried. The CIA has tried. But the fact is… most of their efforts just don&amp;rsquo;t work. Are we doomed to ignorance? Maybe not. We talked to forensic psychologist Andy Morgan about the difficult truth regarding the industry around lying.</description></item><item><title>Episode 1: Animal Instincts | Criminal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9911530260/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 05:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9911530260/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2001, Kathleen Peterson was found dead in a pool of her own blood. Her husband Michael Peterson was convicted of her murder. A curious neighbor, a lawyer named Larry Pollard, had a different theory&amp;hellip; one that brings new meaning to man vs. beast. Explore a theory you won’t find in the Netflix documentary The Staircase. Say hello on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram. Sign up for our occasional newsletter, The Accomplice.</description></item></channel></rss>