<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sex.Life on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/sex.life/</link><description>Recent content in Sex.Life on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 17:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/sex.life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The tell all Q&amp;A. You asked, we answered. | Sex.Life</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5724140001/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5724140001/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been a crazy journey, and we wanted to thank you all for coming along for the wild ride by opening up the mic to you. This episode you take control and ask all the questions, funny questions, serious questions and everything you wanted to know about the secret sex school. How do you become a somatic sexologist? What would happen if no one found you attractive at sex school and what exactly is soaking?</description></item><item><title>Day 9: P in the V | Sex.Life</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5724140002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5724140002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Content warning: R18, Language and Sexual Material May Offend.
And just like that Morgan’s wild time at sex school has come to an end. There’s been earth humping, energetic heart f*cking, genital gazing, group masturbation, and so much more. Before Morgan gives her final verdict on her sex school experience, Hayley reports back on her home play with her special whip.
Morgan finally reveals what happens on the outside with Long Schlong Silver and it seems only one pussy is allowed in the bedroom as an awkward encounter at an Air Bnb unfolds.</description></item><item><title>Day 8: Adult's Wonderland: Whipping, Threesomes, &amp; Wrestling | Sex.Life</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5724140003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5724140003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Content warning: R18, Language and Sexual Material May Offend.
It’s the final night in the temple and we hear there's only one thing Morgan won't do. But before Morgan delves into a night of pure indulgence and pleasure, Hayley reports back on her home play. Long Schlong Silver has made a decision and Morgan considers a new proposition for temple night. Hayley’s jaw is left hanging after hearing the thing that Morgan claims "</description></item><item><title>Day 7: Praying for a Prostate | Sex.Life</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5724140004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5724140004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Content warning: R18, Language and Sexual Material May Offend.
It's day seven and Morgan's time at sex school is quickly coming to an end. The future is uncertain with Long Schlong Silver but today he gives us an interesting clue. The exercise that first piqued Morgans interest in going to this school unfolds today. Hayley embraces her slut energy and reports back on an empowering moment on stage. Get yourself clean and trim your nails because the time has arrived for the infamous sacred spot massage and Morgan shares an intimate moment with unexpected consequences.</description></item><item><title>Day 6: The Best Blowjob Ever | Sex.Life</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5724140005/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5724140005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Content warning: R18, Language and Sexual Material May Offend.
When we left Morgan, she was in bed with Big Cock Jock after experiencing an energetic orgasm that lasted forever. Day six, and she’s still zinging from the night before. Hayley reports back about her home play with a surprising participant for the infamous heart f*ck exercise. Just when you thought it couldn’t get any wilder, under the full moon Morgan confronts her internalised slut shame and embraces a newfound confidence at temple night.</description></item><item><title>Day 5: Energetic heart f*cking and a spiritual awakening | Sex.Life</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5724140006/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5724140006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Content warning: R18, Language and Sexual Material May Offend.
Day five marks the halfway point for Morgan’s wild adventure at sex school. Is this the most intense day yet? The day starts with an exercise opening the heart space then being energetically heart f*cked. Hayley is excited to learn her home play is to try this exercise out. Temple night forces Morgan to confront her deepest fears which leads to a full body spiritual awakening that keeps her pussy activated for hours.</description></item><item><title>Day 4: A smorgasbord of c*ck, sensual showers, and a blood ritual | Sex.Life</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5724140007/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5724140007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Content warning: R18, Language and Sexual Material May Offend.
Day four delves into the masculine and feminine. Morgan is delighted with a smorgasbord of cocks and gets to find her own big dick energy. Things get steamy and very wet as the intimate details of a shower with Mr Whippy are revealed. The afternoon activities take a hilarious turn when Morgan takes part in a blood ritual, but she can't find the respect that is required for the exercise.</description></item><item><title>Day 3: The Field is Open | Sex.Life</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5724140008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5724140008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Content warning: R18, Language and Sexual Material May Offend.
It’s day three at sex school and things are about to get wilder. Morgan reveals a shocking detail about her mystery man that could impact the rest of her stay. Following an afternoon of awkard boundary exercises, temple night starts with a cryptic guideline, ‘the field is now open’. There are moans and groans, face sitting and crotchless panties.</description></item><item><title>Day 2: Let it Be Messy | Sex.Life</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5724140009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5724140009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Content warning: R18, Language and Sexual Material May Offend.
After introducing ZM’s Hayley Sproull to the secret world of sex school, somatic sexologist Morgan Penn shares the details of day two of her wild experience. The second day starts with a round of eye gazing, pillowing thumping and humping, and finishes with group masturbation. Hayley reports back about her first home play assignment and gets a buzz out of her next task.</description></item><item><title>Day 1: Welcome to Sex School | Sex.Life</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5724140010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5724140010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to Sex.Life! In this episode (R18), somatic sexologist, Morgan Penn, and ZM’s Hayley Sproull start a wild journey to reveal what goes on behind the locked gates of a secret sex school in rural New Zealand. Day one at sex school includes unorthodox exercises, making love to the earth, getting nude and an elephant in the room. Before delving into the juicy details, they chat about Hayley's experience of Morgan taking her through her first yoni mapping exercise.</description></item><item><title>Sex.Life Trailer Season 1 Trailer | Sex.Life</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5724140011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 20:54:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5724140011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sex.Life is a podcast that will take you on a wild journey to expose what goes on behind the locked gates of a secret sex school in rural New Zealand. Join somatic sexologist Morgan Penn as she puts her body on the line and shares the jaw dropping experience with comedian Hayley Sproull. Each episode is a new day at sex school which reveals unorthodox exercises and interactions which provides a springboard for a discussion about sex and embracing sexuality.</description></item></channel></rss>