<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Mel Robbins Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-mel-robbins-podcast/</link><description>Recent content in The Mel Robbins Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 05:10:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-mel-robbins-podcast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why Do I Love the Way That I Love: The 4 Attachment Styles Explained | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010132/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why do you love the way that you love? How do you have the best relationships of your life (including the one with yourself)? Today, Mel sits down with expert in attachment theory Thais Gibson to explain the framework to improve any relationship in your life. Her work on the subconscious mind and personal transformation will empower you to set better goals and have happier and healthier relationships. Topics discussed include: • How to have secure and healthy relationships (including your relationship with yourself) • What your “attachment style” means and the 4 types • How your subconscious mind drives a lot of what you do • What love is supposed to look like • How your attachment style impacts your personal goal-setting • The biggest limiting beliefs from childhood (which one is yours?</description></item><item><title>BONUS Meditation: Listen for 21 Days to Reprogram Your Subconscious | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010133/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Want to feel more at peace, in control, and calm in just 15 minutes? If you listen to this meditation for 21 days in a row, you will reprogram your subconscious mind. You will leave feeling free of thoughts, patterns, and behaviors that weigh you down. Today, counselor, expert in attachment styles, and bestselling author Thais Gibson is walking you through a meditation that has helped over 31,000 people.</description></item><item><title>Super Brain: 10 Things to Eat, Think, &amp; Do to Improve Your Memory and Learn Faster | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010131/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Want to boost your reading speed by 30%–50%?
Want to learn faster?
What if you never forgot where you put your keys again?
Mel sits down with world-renowned brain coach Jim Kwik to help you boost your brainpower with his science-backed tools, tips, and strategies.
In this episode, they discuss: How your brain is more powerful than you think The best ways to retain information How to read 50% faster with ONE simple tool 3 tricks to always remember where you put your keys How to remember someone’s name Jim’s proven 3M framework 10 simple steps for a better brain The best foods for increased brain power How to be MORE productive but work LESS How exercise impacts brain function How to crush any job interview How to memorize a speech in one day Why you need to always be a student</description></item><item><title>How to Stop Procrastinating, According to the World’s Leading Expert (It’s Not What You Think) | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010130/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you always the one who is late for everything?
Do you find yourself procrastinating, no matter how hard you try to stay focused?
Does managing your time to get everything done feel impossible?
Mel sits down with THE world’s leading researcher on procrastination.
Dr. Joseph Ferrari is a distinguished Professor of Psychology at DePaul University in Chicago, where he has spent nearly three decades researching with colleagues around the world about why we procrastinate.</description></item><item><title>Boost Your Success in 2024: My Best Advice on Business, Time Management, and Reinvention | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010129/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Want to know the hack that will make you more successful in 2024?
Today, Mel is offering you a masterclass in business at zero cost. By walking you through her learnings and lessons, you will receive the coaching you need to uplevel in business and in life.
Topics discussed include: One thing you need to stop doing today to stay motivated. The 3 most important aspects of business. How to overcome “slow” times in your business.</description></item><item><title>5 Ways to Improve Your Subconscious Mind &amp; Be Happier in 2024: Amazing Insight From Dr. Paul Conti | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010128/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Want to learn how to be a happier and more successful version of yourself… from the psychiatrist that Lady Gaga says “saved her life?”
Mel sits down with Stanford-trained psychiatrist, trauma expert, and best-selling author Dr. Paul Conti to help you improve your mental health and be happier in 2024.
Topics discussed: Toxic self-talk starts in childhood. Cotard’s Syndrome: The extreme side of negative self-talk. Your thoughts become your reality.</description></item><item><title>Reset Your Gut in 5 Days: A Medical Doctor’s Step-by-Step Protocol to Transform Your Health | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010127/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you want to reset your health?
Are you ready for more energy and better overall health?
Do you want to start seeing results in 5 days (or less)?
In today’s episode, Mel is joined by double-board certified Dr. Amy Shah for Part 2 of her masterclass on how to optimize your gut health.
Dr. Amy, a medical doctor trained at Harvard, Cornell, and Columbia University, is an immunologist and leading expert in women’s hormonal health and nutrition.</description></item><item><title>The Science of Your Gut: 3 Easy Steps to Reduce Bloating, Improve Digestion, and Feel Better Today | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010126/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010126/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is bloating, and why don’t your pants fit after just one meal?
What are the 10 foods to avoid when you feel bloated?
What is gut health, and how can you improve yours?
Today Mel is joined by double-board certified Dr. Amy Shah, who is here to explain bloating and optimal gut health in a way that you can understand and easily apply to your life.
Dr. Shah, a medical doctor trained at Harvard, Cornell, and Columbia University, is an immunologist and leading expert in women’s hormonal health and nutrition.</description></item><item><title>4 Surprising Secrets of Successful Relationships (What I Learned From a Fight With My Daughter) | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010125/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010125/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do you have a “healthy” fight with your family?
How do you repair a relationship with someone you love?
Today Mel is joined by her husband Chris, their daughter Kendall, and their son Oakley to answer listener questions about all kinds of relationships.
This is the perfect episode to listen to with your family. You’ll hear the Robbins’ insightful, powerful, fun, and sometimes hilarious advice on how to get along with and love everyone in your family.</description></item><item><title>Outsmart a Narcissist: A Proven 4-Step Plan to Take Your Power Back | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010124/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is it possible to be around narcissistic people and not lose your power? Especially when it&amp;rsquo;s your mom, dad, ex, or boss who’s acting toxic?
Today, Mel is joined by Rebecca Zung, an expert on narcissism and a globally recognized high-conflict negotiator. Rebecca is also a top-ranked trial lawyer who has studied narcissism so that she could win against them in the courtroom. She’s written the playbook, SLAY the Bully: How to Negotiate with A Narcissist and Win.</description></item><item><title>The Surprising Link Between People Pleasing &amp; Your Health: A Medical Doctor’s Recommendation on How to Say “No” | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010122/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Does this doctor have the health secret you’ve been looking for? Does people-pleasing really make you sick?
Dr. Neha Sangwan is an internal medicine physician, bestselling author, and accomplished researcher.
Today, Mel sits down with Dr. Sangwan to learn the truth about people-pleasing.
Topics discussed include:
People-pleasing: What it is.
Are you a “yes” person?
The difference between “going with the flow” and people pleasing.
Why avoiding conflict makes you a people-pleaser.</description></item><item><title>6 Ways to Use My “Let Them” Theory to Improve Any Relationship | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010121/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wouldn’t it be nice if there was a way to not get so annoyed or frustrated with the people that you love?
There is.
It’s called the “Let Them” theory. Mel discovered it while arguing with her son about a taco stand, and she hasn’t stopped using it since.
She first explained the “Let Them” theory in a 60-second reel on Instagram. 63 million views later. The verdict is in.</description></item><item><title>How a Stay-at-Home Mom “With No Experience” Built a $255M Business: Blowouts, Divorces, and the Messy Truth | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010119/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Want to know what it really takes to launch, build, and sell a $255 million-dollar business in ten years flat? Do you have a good idea, but you think you “have no business being in business”?
In this new episode, Mel sits down with the founder of Drybar, Alli Webb, and takes you on a riveting tour of how a stay-at-home mom who had ‘no business being in business’ made $255 million in 10 years.</description></item><item><title>This Teen Cracked the Code on Anxiety and Teaches You How He Did It | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010120/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you tired of feeling anxious?
Want to know a simple way to boost your confidence?
Do you need better boundaries with your family?
Buckling under the pressure of college applications, a job search, or other big life decisions?
Listeners from around the world have been writing in about these issues, asking specifically for both Mel’s advice and her 18-year-old son Oakley’s young adult perspective.
This is a fantastic conversation to listen to as a family.</description></item><item><title>You Can Handle It: This 18-Year-Old Cracked the Code on Anxiety (and So Can You) | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you tired of feeling anxious?
Want to know a simple way to boost your confidence?
Do you need better boundaries with your family?
Buckling under the pressure of college applications, a job search, or other big life decisions?
Listeners from around the world have been writing in about these issues, asking specifically for both Mel’s advice and her 18-year-old son Oakley’s young adult perspective.
This is a fantastic conversation to listen to as a family.</description></item><item><title>Dr. Gina Poe: How to Get Better Sleep and Boost Your Learning, Memory and Energy | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you getting the sleep you need? Do you wish you could improve your sleep, but you’re not sure how?
Dr. Gina Poe is an accomplished researcher and trained neuroscientist with a PhD in basic sleep. Currently a professor at UCLA, Dr. Poe has been researching the functions of sleep for over 30 years and has authored nearly 200 publications on the topic.
Today, Dr. Poe is here to answer your questions like, Why do you sleep?</description></item><item><title>The Science of Strength Training: Learn How Lifting Weights (Even Light Ones) Helps You Lose Weight, Feel Better, and Live Longer | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you missing the one thing that would make all the difference in your effort to be healthier? I was. And the thing I was missing was weight training.
In this episode, you will learn from Dr. Gabrielle Lyon, a medical doctor who is fellowship-trained in nutritional sciences and geriatrics.
Dr. Lyon is a renowned researcher, pioneer, and founder of the Institute for Muscle Centric Medicine. She is the New York Times best-selling author of Forever Strong: A New, Science-Based Strategy for Aging Well and has decades of experience to share with you.</description></item><item><title>6 Signs You’re Addicted to Stress: Psychologist Teaches You How to Remove Drama From Your Life | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010004/</guid><description>Podcast Description I was talking sh*t about my daughter and got caught red-handed. Talk about unnecessary drama.
We&amp;rsquo;ve all been there. And according to today’s expert, this type of conflict is causing more stress than you think.
Today, I am joined by Dr. Scott Lyons, a medical doctor, holistic psychologist, and renowned body-based trauma expert. He says there are 6 telltale signs that you’re addicted to stress.
I never considered myself to be a person who is addicted to stress until this conversation.</description></item><item><title>“You’re Not Obsessed With Your Ex, Patsy; You’re an Addict.” Mel’s Advice, Listener Questions, and More! | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to another round of your questions and my advice. I have a stack of your crazy, raw, and unbelievably direct questions, so we are going to have an unfiltered conversation about sex, competitive parents, getting over your ex, and this light and easy question&amp;hellip; Is there a God?
You are getting the coaching you need right now.
The questions you asked are juicy:
Why am I still obsessed with my ex?</description></item><item><title>How to Have the Best Sex of Your Life: Surprising Ways to Make Sex Better Even if You Are Tired, Single… or Not in the Mood | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010006/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you are going to learn how to have better sex. You have an appointment with a leading sex expert, Dr. Emily Morse. I will be the first to admit that I want to have better sex, but I don’t know how to achieve it.
And I’m asking all the uncomfortable questions you want to ask.
This conversation is going to make you think differently about this topic and inspire you to prioritize pleasure and connection in bed, no matter your age, relationship status, or gender.</description></item><item><title>Renew Your Spirit: 5 Ways I’m Finding Hope &amp; Strength Right Now | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010007/</guid><description>Podcast Description I’m not even going to call our conversation today an episode because it is so much bigger. I am here with a soul-stirring and inspiring message that’s coming from my heart to yours. When the world feels dark, you and I need to bring the light. I was moved to share a deeply personal message with you today about the power you hold to make a difference right now.</description></item><item><title>Conquer Overwhelm: Your Ultimate Guide to Inner Peace With the Amazing Dr. Thema Bryant | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010008/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Dr. Thema Bryant gives you the tools to conquer overwhelm and unlock your inner peace.
Dr. Thema Bryant is the current president of the American Psychological Association. She trained at both Duke and Harvard, teaches at Pepperdine University, has published multiple best-selling books, and has spent decades of her life researching how you can stay calm and centered in any situation.
She calls this kind of peace “coming home” to yourself, and she will teach you how to do it, even if the world around you is in chaos.</description></item><item><title>Beautiful, Healing Words When the World Feels Overwhelming: An Inspiring Episode for Right Now | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 20:59:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010009/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this important and special episode, you will hear the beautiful, profound, and comforting words that are needed in the world right now.
When I woke up this morning, I did not expect to have this conversation.
But, as I watched the news unfold, I felt overwhelmed and hopeless, seeing a world that feels like it’s spinning out of control.
I thought to myself, &amp;ldquo;If I could talk to one person right now who could give you and me the love, support, and tools that help when you feel scared of the world around you, who would it be?</description></item><item><title>Never Enough: 7 Ways to Protect Yourself (and Your Kids) From Toxic Pressure | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010010/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, award-winning Harvard-educated journalist and researcher Jenny Wallace is here to discuss “toxic achievement” and the toxic pressure that makes you feel that no matter what you do or what level of success you achieve, it will never be enough.
You feel toxic pressure at work, and you feel toxic pressure at home. Jenny Wallace, who just completed a major research study with over 6,000 kids and their parents, is here to tell you this unhealthy pressure is trickling down to your kids, who are buckling under the never-ending demands to measure up.</description></item><item><title>Trust Your Gut: The Science and Spirit of Intuitive Decision-Making | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010011/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s episode, prepare to open your mind to larger possibilities and amazing capabilities that you already have.
I am sitting down with intuitive psychic medium Kim Russo, who is here to share her gift and tell you how you can get in touch with your intuitive gift, too.
I first learned about Kim from Oprah Winfrey and immediately knew I needed to get her on the talk show I hosted.</description></item><item><title>Yes, You Can Make a Difference: This Remarkable Story Will Inspire You to Do Something Big | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010012/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s episode, author and entrepreneur Lorenzo Lewis tells you the amazing story of how he is changing the lives of over 3 million people a year.
His story is so inspiring, and I wanted you to meet Lorenzo because I know he’ll inspire you to think bigger about making a difference in your community or the world at large.
Lorenzo had no funding, influence, or experience. He just had a simple idea and a very big heart.</description></item><item><title>6 Magic Words That Stop Anxiety &amp; Overwhelm | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010013/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s episode, I’m sharing the “6 magic words” that I say to myself on repeat whenever I start to spiral.
I call them “magic” because they seem to have an almost spell-like effect on me when I say them out loud.
I’ve shared these 6 magic words with millions of people online, and today you’re going to learn what they are and how to use them to your advantage.</description></item><item><title>You Asked, I Answered: Don’t Blame Me for Delivering the Hard Truth | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010014/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s episode, we are trying something new, and absolutely anything goes. You’ve been flooding my inbox with questions, problems, sticky situations, and big, big dreams and goals.
So today, because you asked, I am going to show up and deliver the hard truth, the surprising advice, the tricks to get you out of any pickle, and the inspiration that you need to take that next step.
Nothing is off the table.</description></item><item><title>Never Fast the Week Before Your Period! The Shocking Science About Intermittent Fasting &amp; Women’s Health | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010015/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, researcher, respected expert on intermittent fasting, and bestselling author of Fast Like A Girl, Dr. Mindy Pelz, is here to explain fasting—and, in particular, how it impacts women’s hormone health.
Men and women’s hormones are different, and because of that, women MUST fast differently than men.
Dr. Mindy is the first person who explained this to me, and this is why I wanted to have her on.</description></item><item><title>6 Intermittent Fasting Protocols for Fat Loss, Mood, Energy, and Improving Your Overall Health | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010016/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, renowned holistic health expert and intermittent fasting devotee Dr. Mindy Pelz is here to explain the 101 of fasting for better health. You’ll learn the empowering science behind why it works and how it can help you achieve so many health goals.
Dr. Mindy is fascinated by our body’s ability to &amp;ldquo;heal itself&amp;rdquo; and how fasting protocols can activate some remarkable results based on extensive research studies.</description></item><item><title>Raw and Refreshing Advice on Navigating Anxiety, Insecurity, Popularity, &amp; Peer Pressure in Your Teenage and 20-Something Years | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lately, I’ve been getting a ton of questions from listeners about how to best support high schoolers and 20-somethings. There are lots of questions about anxiety, peer pressure, and getting young adults to open up.
So, in this episode, I have a pile of your questions in front of me as my son, Oakley, and I go through them rapid-fire style, so you get both of our perspectives on the topics everyone worries about but is too afraid to talk about.</description></item><item><title>The Best Advice I Ever Heard: From Motivation to Paper Plates, 10 Genius Hacks for Keeping Yourself and Your Home Organized | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010018/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s episode, I welcome back KC Davis, therapist, and bestselling author.
The episode before this featured her relatable, hilarious, and breakthrough ideas about everything from laundry to loading a dishwasher and giving yourself the freaking break that you deserve.
That episode was so insanely popular, we moved this up in the queue.
The verdict is in.
You love KC Davis. So today she&amp;rsquo;s answering your deeply personal and surprising questions.</description></item><item><title>11 Crazy Facts About Laundry, Showering, &amp; Getting the “Little Stuff” Done That Will Make You Laugh (and Prove You’re Doing Better Than You Think) | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010019/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s episode, best-selling author and therapist KC Davis answers the question, &amp;ldquo;How can you be successful in many areas of your life but fall short on getting the laundry, dishes, or grocery shopping done?&amp;rdquo;
Which begs the question: why are all the &amp;ldquo;little tasks&amp;rdquo; so hard?!
Because when it’s time to get them done, they don’t &amp;ldquo;feel&amp;rdquo; so little.
KC’s advice, breakthrough ideas, and research will make you realize you’re not the only one who feels like you’re drowning.</description></item><item><title>If You Only Listen to One Podcast Today, Make It This One | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010020/</guid><description>Podcast Description You need to hear today’s episode.
I have something profound to share with you. It is a deeply personal message, straight from my heart to yours.
This is not a pep talk. It’s not a motivational speech. This is a goddamn wake-up call.
Your life is like a melting ice cube.
Your excuses are endless, but time isn’t.
Stop waiting for the perfect time.
Stop waiting to feel ready.</description></item><item><title>New Research: The Surprising Psychology Behind the Secrets Everyone Keeps &amp; What Your Secrets Say About You | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010021/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s episode, you and I are discussing the fascinating science of secrets: why you keep them and how keeping secrets directly impacts your relationships, your self-esteem, your health, and holds you back from living the life you deserve.
Dr. Michael Slepian is a bestselling author, psychologist, associate professor of leadership and ethics at Columbia Business School, and former scholar at Stanford. He has been researching secrets for over a decade and will help you understand what secrets are, why we keep them, and the harm of holding them inside.</description></item><item><title>Get Your Sh*t Together: This 85-Year-Old Badass Does More Than You &amp; Me (Steal Her 7 Amazing Secrets to Life) | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010022/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you will meet Judie, a total badass who has it all figured out, from killer biceps to fulfilling friendships to staying mentally sharp, spunky, and sexy. She’s got it all together.
Who is Judie? She’s my 85-year-old mother-in-law.
You don’t need a library full of books filled with the science of staying young forever. Today you are getting the cliff notes for living a long, happy, healthy, fulfilling, and purposeful life.</description></item><item><title>5 Ways to Improve Your Breathing for Better Health With the #1 Breath Expert in the World | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010023/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s episode, the incredible Patrick McKeown, international bestselling author of ten books on breathing and founder and CEO of The Oxygen Advantage, a world-leading breathwork training program, breaks down all things breathing.
This is not a lecture; it is a masterclass. His decades of research will blow you away, so let’s slow down and learn from the best in class.
You need this, and I need this. Why?</description></item><item><title>6 Steps to Navigating Major Change Like a Pro (a Hilarious Guide to Back-to-School and College Drop-Off Season!) | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010024/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s episode, you are getting a relatable and hilarious guide to navigating major transitions like a pro.
Join me in a real and raw conversation with my friends and colleagues, Amy and Lynne, as we unpack the major mistakes and 6 lessons learned from &amp;ldquo;horrible&amp;rdquo; college drop-off experiences (both our own and the ones we had with our kids) and the fear that comes with any major transition in your life.</description></item><item><title>These 4 Words Will Silence Your Self-Doubt: A Life-Changing Conversation | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010025/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010025/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you and I are dismantling one of the most crippling forms of self-doubt.
&amp;ldquo;Imposter Syndrome&amp;rdquo; is when you think you’re not good enough and that everyone else is smarter, more successful, and has more to contribute than you do. Everyone feels it. It’s so common that the Harvard Business Review found that even 70% of the world’s top executives have struggled with it.
My mission today is to convince you that Imposter Syndrome is actually a GOOD thing.</description></item><item><title>Something Scary Happened the Other Day, and I Wanted to Talk About It With You (and a PhD Trauma Researcher) | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010026/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010026/</guid><description>Podcast Description A few days ago, I was the witness to a very tragic accident, and the experience affected me very deeply.
I reached out to a renowned trauma specialist, and the advice she gave me changed my life.
In this episode, you will hear that incredible advice because she allowed me to record it.
Dr. MaryCatherine McDonald, PhD, a best-selling author and professor, reveals the 5 essential things you need to know about trauma so you can finally move forward with your life.</description></item><item><title>Research From Princeton: 13 Proven Hacks That Boost Your Influence &amp; Make You More Confident | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010027/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you’re getting a crash course in 13 essential hacks that will help you be more successful, and they’re backed by surprising research out of Princeton.
Vanessa Van Edwards is the founder of the behavior lab The Science of People, a behavioral investigator, body language expert, and bestselling author who specializes in the kind of science-based people skills most of us never hear about.
Vanessa’s research proves that anyone can learn these practical skills, earn the trust of others around them, and become more confident, competent, and reliable.</description></item><item><title>Optimize Your Brain: 3 Important Habits for Productivity, Memory, and Longevity (Based on 200,000 Brain Scans) | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010028/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010028/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, world-renowned brain specialist Dr. Daniel Amen reveals the secrets to a happier life, and it all starts with&amp;hellip; (surprise!) your brain.
Dr. Daniel Amen is a medical doctor with 40 years of experience as a psychiatrist, 12 New York Times bestselling books, and he’s conducted over 200,000 brain scans, all of which back up the simple, proven tactics he’s about to share with you.
Dr. Amen shares the 3 most important habits you can start today to make your brain work better for you, based on decades of research.</description></item><item><title>Dial Down Family Drama: 5 Ways to Reduce Conflict With the Ones You Love | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010029/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010029/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you’ll get 5 effective strategies to help you improve your family dynamics, resolve almost any conflict like a pro, and create a better bond.
Spending time with family is awesome, but it can also be challenging because, as much as you wish everyone could get along, different personalities and opinions don’t always mix well together.
When family drama starts, don’t allow yourself to get sucked into it.</description></item><item><title>The Shocking Science and Benefits of Taking a Simple Walk: Research From Oxford-Trained Neuroscientist Dr. Shane O’Mara | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010030/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010030/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, a renowned Oxford-trained neuroscientist teaches you the most incredibly simple, science-backed hack that will change every single part of your life in just 10 minutes.
Professor Shane O’Mara, academic writer, author, and Experimental Brain Researcher at Trinity College in Dublin, walks us through the mind-blowing research behind, of all things, walking.
You’ll be shocked to learn how the right kind of walking can lower depression and anxiety without medication.</description></item><item><title>From PMS to Menopause: How to Hack Your Hormones and Use Science to Lose Weight, Sleep Better and Get Your Mojo Back | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010031/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010031/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, double-board certified Dr. Amy Shah is here to explain the science of hormones, how they impact a woman&amp;rsquo;s body, and more importantly, what you can do about it.
If you’re tired of PMS, bloating, mood swings, hot flashes, the belly &amp;ldquo;bread basket,&amp;rdquo; or the brain fog of menopause&amp;hellip; grab your pen and get ready to take notes.
Dr. Amy, a medical doctor trained at Harvard, Cornell, and Columbia, is an immunologist and leading expert in women’s hormonal health and nutrition.</description></item><item><title>You Are a Badass: Unlock Your Most Authentic Self in 4 Proven Steps | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010032/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010032/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, renowned researcher, bestselling author, and total badass Ritu Bhasin will help you step into your power.
Her work proves that a better life begins when you stop trying to fit in and start showing up as your authentic self.
Does this sound like you?
You say yes to fit in. You stay silent and let others talk over you during meetings. You never ask for that raise you’ve earned.</description></item><item><title>Turn Anxiety Into Power: A 3-Step Process to Master Your Emotions From a Harvard Psychologist | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010033/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010033/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Harvard professor Dr. Luana Marques is going to teach you 3 simple steps to turn anxiety into power. And she’s not fooling around; in the first few minutes, she even called me out.
If you want to be more successful and effective in getting what you want out of your life or career, learning how to master your emotions, especially in difficult situations, is an essential skill.</description></item><item><title>Change Your Relationship With Alcohol – How to Control Your Urge to Drink | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010034/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today on the podcast, you and I are having a deeply personal and eye-opening conversation about alcohol and your relationship to it.
Rachel Hart is a best-selling author and master coach who has helped thousands of people re-examine their relationship with alcohol, and that’s exactly what she is going to help you do today.
Rachel knows the surprising reason you (and I) crave a drink (or have the urge to shop, vape, play video games, scroll on social media, or want something sweet).</description></item><item><title>Is It Too Late? How to Repair a Broken Relationship With Your Friend or Family Member | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010035/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010035/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you’re going to learn that it is never too late to try to repair a broken or difficult relationship.
Research shows that estrangement is not only on the rise but that the majority of us have at least one extended family member or friend who is estranged.
I know this is true in my own extended family, and I also have friends who are estranged from their parents.</description></item><item><title>Where Did All My Friends Go? A Simple Guide to Finding Your People (Steal This!) | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010036/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010036/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, I show you how to find your people, have more fun, and create meaningful friendships as an adult in a very simple way.
And it starts with your morning coffee.
Plus, I’m sharing 4 opening lines and tactics you can use when approaching a potential new friend.
Can we just be honest? Making new friends as an adult is so hard. And I believe that we are all struggling with it.</description></item><item><title>Therapist Reveals Why You Struggle With Relationships &amp; How to Let More Love Into Your Life | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010037/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010037/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you are going to learn why you struggle in certain relationships and how to let more love in.
Whether you struggle in your friendships or your romantic relationships, or you don’t feel connected to your family or the community where you live, today&amp;rsquo;s conversation will give you the insight and tools that you need to create better and more loving relationships everywhere.
Dr. Marisa Franco is a NYT bestselling author, award-winning therapist, and professor of psychology at The University of Maryland.</description></item><item><title>5 Things the Men in Your Life Aren’t Telling You but Need to Talk About | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010038/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010038/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s episode, you will learn the 5 things that men secretly struggle with and how you can open up the conversation to better support them.
I’m proud to introduce you to my husband, Chris, who is the founder of a men&amp;rsquo;s retreat, Soul Degree. He has been leading these retreats for the past 6 years and has worked with everyone from veterans, executives, and first responders to college students.</description></item><item><title>Happiness Is an Option for You: 4 Easy Habits That Make Your Life Better Based on Research | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010039/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010039/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you’re going to learn the 4 happiness habits that, based on research, are scientifically proven to make you happier in 21 days. Happiness is not only possible; it is an option for you.
Our guest today is one of the most respected happiness researchers in the world. Shawn Achor is the author of 4 New York Times bestsellers and has created the largest happiness training program in the world.</description></item><item><title>Stop Taking Things So Seriously: A Hilarious Story About Wedgies, Wardrobe Failures, Art Museums, &amp; Having More Fun | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010040/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010040/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you are going to learn the art of having more fun.
I share a hilarious story about a major wardrobe malfunction with you and two podcast crew members.
You’ll laugh along at all the ridiculous details, but the takeaway is serious:
Learning how to laugh at yourself is a superpower, and research says people who have a sense of humor are more respected and are viewed as more confident and intelligent by their peers.</description></item><item><title>How to Hack Hunger and Cravings Using Science With a Doctor Trained at Harvard, Columbia, and Cornell | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010041/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why do you always crave dessert after dinner? Or a snack mid-afternoon? Today we’re digging into the science of cravings:
-Why you have them
-How to tell the difference between a craving and actual hunger
-How to eat your way to better health and a happier life.
Dr. Amy Shah is a double-board certified medical doctor with training from Cornell, Harvard, and Columbia Universities and an expert on intermittent fasting, hormones, and food cravings.</description></item><item><title>6 Surprising Signs of Adult ADHD | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010042/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010042/</guid><description>Podcast Description More and more adults are being diagnosed with ADHD, so today, we are unpacking the 6 surprising signs of ADHD. I also tell you why so many women, in particular, go undiagnosed.
This episode is deeply personal, but my story is shared by so many women. I lived my entire life with symptoms of ADHD and crushing anxiety because of it. But I was never diagnosed until the age of 47—and I found out by fluke!</description></item><item><title>Harvard Professor Says THIS Is the Secret to Success (It’s Not What You Think) | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010043/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010043/</guid><description>Podcast Description According to Harvard professor Dr. Luana Marques, there is one sneaky habit that holds every single person back – and no one knows what it is.
When she reveals the habit that holds you back, your first reaction will be to stop and think.
And as you listen to her explain it and give you examples, you’ll be shocked that you’ve never before seen it in yourself or heard anyone else point it out to you… until now.</description></item><item><title>The Science of Gratitude &amp; 6 Surprising Ways You’re Getting It Wrong | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010044/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we are digging into the research on gratitude. Gratitude is a critical life skill, yet most of us are practicing it wrong.
That’s right.
According to the research, there are 4 essential elements of genuine gratitude. Without all 4, you can’t unlock the powerful physiological, neurological, and psychological benefits of genuine gratitude.
For example, if you’re just thinking about what you’re grateful for or writing a list before you go to bed, you’re probably not getting the full impact of its power.</description></item><item><title>How a Waitress at Denny’s Built a Billion Dollar Beauty Brand: This Incredible Story Will Unlock Your Purpose! | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010045/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010045/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you’ve ever dreamt of doing something big, today&amp;rsquo;s episode will get your head spinning, open your heart, and inspire you to take the leap.
It doesn’t matter how young or how old you are.
You are meant to go big, to swing for the fence, and to do something no one has ever done before.
No more small plans. You have something big to do.
And there’s no better person to inspire you to make big plans than my friend and IT Cosmetics Founder, Jamie Kern Lima.</description></item><item><title>Giving Up Is Not an Option: The Motivation You Need to Hear Right Now | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010046/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a message for every new graduate.
Whether you’re graduating from college or graduating from a chapter in your life, you need this message today. Your dreams matter, and what happens next is in your hands.
You have a flame inside you that represents the way you were meant to show up in this world.
Today I’m teaching you how to throw gasoline on that flame.
No matter what you&amp;rsquo;re going through in life, your dreams are alive and well, and they are waiting for you to wake up and turn toward them.</description></item><item><title>3 Steps To Finding Your North Star: An Exciting New Approach To Designing Your Life | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010047/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to an exciting new masterclass on designing the life of your dreams.
First, you’ll learn the process for identifying your own North Star, why this is important at the beginning of creating your new life, and how to use your North Star to guide you in the process of designing your life.
Next, you’ll dive deep into the 3-part framework: Emulate, Assimilate, and Innovate.
This framework is the backbone of the University of Southern California’s world-renowned Popular Music major taught at their Thornton School of Music.</description></item><item><title>The “Let Them Theory”: A Life Changing Mindset Hack That 15 Million People Can’t Stop Talking About | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010048/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010048/</guid><description>Podcast Description I shared the &amp;ldquo;Let Them Theory&amp;rdquo; on social media, and it went CRAZY VIRAL. 15 million views, 11,000 comments. Today, it’s your turn to learn this mindset trick. I’ve been using this technique for a while, so I know firsthand how powerful it is.
The &amp;ldquo;Let Them Theory&amp;rdquo; is so simple, you’re going to get it immediately.
And I have some great stories and examples to share with you, because there are three very different ways you can use it.</description></item><item><title>6 Signs You’re Disconnected From Your Power and How to Get It Back: Life-Changing Advice From the Remarkable Dr. Thema Bryant | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010049/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010049/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you feel that something’s missing from your life but have no idea exactly what’s missing or where to begin looking for it, today’s episode will help you reconnect with your power and find greater meaning in your life.
Dr. Thema Bryant is the current president of the American Psychological Association. She trained at both Duke and Harvard, published multiple best-selling books, and has dedicated decades of her life to researching how we connect with each other by first connecting back to ourselves.</description></item><item><title>4 Simple Ways to Stop Giving a Sh*t About What Other People Think of You | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010050/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Imagine how liberating it would be to not care about what other people think of you. You’d take more risks. You’d stop holding yourself back. You’d make more money and have more fun.
That’s what happened to me when I learned the (not-so-subtle) art of not giving a sh*t.
This is the best episode I&amp;rsquo;ve done so far.
I mean it. The best.
It’s hilarious. It’s relatable. It’s packed with takeaways and research.</description></item><item><title>How To Help Anyone In Your Life Who’s Struggling - Fantastic Strategies From A Yale-Educated Psychologist | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010051/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010051/</guid><description>Podcast Description I am thrilled to share this conversation with you. It is packed with practical strategies that will help the people in your life who may be struggling.
Dr. Lisa Damour is a clinical psychologist and author of three New York Times bestsellers. She earned degrees from both Yale and the University of Michigan and has more than 30 years of experience working with teens and families.
Her latest book, The Emotional Lives of Teenagers, has been nothing short of life changing.</description></item><item><title>The Best Years of Your Life Are Ahead of You: A No BS Approach to Feeling Stuck | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010052/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010052/</guid><description>Podcast Description You know what you want and how to start.
But you never make progress.
Here’s my wake up call for you today:
What’s holding you back is never what you think.
Today I am coaching a woman who says:
I can’t make myself do what I need to do. I feel like I’m in quicksand. Every time I try to move…I sink.
She has: -put on an extra 30 pounds -left her relationship with herself in the gutter -no longer does the things that make her happy -broken promises to herself time and again</description></item><item><title>FBI Trained Expert Explains How to Read Body Language | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010053/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010053/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you’re going to learn how to decode body language from one of the world’s leading experts on the topic.
Janine Driver has been trained by the FBI, CIA, and one of the world’s top hostage negotiators.
When a criminal case grabs our attention, every news network calls Janine to analyze body language and critical verbal cues that suspects, politicians, and celebrities are sending so we can tell when somebody is lying.</description></item><item><title>Stop Trying to "Trust Your Gut." Do This Instead. Works Way Better! | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010054/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last week, I learned a really cool trick to help you go with your gut.
I guarantee you’ve never heard gut decisions explained this way before. Because I stumbled upon it in a very random way—while touring colleges with our son Oakley!
We hit 5 schools in 4 days, and over the course of that time, it hit me. Holy smokes, that&amp;rsquo;s the perfect hack for making big decisions.</description></item><item><title>How to Make Hard Choices: Practical Tips for When Sh*t Gets Real | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010055/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Oh…sometimes life is a real doozy.
You make all these plans, and boom. You step right into a pile of you-know-what. And then you realize that pile was there all along—you just missed it.
Which brings us to the topic of today’s episode: making hard decisions and moving on from hard relationships.
How do you move forward when…
You feel so torn about what to do.
You don’t trust yourself.</description></item><item><title>Are You an “Over” or “Under” Functioner? A Hilarious and Helpful Guide to YOUR Stress Style | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010056/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010056/</guid><description>Podcast Description At some point, the you-know-what is going to hit the fan.
And it happened to me the other morning when I was driving my husband to his colonoscopy.
This is the first episode without a video version because I recorded it from my iPhone after dropping my husband off at the hospital.
I promised to take you into my life; I just didn&amp;rsquo;t expect it to be as a stressful situation was unfolding in real time.</description></item><item><title>You’ve Got Money All Wrong: A Step by Step Guide to Living a Rich Life | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010057/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010057/</guid><description>Podcast Description You can be rich.
(Don’t roll your eyes at me; I’m serious.)
This is not what you think.
This episode today is so digestible. So counterintuitive. One of the most enlightening conversations I’ve had with anybody.
If I had a nickel for every epiphany I had during this episode, I’d be rich.
Most of us have been thinking about money all wrong.
It turns out that the amount of money you have in the bank (or don’t have in the bank) is only a small part of your relationship with money.</description></item><item><title>Incredible Research From Harvard: 4 Simple Tools to Conquer Your Fear | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010058/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010058/</guid><description>Podcast Description A few years ago, I found this study from Harvard, and it changed my life.
It&amp;rsquo;s research about performance and feeling nervous, with a simple reframing method that you can use to never let fear stop you again.
I’ve been using this technique with my five second rule for years, and the first way I applied it was to get control of my nerves and fear of public speaking.</description></item><item><title>Take Control of Your Mindset: Master Your Mental Habits for a Happier Life | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010059/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010059/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you’re learning a simple but powerful way to take control of your mindset.
You need to get serious about your mindset. The way you think and talk to yourself has serious consequences.
Your thoughts become your beliefs.
Your beliefs turn into actions.
Your actions become habits.
And your habits determine who you are and what you achieve in life, or not.
That’s why you need a Mindset Reset.</description></item><item><title>5 Easy Steps to Make Your Home and Your Mind Clutter-Free | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010060/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010060/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode blew my freakin’ mind.
After you meet our expert today and learn her revolutionary approach to simplifying your life, you will never approach the topic of picking up, cleaning up, or organizing the same way again.
Whether it’s your desk or closet that is overwhelming you, or like me, you are guilty of constantly starting projects and putting things in piles, only to run out of time or get flustered, creating bigger projects to deal with in the future, today’s episode will change your entire life.</description></item><item><title>The Toolkit for Healing Anxiety, Part 2 | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010061/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s episode is a continuation of our exclusive two-part series with world-renowned medical expert Dr. Russell Kennedy.
If you thought Part 1 of this series was life-changing, buckle up! Part 2 of this Toolkit brings you even more strategies and tools as we take questions from three more listeners of the podcast.
Is anxiety impacting your ability to sleep?
Tired of the negative loop of thoughts in your mind?</description></item><item><title>The Toolkit for Healing Anxiety, Part 1 | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010062/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s episode is my gift to you and anyone in your life who struggles with anxiety.
I created this exclusive series, &amp;ldquo;The Toolkit for Healing Anxiety,&amp;rdquo; because of the number of questions I am receiving from listeners asking for more resources on this topic.
Part 1 is packed with tactical takeaways and features Dr. Russell Kennedy, one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most respected medical experts on anxiety.
Dr. Kennedy is a medical doctor and neuroscientist who has a revolutionary and effective approach to helping his patients understand and heal anxiety.</description></item><item><title>5 Ways to Take Your Power Back When People Disrespect You | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010063/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, you and I are calling BS on partners, friends, siblings, colleagues, and roommates who ride on your coattails, mooch off your generosity, and love the fact that you do everything. (While they do next to nothing.…)
It’s time to take your power back with 5 actionable takeaways to get people in your life to step up and do their part.
I’m not messing around. The first person you’ll meet in this episode is tired of being the only one holding her family together.</description></item><item><title>How to Handle Negative People: 6 Strategies to Protect Your Peace | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010064/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010064/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you and I are talking about how to protect your peace.
You already spend a lot of time trying to be positive - so today I want to remind you that it is just as important to protect your energy from people and situations who suck it dry.
You know the ones.
The friend who is so n-e-g-a-t-i-v-e, about everything! The rude person at the coffee shop.</description></item><item><title>Every Tattoo Has a Story: Here’s Mine | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010065/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010065/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s episode, I’m finally answering the #1 personal question that I get asked:
What’s the story behind my tattoo on my right wrist?
Pull up a seat to laugh along with us as Chris and I share our tattoo adventure - complete with anxiety, jealousy, intention, love, a huge mistake on my part, and the most incredible moments of synchronicity.
But it’s not just a story; there’s a much more profound topic we are discussing today.</description></item><item><title>How to Speak Up for Yourself: Simple Strategies for Being Heard | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010066/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010066/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you’re learning how to speak up for yourself and make sure that you are heard.
Whether you want to be more influential and visible at work or there’s a hard conversation that you’ve been avoiding with a family member, this episode will empower you to have a breakthrough.
Most of us have never been taught the skills we need to have challenging conversations or to better advocate for our needs.</description></item><item><title>Reset Your Health in 10 Days: Advice From a Renowned MD | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010067/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010067/</guid><description>Podcast Description I made you an appointment with one of the world’s leading doctors in functional medicine.
Dr. Mark Hyman has written an incredible 14 (!!!) New York Times best sellers. He is the founder and director of The UltraWellness Center, and Head of Strategy and Innovation at the Cleveland Clinic Center for Functional Medicine. His latest book, Young Forever, teaches you science-backed, actionable steps to slow down the aging process and even reverse disease.</description></item><item><title>Practical, Proven Tools I Use When I Feel Overwhelmed | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010068/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010068/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you and I are tackling overwhelm together as I coach five listeners just like you who are tired of feeling so stressed.
I promise this will be helpful, fun, and full of powerful tools you can put to use immediately.
You need that because you’re drowning in your to-do lists, taking care of everyone else but yourself, and you’re saying yes to every commitment that enters your inbox.</description></item><item><title>What to Do When You’ve Been Cheated On | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010069/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010069/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, we are digging into betrayal and learning how to get your power back after someone shatters your trust.
It’s happened to me and I know it’s happened to you, too.
Maybe someone cheated on you. Maybe someone stole from you in business. Perhaps it was a friend who stabbed you in the back.
It’s painful.
You might not be sure how to confront that person, or if it’s even worth it.</description></item><item><title>Unlock a Happier Life: 3 Research-Backed Secrets | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010070/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010070/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you and I are getting intentional about your happiness.
Happiness is misunderstood.
Fortunately, there’s a ton of research that explains why it can be so elusive and, even better, HOW you can create a happier life, starting today.
Our conversation about happiness begins with breaking down the two types of happiness and why it’s important for you to include both in your life.
You’ll also learn four practical takeaways that research says are key for cultivating more happiness in your daily life.</description></item><item><title>Are You the Driver in Your Life or Just the Passenger? | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010071/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s episode is a trip.
I can’t wait to introduce you to my favorite metaphor - a road trip - to inspire you to have more fun and enjoy the ride on this thing called life.
After all, life is a journey. And no one’s path is exactly the same.
So today, I’m asking you to think about this road trip called life.
And I’m going to be asking you to consider some thought-provoking questions:</description></item><item><title>Toolkit for Building Unstoppable Confidence (According to Research) | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010072/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010072/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you are getting a brand new definition of confidence.
This definition is based on research studies on how confidence is built.
Confidence is not what you think it is.
It is not a personality trait you’re born with, and it’s not reserved only for extroverts.
Confidence is a skill that anyone can master.
And today is the perfect day for you to start.
You and I are breaking down the science together, and you’re invited to join in as I coach several listeners who are struggling with self-doubt.</description></item><item><title>Before You Waste Another Year of Your Life, Get Serious About Healing Your Past | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010073/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010073/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is an episode about how to face the things that you’re scared to admit, or as in the case of my guest today, have never publicly spoken about.
Today, you and I are going on a healing journey so that you can put the past where it belongs: in the rearview mirror.
You deserve healing.
It’s the only pathway for experiencing true peace, happiness, and the greatness you’re capable of.</description></item><item><title>Start Putting Yourself First: Tools to Say No Without Guilt or Drama | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010074/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010074/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you are going to learn how to put yourself first.
Which means you and I are having a conversation about people-pleasing.
You know you do it. I do it, too.
In fact, unless you&amp;rsquo;re a narcissistic jerk (and you’re not if you’re listening to these podcast episodes), we are all people-pleasers to some extent.
Being a people-pleaser is a coping mechanism and it is destroying your energy, your time, your dreams, and your sanity.</description></item><item><title>Hate Your Job? Burnt Out? Laid Off? Reimagine Your Future &amp; Take the Next Right Step | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010075/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010075/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, I’m on a mission to open your eyes to new possibilities.
What do you really want from your life?
And how can you reimagine your next career move to help you fulfill it?
If you’re feeling stuck in a job you hate, were just laid off or fired, just graduated, or you have no idea what you want to do with your life, this episode is my gift to you.</description></item><item><title>The Only Way to Stop Procrastinating (Based on Research) | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010076/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010076/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, we’re attacking procrastination head on – using science.
Just think about how many hours, or heck YEARS, you have wasted thinking about what you needed to do instead of doing it.
That ends today.
This episode is packed with a simple, research-backed method to understanding why you procrastinate (it’s not what you think) and what researchers claim is the best way of tackling it.
I predict this episode will be one of the most shared this year because procrastination kills more dreams than fear ever does.</description></item><item><title>If You Struggle With Anxiety, This Episode Will Change Your Life | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010077/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010077/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you’re invited to sit in on a really personal and raw conversation with our 17-year-old son, Oakley.
Whether you experience anxiety yourself or you’re just worried about someone you love who does, this episode is a powerful gift from my family to you.
What Oakley shares based on his personal experience is life-changing.
You will hear Oakley describe two periods of anxiety and some pretty scary and overwhelming thoughts that rose up freshman and sophomore years of high school.</description></item><item><title>A Toolkit for Creating the Perfect Morning Routine | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010078/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010078/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, we’re discussing morning routines. This episode is very tactical and covers 5 simple but essential components of a perfect morning routine.
I’m really glad that you’re taking this topic seriously because every successful person you admire is serious about their mornings.
I sure am.
How you set up your day is typically how it ends up.
I love my morning routine so much that I call it the Million Dollar Morning, because it makes me feel like a million bucks for the rest of my day – and it creates a level of discipline in my life that helps me make millions of dollars too.</description></item><item><title>How to Find Your Purpose: Stop Searching and Do This Instead | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010079/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s episode is a masterclass on finding your purpose, listening to your gut, and never giving up (no matter what other people say).
So many of you write in asking for advice about purpose that I’ve decided to introduce you to a guest whose life story is the epitome of purpose.
You’re about to meet a woman who went from serving up stacks of pancakes at Denny’s to creating a billion-dollar product that would help millions of women around the world feel confident in their own skin.</description></item><item><title>The #1 Hack for Being More Productive Tomorrow | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010080/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010080/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, we are talking about the #1 thing you can do to make sure tomorrow is a productive and awesome day.
I’m sure you know the importance of a good morning routine.
But what you may not know is that a rock-solid morning routine – the kind that kickstarts you and your day for maximum focus and to feel more in control, calm, and like the rockstar that you are…</description></item><item><title>A Toolkit for Love: How to Find It, Keep It, and Let It Go | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010081/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010081/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you and I are getting a masterclass on the topic of love.
And it’s not what you think.
This is not an episode about relationships – it is an episode about YOUR relationship to love and how you can let more love into your life.
My mission with this episode is to inspire you to stop and consider the profound subject of love, how important it is, and why you deserve to feel more love in your daily life.</description></item><item><title>I Don’t Usually Share Advice Like This: 6 Lessons on Making Any Relationship Work | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010082/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010082/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, I’m getting brutally honest with you about relationships.
Our conversation begins with a question from a listener who asked me for advice on how to make your relationship go the distance in this messy modern world.
I’ve always shied away from giving relationship advice, mainly because after 26 years of marriage, I know the only secret is this: it takes a lot of consistent work.</description></item><item><title>Why Do I Have Few Memories From Childhood? Deepen Your Healing &amp; Find Answers With Dr. Nicole LePera | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010083/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010083/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you will learn how to deepen your healing by understanding how your parents may have created silent trauma that is still impacting you as an adult.
I want to introduce you to a woman who has had a really big impact on my own healing.
She is the renowned psychologist and #1 New York Times bestselling author, Dr. Nicole LePera, who you may also know as The Holistic Psychologist.</description></item><item><title>Take Control of Your Life: A Toolkit for Healing | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010084/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010084/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, I’m making the topic of trauma easier to understand by taking you step by step through my recent revelation that I was struggling with past trauma.
I was one of those people who thought I didn’t have trauma. And you may be like that too.
But if you have trouble managing emotions, expressing your feelings, dealing with upset, you go on edge easily, you have trouble focusing, or you struggle with anything like anxiety….</description></item><item><title>Mindset Reset Toolkit: How to Make Your Mind Work for You (Using Simple Neuroscience) | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010085/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010085/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you’ll learn how to use simple neuroscience to train your mind to start working for you.
The research, tools, and strategies you’ll learn in this episode are from an experience I created and taught to more than 250,000 students called “Mindset Reset.”
The fact is, your mindset is critical to your happiness, success, relationships, and fulfillment.
Listen to today’s episode and you’ll learn how to train your mind using this easy, science-backed method.</description></item><item><title>5 Essential Hacks I’m Using to Make New Habits Stick | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010086/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010086/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you’re about to learn how to make your new habits stick.
If you’ve struggled to be consistent with behavior change, you’re not alone. It’s easy to talk about habits. It’s a whole different thing to apply the science to your life.
You are not the problem.
The problem, when it comes to habits, is the lack of systems and hacks that help you stay consistent.</description></item><item><title>The Ultimate Toolkit for Creating New Habits: The Science Made Easy | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010087/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010087/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you’re going to learn exactly what you need to form new habits.
Even if you think you already know everything there is to know about habits, you probably still struggle to apply this knowledge and make change stick.
And if this topic is brand new to you, don’t worry; I have a way of explaining it that’s fun, and so simple even a 5-month-old puppy can understand it.</description></item><item><title>Feel like giving up? Before you say F*** It, listen to this. | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010088/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010088/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the pep talk you need.
Change is hard.
Which means you’re going to want to quit or give up.
I call those moments F*** It Moments.
Today’s episode is a little different because you’re going to hear me get in someone’s face who is about to throw in the towel on a big goal and a promise that she has made.
When you hear me coach her, it will be like I’m coaching you.</description></item><item><title>Goal Setting Toolkit: Why Behavior Change Often Fails &amp; How to Set the Right Goals for You | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010089/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010089/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode will help you set the right goals for you.
Goals matter. They make your life easier and they create a sense of purpose and meaning.
But most people don’t set goals the right way, which is why they fail before they even start.
That’s not going to be you.
This episode is a comprehensive toolkit that will help you set the goals that inspire you and make you feel excited about the year ahead.</description></item><item><title>The One Science-Backed Habit You Need in 2023 | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010090/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010090/</guid><description>Podcast Description I want this year to be the best year of your life.
So we’re going to talk about the one habit that researchers say has the biggest, overall impact on the quality of your life.
And that habit is learning to be kind and loving to yourself.
We all know we need to learn how to love ourselves, but no one has taught you HOW.
Until now.
In this episode, I am teaching you how to start loving yourself with a simple habit that you can add to your morning routine.</description></item><item><title>Brand New Research: 8 Simple &amp; Surprising Changes That Improve Your Life | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010091/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010091/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, I am sharing 8 brand new studies and exciting new research about simple changes supported by science that can help you improve your day to day life, like…
How to cut your gym time IN HALF and still get the same benefits.
The surprising sound researchers say will boost your mood for EIGHT hours.
The research on how mindfulness reduces your anxiety by 30% - the same as Lexapro.</description></item><item><title>3 Lessons From One of the Hardest Years of My Life | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010092/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever had one of those years where life seems to punch you in the face?
Where one thing after another knocks you down, over and over, until you start to feel like you are never getting back up.
Well, that was this past year for me.
People I trusted betrayed me. Plus, I was living 150 miles away from my husband and son, alone in Boston during the week for work.</description></item><item><title>A Toolkit for Families: Practical Wisdom That Makes You Closer to the People You Love | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010093/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010093/</guid><description>Podcast Description I’ve got a very special invitation for you today.
Grab a spot on the couch next to me and my family here in Southern Vermont.
Join our family as our three kids discuss all the parenting mistakes Chris and I made – and the things we did that built trust and brought us all closer.
I’m really excited and proud to share this with you, even though there are moments where my kids absolutely school me.</description></item><item><title>There Is Only One Thing You Should Do This Week | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010094/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010094/</guid><description>Podcast Description I know you’re busy. Which is why today’s message is the one thing you need to hear right now.
I need this message too. We all do.
Because there’s only one thing I want you to do this week:
NOTHING.
That’s right. I want you to do absolutely nothing.
No, I’m not smoking anything funny when I say this. I’m dead serious.
Hear me out.
There is an art and a science to doing nothing, and we need to put it into our daily lives.</description></item><item><title>I Didn’t Expect to Record This: I Want to Talk to You About tWitch’s Death | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010095/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 17:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010095/</guid><description>Podcast Description I’m checking in on you and me. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot going on in the world right now, and I am still reeling from the news that Stephen ‘tWitch’ Boss died from suicide.
If you had to ask me to list the 5 most positive people on the planet, The Rock would be #1, and tWitch would be #2.
Having lost too many friends and people I love to mental health challenges like depression, addiction, trauma, and hopelessness – all of who died from suicide – I’m just so heavy with emotion.</description></item><item><title>Hacking Dopamine &amp; Simple Ways to Improve Your Brain Health | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010096/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010096/</guid><description>Podcast Description I’ve lived with ADHD, dyslexia, and anxiety for most of my life.
And I’ve spent the last decade immersed in research around how to improve my mental health, but only recently did I realize there was a big missing piece to the puzzle when it came to being happier, more confident, and more present.
That’s taking care of the brain.
Your brain is your problem-solver. It’s your memory keeper.</description></item><item><title>3 Things You Need to Accept About Other People | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010097/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today you and I are digging into three things you must accept about other people.
It took me years to understand these truths.
It sounds horrible, but I always wondered, “What’s wrong with people? Why don’t they change?”
I know you can relate. Because today I’m taking your questions about trying to change other people.
You’re frustrated by the fact that your spouse or partner won’t exercise more. You get angry seeing how much money your daughter wastes going out every weekend.</description></item><item><title>Train Your Mind: How &amp; Why the Science of Synchronicity Can Improve Your Life | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010098/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever had such a powerful coincidence happen in your life that you think…
This must be a sign.
The person sitting next to you at an event turns out to be part of the team you’re interviewing with next week.
There is a hummingbird outside your apartment window on move-in day, and your grandmother always said she’d come back as one.
You’re sitting in your favorite coffee shop, thinking of someone you haven’t seen in a long time, and right at that moment, they text you.</description></item><item><title>You’ll Never Be Truly Happy Until You Start Doing This | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010099/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010099/</guid><description>Podcast Description I was lying in bed one morning, and all of a sudden it hit me…
If I ever want to be truly happy, I have to stop doing THIS.
So do you.
What is this thing we need to stop doing?
I call it the “Campaign of Misery.” In the background of your mind, there’s a campaign of misery running on a loop. And until you stop it, you will never experience the happiness, joy and contentment you deserve.</description></item><item><title>The “It” Factor: How to Hack Charisma &amp; Use Body Language to Boost Your Influence, Income, and Impact | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010100/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Buckle up and get ready to take notes because this episode is a masterclass.
The tools you’re about to learn will help you become more confident, influential, and even make more money.
Today, we’re talking about The “It” Factor.
Some people just seem to have IT, right?
When I think of The It Factor, people like Oprah, The Rock, Taylor Swift, the Dalai Lama, and Martin Luther King, Jr.</description></item><item><title>How Do I Learn to Love Myself, Really? | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010101/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Whatever you&amp;rsquo;re doing right now, stop and make time for this conversation.
Every single day, I get questions from listeners about self-love, self-hatred, and what it actually means to like yourself.
I understand why it’s confusing.
The topic of self-love is so broad, and there is very little actionable advice on how exactly you learn to like yourself, especially if you’ve spent your whole life being hard on yourself.</description></item><item><title>How to Have More Fun: A Guide to Enjoying the Holidays | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010102/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010102/</guid><description>Podcast Description I want you to get serious about inserting fun back into the holidays this year.
It might seem odd to have an entire conversation about fun. But here’s why we have to: most of us aren’t having any.
In fact, it’s gotten so bad that researchers have a term for it: “a fun drought.” You’re not alone – 97% of people want to have more fun.
And wouldn’t it be fabulous if you had an absolute blast with your family this holiday season?</description></item><item><title>The Secret to Stopping Fear &amp; Anxiety (That Actually Works) | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010103/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010103/</guid><description>Podcast Description I used simple research from Harvard Business School and UCLA to tame my fear of public speaking and become one of the most successful keynote speakers in the world.
I used this same tool to overcome my fear of flying.
If nerves or fear are holding you back from applying for that promotion, asking someone on a date, speaking up at a meeting, or traveling to another part of the world, this brain hack will change your life.</description></item><item><title>How to Improve Any Relationship: The 4 Attachment Styles You Need to Know &amp; Tools to Become More Secure | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010104/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010104/</guid><description>Podcast Description What if you could show up in any relationship feeling secure, exactly as you are?
You didn’t have to overthink every text you sent.
You wouldn’t have to play the dating games.
If somebody ghosted you, it wouldn’t be the end of the world.
Well I’m here to tell you today that you CAN be that person.
Meet the phenomenal Dr. Marisa Franco, New York Times bestselling author of “Platonic” and expert on attachment theory.</description></item><item><title>How to Manifest Anything You Want: 4 Simple Steps Backed by Neuroscience &amp; Olympic Athletes | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010105/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010105/</guid><description>Podcast Description According to neuroscience research, there are four major mistakes you make when it comes to manifesting.
Done correctly, manifesting is a mindset tool that elite athletes and the world’s most successful people use to perform at the highest levels and achieve remarkable goals.
Today, I’ll reveal those mistakes and more importantly, teach you how to manifest the right way.
This episode is all about the HOW.
If you love takeaways and tools, you’ll eat this up.</description></item><item><title>Your Dreams Are Not a Joke: It’s Time to Dream Big Again &amp; 3 Ways to Get Started | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010106/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010106/</guid><description>Podcast Description THIS is the pep talk you need to hear right now.
I’m showing up with a level of intensity in a way you’ve never heard me before.
We are talking about you and your big dreams.
No matter what you&amp;rsquo;re going through in life, your dreams are alive and well and they are waiting for you to wake up and turn toward them.
If you’re not ready for some Mel Robbins inspirational firepower, bookmark this for another day.</description></item><item><title>The Power of a Pause: Do This When Life Disappoints You | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010107/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010107/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the inspiration and wisdom you need to hear today.
It’s been quite a week and it’s only Monday.
I woke up yesterday and was so sick, I had to cancel some really important work and personal commitments.
Cue: the disappointment, the anxiety of upsetting others, and my own sadness that life was not going as I had planned.
This is one of those episodes that I recorded for myself and for you.</description></item><item><title>2 Secrets to Handling a Narcissist: A Toolkit for Dealing With Toxic Behavior at Work, Dating, Marriage, and Family (With World-Renowned Dr. Ramani) | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010108/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010108/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do I know if I’m in a relationship with a narcissist? Are certain personalities more drawn to narcissists? Can I heal if I was raised by a narcissist? How do I handle narcissists at work? Why do I keep attracting narcissists into my life? How can I keep a narcissist in my life… and not go crazy?
And, most of all:
What EXACTLY do I do to cope with narcissists?</description></item><item><title>Why Is Adult Friendship So Hard? 5 Lies You Tell Yourself &amp; the Truth You Need to Hear | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010109/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010109/</guid><description>Podcast Description A survival guide to adult friendship: how to find your people, have more fun, and create meaningful friendships as an adult.
This is the topic you and everyone else are thinking about.
From making new friends to staying connected to your old ones, to the thing that’s really hard: what do you do when your friendships start to fade?
This is something I’ve been dying to talk to you about because I am right here, shoulder to shoulder with you, feeling lonely, left out, and wondering… Where did all my friends go?</description></item><item><title>Why Am I So Triggered? 3 Steps to Control Your Emotions &amp; Rewire Your Response to Stress | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010110/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s conversation is required listening for everyone.
We are going to blow the lid off of emotional triggers.
Let’s get to the bottom of why you and I react the way we do, and more importantly, learn simple ways to take control of our emotions.
It doesn’t matter where you live, how you grew up, or even if you’re a freakin’ saint to everyone else, I know you have something that triggers you.</description></item><item><title>Steal This From My Therapist: 2 Steps to Flip a Bad Day Into an Amazing One | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010111/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010111/</guid><description>Podcast Description You know those days when you just feel “off”? Well, last week, both my friend Amy and I were having bad days.
Thankfully, I had just had an appointment with my amazing therapist that morning.
So, as Amy and I started to talk about why we didn’t “feel like ourselves,” I got this crazy idea that maybe we should invite YOU to join us as the conversation started to unfold.</description></item><item><title>5 Signs You’re Dealing With a Narcissist &amp; How to Protect Yourself | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010112/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Narcissism is on the rise and you need to learn how to spot it in other people and have tools to protect yourself.
We all know those people who constantly turn a conversation toward themselves, who only call you when they want something, and who have a way of making everything someone else’s fault.
Well, guess what? Turns out narcissism goes far beyond that.
I’m telling you right now, even if you THINK you know what a narcissist is, you need to listen.</description></item><item><title>How to Let Go: 2 Simple Ways to Find Clarity &amp; Move On | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010113/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010113/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do you know if the thing you’re holding on to is something you should keep fighting for or if it’s time to let go?
Phenomenal question. I’ve got the answer.
The truth is, most of us never let go.
You spend a lot of time adding things into your life – new projects, new relationships, new stuff – but when was the last time you subtracted something?</description></item><item><title>The Truth About Anxiety and How To Heal It: Tools for Anxiety From a Neuroscientist MD | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010114/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Everything you think about anxiety is wrong.
Yes, we’re starting there.
And yes, we’re going deep.
I know that this episode will change your life. It has done the same for mine.
It’s not a secret that I’ve struggled with anxiety for pretty much my whole life. I swear I came out of the womb in a full-blown panic attack, and I was just warming up for a life of worry on a very elite, professional level.</description></item><item><title>Motivation Is Garbage | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010115/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010115/</guid><description>Podcast Description The biggest secret to getting the life you want is understanding 3 words I hope you never forget:
Motivation. Is. Garbage.
Right now, think about something you want to change or improve.
I bet you know WHAT you want to change – and what you need to do.
But the 100 million dollar question is: HOW?
How do you get started?
And how do you keep going even when you don’t feel like it?</description></item><item><title>2 Ways to Take Your Power Back When You Feel Insecure | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010116/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010116/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do you find your power when life knocks you down?
What do you do when you are in the middle of an emotional tsunami?
How do you respond when the universe is testing you?
This is the ultimate episode about resilience, confidence, and taking your power back.
Yes, you can take control with simple tools whenever you feel that insecurity spiral kick in. You can pick yourself up, shake off the sh*t, and you can make it a win for you.</description></item><item><title>3 Simple Steps to Change Your Life | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010117/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010117/</guid><description>Podcast Description You can change your life. Period.
My mission in this episode is to remind you of who you are and help you tap into the power inside of you. I want you to see something bigger for your life this year. I want to empower you with 3 simple steps you can take to make that vision a reality.
In this episode, you will learn the 3 steps I used to reinvent every aspect of my life over the past two years.</description></item><item><title>Trailer | The Mel Robbins Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7535010118/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7535010118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mel Robbins has spent the last 10 years helping millions of people change their lives. In The Mel Robbins Podcast, Mel shares the relatable stories and science-backed tools she’s built her career around to inspire, motivate, and empower you to create a better life. Starting October 6th, Mel is here for you twice a week with new episodes every Monday and Thursday.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>