<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>How to Keep Time on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/how-to-keep-time/</link><description>Recent content in How to Keep Time on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/how-to-keep-time/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to Leave Work Time at Work | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590057/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Before laptops allowed us to take the office home and smartphones could light up with notifications at any hour, work time and “life” time had clearer boundaries. Today, work is not done exclusively in the workplace, and that makes it harder to leave work at work. Co-hosts Becca Rashid and Ian Bogost examine the habits that shrink our available time, and Ignacio Sánchez Prado, a professor of Latin American Studies at Washington University in St.</description></item><item><title>How to Look Busy | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Many of us complain about being too busy—and about not having enough time to do the things we really want to do. But has busyness become an excuse for our inability to focus on what matters? According to Neeru Paharia, a marketing professor at Arizona State University, time is a sort of luxury good—the more of it you have, the more valuable you are. But her research also revealed that, for many Americans, having less time and being busy can be a status symbol for others to notice.</description></item><item><title>How to Waste Time | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Co-hosts Becca Rashid and Ian Bogost explore our relationship with time and how to reclaim it. Why is it so important to be productive? Why can it feel like there’s never enough time in a day? Why are so many of us conditioned to believe that being more productive makes us better people? Author Oliver Burkman offers some insights. This episode was co-hosted by Becca Rashid and Ian Bogost.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: How to Keep Time | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why can it feel like there’s never enough time in a day, and why are so many of us conditioned to believe that being more productive makes us better people? On How to Keep Time, co-hosts Becca Rashid and contributing writer Ian Bogost talk with social scientists, authors, philosophers, and theoretical physicists to learn more about time and how to reclaim it. How to Keep Time launches December 2023.</description></item><item><title>‘Everyone Used to be Nicer,’ And Other Persistent Myths | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590004/</guid><description>Podcast Description A lot of people are plagued by the feeling that society used to be better, that neighbors were more helpful, that strangers once talked to you. Some people channel that belief into political action, as in the Make America Great Again movement. A new study explains why the sense that people and the culture have gotten worse is a psychological illusion. This special episode features Hanna Rosin, the host of Radio Atlantic.</description></item><item><title>How to Not Go It Alone | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590005/</guid><description>Podcast Description The values of individualism that encourage us to go it alone are in constant tension with the desire for community that many people crave. But when attempting to do things on our own, we may miss out on the joys of coming together. This season’s finale conversation features writer Mia Birdsong, who highlights the cultural and philosophical roots of Americans’ struggle to build community. In a culture pushing us to put our own oxygen mask on first, Mia argues for the quiet radicalness of asking for help and showing up for others.</description></item><item><title>How to Know Your Neighbors | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are commitment issues impacting our ability to connect with the people who live around us? Relationship building may involve a commitment to the belief that neighbors are worthy of getting to know. In this episode of How to Talk to People, author Pete Davis makes the case for building relationships with your neighbors and wider community and offers some practical advice for how to take the first steps. This episode was produced by Rebecca Rashid and is hosted by Julie Beck.</description></item><item><title>What Makes a House a Home | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590007/</guid><description>Podcast Description What motivated two families to engage in the organized chaos of shared living and how did they learn to talk through, and shape, new expectations for their family life at home? In this episode of How to Talk to People, we hear from Deborah Tepley and Luke Jackson, who remember when they first asked their best friends to buy a house with them. The Flemings—soon to be expecting their first child—didn’t hesitate to say yes.</description></item><item><title>What do we owe our friends? | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590008/</guid><description>Podcast Description The terms of friendship are both voluntary and vague—yet people often find themselves disappointed by unmet expectations. In this episode of How to Talk to People, we explore how to have the difficult conversations that can make our friendships richer and how to set expectations in a relationship defined by choice. This episode was produced by Rebecca Rashid and is hosted by Julie Beck. Editing by Jocelyn Frank and Claudine Ebeid.</description></item><item><title>The Infrastructure of Community | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590009/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Coffee shops, churches, libraries, and concert venues are all shared spaces where mingling can take place. Yet the hustle and bustle of modern social life can pose challenges to relationship-building—even in spaces designed for exactly that. In this episode of How to Talk to People, we analyze how American efficiency culture holds us back from connecting in public, whether social spaces create a culture of interaction, and what it takes to actively participate in a community.</description></item><item><title>How to Make Small Talk | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Making small talk can be hard—especially when you’re not sure whether you’re doing it well. But conversations are a central part of relationship-building. In this first episode of How to Talk to People, we explore the psychological barriers to making good small talk and unravel the complexities of the mutual discomfort that comes with talking to people we don’t know well. The social scientist Ty Tashiro and the hairstylists Erin Derosa and Mimi Craft help us understand what it means to integrate awkwardness into our pursuit of relationships.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: How to Talk to People | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590011/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590011/</guid><description>Podcast Description On How to Talk to People we explore the barriers to relationship building and why—in a world of endless potential for connection—so many people still feel alone. From the struggle to prioritize non-romantic relationships, to just feeling uncertain of what to talk about with strangers, host Julie Beck and producer Rebecca Rashid unravel the complexities of putting yourself out there—in hopes of revealing the rewards of showing up. Talk to How to Talk to People—by “talk,” we mean write to us—at howtopodcast@theatlantic.</description></item><item><title>Trailer: How to Talk to People | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590035/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590035/</guid><description>Podcast Description On How to Talk to People we explore the barriers to relationship building and why—in a world of endless potential for connection—so many people still feel alone. From the struggle to prioritize non-romantic relationships, to just feeling uncertain of what to talk about with strangers, host Julie Beck and producer Rebecca Rashid unravel the complexities of putting yourself out there—in hopes of revealing the rewards of showing up. Talk to How to Talk to People—by “talk,” we mean write to us—at howtopodcast@theatlantic.</description></item><item><title>Introducing Holy Week | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Holy Week: The story of a revolution undone. The assassination of Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. on April 4, 1968, is often recounted as a conclusion to a powerful era of civil rights in America, but how did this hero’s murder come to be the stitching used to tie together a narrative of victory? The week that followed his killing was one of the most fiery, disruptive, and revolutionary, and is nearly forgotten.</description></item><item><title>A New Formula for Happiness | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590013/</guid><description>Podcast Description We often follow a misguided formula for happiness—pushing us toward material wealth and other worldly successes. But when our expectations set us down the wrong path, it may be time to reorient ourselves around something new: universal happiness principles we can practice at any age. In our finale episode of this season, a conversation with psychiatrist Robert Waldinger provides a scientific insight into key elements for happy living, whatever your age.</description></item><item><title>How To Build a Happy Life: The Right Choices in Parenting | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590036/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590036/</guid><description>Podcast Description The mandates of modern parenting can be dizzying. But in the effort to optimize our parenting, we may lose sight of the values we hope to impart to our children—and the skills necessary for individual decision making. A conversation with economist Emily Oster helps with understanding the nuances of choice-making in parenthood. This episode was produced by Rebecca Rashid and is hosted by Arthur Brooks. Editing by A.C. Valdez and Claudine Ebeid.</description></item><item><title>The Right Choices in Parenting | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590014/</guid><description>Podcast Description The mandates of modern parenting can be dizzying. But in the effort to optimize our parenting, we may lose sight of the values we hope to impart to our children—and the skills necessary for individual decision making. A conversation with economist Emily Oster helps with understanding the nuances of choice-making in parenthood. This episode was produced by Rebecca Rashid and is hosted by Arthur Brooks. Editing by A.C. Valdez and Claudine Ebeid.</description></item><item><title>How To Build a Happy Life: Subtraction as a Solution | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590037/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590037/</guid><description>Podcast Description From how we build our cities to how we shop, it can seem as though our natural human tendency is to add. But a culture of accumulation may be exactly what holds us back from the simple solution in front of us: taking things away. University of Virginia professor Leidy Klotz helps us analyze the benefits of subtraction and how less may create the space for what we truly desire.</description></item><item><title>Subtraction as a Solution | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590015/</guid><description>Podcast Description From how we build our cities to how we shop, it can seem as though our natural human tendency is to add. But a culture of accumulation may be exactly what holds us back from the simple solution in front of us: taking things away. University of Virginia professor Leidy Klotz helps us analyze the benefits of subtraction and how less may create the space for what we truly desire.</description></item><item><title>How To Build a Happy Life: Spend Time on What You Value | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590038/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590038/</guid><description>Podcast Description We try to use our time wisely—both at work and in leisure—but we often waste it. We may blame work for stripping us of recreation, but when valuable free time comes around, we can often revert back to more work. What explains the gap between how we use our time and how we want to use our time? A conversation with Harvard Business School professor Ashley Whillans helps us analyze our complex relationship with time and how to orient our time use around what we value.</description></item><item><title>How to Spend Time on What You Value | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590016/</guid><description>Podcast Description We try to use our time wisely—both at work and in leisure—but we often waste it. We may blame work for stripping us of recreation, but when valuable free time comes around, we can often revert back to more work. What explains the gap between how we use our time and how we want to use our time? A conversation with Harvard Business School professor Ashley Whillans helps us analyze our complex relationship with time and how to orient our time use around what we value.</description></item><item><title>How To Build a Happy Life: The Complexities of Human Love | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590039/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dating apps show us what we want—a relationship—without always accurately reflecting the experience of it. Our expectation that tech will create anything more than opportunities for social connectedness may overlook the hard work of coexisting with another human being. A conversation with University of Kansas social psychologist Omri Gillath helps us parse the divide between what tech promises and how it satisfies our emotional needs. This episode was produced by Rebecca Rashid and is hosted by Arthur Brooks.</description></item><item><title>The Complexities of Human Love | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dating apps show us what we want—a relationship—without always accurately reflecting the experience of it. Our expectation that tech will create anything more than opportunities for social connectedness may overlook the hard work of coexisting with another human being. A conversation with University of Kansas social psychologist Omri Gillath helps us parse the divide between what tech promises and how it satisfies our emotional needs. This episode was produced by Rebecca Rashid and is hosted by Arthur Brooks.</description></item><item><title>How To Build a Happy Life: When Virtues Become Vices | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590040/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590040/</guid><description>Podcast Description When the behaviors we thought would make us happy don’t, we’re forced to bridge the gap between where we are and where we want to be. But our happiness goals are often stifled by the disease of addiction—and its complex neurochemical influence on our desires. A conversation with psychiatrist Anna Lembke helps us understand the gap between the cravings that drive us and the happiness we seek. This episode was produced by Rebecca Rashid and is hosted by Arthur Brooks.</description></item><item><title>When Virtues Become Vices | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590018/</guid><description>Podcast Description When the behaviors we thought would make us happy don’t, we’re forced to bridge the gap between where we are and where we want to be. But our happiness goals are often stifled by the disease of addiction—and its complex neurochemical influence on our desires. A conversation with psychiatrist Anna Lembke helps us understand the gap between the cravings that drive us and the happiness we seek. This episode was produced by Rebecca Rashid and is hosted by Arthur Brooks.</description></item><item><title>How To Build a Happy Life: When Expectations Don’t Meet Reality | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590041/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 12:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590041/</guid><description>Podcast Description In our pursuit of a happy life, we build, we structure, and we plan. Often, we follow conventional wisdom and strategize. But what happens when our plans fall through and expectations don’t meet reality—when the things that should make us happy don’t? In season 3 of our How To series, Atlantic happiness correspondent Arthur Brooks and producer Rebecca Rashid seek to navigate the unexpected curves on the path to personal happiness—with data-driven insights and a healthy dose of introspection.</description></item><item><title>How To Season 3: When Expectations Don’t Meet Reality | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 12:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590019/</guid><description>Podcast Description In our pursuit of a happy life, we build, we structure, and we plan. Often, we follow conventional wisdom and strategize. But what happens when our plans fall through and expectations don’t meet reality—when the things that should make us happy don’t? In season 3 of our How To series, Atlantic happiness correspondent Arthur Brooks and producer Rebecca Rashid seek to navigate the unexpected curves on the path to personal happiness—with data-driven insights and a healthy dose of introspection.</description></item><item><title>How to Forgive Ourselves for What We Can’t Change | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590020/</guid><description>Podcast Description When we regret our past, it can feel like we’re incapable of changing our future. But it may be our past “mistakes” that help us realize there is room to evolve. In the finale episode of How to Start Over, we explore how regret can be a catalyst of change, what holds us back from self-forgiveness, and how to reconcile our past mistakes—and move forward for good. Conversations with Shai Davidai, an assistant professor at the Columbia Business School, and forgiveness expert Everett Worthington help us identify whether regret hinders our growth or serves as a catalyst of change.</description></item><item><title>How to Start Over: Forgive Ourselves for What We Can’t Change | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590042/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590042/</guid><description>Podcast Description When we regret our past, it can feel like we’re incapable of changing our future. But it may be our past “mistakes” that help us realize there is room to evolve. In the finale episode of How to Start Over, we explore how regret can be a catalyst of change, what holds us back from self-forgiveness, and how to reconcile our past mistakes—and move forward for good. Conversations with Shai Davidai, an assistant professor at the Columbia Business School, and forgiveness expert Everett Worthington help us identify whether regret hinders our growth or serves as a catalyst of change.</description></item><item><title>How to Start Over: The Misgivings of Friend-Making | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590043/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 12:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590043/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the post-social-distancing era, some of us can’t remember how to make a new friend. But for many, making friends has always been a challenge—left as an unfulfilled desire without any clear course of action. In this episode of How to Start Over, we explore the barriers to friendship formation in adulthood, how to navigate conflict, and why starting over as a better friend begins with getting out of our own heads.</description></item><item><title>The Misgivings of Friend-Making | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 12:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590021/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the post-social-distancing era, some of us can’t remember how to make a new friend. But for many, making friends has always been a challenge—left as an unfulfilled desire without any clear course of action. In this episode of How to Start Over, we explore the barriers to friendship formation in adulthood, how to navigate conflict, and why starting over as a better friend begins with getting out of our own heads.</description></item><item><title>How to Start Over: When Can a Marriage Be Saved? | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590044/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Romantic relationships often show us the deep divide between expectations and reality. For any relationship struggling to overcome conflict, the first step to starting over may be identifying how your vision of marriage is out of step with your partner’s. In this episode of How to Start Over, we explore why some marriages can withstand conflict, why most couples struggle to validate their partner’s needs, and how to think about when a breakup is in order—by better understanding why the relationship is struggling.</description></item><item><title>When Can a Marriage Be Saved? | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Romantic relationships often show us the deep divide between expectations and reality. For any relationship struggling to overcome conflict, the first step to starting over may be identifying how your vision of marriage is out of step with your partner’s. In this episode of How to Start Over, we explore why some marriages can withstand conflict, why most couples struggle to validate their partner’s needs, and how to think about when a breakup is in order—by better understanding why the relationship is struggling.</description></item><item><title>How to Start Over: When Partnership Is Not the Destination | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590045/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590045/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a society dominated by romantic couples, it can be hard to accept your unpartnered state for what it is. But for the “single at heart,” the desire for partnership is nonexistent—replaced with a sense of self-sufficiency, satisfaction, and robust friendships. In this episode of How to Start Over, we explore misconceptions about singlehood and what explains a broad perception of it as an unwelcome fate. We also talk about how social and economic structures orient themselves around couples, and discuss arguments for why stigmas against solo living and single life are long overdue for a change.</description></item><item><title>When Partnership Is Not the Destination | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590023/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a society dominated by romantic couples, it can be hard to accept your unpartnered state for what it is. But for the “single at heart,” the desire for partnership is nonexistent—replaced with a sense of self-sufficiency, satisfaction, and robust friendships. In this episode of How to Start Over, we explore misconceptions about singlehood and what explains a broad perception of it as an unwelcome fate. We also talk about how social and economic structures orient themselves around couples, and discuss arguments for why stigmas against solo living and single life are long overdue for a change.</description></item><item><title>'Parents Are Not All Good and All Bad' | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Some families have the frictionless ease of unconditional love and understanding, but for many the stalemate of family tensions can be insurmountable. In this episode of How to Start Over, we explore what can be done to evaluate the dynamics in lifelong family relationships, find ways to manage our emotional response when tensions boil over, and analyze what it means to change a parent-child relationship as an adult. This episode was produced by Rebecca Rashid and is hosted by Olga Khazan.</description></item><item><title>How to Start Over: 'Parents Are Not All Good and All Bad' | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Some families have the frictionless ease of unconditional love and understanding, but for many the stalemate of family tensions can be insurmountable. In this episode of How to Start Over, we explore what can be done to evaluate the dynamics in lifelong family relationships, find ways to manage our emotional response when tensions boil over, and analyze what it means to change a parent-child relationship as an adult. This episode was produced by Rebecca Rashid and is hosted by Olga Khazan.</description></item><item><title>How to Start Over: When You Think It's Too Late | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590047/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590047/</guid><description>Podcast Description A professional change in midlife can provide a much-needed reset—at least when you’re looking for a career that more closely aligns with your passion. But finding what you love, especially once you’ve gone down an entirely different path, can feel impossible. How do we redirect our efforts away from what we’re used to and toward what we want to do? In this episode of How to Start Over, we explore what impacts our decision making in midlife, whether midlife malaise explains our need for change, and how to know if a professional change is worth it.</description></item><item><title>Starting Over When You Think It's Too Late | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590025/</guid><description>Podcast Description A professional change in midlife can provide a much-needed reset—at least when you’re looking for a career that more closely aligns with your passion. But finding what you love, especially once you’ve gone down an entirely different path, can feel impossible. How do we redirect our efforts away from what we’re used to and toward what we want to do? In this episode of How to Start Over, we explore what impacts our decision making in midlife, whether midlife malaise explains our need for change, and how to know if a professional change is worth it.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: How To Start Over | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590026/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 13:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590026/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this series, Atlantic staff writer Olga Khazan analyzes what it takes to change our relationships, our work, and our perspective—with a practical approach to one of life’s greatest mysteries: how to start over. Change can be really hard. Inertia is powerful, mortgages and marriages are long-term, and personality traits can feel pretty hardwired. But we’re in an era characterized by change. This series is your guide to starting over in the ways you’ve always wanted, why change is so hard, and whether it is, sometimes, overrated.</description></item><item><title>Trailer: How To Start Over | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590048/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 13:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590048/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this series, Atlantic staff writer Olga Khazan analyzes what it takes to change our relationships, our work, and our perspective—with a practical approach to one of life’s greatest mysteries: how to start over. Change can be really hard. Inertia is powerful, mortgages and marriages are long-term, and personality traits can feel pretty hardwired. But we’re in an era characterized by change. This series is your guide to starting over in the ways you’ve always wanted, why change is so hard, and whether it is, sometimes, overrated.</description></item><item><title>How to Build a Happy Life: How to Identify What You Enjoy | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590027/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590027/</guid><description>Podcast Description In adulthood, many of us are forced to recalibrate our relationship with joy. As responsibilities multiply exponentially, time grows limited, and challenges mount, it becomes harder to make time for fun, let alone remember what it feels like. As we explore the key components of happiness—pleasure, joy, and satisfaction—we ask the foundational question: What really brings me joy? In this special-edition, bonus episode of How to Build a Happy Life, the psychotherapist and Atlantic contributing writer Lori Gottlieb demystifies one of the vital components of a happy life: enjoyment.</description></item><item><title>How to Build a Happy Life: Identify What You Enjoy | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590049/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590049/</guid><description>Podcast Description In adulthood, many of us are forced to recalibrate our relationship with joy. As responsibilities multiply exponentially, time grows limited, and challenges mount, it becomes harder to make time for fun, let alone remember what it feels like. As we explore the key components of happiness—pleasure, joy, and satisfaction—we ask the foundational question: What really brings me joy? In this special-edition, bonus episode of How to Build a Happy Life, the psychotherapist and Atlantic contributing writer Lori Gottlieb demystifies one of the vital components of a happy life: enjoyment.</description></item><item><title>How to Build a Happy Life: How to Live When You’re In Pain | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590028/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590028/</guid><description>Podcast Description As we wind down this series, a paradox remains in our pursuit of happiness—joy comes to those who have known pain. In order to overcome struggle—breakups, illness, even death—we must first accept and acknowledge its inevitability. Exploring the darkness of our suffering may seem counterintuitive, but often it’s the only way to see the light. In this week’s episode, Arthur C. Brooks sits down with BJ Miller, a palliative-care physician, to uncover how we can face our deepest fears, why we should accept our natural limitations as human beings, and how to make peace with the ebb and flow of joy and suffering in human life—an experience we all share.</description></item><item><title>How to Build a Happy Life: Live When You’re In Pain | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590050/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590050/</guid><description>Podcast Description As we wind down this series, a paradox remains in our pursuit of happiness—joy comes to those who have known pain. In order to overcome struggle—breakups, illness, even death—we must first accept and acknowledge its inevitability. Exploring the darkness of our suffering may seem counterintuitive, but often it’s the only way to see the light. In this week’s episode, Arthur C. Brooks sits down with BJ Miller, a palliative-care physician, to uncover how we can face our deepest fears, why we should accept our natural limitations as human beings, and how to make peace with the ebb and flow of joy and suffering in human life—an experience we all share.</description></item><item><title>How to Build a Happy Life: Find the Secret to Meaningful Work | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590051/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590051/</guid><description>Podcast Description The road to purposeful work is paved with good intentions; but for many, happiness at work can feel like a hopeless cause. What if the secret to happiness at work has less to do with our extrinsic motivations—money, rewards, and personal gain—and more to do with our intrinsic motivations—the meaningful relationships we build, and the ability to be in service to those who need it? In this episode of How to Build a Happy Life, we’ll explore workplace practices to live out purpose-driven principles.</description></item><item><title>How to Build a Happy Life: How to Find the Secret to Meaningful Work | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590029/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590029/</guid><description>Podcast Description The road to purposeful work is paved with good intentions; but for many, happiness at work can feel like a hopeless cause. What if the secret to happiness at work has less to do with our extrinsic motivations—money, rewards, and personal gain—and more to do with our intrinsic motivations—the meaningful relationships we build, and the ability to be in service to those who need it? In this episode of How to Build a Happy Life, we’ll explore workplace practices to live out purpose-driven principles.</description></item><item><title>How to Build a Happy Life: How to Know That You Know Nothing | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590030/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590030/</guid><description>Podcast Description If there’s one thing we might regret at the end of life, it’s that we missed out on moments that mattered—not because we weren’t physically there, but because our mind wandered off to some unknown place. In this episode of How to Build a Happy Life, we explore why it’s uniquely challenging to “live in the moment,” how we limit our own curiosity by assuming we know best, and why the illusion of stability pulls us from living every day fully, and in the moment.</description></item><item><title>How to Build a Happy Life: Know That You Know Nothing | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590052/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590052/</guid><description>Podcast Description If there’s one thing we might regret at the end of life, it’s that we missed out on moments that mattered—not because we weren’t physically there, but because our mind wandered off to some unknown place. In this episode of How to Build a Happy Life, we explore why it’s uniquely challenging to “live in the moment,” how we limit our own curiosity by assuming we know best, and why the illusion of stability pulls us from living every day fully, and in the moment.</description></item><item><title>How to Build a Happy Life: Don't Be Your Own Worst Enemy | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590053/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590053/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the social-media age, we curate images of our lives on a screen—making it especially easy to translate images of perfection as the image of oneself. But the pressure to pretend we are perfect is exactly the thing holding us back from experiencing the happiness we seek—and limiting our ability to be our whole, authentic selves. In this episode of How to Build a Happy Life, we’ll define what we mean by “authenticity” and explore the psychological underpinnings of our ego-driven identities.</description></item><item><title>How to Build a Happy Life: How Not to Be Your Own Worst Enemy | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590031/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590031/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the social-media age, we curate images of our lives on a screen—making it especially easy to translate images of perfection as the image of oneself. But the pressure to pretend we are perfect is exactly the thing holding us back from experiencing the happiness we seek—and limiting our ability to be our whole, authentic selves. In this episode of How to Build a Happy Life, we’ll define what we mean by “authenticity” and explore the psychological underpinnings of our ego-driven identities.</description></item><item><title>How to Build a Happy Life: How to Know You're Lonely | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590032/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 15:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590032/</guid><description>Podcast Description The irony in loneliness is that we all share in the experience of it. In this episode of How to Build a Happy Life, we sit down to discuss isolated living and Americans’ collective struggle to create a relationship-centric life. As we continue along our journey to happiness we ask: How can I build my life around people? This episode features Dr. Vivek H. Murthy, the U.S. Surgeon General.</description></item><item><title>How to Build a Happy Life: Know You're Lonely | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590054/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 15:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590054/</guid><description>Podcast Description The irony in loneliness is that we all share in the experience of it. In this episode of How to Build a Happy Life, we sit down to discuss isolated living and Americans’ collective struggle to create a relationship-centric life. As we continue along our journey to happiness we ask: How can I build my life around people? This episode features Dr. Vivek H. Murthy, the U.S. Surgeon General.</description></item><item><title>How to Build a Happy Life: Be Self-Aware | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590055/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Only when we admit we have a problem can we begin to find solutions. On the first episode of How To Build a Happy Life, we explore the neuroscience of emotional management, practices that help us befriend our inner monologue, and challenges to getting in touch with our feelings. Our journey to happier living starts with the question: How do I feel right now? This episode features Dan Harris, former ABC News anchor, meditation expert and founder of Ten Percent Happier.</description></item><item><title>How to Build a Happy Life: How to Be Self-Aware | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590033/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Only when we admit we have a problem can we begin to find solutions. On the first episode of How To Build a Happy Life, we explore the neuroscience of emotional management, practices that help us befriend our inner monologue, and challenges to getting in touch with our feelings. Our journey to happier living starts with the question: How do I feel right now? This episode features Dan Harris, former ABC News anchor, meditation expert and founder of Ten Percent Happier.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: How to Build a Happy Life | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590034/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 13:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to How to Build a Happy Life! In this series, host Arthur Brooks digs into research and offers tools to help you live more joyfully. Join us for deep conversations with psychologists, experts, and friends of The Atlantic&amp;rsquo;s Chief Happiness Correspondent. For more info, visit www.theatlantic.com/happy Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trailer: How to Build a Happy Life | How to Keep Time</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1273590056/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 13:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1273590056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to How to Build a Happy Life! In this series, host Arthur Brooks digs into research and offers tools to help you live more joyfully. Join us for deep conversations with psychologists, experts, and friends of The Atlantic&amp;rsquo;s Chief Happiness Correspondent. For more info, visit www.theatlantic.com/happy Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>