<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Football Weekly on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/football-weekly/</link><description>Recent content in Football Weekly on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 12:24:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/football-weekly/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Liverpool and Manchester City drop points in the title race – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680296/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 12:24:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680296/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Barney Ronay and Jonathan Liew as Manchester City draw once again and Liverpool fail to make chances count against Manchester United. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Newcastle crash out on a dramatic European night – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 13:46:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Nicky Bandini, Archie Rhind-Tutt and Lars Sivertsen as Newcastle finish last in their Champions League group. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Manchester United crash out of Europe after latest limp display – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 12:08:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Mark Langdon, Jonathan Fadugba and Philippe Auclair to react to Manchester United’s worst every Champions League campaign. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>An episode from Women’s Football Weekly: Arsenal thrash Chelsea to blow title race wide open | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 16:14:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680003/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a massive weekend of WSL action, we wanted to bring the latest episode of our sister podcast where Faye Carruthers, Sophie Downey, Emma Sanders and Chris Paouros round up all the action and look ahead a busy weekend of cup action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Manchester United lurch back into crisis and are Villa in title race? – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 12:19:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by John Brewin, Troy Townsend and Jordan Jarrett-Bryan as Bournemouth win their first ever game at Old Trafford and Aston Villa find themselves just two points off top spot. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Everton leap clear of the relegation zone and Spurs slump – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680005/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 13:08:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Robyn Cowen is joined by Paul MacInnes, Nedum Onuoha and Sanny Rudravajhala as Everton’s fine run of form continues with a 3-0 win over Newcastle. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Fortress Villa Park and McTominay magic – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 12:41:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Robyn Cowen is joined by Jonathan Liew, Will Unwin and Nooruddean Choudry as Manchester United beat Chelsea, while Aston Villa emerge as potential title contenders. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Goals galore on a thrilling weekend in the Premier League – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 15:15:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Robyn Cowen is joined by Jonathan Wilson, Lucy Ward, and Barney Ronay to discuss all the weekend’s Premier League action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A chaotic Istanbul classic and Arsenal’s easy night – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 12:26:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Mark Langdon and Lars Sivertsen as Manchester United throw away a two-goal lead twice to leave themselves in a perilous Champions League position. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>PSG reignite the handball debate and Wolves v VAR – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 11:28:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini and Philippe Auclair as a controversial handball means Newcastle are denied a vital win. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Arsenal go top and a tribute to Terry Venables – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 12:21:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, John Brewin and Troy Townsend to review the weekend’s Premier League action and pay tribute to Terry Venables. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Premier League returns and Euro 2024 chat – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 14:55:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Liew and Nicky Bandini to preview the weekend’s Premier League games. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>England and Italy qualify but what to make of their campaigns? – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680012/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 14:52:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Wilson, Lars Sivertson, and Nicky Bandini to discuss the Euro 2024 qualifiers. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Everton deducted 10 points and Wales falter in Armenia – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 13:41:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Paul Watson, Mark Langdon, and Elis James to talk about Everton and the Euro qualifiers. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Euro 2024 qualifying preview and Man Utd shake-up – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680014/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 14:40:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, John Brewin and Nedum Onuoha to preview the upcoming European qualifiers. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Will anyone catch Leicester and Ipswich in the Championship? – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 14:38:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by George Elek, Sanny Rudravajhala, and Ben Fisher to round up what’s been going on across the EFL. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Goals galore at Chelsea and Manchester United lead form table – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 14:04:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Lars Sivertson, and Robyn Cowen to discuss all of the weekend’s Premier League action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chaos in Copenhagen and Arsenal’s easy night – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 12:52:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Mark Langdon and Archie Rhind-Tutt discuss Manchester United’s latest Champions League setback. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dortmund do double over Newcastle and Milan beat PSG – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 13:54:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Fadugba, and Nicky Bandini to discuss all of Tuesday night’s Champions League action and Monday night’s Premier League game. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Arsenal feel hard done by and Luton hold Liverpool – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 15:34:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jordan Jarrett-Bryan, and Jonathan Wilson to discuss all the weekend’s Premier League action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Manchester United and Arsenal crash out of Carabao Cup – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:02:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Liew and John Brewin to ask if time is running out for Erik ten Hag. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bellingham bosses the clásico but how long can he keep this up? – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 13:28:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini, Sid Lowe and Lars Sivertsen to round up the biggest stories from across Europe. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Manchester United left feeling blue after City boss derby – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 13:22:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Wilson and Will Unwin as City comfortably beat United in the game of the weekend. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dortmund rock Newcastle, Celtic make Atlético sweat – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 12:44:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Archie Rhind-Tutt, Philippe Auclair and Sid Lowe to analyse the latest from the Champions League group stage. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Double redemption at Old Trafford and Jesus shines in Seville – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 12:30:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Nicky Bandini, Lars Sivertsen and Mark Langdon to discuss all the latest Champions League action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sir Bobby Charlton, keeper gaffes and Pascal Chimbonda - Football Weekly podcast | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 12:08:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Paul MacInnes, John Brewin and Jordan Jarrett-Bryan to review the weekend’s Premier League football and pay tribute to Sir Bobby Charlton. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Merseyside derby kicks off Premier League’s return – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680026/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 13:50:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Nooruddean Choudry, Jonathan Fadugba and Nick Ames to preview the return of club football. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>England seal Euro 2024 spot and San Marino score a goal – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680027/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 13:51:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Nicky Bandini, Lars Sivertsen, and Will Unwin to discuss England’s triumph over Italy and the rest of the Euro 2024 qualifiers. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Scotland reach Euro 2024 and Wales edge closer – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680028/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 13:50:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Philippe Auclair, Lucy Ward, Jonathan Liew, and Ewan Murray to talk about the latest Euro 2024 qualifiers. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Euro 2024 qualifiers and World Cup dreams in Asia – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680029/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 14:30:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Robyn Cowen, Ed Aarons and Paul Watson to preview the latest international games. Plus, Kieran Maguire and Kevin Day join to talk about their new book about football ownership.. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Leicester and Ipswich flying, Pompey on the rise and EFL chat – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680030/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 12:02:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Ben Fisher, George Elek and Sanny Rudravajhala for an update on the latest in the EFL. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A huge win for Arsenal and Spurs sitting pretty at the top – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680031/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 11:38:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Paul MacInnes, Nedum Onuoha and John Brewin as Arsenal claim their first league win over Manchester City in eight years. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Newcastle put Mbappé and PSG to the sword – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680032/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 12:15:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Nicky Bandini, Philippe Auclair and Mark Langdon to discuss all the Champions League action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Galatasaray leave United in disarray and VAR tape causes a stir - Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680033/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 11:54:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Jonathan Wilson, Archie Rhind-Tutt and Lars Sivertsen to discuss defeats for Manchester United and Arsenal as well as the release of the VAR bungle audio from Spurs. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>VAR games at Spurs and Wolves bring life to the title race – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680034/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 11:21:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barney Ronay, John Brewin and Jordan Jarrett-Bryan after a dramatic weekend of Premier League football. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Newcastle take out Manchester City and the WSL returns – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680035/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 11:27:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Fadugba, Will Unwin and Suzy Wrack for a midweek review and a weekend preview. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Barça bounce back, a Juve calamity and madness in Marseille – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680036/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 11:33:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini, Philippe Auclair and Sid Lowe for a round-up of the biggest stories in European football. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Blades put to the sword and north London honours shared – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680037/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 12:02:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Kate Mason, and Nick Ames to discuss the Premier League action, including the north London derby. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Manchester United slump again as Arsenal return in style – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680038/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 11:55:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Mark Langdon and Archie Rhind-Tutt discuss Manchester United, Arsenal and the Champions League. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Newcastle dig deep, relentless City and a goalscoring keeper – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 12:03:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini and Lars Sivertsen as this season’s Champions League Group Stage begins. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Crisis at Old Trafford and the late late show at Spurs - Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680040/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 11:59:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Wilson and John Brewin as Manchester United’s very poor start to the season continues. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Manchester United in perma-crisis as Premier League returns – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680041/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 12:57:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Robyn Cowen and Jordan-Jarrett Bryan to preview the upcoming Premier League fixtures. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>It’s the Bellingham show as England beat Scotland – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 11:58:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini, Jonathan Liew and Ewan Murray as England look a class above Scotland in their 3-1 win at Hampden Park. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>England falter, Scotland soar and Flick’s off for Germany – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680043/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 11:28:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Barney Ronay, Philippe Auclair and Archie Rhind-Tutt to round up the latest international fixtures. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Scotland shining and Maguire makes the England squad - Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680044/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 11:54:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Paul Watson and Jonathan Fadugba to preview the upcoming Euro qualifiers and beyond. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bellingham, Henderson and your questions answered – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680045/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 12:14:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Wilson, Nick Ames and Sid Lowe for updates from Spain and a listener mailbag. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Arsenal leave it late, but Newcastle and Chelsea slip up again – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 11:37:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Lucy Ward and Will Unwin after a dramatic weekend in the Premier League. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Carabao Cup drama and transfer deadline day – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680047/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 11:12:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, John Brewin and Lars Sivertsen to preview the upcoming games and the window closing. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Luis Rubiales and Spain: what happens now? – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680048/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 12:03:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Suzy Wrack, Semra Hunter, Robyn Cowen and Ceylon Andi Hickman discuss Luis Rubiales, Spain and a look back at the World Cup. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Darwin at the double and Everton already in trouble – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680049/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 11:26:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Wilson and Troy Townsend to review all the Premier League action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Premier League previews and Saudi season kicks off – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680050/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 12:22:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning and Nooruddean Choudry to discuss the upcoming top-flight games while Paul MacInnes reports on the Saudi Pro League. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jude Bellingham’s flying start, Harry Kane mania and more – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680051/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 11:33:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini, Semra Hunter and Archie Rhind-Tutt for the first Euro pod of the season. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lionesses fly home while Spurs 2.0 blossom under Angeball - Football Weekly podcast | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680052/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 13:12:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Barney Ronay and Nedum Onuoha as Chelsea and Manchester United fail to impress. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Women’s Football Weekly: Heartbreak for England as Spain lift World Cup | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680053/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 21:23:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Faye Carruthers, Suzanne Wrack, Jonathan Liew and Marva Kreel reflect on Spain’s World Cup final triumph over England. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>England march on to Women’s World Cup final – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680054/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 11:37:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Suzanne Wrack, Jonathan Fadugba and Jordan Jarrett-Bryan as England set up a final against Spain. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>VAR controversy at Old Trafford and big spenders at Stamford Bridge - Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680055/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 12:30:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Philippe Auclair and Will Unwin as Manchester United labour to a 1-0 win over Wolves.. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Premier League returns with a bang and sanitation issues – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680056/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 12:33:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini and John Brewin as the Premier League season gets under way. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Women’s Football Weekly: Lionesses to face Matildas in semi-final clash | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680057/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 20:17:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Faye Carruthers, Suzanne Wrack, Marva Kreel and Jo Khan take a breath after a tough quarter final fight between England and Colombia, and look ahead to a massive semi-final for the Lionesses against Australia. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Premier League season preview: Liverpool to Wolves – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680058/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 11:48:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Wilson and Mark Langdon for our second Premier League preview show.. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Premier League season preview: Arsenal to Fulham – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680059/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 11:25:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Troy Townsend and Lars Sivertsen for the first of two Premier League preview shows. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Women’s Football Weekly: Lionesses find a way to win after James red card | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680060/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 20:01:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Faye Carruthers, Suzanne Wrack, Ceylon Andi Hickman and Tim Stillman discuss an eventful three days of last-16 Women’s World Cup action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EFL back with a bang and Arsenal shake City hoodoo - Football Weekly podcast | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680061/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 12:17:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Ben Fisher, George Elek and Sanny Rudravajhala as domestic football returns. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Women’s Football Weekly: England imperious as USA scrape through | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680062/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 19:38:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Faye Carruthers is joined by Suzy Wrack, Sophie Downey and Anita Asante to reflect on England’s incredible 6-1 win over China. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>World Cup shocks and Henderson heads to Saudi Arabia – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680063/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 11:30:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Ceylon Andi Hickman, Lars Sivertsen and Tariq Panja for an update on the Women’s World Cup and more. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Women’s Football Weekly: England win again, Walsh’s pain and Nigeria joy | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680064/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 15:54:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Another episode from our sister podcast from yesterday: Faye Carruthers is joined by Suzanne Wrack, Jonathan Liew and Marva Kreel For more like this, make sure to subscribe to Women’s Football Weekly, wherever you get your podcasts. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Women’s Football Weekly: Lionesses struggle to find their roar despite win | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680065/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 18:51:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680065/</guid><description>Podcast Description A special drop of our sister podcast, with Faye Carruthers who is joined by Suzy Wrack, Ceylon Andi Hickman, Claire Rafferty, and Jeff Kassouf to discuss England and USA’s opening games of the Women’s World Cup. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Get ready for the Women’s World Cup 2023 – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680066/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 13:19:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Faye Carruthers and Suzy Wrack to cover the big stories ahead of the Women’s World Cup which kicks off on Thursday. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>England’s Under-21 heroes, transfer talk and Sean Dyche’s hat – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680067/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 12:56:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Lars Sivertsen, and Jonathan Wilson assemble for the first pod of pre-season. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The life and times of Nicky Bandini – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680068/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 04:00:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nicky Bandini joins Max Rushden and Barry Glendenning to discuss everything from Young Gunners bus trips to covering games at San Siro. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The life and times of Troy Townsend – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680069/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 04:00:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Troy Townsend joins Max Rushden and Barry Glendenning to discuss his life and times, including his early playing career, the tragic loss of his son and his tireless campaigning against racism in football. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Seventh heaven for England and some shock sackings – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680070/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 14:11:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Robyn Cowen, Nedum Onuoha and Ben Fisher admire England’s rampant performance versus North Macedonia and debate Gary O’Neil’s surprise sacking by Bournemouth. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Scotland stun Norway, England cruise and Spain’s new start – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680071/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 13:24:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Lars Sivertsen, John Brewin, Jordan Jarrett-Bryan and Jim Burke talk Euro 2024 qualifiers, the Nations League and more. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bellingham joins Madrid and Croatia go deep again – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680072/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 12:08:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Mark Langdon and Paul Watson also preview the upcoming internationals because football never stops. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mbappé on the move? And an end-of-season mailbag – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680073/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 10:48:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Wilson and Jonathan Liew for an end-of-season Q&amp;amp;A. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Have Manchester City completed football? - Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680074/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 11:24:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini and Will Unwin as Manchester City win their first Champions League trophy, capping off a remarkable treble season. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>West Ham’s historic night and a Saudi spending spree – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680075/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 11:32:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini and Philippe Auclair as West Ham win their first major trophy in over 40 years. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two down, one to go for Manchester City after FA Cup final – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680076/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 13:32:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Troy Townsend, Robyn Cowen and Jim Burke as City defeat United at Wembley, Celtic land their own treble and Barça win the Women’s Champions League. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Seventh heaven as Sevilla win Europa League again – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680077/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 12:13:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini, Lars Sivertsen and Sid Lowe as Sevilla beat Roma to win the Europa League for a record-extending seventh time. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Heroic Hatters headline long weekend of EFL playoff drama – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680078/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 11:42:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Ali Maxwell, Sanny Rudravajhala, Faye Carruthers and Archie Rhind-Tutt. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Premier League final day: Everton survive, Leicester and Leeds drop – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680079/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 11:26:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Barney Ronay and Jonathan Fadugba as the 2022-23 Premier League season draws to a close. Plus, Suzy Wrack is here for a WSL debrief.. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Brilliant Brighton, Bundesliga duel and relegation battle – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680080/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 13:59:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Lucy Ward and Paul MacInnes to discuss the Premier League, with Archie Rhind-Tutt joining to talk Bundesliga. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Newcastle in Champions League and Soccer Saturday chat – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680081/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 11:37:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Liew and John Brewin to discuss Newcastle’s return to Europe and more. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Manchester City are Premier League champions again – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680082/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 11:27:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nedum Onuoha and Will Unwin as Manchester City claim their fifth Premier League title in six years. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>City charge towards treble and what next for Madrid? – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680083/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 12:44:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Wilson, Philippe Auclair and Sid Lowe to review a seismic Champions League night. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Inter and Luton move within a step of promised lands – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680084/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 11:41:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini, Lars Sivertsen and Faye Carruthers talk Inter, Luton, Leicester and VAR on TV. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Premier League title looks over and Southampton sunk – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680085/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 11:37:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, John Brewin and Jordan Jarrett-Bryan to look back at a pivotal top-flight weekend. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Advantage Inter in the Milan derby semi, while WSL title race hots up – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680086/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 10:59:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini and Mark Langdon as Inter claim a 2-0 victory over Milan in the Champions League. Plus Suzy Wrack is here to update us on the WSL title race. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Manchester City and Real Madrid trade blows at Bernabéu – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680087/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 11:36:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Philippe Auclair, Jonathan Fadugba, Sid Lowe and Ewan Murray to review a Champions League classic. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Premier League survival news and a big EFL review – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680088/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 12:48:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Ben Fisher, George Elek and Sanny Rudravajhala as the relegation battle in the English top flight heats up spectacularly, while the Football League regular season wraps up, with the playoffs set. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Top-four tension, Cambridge joy and Notts County drama – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680089/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 11:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Wilson and Troy Townsend to discuss a busy weekend in the top flight and beyond. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Haaland hitting higher targets and Watford woes – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680090/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 12:31:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Simon Burnton and Lars Sivertsen to discuss Erling Haaland’s goalscoring exploits and much more. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Arsenal add to Chelsea’s woes and Big Sam rides again – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680091/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 11:44:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Robyn Cowen and Nick Ames as Frank Lampard’s Chelsea lose their sixth game in a row. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Manchester City back on top and have we seen peak Spurs? – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680092/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 13:02:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Barney Ronay and Jordan Jarrett-Bryan to discuss all the top-flight drama. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Isak’s spellbinding dribble and is it all over for Southampton? – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680093/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 00:45:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, John Brewin and Nooruddean Choudry as the latest round of midweek Premier League fixtures concludes. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Manchester City pick apart Arsenal’s title hopes – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680094/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 11:17:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini and Jonathan Fadugba as Manchester City beat Arsenal 4-1, while Chelsea slump again, Liverpool win in London and news from Italy. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Shambolic Spurs, an all-Manchester final and Wrexham up – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680095/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 11:56:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Will Unwin and Jonathan Wilson after an important weekend in the Premier League and FA Cup. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Audio Long Read: The impossible job – inside the world of Premier League referees | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680096/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 04:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680096/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re bringing you a special episode today from our sister podcast, The Audio Long Read. Players, pundits and fans complain bitterly that referees are getting worse each season – but is that fair?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Manchester City show no mercy in Munich and what now for handball law? – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680097/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 11:33:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Philippe Auclair and Lars Sivertsen as Manchester City and Internazionale complete the Champions League semi-final lineup. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chelsea’s reality check and the simple joy of pick-up games – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 11:47:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini and Mark Langdon as Chelsea and Napoli bid farewell to the Champions League. Plus James Bird from Mundial is here to talk about the joy of pick-up football. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Manchester City gain edge in title race as Arsenal wobble – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680099/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 12:42:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Wilson and Nedum Onuoha to review the weekend’s action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chelsea fizzle in Madrid, Milan fireworks and more – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680100/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 10:47:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Sid Lowe, Nicky Bandini and Lars Sivertsen as the men’s Champions League quarter-finals continue. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Manchester City muller Bayern and Dean Smith returns – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680101/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 12:06:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Archie Rhind-Tutt and Philippe Auclair as the men’s Champions League quarter-finals kick off. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two points dropped or one gained for Arsenal at Anfield? – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680102/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 11:44:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Troy Townsend and Will Unwin after another enthralling weekend at both ends of the table.. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Can Frank Lampard fix Chelsea? – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680103/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 10:50:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Robyn Cowen and Jonathan Liew as Newcastle United thrash West Ham and Chelsea look set to bring in Frank Lampard as manager (again).. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chelsea and Liverpool extend drought and Villa eye Europe – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680104/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 11:51:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, John Brewin and Jordan Jarrett-Bryan to discuss the latest Premier League action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rodgers and Potter out on busy Premier League weekend – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680105/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 12:33:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Wilson and Barney Ronay after two top-flight managers depart on the same day. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Premier League returns and Qatar revisited – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680106/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 11:39:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Nick Ames, Lucy Ward and Nedum Onuoha to preview the upcoming top-flight fixtures and discuss the situation in Qatar, 100 days on from the World Cup. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Scotland stun Spain at Hampden and Belgium make history – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680107/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 12:11:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Philippe Auclair, Jonathan Fadugba and Jim Burke look back at all the international action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Starboy Saka, last-gasp Wales and arrivederci Antonio – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680108/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 12:15:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Lars Sivertsen, Troy Townsend and Nooruddean Choudry after a weekend of international football. Plus cameos from Keith Bailie and Elis James.. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Harry Kane leads England to first win in Italy since 1961 – Football Weekly podcast | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680109/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 01:19:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, John Brewin and Nicky Bandini as Harry Kane became England’s all-time record scorer in Naples. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Euro 2024 qualifiers and the return of Roy Hodgson – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680110/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 13:12:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Paul Watson and Mark Langdon preview the upcoming international fixtures, while Suzy Wrack is here on the BBC’s recent investigation into the Afghanistan women’s national team. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Conte’s off-pitch outburst and Mitrovic’s on-field rage – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680111/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 12:43:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Robyn Cowen and Will Unwin to review the weekend action, from the Premier League and FA Cup. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Napoli break new ground and Liverpool are bundled out – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680112/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 13:15:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Mark Langdon, Nicky Bandini, Jonathan Fadugba and Jonathan Liew discuss Wednesday’s Champions League and Premier League action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Haaland hits new heights and Inter scrape through – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680113/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 15:50:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Nedum Onuoha, Philippe Auclair and Lars Sivertsen discuss Manchester City’s demolition of RB Leipzig and look ahead to Wednesday night’s games. Plus; Phillipe brings us the latest from his Fifa corner. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Linekergate and the weekend’s Premier League verdict – Football Weekly podcast | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680114/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 15:58:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Jonathan Wilson, Troy Townsend and Nooruddean Choudry discuss the Gary Lineker fallout and actual football in the Premier League. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Spurs and PSG slump out of Europe with a whimper – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680115/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 13:36:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini and Archie Rhind-Tutt discuss Champions League joy for Bayern and Milan … but woe elsewhere. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Graham Potter’s big night and Club Brugge’s lack of fight – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680116/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 12:59:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Philippe Auclair and Mark Langdon as Chelsea and Benfica book their places in the Champions League quarter-finals, plus wood and supermodels. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Crisis, what crisis? Liverpool hit Manchester United for seven – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680117/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 13:37:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Robyn Cowen and Barney Ronay to review the weekend’s Premier League action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A historic night for Grimsby and Arsenal hit four to go five clear – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680118/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 13:32:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, John Brewin and Lars Sivertsen after midweek FA Cup and Premier League action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Football and disability – Football Weekly special | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680119/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 10:36:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning and Jordan Jarrett-Bryan speak to the CEO of Level Playing Field along with a host of fans, journalists and charity ambassadors about the match-day experience of disabled fans, how – if – things have changed and how important media representation is. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Casemiro furthers case for player of the season at Wembley – Football Weekly podcast | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680120/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 14:35:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Troy Townsend and Nedum Onuoha to dissect the League Cup final and Premier League action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Manchester City pegged back again and the English game’s white paper – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680121/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 13:45:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini and Jonathan Wilson after more Champions League knockout action, plus Kevin Miles from the FSA joins to discuss the new football white paper. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Real hammering for Liverpool in the Champions League - Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680122/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 12:47:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Sid Lowe, Jonathan Fadugba and Archie Rhind-Tutt after the latest round of 16 action in the Champions League. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Arsenal on top, drum’n’bass Q&amp;As and Rashford on fire – Football Weekly podcast | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680123/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 12:38:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jordan Jarrett-Bryan and John Brewin to review the weekend’s Premier League action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Manchester City leapfrog Arsenal while Chelsea slip up again – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680124/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 14:30:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Mark Langdon and Lars Sivertsen discuss the top-of-the-table Premier League clash between Arsenal and Manchester City, and all the action from the Champions League. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Champions League troubles for flat PSG and Spurs – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680125/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 13:42:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Philippe Auclair, Nicky Bandini and Marva Kreel on the Champions League action and the Merseyside derby. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nathan Jones, we hardly knew ye – Football Weekly podcast | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680126/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 15:55:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Barney Ronay, and Nooruddean Choudry to discuss the weekend’s Premier League action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Leeds’ no-manager bounce and a big weekend ahead – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680127/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 12:59:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Liew and Lucy Ward to preview the upcoming round of Premier League fixtures. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Manchester City investigated, an EFL round-up and Southend United – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680128/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 13:38:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, George Elek and Ben Fisher round up the latest stories in the Football League. Plus Kieran Maguire and James Schooley join to discuss the latest at Manchester City and Southend. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Citizens Kaned by Spurs and Sean Dyche rides again – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680129/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 12:47:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nedum Onuoha and Jonathan Wilson to review the weekend’s action as the Premier League’s top two both lost. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Manchester United cruise to Wembley and a Mundial cameo – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680130/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 13:30:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Paul MacInnes, Jordan Jarrett-Bryan, and James Bird to discuss the latest action and transfers. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Newcastle are roared to Wembley and transfer window shuts – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680131/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 13:29:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Robyn Cowen and Lars Sivertsen as Newcastle make their first major final since 1999. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Wrexham blockbuster and Brighton rock Liverpool again – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680132/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 13:02:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Troy Townsend and John Brewin to reflect on the fourth round of the FA Cup. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Manchester United close on Wembley and an FA Cup preview – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680133/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 12:40:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Mark Langdon and Jonathan Fadugba to discuss the Carabao Cup and the upcoming FA Cup. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Everton in crisis and Newcastle on the road to Wembley – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680134/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 14:31:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Paul Watson, Nicky Bandini and Marva Kreel to discuss the latest on and off the pitch. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A throwback classic between Arsenal and Manchester United – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680135/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 14:07:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Jonathan Wilson, Barney Ronay and Robyn Cowen as Arsenal overcome rivals to keep their title dreams alive. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Palace halt Manchester United charge. Plus the John Yems findings – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680136/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 13:35:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Nedum Onuoha, John Brewin and Nick Ames after midweek action in the Premier League and FA Cup. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sam Kerr does Sam Kerr things on WSL’s big return – Women’s Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680137/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 10:53:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680137/</guid><description>Podcast Description With the return of the WSL, we wanted to bring you the latest episode of our brilliant Women’s Football Weekly podcast. In it, Faye Carruthers has Suzanne Wrack, Ceylon Andi Hickman and Moyo Abiona alongside her to round up all the action after the winter break. Make sure to search, listen and subscribe wherever you get your podcasts. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Napoli surge on in Serie A while PSG remain patchy – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680138/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 11:49:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680138/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Nicky Bandini, Lars Sivertsen and Philippe Auclair for the first Europod of 2023. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>North London and Manchester turn red on derby-filled weekend - Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680139/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 14:19:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Jonathan Wilson, Troy Townsend and Nooruddean Choudry to discuss the dramatic Premier League matches. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Southampton stun Manchester City and Forest sink Wolves – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680140/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 14:49:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Jordan Jarrett-Bryan and Robyn Cowen discuss the Carabao Cup quarter-finals and look ahead to the Premier League’s return. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Burn’s night, Bale’s farewell and a new Chelsea arrival – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680141/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 14:57:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Liew and Lucy Ward on the first League Cup quarter-finals, plus Elis James bids farewell to Gareth Bale. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Stevenage and Wrexham star amid the FA Cup shocks – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680142/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 12:39:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Wilson and John Brewin to also discuss Owls, parakeets and pressure for Potter. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Harry Kane sparks Spurs, plus West Brom’s worries – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680143/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 15:18:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Fadugba and Paul MacInnes after Wednesday night’s Premier League games. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Angry Arteta, Merseyside misery and Brighton brilliance – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680144/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 13:45:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680144/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Troy Townsend and Ed Aarons after Tuesday night’s Premier League action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>New year, same, rather good Arsenal? – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680145/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 22:31:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nedum Onuoha and Philippe Auclair as Arsenal move seven points clear at the top. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What is Pelé’s legacy? – Football Weekly special | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680146/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 05:00:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Philippe Auclair, Andrew Downie and Samindra Kunti for a special on the life of Pelé, possibly the greatest footballer ever. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Haaland leads the way for Manchester City – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680147/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 13:01:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Wilson and Robyn Cowen after more midweek Premier League action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Premier League is back and nothing has changed – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680148/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 12:25:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Lars Sivertsen, John Brewin and Jordan Jarrett-Bryan as the Premier League returns from its Winter World Cup hiatus. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tackling your questions from the Christmas mailbag – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680149/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 05:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Wilson and John Brewin for a special festive Q&amp;amp;A. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The greatest World Cup final ever? – Football Daily | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680150/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 22:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Lars Sivertsen, Philippe Auclair and Barney Ronay as Argentina lift the 2022 World Cup. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Qatar 2022: what have we learned? – Football Daily podcast | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680151/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 05:00:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Philippe Auclair, Pete Pattisson, James Montague, Shireen Ahmed and Nooruddean Choudry look back over the World Cup in Qatar. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Has Griezmann finally found his right position? - Football Daily podcast | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680152/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 00:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Philippe Auclair and Nedum Onuoha as France complete the final line-up for the 2022 World Cup. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Majestic Messi earns Argentina a place in World Cup final – Football Daily | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680153/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 00:05:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680153/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini, John Brewin and Marcela Mora y Araujo as Argentina overcome Croatia to book their place in the World Cup final. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Previewing the World Cup semi-finals – Football Daily podcast | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680154/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 14:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Mark Langdon, Robyn Cowen, and Marcela Mora y Araujo take a look at the final four contenders. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Heartbreak for England and more Moroccan miracles – Football Daily | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680155/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 23:35:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Philippe Auclair and Lars Sivertsen as England bow out of Qatar 2022. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Brazil bow out, Messi magic and so much World Cup drama – Football Daily | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680156/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 23:49:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini and Troy Townsend after a blistering start to the World Cup quarter-finals. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Looking ahead to all four World Cup quarter-finals – Football Daily podcast | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680157/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 05:00:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680157/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Mark Langdon, Robyn Cowen and Lars Sivertsen to preview an intriguing set of last-eight ties in Qatar. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>From our Science Weekly podcast: will the Qatar World Cup really be carbon neutral? | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680158/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 13:26:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680158/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we’re bringing you an episode of our sister podcast Science Weekly about the environmental impact of the 2022 World Cup. Madeleine Finlay speaks to sports reporter Paul MacInnes about the environmental burden of building stadiums, flying in players and fans from around the world and keeping the pitches green. So, is football really ready to face up to its carbon footprint?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.</description></item><item><title>Portugal hit Switzerland for six and Morocco shock Spain – Football Daily podcast | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680159/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:21:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Fadugba, and John Brewin discuss the concluding games of the World Cup round of 16 after Portugal thrashed Switzerland and Morocco shocked Spain. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Brazil find their samba to strut into World Cup last eight – Football Daily podcast | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680160/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 23:09:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680160/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Lars Sivertsen, Jordan Jarrett-Bryan, and Ben Mabley discuss Brazil’s win over South Korea and Japan v Croatia in the World Cup round of 16. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>England are through and France await – Football Daily podcast | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680161/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 23:40:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680161/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Mark Langdon and Philippe Auclair as England secure their spot in the Quarter-Finals with a comfortable win over Senegal. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Australia and USA bow out bravely as World Cup last 16 begins – Football Daily | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680162/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 23:14:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680162/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Nicky Bandini, Jonathan Wilson, Marcela Mora y Araujo and Bryan Graham as the knockout stages commence. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>South Korea soar, Switzerland celebrate and Luis Suárez sobs – Football Daily | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680163/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 22:49:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nedum Onuoha, Ed Aarons and Nick Ames on a dramatic final day of group games in Qatar. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Germany and Belgium out but did Japan keep the ball in play? – Football Daily | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680164/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 00:51:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680164/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Lars Sivertsen, Jonathan Fadugba and Archie Rhind-Tutt assess the fallout from an extraordinary night of drama. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Socceroos set up Argentina tie as Denmark flop – Football Daily podcast | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680165/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:33:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, John Brewin, Philippe Auclair, Mark Langdon, Marcela Mora y Araujo and Emma Kemp dissect the final action in Groups C and D. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Wales wave goodbye as England wrap up first place in Group B – Football Daily | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680166/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 23:47:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680166/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Troy Townsend, Elis James, Barney Ronay and Nick Ames as England seal their neighbours’ fate. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Aboubakar scoop and Kudus strike add to World Cup goalfest – Football Daily | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680167/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 23:22:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, John Brewin and Jordan Jarrett-Bryan to talk about the games of the tournament so far. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Germany grit, Morocco magic and Croatia crush Canada – Football Daily | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680168/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 23:28:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Nicky Bandini, Ed Aarons and Archie Rhind-Tutt as the second round of fixtures in Group E &amp;amp; F are played. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Messi revives Argentina and Mbappé fires France into last 16 – Football Daily podcast | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680169/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 23:55:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Lars Sivertson, Philippe Auclair, Marcela Mora y Araujo, and Emma Kemp discuss the second round of games in Groups C and D. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Frustration for England, USA impress and agony for Wales – Football Daily | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680170/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 23:09:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nick Ames and Paul MacInnes as England draw with the USA and Wales lose late on to Iran. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ronaldo makes history as Brazil join the party – Football Daily podcast | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680171/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:34:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680171/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Wilson and Jonathan Fadugba recap the Group G and H action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Japan defeat Germany and Spain hit seven – Football Daily podcast | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680172/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 23:42:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Mark Langdon, Archie Rhind-Tutt, Jonathan Liew, and Sid Lowe discuss the opening games in Groups E and F.. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Saudi Arabia stun Argentina as holders France put on a show – Football Daily | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680173/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 00:53:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680173/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini, Philippe Auclair, Marcela Mora y Araujo and Paul MacInnes round up an eventful day of action in Groups C and D. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A perfect start for England while Wales leave it late – Football Daily | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680174/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 22:53:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680174/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nedum Onuoha and John Brewin as England beat Iran 6-2 in their opening game and Wales nab a late equaliser against USA. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Qatar 2022 kicks off but hosts slump to Ecuador – Football Daily podcast | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680175/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 21:52:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680175/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Lars Sivertsen and Troy Townsend as the World Cup in Qatar commences. Plus Jonathan Wilson joins from the Al Bayt Stadium. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>World Cup Groups G and H, plus: women in Qatar – Football Daily podcast | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680176/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 16:21:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680176/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Nick Ames, Jonathan Fadugba and Tim Vickery preview Groups G and H. Plus Max, Philippe Auclair, Rothna Begum of Human Rights Watch and Louise Donovan from the Fuller Project discuss life for women in Qatar. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>World Cup Groups E and F, plus: migrant workers in Qatar – Football Daily podcast | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680177/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 15:23:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680177/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Lars Sivertson, John Brewin, Sid Lowe, and Archie Rhind-Tutt preview the Groups E and F. Plus Max, Barry Glendenning, Nick McGeehan of FairSquare, and Felix Jakens from Amnesty discuss the situation concerning migrant workers in Qatar. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>World Cup Groups C and D, plus: the life of LGBTQ+ Qataris – Football Daily podcast | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680178/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 14:35:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680178/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Marcela Mora y Araujo, Mark Langdon and Philippe Auclair to preview Groups C and D. Plus Max, Philippe, Rosie Garthwaite, David Harding and Dr Nasser Mohamed discuss the life of the LGBTQ+ community in Qatar. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>World Cup Groups A and B, plus: how did we get here? – Football Daily podcast | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680179/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 14:54:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Ed Aarons, Jonathan Liew and Barney Ronay preview the World Cup. Plus Max, Barney, Barry Glendenning, Philippe Auclair and John McManus discuss all things Qatar in ‘How did we get here?’. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Toney makes a point as the Premier League powers down for Qatar – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680180/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 11:22:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Jonathan Wilson, Troy Townsend and John Brewin as the English top flight goes on hold until after the World Cup. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Carabao Cup review and World Cup squads – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680181/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 12:39:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Ben Fisher, Jordan Jarrett-Bryan and Robyn Cowen to discuss the League Cup and World Cup squads for Qatar. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Champions League’s blockbuster draw and Liverpool’s future – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680182/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 13:34:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680182/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Wilson and Philippe Auclair as the Champions League round of 16 is drawn. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Arsenal stay top and Ralph Hasenhüttl gets the chop – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680183/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 14:07:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680183/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Paul MacInnes and Lucy Ward to discuss all the weekend’s Premier League action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Champions League review and a Ronnie Radford tribute – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680184/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 14:42:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680184/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini and Mark Langdon discuss the final group games, and look ahead to the weekend action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Spurs belatedly bring the fireworks to deny Marseille – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680185/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 15:05:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680185/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Lars Sivertsen and Archie Rhind-Tutt round up the final Champions League action in groups A to D. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Arsenal are flying and are Liverpool in crisis? – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680186/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 15:25:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680186/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Nedum Onuoha, and John Brewin discuss all the weekend’s Premier League action as well as a 4-4 draw at The Valley. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The very late show in London and Madrid – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680187/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 13:53:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680187/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini, and Lars Sivertsen discuss Wednesday’s Champions League games, the Socceroos’ statement about Qatar’s human rights and look ahead to the weekend’s action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chelsea top group, City penalty blues and a shocking miss – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680188/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 14:14:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680188/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Fadugba and Philippe Auclair as the penultimate round of Champions League group games began.. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Forest fell Liverpool and Arsenal slip up at Southampton – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680189/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 11:44:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680189/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nick Ames and Robyn Cowen after a packed weekend of Premier League football. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ronaldo-less United have more than enough for Spurs – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680190/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 11:36:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680190/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Liew and Troy Townsend after the midweek round of games in the Premier League. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Women’s Football Weekly: a punchy WSL return and Ballon d’Or debate | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680191/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 11:26:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680191/</guid><description>Podcast Description A special drop of our sister podcast, with Faye Carruthers, Suzanne Wrack, Anita Asante and Robyn Cowen, as they wrap up the latest round of WSL action – plus a word on the Ballon d’Or and the Championship. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The state of play in the Championship and rest of the EFL – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680192/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 11:33:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680192/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, George Elek and Ben Fisher to assess the runners and riders in the Football League. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Liverpool make their mark on title race as Arsenal go clear – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680193/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 10:58:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680193/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Wilson and Jordan Jarrett-Bryan after Liverpool beat Manchester City 1-0 at Anfield. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Salah’s six-minute special and Barça misfire again – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680194/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 11:58:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680194/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Fadugba and Mark Langdon after a thrilling evening of Champions League action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chelsea’s stylish start under Potter and Mbappé’s future – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680195/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 12:11:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680195/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini and Lars Sivertsen as Chelsea seal a double over Milan and Juve slump into crisis. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Arsenal’s ascent continues and one year on at Newcastle – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680196/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 11:57:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680196/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Barney Ronay and Jonathan Wilson to review the weekend’s action and major news. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chelsea and Manchester City cruise in Champions League – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680197/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 12:04:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680197/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Nedum Onuoha, Nicky Bandini and Sid Lowe pick over the latest Champions League action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trent Alexander-Arnold, Spurs and the Maddison question – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680198/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 11:27:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680198/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Lars Sivertsen and Philippe Auclair after an evening of Champions League football. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Erling Haaland does it again and Arsenal stay top – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680199/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 12:41:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680199/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, John Brewin and Troy Townsend after a weekend that included the Manchester derby, the north London derby and Wolves sacking Bruno Lage. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to fix football with Gary Neville – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680200/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 04:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680200/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning and Gary Neville to discuss his new book The People’s Game, covering: inequality, the European Super League, clubs going out of business, human rights, racism and the importance of the women’s game. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Signs of life for Southgate and business as usual at Watford – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680201/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 12:32:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680201/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Archie Rhind-Tutt and Lucy Ward after England’s 3-3 draw with Germany at Wembley. Plus Mike Parkin joins to discuss yet another managerial sacking at Vicarage Road. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Are England going backwards under Gareth Southgate? – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680202/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 12:29:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680202/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Wilson and Paul Watson to discuss the latest from the Nations League. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How the Champions League final nearly ended in disaster – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680203/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 04:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680203/</guid><description>Podcast Description Liverpool fans attending this year’s Champions League final faced a crush outside the stadium that held stark echoes of the worst day in the club’s history. David Conn has spent months investigating what happened. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Nations League returns and what fans can expect in Qatar – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680204/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 12:22:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680204/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by John Brewin, Nick Ames and Lars Sivertsen to preview the upcoming Nations League games. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Are Bayern Munich and Juventus at crisis point? – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680205/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 12:58:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680205/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Nicky Bandini, Mark Langdon and Philippe Auclair for the biggest stories from across the continent. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The prodigal Son returns for Tottenham and WSL off to a flyer – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680206/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 11:46:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680206/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barney Ronay, Nedum Onuoha and Robyn Cowen to discuss the latest action from the Premier League. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Haaland fling and Potter’s Chelsea bow – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680207/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 12:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680207/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Liew and Troy Townsend to discuss the latest from the Champions League. Plus, Sid Lowe joins for an update from La Liga. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Liverpool leave it late and Spurs stutter in Champions League – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680208/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 12:13:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680208/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Philippe Auclair and Rory Smith to discuss the latest action in the Champions League. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Postponements, Potter and delving into the mailbag – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680209/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 11:55:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680209/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Ed Aarons and Jonathan Wilson to answer listener questions in a special edition of the show. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Napoli rout Liverpool, plus vintage Simeone – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680210/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 12:37:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680210/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini and Mark Langdon discuss Wednesday’s Champions League games, Graham Potter’s potential appointment at Chelsea and look ahead to the weekend’s action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tuchel sacked, Champions League and perfect Lionesses – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680211/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 13:50:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680211/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Lars Sivertson, Jonathan Fadugba and Faye Carruthers discuss Thomas Tuchel’s sacking, the Champions League and the Lionesses 10-0 win against Luxembourg. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>VAR infuriates and Manchester United end Gunners perfect start – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680212/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 12:58:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680212/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Wilson and Barney Ronay discuss VAR and the weekend’s Premier League action.. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Klopp-age time at Anfield, while Aston Villa let it slip – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680213/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 13:59:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680213/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Ewan Murray, Jonathan Liew, Jordan Jarrett-Bryan and Barry Glendenning to review all the midweek action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chelsea the latest crisis club and Mitrovic is on fire – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680214/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 14:31:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680214/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Paul MacInnes and Robyn Cowen to wrap up Chelsea’s sorry showing on the south coast, another three points for surprise package Fulham and time-wasting at Elland Road. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Liverpool pick Cherries apart and Haaland’s heroics – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680215/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 15:10:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680215/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Philippe Auclair and Lucy Ward to discuss nine goals without reply at Anfield, another comeback for Manchester City and too much celebrating for some at the Emirates. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rangers reach Champions League promised land – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680216/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 12:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680216/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Troy Townsend, John Brewin and Colin McMillan as Rangers make it through to the Champions League group stage for the first time in more than a decade. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Manchester United bounce back and Ellen White bows out – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680217/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 12:38:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680217/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Ceylon Andi-Hickman and Jonathan Wilson discuss Monday night’s game at Old Trafford. Plus: Nick Ames joins from Ukraine, where domestic football is about to resume. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Newcastle put Manchester City in a spin and Leeds Marsch on – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680218/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 11:56:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680218/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nedum Onuoha and Lars Sivertsen to discuss a dramatic weekend of Premier League football. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Will the Glazers sell? And a Premier League preview – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680219/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 12:09:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680219/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Robyn Cowen, Jonathan Liew and Ben Fisher to preview the Premier League games this weekend and look over the latest action from the EFL. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Liverpool’s shaky start and Jonathan Wilson’s new book – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680220/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 12:35:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680220/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Wilson and Paul Watson to discuss Liverpool’s so-so start to the season. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Manchester United’s new low and men being Proper Men – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680221/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 14:01:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680221/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barney Ronay, Barry Glendenning and Paul Macinnes review the weekend’s Premier League action and much, much more. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Super Madrid and a Premier League preview – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680222/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 11:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680222/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Archie Rhind-Tutt, Jordan Jarrett-Bryan and Lucy Ward discuss Real’s Super Cup win, the opening round in the Bundesliga and preview the forthcoming Premier League games. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What is going on at Barcelona? – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680223/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 11:52:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680223/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini, Philippe Auclair and Sid Lowe for the first Euro pod of the season. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is Arnautovic really the answer to Ten Hag’s problems? – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680224/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 11:47:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680224/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Lars Sivertsen and John Brewin to review the first weekend season. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Premier League season preview: Leicester to Wolves – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680225/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 12:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680225/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Wilson and Simon Burnton for our second round of top-flight season previews. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Premier League season preview: AFC Bournemouth to Leeds - Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680226/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 13:10:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680226/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nedum Onuoha and Troy Townsend for the first of two Premier League preview shows. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Joy, relief and celebration confusion: the Lionesses win Euro 2022 – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680227/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 12:39:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680227/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Suzy Wrack and Robyn Cowen as England leave it until extra time to win the Women’s Euros at Wembley. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Germany book Euro 2022 final and EFL returns – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680228/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 11:59:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680228/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Tim Stillman, Ceylon Andi Hickman and Ben Fisher to review the Euro 2022 semi-final between Germany and France and look ahead to the EFL season which starts this weekend. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>England are one step closer to history – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680229/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 13:15:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680229/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Robyn Cowen, Anita Asante and Jordan Jarrett-Bryan as England reach the final of Euro 2022. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Euro 2022, Lewandowski and Fulham ticket prices – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680230/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 13:06:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680230/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Archie Rhind-Tutt, Beth Fisher and Jonathan Liew discuss England’s quarter-final triumph and what’s happening in Germany. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Who’s winning the transfer market? – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680231/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 14:25:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680231/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jordan Jarret-Bryan, Barry Glendenning, Lucy Ward and Nick Ames discuss the Euros and recent transfer news. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How are Barcelona still able to buy players? – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680232/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 16:28:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680232/</guid><description>Podcast Description The day after our final live show in Glasgow, Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Wilson and Philippe Auclair to discuss the latest football news. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lionesses trample Norway and Northern Ireland bow out – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680233/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 14:02:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680233/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Suzanne Wrack and Nicky Bandini after England’s emphatic 8-0 win over Norway. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>England get the Euro 2022 party started with a win – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680234/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 12:04:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680234/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Robyn Cowen and Ceylon Andi Hickman as England open the Women’s Euros with a victory. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Introducing our new Women’s Football Weekly podcast: Euro 2022 preview – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680235/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 14:26:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680235/</guid><description>Podcast Description We wanted to share the first episode of our new women’s football podcast. Faye Carruthers, Suzanne Wrack and a host of experts – some of whom you’ll know from the show – will be on hand three times a week to give instant reaction and analysis from the Women’s Euro 2022 competition. In this episode, which was recorded on Monday, Faye and Suzanne are joined by Robyn Cowen and Jonathan Liew to preview the groups of Euro 2022, which kicks off on Wednesday.</description></item><item><title>Could England go all the way and win Women’s Euro 2022? – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680236/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 17:38:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680236/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Wilson, Mark Langdon and Faye Carruthers discuss the Euros and recent transfer news. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Football Weekly Extra – live stream announcement | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680237/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 12:19:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680237/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning to bring exciting Football Weekly Live our news. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to tackle LGBTQ+ discrimination in the game – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680238/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 15:50:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680238/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Rishi Madlani, Chris Paouros and Nicky Bandini as they share their experiences along with listeners. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The life and times of Nedum Onuoha – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680239/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 14:21:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680239/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning and Nedum Onuoha to discuss the former Manchester City defender’s storied career. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>England’s Nations League ennui and Ireland’s goal rush – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680240/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 16:19:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680240/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, John Brewin and Barney Ronay to discuss the weekend’s Nations League games. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How should we change the game? – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680241/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 13:15:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680241/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Philippe Auclair, Jordan Jarrett-Bryan and Archie Rhind-Tutt as they and the listeners propose some sensible and some ridiculous changes to improve football. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>England claw a draw in Germany and the latest on Italy – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680242/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 12:49:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680242/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Nedum Onuoha, Nicky Bandini and Jonathan Liew to discuss England’s Nations League draw in Germany. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tears and cheers as Wales’s World Cup wait is ended – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680243/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 12:01:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680243/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Elis James, Troy Townsend and Jonathan Wilson after Wales beat Ukraine to qualify for their first World Cup since 1958. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Scotland’s World Cup dream over as Ukraine win – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680244/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 12:02:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680244/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Nick Ames, Ben Fisher and Ewan Murray discuss an emotional night as Ukraine move a step closer to the World Cup. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Forest’s Premier League return and your questions answered – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680245/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 13:01:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680245/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Robyn Cowen, Jonathan Wilson and Philippe Auclair to answer your questions on crowd trouble, Qatar and much more. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Real Madrid reign supreme after crowd chaos rears its head – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680246/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 11:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680246/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, John Brewin and Jonathan Wilson to reflect on Real Madrid’s Champions League win. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Roma rejoice and a Champions League final preview – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680247/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 12:06:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680247/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Ceylon Andi-Hickman and Nedum Onuoha after José Mourinho secured his fifth European trophy, and the pod look ahead to the big Liverpool v Real Madrid final in Paris. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Milan take the spoils in Serie A, plus Mbappé’s motives – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680248/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 13:06:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680248/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini, Philippe Auclair and Mark Langdon to round up the biggest stories from the continent. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Manchester City’s glory, Raphinha in the stands and Mbappé – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680249/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 13:20:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680249/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Troy Townsend and Jonathan Liew to reflect on a momentous final day in the Premier League. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Eintracht Frankfurt break Rangers’ hearts – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680250/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 13:06:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680250/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Katie Shanahan, Archie Rhind-Tutt and Colin McMillan discuss the Europa League final and much more. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Arsenal blow up in race for top four and praise for Jake Daniels – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680251/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 12:48:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680251/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Lars Sivertsen and Philippe Auclair as Newcastle beat Arsenal to make their hopes of a top-four finish seem very unlikely. Plus, Chris Paouros joins us to talk about Jake Daniels - the first active British male professional footballer to publicly come out. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Another Wembley win for Liverpool and Emma Hayes doubles up - Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680252/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 11:23:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680252/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Gregg Bakowski and Jonathan Wilson as Liverpool make it two out of four at Wembley on their quest for the Quadruple this season and Chelsea’s Women win the Double. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Holding sees red as Spurs heat up the race for fourth – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680253/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 12:33:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680253/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jordan Jarrett-Bryan and Nick Ames to discuss the north London derby and Nick’s time with the Ukrainian national team. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>De Bruyne hits Wolves for four and Celtic make it 10 in 11 – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680254/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 14:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680254/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, John Brewin, Lucy Ward and Jim Burke to discuss all the midweek Premier League action as well Celtic’s triumph in the Scottish Premiership. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Reds blink first in Premier League and it’s a blue day in WSL – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680255/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 14:25:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680255/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Barney Ronay, Troy Townsend and Suzy Wrack to discuss all the weekend’s Premier League action as well as another WSL title win for Chelsea. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ibrox rocks but West Ham fade in Frankfurt - Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680256/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 14:19:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680256/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Lars Sivertsen and Archie Rhind-Tutt as the Europa League and Conference League semis conclude. Plus Colin McMillan from the Rangers podcast Heart and Hand joins. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rodrygo rocks City as Madrid refuse to be put away – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680257/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 13:46:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680257/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nedum Onuoha, Philippe Auclair and Sid Lowe after another classic Champions League clash between Real Madrid and Manchester City. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Liverpool into Paris final and Bournemouth are back – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680258/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 12:48:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680258/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini and Simon Burnton as Liverpool confirm their place in the Champions League final. Plus, Ben Fisher joins to reflect on Bournemouth’s promotion. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Everton re-energised while Leeds look limp – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680259/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 12:01:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680259/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Jonathan Wilson, Robyn Cowen and Jonathan Liew after a weekend of Premier League football that saw Leeds’s relegation worries deepen. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Have West Ham’s Europa League hopes gone up in smoke? – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680260/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 12:51:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680260/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Nick Ames, Archie Rhind-Tutt and Jonathan Fadugba discuss the first legs in both the Europa League and Europa Conference League semis, plus down the running order is Manchester United v Chelsea. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Superlatives for Liverpool and the plight of Oldham – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680261/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 13:45:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680261/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Mark Langdon, Lars Sivertsen and Sid Lowe recap Liverpool’s win over Villarreal. Plus, author and journalist Mike Keegan joins us for an update on the fall and fall of Oldham Athletic. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Manchester City, Real Madrid and a Champions League classic – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680262/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 12:12:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680262/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini and Sid Lowe look back at a barnstorming first leg. Plus Calum Jacobs joins to discuss his book A New Formation: How Black Footballers Shaped the Modern Game. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Are Everton going down? - Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680263/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 12:22:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680263/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jordan Jarrett-Bryan and Paul MacInnes after a weekend on Premier League action that saw Arsenal reclaim 4th spot and Burnley climb out of the bottom three.. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Arsenal back in business and Newcastle in tune – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680264/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 12:15:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680264/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Troy Townsend and Nedum Onuoha to discuss the midweek Premier League action … and bigger issues. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Liverpool reinforce gulf in class with Manchester United – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680265/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 11:51:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680265/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, John Brewin and Ben Fisher after Liverpool thrash Manchester United and the Football League season draws closer to its conclusion. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Liverpool and Chelsea set up another final face-off – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680266/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 11:13:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680266/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Ed Aarons and Jonathan Wilson after a busy weekend of Premier League and FA Cup action. Plus Ewan Murray joins to discuss the Scottish Cup semi-finals. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Champions League: and then there were four – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680267/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 13:42:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680267/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini and Philippe Auclair after a spicy affair in Madrid and a sort-of-thriller at Anfield. Plus Suzy Wrack joins for the latest on Northern Ireland Women’s Kenny Shiels. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Real thriller in Madrid and Emery’s Villarreal masterclass – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680268/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 11:49:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680268/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Lars Sivertson, Sid Lowe and Archie Rhind-Tutt to discuss the Champions League quarter-final drama. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The greatest game in the greatest league in the world? – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680269/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 13:36:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680269/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Barney Ronay, and John Brewin to discuss the weekend’s Premier League action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Everton in deep trouble and brilliant Benzema – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680270/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 13:31:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680270/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Mark Langdon and Archie Rhind-Tutt after a night of Spanish success and another game to forget for Frank Lampard’s side. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Wins for Liverpool and City but Arsenal embarrassed at Palace – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680271/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 11:42:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680271/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Lars Sivertsen and Jonathan Fadugba to discuss the Champions League quarter-final games and more. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Brilliant Brentford, super Spurs and the World Cup draw is set – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680272/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 12:39:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680272/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Wilson and Robyn Cowen to discuss a busy weekend of action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The World Cup draw and a record clásico – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680273/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 11:43:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680273/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Paul MacInnes, Jordan Jarrett-Bryan and Suzy Wrack to discuss the upcoming 2022 World Cup draw and an historic night at the Camp Nou in the Women’s Champions League. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>World Cup qualifiers decided, England win and laser pens – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680274/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 12:06:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680274/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Paul Watson and Jonathan Liew after World Cup qualifiers were decided and England beat Ivory Coast. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Welsh wonders, Italian woe and Kane’s England record – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680275/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 11:19:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680275/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Barney Ronay and Ben Fisher after a weekend of international football. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is this Wales’ biggest game for 64 years? - Football Weekly Extra | Podcast | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680276/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 14:51:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680276/</guid><description>Podcast Description Faye Carruthers is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Wilson, Nedum Onuoha to preview the upcoming international fixtures. Plus Suzy Wrack joins for a Women’s Champions League round-up.. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Will Barcelona’s clásico win be a turning point? – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680277/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 14:37:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680277/</guid><description>Podcast Description Faye Carruthers is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini, Philippe Auclair and Sid Lowe to cover the biggest stories from around Europe. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Harry Kane heroics and frustrated Frank Lampard – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680278/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 14:05:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680278/</guid><description>Podcast Description Faye Carruthers is joined by Barry Glendenning, Troy Townsend and John Brewin after a weekend of Premier League and FA Cup action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chelsea stand firm and Villarreal rock Juventus – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680279/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 13:21:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680279/</guid><description>Podcast Description Faye Carruthers is joined by Nick Ames, Nicky Bandini and Jordan Jarrett-Bryan after Wednesday’s Champions League and Premier League action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Manchester United bow out and Chelsea’s statement saga – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680280/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 12:37:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680280/</guid><description>Podcast Description Faye Carruthers, Simon Burnton, Lars Sivertsen, Jonathan Fadugba and Sid Lowe are on the pod as Atlético knock Manchester United out of Europe. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A strange Stamford Bridge backdrop to Chelsea v Newcastle – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680281/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 14:21:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680281/</guid><description>Podcast Description Faye Carruthers is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Wilson and Robyn Cowen after another eventful weekend in the Premier League.. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What next at Chelsea as Abramovich hit by sanctions? – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680282/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 15:23:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680282/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Lars Sivertsen and Philippe Auclair to discuss Chelsea’s future amid breaking news. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Liverpool look up but are Everton going down? – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680283/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 12:04:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680283/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini and Mark Langdon to discuss the latest domestic and Champions League action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>‘In Ukraine we speak only about war, not football’ – Football Weekly Special | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680284/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 05:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680284/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning and Nick Ames to speak to Mladen Bartulovic, assistant coach of Ukrainian side Inhulets Petrove. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Manchester derby to savour (for some) – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680285/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 14:08:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680285/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Barney Ronay and Troy Townsend after a busy weekend of Premier League action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What will be Roman Abramovich’s Chelsea legacy? – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680286/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 15:16:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680286/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden, Barry Glendenning, Katie Shanahan and Jonathan Liew discuss the latest at Chelsea and more midweek FA Cup fixtures. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Magic Middlesbrough and is it the end of Roman’s reign? – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680287/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 14:57:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680287/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jordan Jarrett-Bryan and Paul MacInnes to discuss the latest in the FA Cup and Premier League and speak to Rob Davies about how gambling conquered Britain. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Liverpool’s Wembley win and fans unite to support Ukraine – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680288/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 14:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680288/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Jonathan Wilson, Nedum Onuoha and Andrew Todos to discuss the latest games and football’s ever-changing relationship with Russia. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Elanga saves Manchester United and Conte’s Spurs woes – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680289/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 13:36:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680289/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Lars Sivertsen, John Brewin, Sid Lowe and Suzy Wrack to discuss the latest Champions League and Premier League action, plus England’s victory in the Arnold Clark Cup. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Havertz steps up as Lukaku feels the chill at Chelsea – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680290/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 13:09:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680290/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini, Jonathan Fadugba and Ewan Murray after another midweek round of Champions League fixtures. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kane and Spurs blow Premier League title race wide open – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680291/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 14:54:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680291/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Barney Ronay, and Seb Hutchinson to discuss the weekend’s Premier League action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bayern Munich’s ‘mini-crisis’ and Liverpool roll on – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680292/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 14:30:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680292/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Nicky Bandini, and Archie Rhind-Tutt to discuss the latest Champions League action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Manchester City and Kylian Mbappé look magnifique – Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680293/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 14:28:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680293/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Barry Glendenning, Philippe Auclair, Mark Langdon and Sid Lowe to discuss the latest Champions League action. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>As Manchester United falter again, will Wolves go fourth? - Football Weekly | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680294/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 13:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680294/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Jonathan Wilson, Troy Townsend and Paul MacInnes after a busy weekend at both ends of the Premier League table. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Martinelli mayhem and Chelsea’s Club World Cup bid – Football Weekly Extra | Football Weekly</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1608680295/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 14:30:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1608680295/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Rushden is joined by Lars Sivertsen, Robyn Cowen and Nick Ames to discuss the midweek Premier League fixtures and we get an update on the Club World Cup from Jacob Steinberg. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/footballweeklypod
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>