<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Real Survival Stories on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/real-survival-stories/</link><description>Recent content in Real Survival Stories on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:01:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/real-survival-stories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Battered by a Megastorm: Yacht Race Catastrophe | Real Survival Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6207610001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6207610001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick Ward is a young English sailor chasing a lifetime ambition, as he competes in one of the world’s elite yacht races. But out in the Celtic Sea, he and his crewmates find themselves caught in a once-in-a-generation storm. For hours they’ll fight together, side by side. But after one wave too many, Nick will be left to face this life-or-death struggle alone… A Noiser production, written by Dan Smith.</description></item><item><title>Snowboard Misadventure: Off-Piste Odyssey (Part 2 of 2) | Real Survival Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6207610002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6207610002/</guid><description>Podcast Description We return to Eric LeMarque, whose ordeal on Mammoth Mountain is far from over. Before he can even think about navigating his way to safety, he has to survive the raging torrent he’s fallen into. And it’s not just the icy clutches of the river. There’s also the 80-foot waterfall that lies downstream… A Noiser production, written by Joe Viner. For more on Eric’s story, read 6 Below: Miracle on the Mountain.</description></item><item><title>Snowboard Misadventure: Last Man on the Mountain (Part 1 of 2) | Real Survival Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6207610003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6207610003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eric LeMarque is a former professional ice hockey player, an Olympian who’s tasted incredible highs in his sport. But in 2004, his life is spiralling out of control. Hoping to escape his demons, he takes a snowboarding trip to Mammoth Mountain. After one run too many, he’ll find himself lost in a sprawling alpine wilderness, where the cold isn’t the only thing that bites… A Noiser production, written by Joe Viner.</description></item><item><title>Swallowed by a Hippo: Zambezi River Safari | Real Survival Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6207610004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6207610004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Paul Templer has one of the most wholesome jobs imaginable: paddling entranced visitors along Africa’s beautiful Zambezi River to the majestic Victoria Falls. But one day, his tour party is attacked… by a ferocious bull hippopotamus. As panic descends, Paul must do his utmost to ensure no man is left behind… A Noiser production, written by Susan Allott. For more on Paul’s story, read Marked for Life: Finding Grace and Grit Where You Least Expect It.</description></item><item><title>‘Beware of Alligators’ | Real Survival Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6207610005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6207610005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeffrey Heim spends every minute of his free time pursuing his passion: scouring Florida’s waterways for fossilised shark teeth. But on one river diving expedition, he encroaches on the territory of a living, thriving, reptilian predator. With barely time to think, let alone react, Jeffrey’s survival will hinge on decisions made in the blink of an eye. A Noiser production, written by Joe Viner. For ad-free listening, bonus material and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Pacific Castaways: Adrift on the Ocean (Part 2 of 2) | Real Survival Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6207610006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6207610006/</guid><description>Podcast Description We return to the shipwrecked crew of the Lucette. After their yacht was sunk by killer whales, the Robertsons have failed to flag down a passing ship. Now, with just a raft and a dinghy to carry them, the castaways must summon their resilience and focus on Plan B: navigating six hundred miles back to dry land… You can see the Robertsons’ tiny dinghy at the National Maritime Museum in Falmouth, UK: nmmc.</description></item><item><title>Pacific Castaways: Family Shipwrecked (Part 1 of 2) | Real Survival Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6207610007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6207610007/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s one of the all-time, epic survival stories. In 1971, Douglas Robertson is just a teenager when he and his family embark on the trip of a lifetime. Their aim is to sail around the globe. But when their small yacht is sunk in the middle of the Pacific Ocean, their dream of circumnavigation turns into a nightmare of self-preservation. The Robertsons must stick together and battle extraordinary adversity as a family.</description></item><item><title>Survival Expert Trapped in the Wild | Real Survival Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6207610008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6207610008/</guid><description>Podcast Description As an outdoors survivalist, Ken Hildebrand believes he’s prepared for any eventuality. But when he upends his quad bike on a remote mountain pass, his skills and training are strained to the limit. Trapped underneath the vehicle, can he stay calm and put theory into practice? And with his gear tantalisingly out of reach, can he improvise a solution to each new challenge that arises? A Noiser production, written by Susan Allott.</description></item><item><title>Clinging to a Mountain: Ski Trip Gone Wrong | Real Survival Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6207610009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6207610009/</guid><description>Podcast Description A young college graduate, Jean Muenchrath, embarks on a cross country skiing trip with her boyfriend. Their thrilling adventure is all going to plan, until it isn’t. When an enormous weather front engulfs Mount Whitney, the young couple are forced into a rapid, unplanned descent. Their trip of a lifetime has become an epic fight against the elements. Jean must dig deep to find an inner strength she never knew she had… For more on this incredible story, read If I Live Until Morning: A True Story of Adventure, Tragedy and Transformation.</description></item><item><title>Lost Hiker: Alone in the Desert | Real Survival Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6207610010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6207610010/</guid><description>Podcast Description A momentary lapse in concentration nearly costs a hiker his life. One wrong turn takes Ed Rosenthal off the beaten track and into the desert. As he scrambles to find the path, he’s drawn deeper and deeper into the wild. Stumbling ever onwards, the endless march will push his body to its limits, taking his mind to profound and unexpected places… For more on Ed’s amazing story, read Salvation Canyon: A True Story of Desert Survival in Joshua Tree.</description></item><item><title>Mineshaft Accident: Digging for Gold, Encircled by Rattlesnakes | Real Survival Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6207610011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6207610011/</guid><description>Podcast Description They call it ‘gold fever’ and John Waddell has got it bad. In 2018, the Arizona prospector takes his life in his hands when he explores an ancient, abandoned gold mine. His curiosity leads him deep underground and into a life or death struggle. Stuck 100 feet down the shaft, will anyone find him before it’s too late? And as the daylight fades, what unseen dangers lurk in the darkness?</description></item><item><title>Ravine Rescue: Canine Hero | Real Survival Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6207610012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6207610012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Danelle Ballengee is an endurance athlete, an experienced trail-runner who knows the Utah backcountry like the back of her hand. But when a training run through the sandstone mesas goes disastrously wrong, she’s left immobile and incapacitated. Trapped in a ravine, there is just the faintest glimmer of hope. Danelle will come to realise that her loyal pooch, Taz, could offer a moonshot chance of survival… A Noiser production, written by Joe Viner.</description></item><item><title>Helicopter Down Inside Hawaiian Volcano | Real Survival Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6207610013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6207610013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris Duddy is a young camera assistant shooting on location in Hawaii for a Hollywood film. But he’s cast in his very own disaster story when his helicopter crashes inside an active volcano. With toxic gases swirling around and the lava lake bubbling below, the sheer crater wall offers the only route out… A Noiser production, written by Sarah Ward. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Mayday in Africa: Crash-Landing on the Savannah | Real Survival Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6207610014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6207610014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Greg Rasmussen is a wildlife conservationist, a man dedicated to protecting endangered species. But when he crashes his light aircraft deep in the Zimbabwean bush, he’ll become a prisoner in the landscape he strives to preserve. It’s a place known for breathtaking safari. But Greg must deal with life-threatening injuries and the searing heat. And then, as night closes in, the predators start circling… Find out more about Greg’s conservation work at www.</description></item><item><title>Canoeing Trip Wildfire: Inferno in Paradise | Real Survival Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6207610015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6207610015/</guid><description>Podcast Description A couple’s serene vacation is thrown into chaos by a terrifying wildfire. Julie &amp;amp; Greg Welch are oblivious as they paddle deep into nature and far away from civilisation. Soon they will find themselves surrounded by a 20-foot wall of flames. With daylight disappearing and smoke filling the air, they’ll need a miracle to make it out alive… A Noiser production, written by Susan Allott. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Mountain Blizzard: Stuck in a Snow Cave | Real Survival Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6207610016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6207610016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mark Inglis is a search &amp;amp; rescue mountaineer. It’s his job to save other people. But on a routine practice mission, he’ll find himself in deep trouble. Caught in a whiteout halfway up New Zealand’s highest peak, Mark and his colleague Phil take refuge in a tiny snow cave. But as the hours tick by into days, how long can they hunker down before their bodies, and minds, give out?</description></item><item><title>Grizzly Bear Attack: Ambushed in the Rockies | Real Survival Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6207610017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6207610017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeremy Evans is a man most at home hiking and fishing in the Canadian wilderness. But one day, on a solo camping trip, he stumbles across a Grizzly and her cub. Scarcely surviving a frenzied attack, Jeremy is left battered and broken. Despite everything, something inside will compel him to just keep going, driving him homewards… Many thanks to Jeremy Evans. For more on his story, read Mauled: Lessons Learned from a Grizzly Bear Attack.</description></item><item><title>Glacier Escape: Trapped Under the Ice | Real Survival Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6207610018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6207610018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two friends embark on an awe-inspiring trip into the mountains. But then, one false step sends Jim Davidson and Mike Price plummeting into a crevasse. Trapped deep beneath the surface of a glacier, surrounded by sheer walls of ice, Jim will come to realise there’s only one way he can possibly escape… Many thanks to Jim Davidson. For more about this epic story, read The Ledge: An Inspirational Story of Friendship and Survival by Jim Davidson and Kevin Vaughan.</description></item><item><title>Abandon Ship: Stranded in the South Atlantic (Part 2 of 2) | Real Survival Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6207610019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6207610019/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Sudur Havid is submerged beneath the freezing waters of the South Atlantic. As the captain and first mate struggle to respond, it falls to Matt to coordinate a last-ditch effort to abandon ship. But in these Antarctic waters, with woefully inadequate clothing and survival gear, they’re about to be cast adrift in a raft no bigger than a child’s paddling pool… Many thanks to Matt Lewis. For more on his story, read Last Man Off: A True Story of Disaster and Survival on the Antarctic Seas.</description></item><item><title>Abandon Ship: Sinking in 30-Foot Waves (Part 1 of 2) | Real Survival Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6207610020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6207610020/</guid><description>Podcast Description A rookie sailor goes looking for adventure in the remote waters of the sub-Antarctic… and finds it. Matt Lewis joins the crew of a deep sea fishing trawler sailing out of Cape Town. But far out in the South Atlantic, a polar storm will catch them all unawares. Battered by giant swells, before they know what’s hit them they’re taking on water. The ship is going down… Many thanks to Matt Lewis.</description></item><item><title>Paragliding Disaster: Sucked Towards the Stratosphere | Real Survival Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6207610021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6207610021/</guid><description>Podcast Description A picturesque paragliding flight becomes a terrifying nightmare when a massive storm rolls in. Sucked into the clouds, Ewa Wiśnierska is pelted by hailstones the size of oranges. With lightning crackling all around her, she is sent hurtling upwards - still clinging to her parachute. Soon, she’ll be higher than Everest and nearing the cruising altitude of a jumbo jet. Covered in ice, approaching the edge of the breathable atmosphere… how on earth does she make it down in one piece?</description></item><item><title>Real Survival Stories | Real Survival Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6207610022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 11:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6207610022/</guid><description>Podcast Description The new show from award-winning podcasters, Noiser. Launching July 27th, 2023. Early access to new episodes for Noiser+ subscribers. For advertising enquiries email info@adelicious.fm Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>