<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>DeepLearningAI on SWIEST - Transcripts 路 Screenplays 路 Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/deeplearningai/</link><description>Recent content in DeepLearningAI on SWIEST - Transcripts 路 Screenplays 路 Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 17:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/deeplearningai/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DeepLearningAI - ChatGPT Prompt Engineering for Developers - Conclusion</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3001800009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001800009/</guid><description>Congratulations on making it to the end of this short course.
In summary, in this short course you&amp;rsquo;ve
learned about two key principles for prompting. Write
clear and specific instructions, and when it&amp;rsquo;s appropriate, give the
model time to think. You also learned about iterative
prompt development and how having a
process to get to the prompt that&amp;rsquo;s right for
your application is key. And we went through a few capabilities of large</description></item><item><title>DeepLearningAI - ChatGPT Prompt Engineering for Developers - Chatbot</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3001800008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001800008/</guid><description>One of the exciting things about a large
language model is you can use it to build a custom chatbot
with only a modest amount of effort. ChatGPT, the web interface,
is a way for you to have a conversational interface,
a conversation via a large language model. But one of the
cool things is you can also use a large language model to
build your custom chatbot to maybe play the role of an AI</description></item><item><title>DeepLearningAI - ChatGPT Prompt Engineering for Developers - Expanding</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3001800007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001800007/</guid><description>Expanding is the task of taking a short piece of text,
such as a set of instructions or a list of topics,
and having the large language model generate a
longer piece of text, such as an email or
an essay about some topic. There are some great uses of this,
such as if you use a large language model as a brainstorming partner.
But I just also want to acknowledge that</description></item><item><title>DeepLearningAI - ChatGPT Prompt Engineering for Developers - Transforming</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3001800006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001800006/</guid><description>Large language models are very good at transforming its input to a
different format, such as inputting a
piece of text in one language and transforming
it or translating it to a different language,
or helping with spelling and grammar corrections,
so taking as input a piece of text that may not be
fully grammatical and helping you to fix that up a bit,
or even transforming formats such as inputting HTML and</description></item><item><title>DeepLearningAI - ChatGPT Prompt Engineering for Developers - Inferring</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3001800005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001800005/</guid><description>This next video is on inferring. I like to think
of these tasks where the model takes a text as input and
performs some kind of analysis. So this could be extracting labels,
extracting names, kind of understanding the
sentiment of a text, that kind of thing.
So if you want to extract a sentiment, positive or negative,
with a piece of text, in the traditional
machine learning workflow, you&amp;rsquo;d have to collect the label data set, train</description></item><item><title>DeepLearningAI - ChatGPT Prompt Engineering for Developers - Summarizing</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3001800004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001800004/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s so much text in today&amp;rsquo;s world, pretty much none of us have
enough time to read all the things we wish we had time to. So one
of the most exciting applications I&amp;rsquo;ve seen of
large language models is to use it to
summarise text. And this is something that I&amp;rsquo;m seeing multiple teams
build into multiple software applications. You can do this
in the Chat GPT Web Interface. I do this all</description></item><item><title>DeepLearningAI - ChatGPT Prompt Engineering for Developers - Iterative</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3001800003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001800003/</guid><description>When I&amp;rsquo;ve been building applications with
large language models, I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;ve ever come to the prompt that
I ended up using in the final application on my first attempt.
And this isn&amp;rsquo;t what matters. As long as you have a good process
to iteratively make your prompt better, then you&amp;rsquo;ll
be able to come to something that works
well for the task you want to achieve.
You may have heard me say that when I train a machine learning model,</description></item><item><title>DeepLearningAI - ChatGPT Prompt Engineering for Developers - Guidelines</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3001800002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001800002/</guid><description>In this video, Isa will present some guidelines for prompting to
help you get the results that you want.
In particular, she&amp;rsquo;ll go over two key principles for how to write
prompts to prompt engineer effectively. And
a little bit later, when she&amp;rsquo;s going over the Jupyter Notebook examples, I&amp;rsquo;d
also encourage you to feel free to pause the video every
now and then to run the code yourself so you can see</description></item><item><title>DeepLearningAI - ChatGPT Prompt Engineering for Developers - Introduction</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3001800001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001800001/</guid><description>Welcome to this course on ChatGPT prompt engineering
for developers. I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to have with
me Isa Fulford to teach this along with me. She
is a member of the technical staff of
OpenAI and had built the popular ChatGPT
retrieval plugin and a large part of the work has been teaching
people how to use LLM or large language
model technology in products. She&amp;rsquo;s also contributed to the
OpenAI cookbook that teaches people prompting.</description></item></channel></rss>