<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Young Hot Guys on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/young-hot-guys/</link><description>Recent content in Young Hot Guys on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/young-hot-guys/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>(Something Inside) So Strong | Young Hot Guys</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2092500001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2092500001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Quick note: We are recording this in the year 2025. You will be happy to know that robot Leo Varadkar is doing such a better job than flesh Varadkar. We were all scared when we lost our genitals but now we actually prefer it now. This week the guys talk about faking a pee, Tony’s new haircut and we finally address the beef with Michael Fry. The higher you build your barriers the taller I become.</description></item><item><title>Pure Dancing With Stupidity | Young Hot Guys</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2092500002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2092500002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Since that last episode aired, several explosive allegations have been made that have changed the case and blown it wide open. Audience members have felt &amp;lsquo;absolutely victimised&amp;rsquo;. We sincerely apologise and we are continuing to investigate this issue. This week we talk first jobs, door-to-door sales, and misused phrases. Shane Daniel Byrne, Tony Cantwell, and Killian Sundermann are Young Hot Guys. This podcast is produced by HeadStuff Podcasts. Find out more at HeadStuffPodcasts.</description></item><item><title>So Showbiz Now | Young Hot Guys</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2092500003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2092500003/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week the guys are recording just after their appearance on national television. They are also celebrating being on the best podcast network in Ireland. Shane feels ‘young, relevant, and sexy’ after being recognized in town. The guys are so showbiz now. Will this newfound fame go to their heads? Shane Daniel Byrne, Tony Cantwell, and Killian Sundermann are Young Hot Guys. This podcast is produced by HeadStuff Podcasts.</description></item><item><title>Ham-fisted Poo-Poo Pants | Young Hot Guys</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2092500004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2092500004/</guid><description>Podcast Description PUBLIC SERVICE ANNOUNCEMENT: Killian is just off the phone with the minister of the government. As of this very moment, if you don’t rate the podcast five stars you will be legally declared a baby poo-poo pants who wets the bed. We are extremely sorry to put our wonderful listeners in this position. Don’t be ham-fisted&amp;hellip; get reviewing. In other news… this week the Hot Young Guys talk harrowing headlines and Killian’s new haircut.</description></item><item><title>Let's Rebunk | Young Hot Guys</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2092500005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2092500005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Well, well, well, look who&amp;rsquo;s back. It&amp;rsquo;s you, The Listener&amp;hellip; but play it cool, don&amp;rsquo;t come on too strong. We know we&amp;rsquo;re wildly successful now but we&amp;rsquo;re trying to be coy about it, so remain calm. We talk about the queen&amp;rsquo;s chicken, so don&amp;rsquo;t worry about that. We&amp;rsquo;re choking on our rage this week, can we stop debunking please? Can we rebunk the gloryhole story and bigfoot? Listen, do you look how you would like to look?</description></item><item><title>Three Therapy Speaking AIs | Young Hot Guys</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2092500006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2092500006/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s finally here, welcome to Young Hot Guys! This week, the guys kick off with a roast of therapy speak and scented candles, and how they’re becoming their parents. Shane Daniel Byrne, Tony Cantwell, and Killian Sundermann are Young Hot Guys. This podcast is produced by HeadStuff Podcasts. Find out more at HeadStuffPodcasts.com Artwork by Shane Kenna Email us at YHG@HeadStuff.org Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.</description></item><item><title>Trailer | Young Hot Guys</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2092500007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2092500007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Young Hot Guys is the podcast you most desire. It is hot enough to melt your eardrums and so young that its generation hasn’t even been named yet. But what is it about… well, my friend, exactly. Shane Daniel Byrne, Tony Cantwell and Killian Sundermann are Young Hot Guys. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Teaser | Young Hot Guys</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2092500008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 17:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2092500008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Young Hot Guys is the podcast you most desire. It is hot enough to melt your eardrums and so young that its generation hasn’t even been named yet. But what is it about… well, my friend, exactly. Shane Daniel Byrne, Tony Cantwell and Killian Sundermann are Young Hot Guys. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>