<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dish on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/dish/</link><description>Recent content in Dish on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 01:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/dish/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Massimo Bottura, a miso pork ramen and a pinot noir | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome the world’s number 1 chef to Dish HQ.
Massimo Bottura hails from the Emilia-Romagna region of Italy, the nation’s food capital. A renowned restaurateur, hotelier and contemporary art aficionado, Massimo established Osteria Francescana, his three-Michelin-star restaurant in Modena, in 1995. The eatery was voted the world&amp;rsquo;s best restaurant in 2016 and 2018 and features in the Netflix show, Chef’s Table. Massimo Bottura is highly respected for his innovative approach to Italian cuisine, combining tradition with modern techniques.</description></item><item><title>Joe Wicks, spaghetti carbonara and a pinot gris | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome the UK’s favourite PE teacher to Dish HQ.
The Body Coach began his career as a personal trainer in south-west London in 2012. Joe Wicks harnessed the power of social media and soon thousands of people were following his food and fitness content. During the Covid pandemic, he launched PE with Joe and live-streamed daily workouts for kids stuck at home, which became a global hit and raised money for the NHS.</description></item><item><title>Cheese and wine special with Helen McGinn and a listener Q&amp;A | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome a wine expert to Dish HQ.
Helen McGinn is an award-winning author, drinks writer and TV wine presenter. Having cut her teeth as a supermarket wine buyer, she went on to found a blog, The Knackered Mother’s Wine Club, which has since become a best-selling book. Helen is the much-loved wine expert on BBC1’s Saturday Kitchen and writes a monthly wine column for Waitrose Food Magazine.</description></item><item><title>Maggie Aderin-Pocock, spiced lamb &amp; plum tagine and prosecco | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome a professional stargazer to Dish HQ.
Dr. Maggie Aderin-Pocock MBE is a renowned space and science educator and a prominent figure in the field of astronomy. She began watching the skies from her council flat in North London as a child and went on to study physics and mechanical engineering at Imperial College London. It is Maggie’s ambition to go to space one day and last year she was named a ‘Barbie Role Model’ for her work promoting science careers to girls.</description></item><item><title>Miriam Margolyes, sage and rosemary chicken stew and mash potato | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome their most anticipated guest so far to Dish HQ.
Miriam Margolyes OBE is renowned for her acting career spanning over five decades, but it is her inimitable sense of humour that has earned her a special place in the hearts of audiences worldwide. Miriam was the voice of the Cadbury’s caramel bunny in 1990, won a BAFTA for her role in The Age of Innocence in 1994 and portrayed Professor Sprout in the Harry Potter franchise.</description></item><item><title>Monty Don, Daube de Boeuf with macaroni gratin and a pinot noir | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome the UK’s favourite gardener to DISH HQ.
Monty Don OBE is a horticulturist, broadcaster and writer. He made his TV debut on the gardening segment on This Morning, which led to further work with the BBC and Channel 4. In 2002, he was announced as the new lead presenter on Gardeners’ World, taking over from Alan Titchmarsh, and was the first self-taught horticulturist/presenter in the show&amp;rsquo;s history.</description></item><item><title>Kirsty Young, Lebanese-style lamb and aubergine stew and a primitivo | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome broadcasting royalty to DISH HQ.
Kirsty Young began her career at BBC Radio Scotland. From there, she went into television news, presenting the flagship programmes on Channel 5 and ITV. In 2006, Kirsty was announced as Sue Lawley’s replacement on BBC Radio 4’s iconic show Desert Island Discs. Over a 12-year tenure, she interviewed the likes of David Beckham, David Attenborough and Dame Judi Dench.</description></item><item><title>Sara Cox, mackerel with a watermelon rojak and a rosé | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome a TV and radio broadcaster to DISH HQ.
Sara Cox is a proud northern lass from Bolton and began her career as a model in her teens. With the chops for more, Sara auditioned for The Girlie Show on Channel 4 and didn’t take no for an answer. From there, work on the wireless beckoned and she became the host of the Radio 1 Breakfast Show in the year 2000.</description></item><item><title>Rose Matafeo, marmalade pork belly with soy and ginger and an Asahi | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome a BAFTA-nominated actor, writer and comedian to DISH HQ.
Rose Matafeo was born in Auckland and began doing stand-up at 15. She moved to the UK in 2015 and three years later her debut show Horndog won the Best Comedy show award at the Edinburgh Festival Fringe. Having conquered the stage, Rose turned her attention to TV writing and, while on a long-haul flight, created the super successful Starstruck with her best friend Alice Snedden.</description></item><item><title>Richard Corrigan &amp; Valentine Warner, pappardelle with fennel &amp; sausage ragu and a malbec | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome two chefs to DISH HQ
Richard Corrigan is an Irish chef and restaurateur who has had an illustrious career in food. Over the years he has gained Michelin stars and cooked for the Queen and Barack Obama. He runs four restaurants in London - Bentley’s Oyster Bar &amp;amp; Grill, Corrigan’s Mayfair and Daffodil Mulligan - and has recently opened The Portrait Restaurant atop the National Portrait Gallery.</description></item><item><title>Joanne McNally, the perfect roast chicken sandwich and a wine tasting | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome a comedian and podcaster to DISH HQ.
Joanne McNally has been touring her record-breaking stand up show The Prosecco Express for the last two years and is about to embark on the US leg of the tour. It’s clear her star is on the rise as Variety has recently named her one of their Top 10 comedians to watch in 2023. When she’s not on stage, Joanne co-hosts her super successful podcast My Therapist Ghosted Me with Vogue Williams which is coming to a venue near you soon.</description></item><item><title>AJ Odudu and Will Best, a Mexican feast and fiery lime margaritas | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome the new hosts of Big Brother to DISH HQ
AJ Odudu and Will Best are HUGE Big Brother fans and both have previous when it comes to the original reality TV show. AJ presented Big Brother&amp;rsquo;s Bit on the Side, alongside Emma Willis and Rylan Clark in 2013, with Will appearing as a regular panellist over the years. AJ co-hosted a one-off revival of The Big Breakfast alongside Mo Gilligan in 2021 and more recently appeared on this year’s Eurovision.</description></item><item><title>The Whitehalls, plaice with buttery capers &amp; shallots and a rosé | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome Michael and Hilary Whitehall to DISH HQ.
Before making his name as Jack Whitehall’s TV travel companion, Michael Whitehall had an illustrious career as a theatrical agent and producer. His clients included Daniel Day-Lewis, Judi Dench, Colin Firth and Michael Fassbender. He and Hilary met while she was in search of new representation, while he, she says, was looking for a wife. Jack and Michael have made five series of Travels With My Father for Netflix and co-authored How To Survive Family Holidays with Hilary.</description></item><item><title>Gordon Ramsay, crab linguine with chilli &amp; garlic and a Soave | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 4 kicks off as Nick and Angela welcome Gordon Ramsay to DISH HQ.
Gordon Ramsay OBE is arguably the most famous chef in the world. His global restaurant empire has been awarded 17 Michelin stars; he has hosted some of the biggest shows on UK and US TV, including Hell’s Kitchen and Kitchen Nightmares; and he has a string of bestselling books. The internet loves Gordon Ramsay and over 60 million people follow him on social media.</description></item><item><title>Candice Brathwaite, spaghetti agli scampi and a Pinot Gris | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome an author and podcaster to DISH HQ for the final episode of series 3.
Candice Brathwaite is a critically acclaimed writer, journalist and TV presenter. A self-confessed fashion and beauty addict, Candice often appears on ITV&amp;rsquo;s Lorraine and has designed a bestselling handbag collection with the sustainable accessories label, Been. Her first book, I Am Not Your Baby Mother, made it onto the Sunday Times Bestsellers List in 2020, and her first foray into fiction, a young adult novel called Cuts Both Ways, was released in August 2022.</description></item><item><title>Stephen and Anita Mangan, Palestinian slow-roast lamb and an organic red | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome their first siblings to DISH HQ.
Stephen Mangan is an actor, writer and presenter known for his roles in Green Wing with Olivia Colman, I’m Alan Partridge and The Split opposite Nicola Walker. He currently presents Portrait Artist of the Year with Joan Bakewell.
Anita Mangan is an illustrator who has designed over 70 cookbooks including Kelis&amp;rsquo; My Life on a Plate, Gizzi Erskine’s Seasons Greetings and Fearne Cotton’s Cook Happy Cook Healthy.</description></item><item><title>Clara Amfo, cherry &amp; quinoa tabbouleh with goat's cheese and a cosmopolitan | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome radio royalty to DISH HQ.
Clara Amfo is an award-winning broadcaster, podcaster and television presenter best known for her work on BBC Radio 1, where she now presents Future Sounds. Clara has interviewed some of the biggest names in music including Jay-Z, Kendrick Lemar, Sir Elton John, and Billie Eilish who personally requested Clara for her LA Special. On her podcast This City she chats with guests like Louis Theroux, Little Simz and Edward Enninful who share their stories of life in London.</description></item><item><title>Caitlin Moran, egg &amp; dill salad with smoked mackerel and an Albariño | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome a bestselling author and journalist to DISH HQ.
Caitlin Moran grew up in Wolverhampton in a family of eight kids and spent most of her time reading books at the local library instead of attending school. Unsurprisingly, Caitlin had written her first novel by the time she was 13. She moved to London at 16 and began writing for Melody Maker where she met her husband, Pete Paphides.</description></item><item><title>Tim Minchin, chargrilled vegetable &amp; orecchiette salad with pesto and a Pinot Noir | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome their first Grammy-nominated guest to DISH HQ.
Writer, actor and composer Tim Minchin was born in the UK and raised in Perth, Western Australia. He gained notoriety when he won the Perrier Best Newcomer Award at the Edinburgh Fringe Festival in 2005 and his (unplanned) career in comedy took off. These days, Tim MInchin is busy collecting accolades for his theatre shows, winning a Tony and an Olivier for Matilda: The Musical.</description></item><item><title>Chris Evans, orange &amp; herb butter spatchcock chicken and a Chardonnay | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela are overjoyed to welcome their biggest fan to DISH HQ.
In 1983 a young lad from Warrington began his professional career on Piccadilly Radio in Manchester. Forty years on and Chris Evans is a legend of TV and Radio broadcasting, with the Big Breakfast, the Radio 1 Breakfast Show and TFI Friday garnering cult status. Chris has also found time to pen some books on his incredible life and his passion, running, which he took up age 47.</description></item><item><title>Andi &amp; Miquita Oliver, sweet and sour pork belly and a Viognier | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome their friends Andi and Miquita Oliver to DISH HQ.
Andi Oliver is a chef, broadcaster, author and restaurateur. She is best known as the presenter of Great British Menu, having previously also been a judge. Andi has just released her first cookbook The Pepperpot Diaries: Stories From My Caribbean Table. It&amp;rsquo;s a biographical journey of food and family and is available now.
Miquita Oliver is a television presenter and radio personality, best known for hosting T4 in the early noughties.</description></item><item><title>Chris &amp; Rosie Ramsey, a tomahawk steak and a Cabernet Sauvignon | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 06:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris and Rosie Ramsey, a tomahawk steak and a Cabernet Sauvignon
Nick and Angela are joined by podcast mega stars Chris and Rosie Ramsey.
Chris and Rosie have presented the award-winning podcast Shagged. Married. Annoyed for the last four years, amassing a huge following. The pair met when they were teenagers, attending the same college. They got married in 2014 and have two sons, Robin and Rafe. Before podcasting, Rosie presented a radio show on Capital North East while Chris was in comedy full time.</description></item><item><title>Ruby Wax, spiced cauliflower &amp; pomegranate salad and a mimosa mocktail | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela are joined by broadcasting icon Ruby Wax.
Ruby Wax is an actress, comedian, writer, television personality and mental health campaigner. Her life in show business began at the Royal Shakespeare Company and from there the lures of TV beckoned. Ruby presented shows like The Full Wax and Ruby Wax Meets in the nineties and noughties, interviewing Donald Trump, OJ Simpson, Goldie Hawn and Pamela Anderson in her inimitable style.</description></item><item><title>Charlotte Church, a savoury cheese cake and a pinot noir | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480024/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Nick and Angela welcome Charlotte Church to Dish HQ.
Charlotte Church released her debut album Voice of an Angel in 1998 - she was twelve. Since then, she has become one of the most recognisable names in music, selling more than ten million albums worldwide. Charlotte has performed for Queen Elizabeth, the Pope and at George Bush’s inauguration. She fronted The Charlotte Church Show for three seasons and won Best Female Newcomer award at the British Comedy Awards in 2006.</description></item><item><title>Comedian Nish Kumar, gnocchi with roasted red pepper and chilli pesto | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480025/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Nick and Angela welcome Nish Kumar to Dish HQ.
Nish is a critically acclaimed comic who has won rave reviews and prestigious award nominations for his stand-up. Away from the comedy circuit, he is a regular on TV shows like 8 out of 10 Cats Does Countdown, Live at the Apollo and Taskmaster, and can often be heard presenting The News Quiz on BBC Radio 4.</description></item><item><title>Aisling Bea, a tuna niçoise and a whiskey | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome comedian Aisling Bea to Dish HQ.
Aisling is an award-winning comedian, actor and writer. She created, wrote and starred in the comedy series This Way Up on Channel 4 with Sharon Horgan. Aisling also starred in the Netflix show Living with Myself alongside Paul Rudd in 2019 and 2020, winning a BAFTA for Breakthrough Talent.
Angela prepares a tasty niçoise salad with Jersey Royals and tuna steak.</description></item><item><title>Scott Mills, sea bass with sauce vierge, new potatoes &amp; asparagus | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480027/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480027/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s Eurovision week and Nick and Angela are joined by superfan Scott Mills.
Scott fulfilled a childhood dream when he joined BBC Radio 1 in 1998 – and he&amp;rsquo;s now the network&amp;rsquo;s longest serving daytime presenter. He has won many awards for his work, including an ARIA for Best Music Entertainment Show in 2021. Scott made the move to BBC Radio 2 last year, taking over from Steve Wright in the afternoon.</description></item><item><title>Dame Prue Leith, Jeremy Lee’s spring salmagundi and herby rack of lamb | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480028/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s Coronation week and Nick and Angela are joined by food royalty, Dame Prue Leith.
Prue Leith, DBE is an octogenarian with no intention of slowing down. Her illustrious career in food includes restaurants, cookery schools, writing and TV. She has published eight novels, a memoir, and fourteen cookbooks. Her latest, Bliss on Toast, was published in 2022.
Best known as a judge on the Great British Bake Off, last year she also presented a gardening programme, Prue’s Great Garden Plot, with her husband, and this year will judge the American equivalent of Bake Off.</description></item><item><title>Rick Edwards &amp; Emer Kenny, five-spice duck with stir fried cucumber &amp; cashews | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480029/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela are joined by hilarious husband and wife duo, Rick Edwards and Emer Kenny.
Rick Edwards graduated with a Natural Science degree from Cambridge University but soon changed tack in favour of a job in TV. Rick presented T4 with Nick for four years and then hosted Tool Academy on E4. He can now be found waking up the nation on the BBC Radio 5 Live breakfast show with Rachel Burden.</description></item><item><title>Adam Hills, sticky pork ribs and a spicy cabbage salad. | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480030/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela are joined by Aussie comedian and BBQ King, Adam Hills, MBE.
Adam Hills began performing comedy at 19, toured ten solo shows internationally and presented several TV shows in Australia before he made the move to the UK. In 2012, he was asked to front The Last Leg with Alex Brooker and Josh Widdicombe, a show created to run alongside the London Paralympics coverage on Channel 4.</description></item><item><title>Alex Jones, puttanesca and a Chianti | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480031/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Angela and Nick are joined by national treasure, Alex Jones.
Alex Jones’ route to The One Show couch was far from linear. She began her career by getting fired, twice, but returned to work unphased, prompting the production company to suggest a screen test. Alex aced that and having found her niche, was soon presenting a dating show in Magaluf. Alex joined The One Show in 2010 and appeared on Strictly the following year.</description></item><item><title>Rob Delaney and a braised leg of lamb with mint, parsley &amp; almond pesto | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480032/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dish is back! Season three kicks off with US comedian, writer and author, Rob Delaney.
Twitter launched Rob Delaney’s career in comedy and in 2012 he was named Funniest Person on Twitter by Comedy Central. In 2014, Rob and his wife Leah moved their family from Santa Monica to North London so he could co-write and co-star in Catastrophe with Sharon Horgan. The show ran for four series and the pair won a BAFTA for best comedy writer in 2016.</description></item><item><title>Spencer and Vogue, lamb and cheesy hasselback potatoes | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480033/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480033/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the final episode of season two, it’s a family affair at DISH HQ with Spencer, Vogue and baby Otto.
Angela and Nick host two stars that risked life and limb on reality tv. Now married, these two entrepreneurs have three kids and several podcasts between them: Spencer &amp;amp; Vogue, My Therapist Ghosted Me and 6 Degrees with Jamie and Spencer. Vogue also has her own fake tan range, Bare by Vogue while Spencer has his own low ABV spirits company, CleanCo, available at Waitrose.</description></item><item><title>Phil Wang, beef &amp; broccoli noodles and a beer | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480034/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome British-Malaysian comic Phil Wang.
While studying Engineering at Cambridge, Phil got a sniff of stand-up comedy and was hooked. In 2010 and 2011, he was voted funniest student in the UK and the MBA his mother had always dreamed of, was no longer on the table.
Phil has mastered all mediums, with Netflix specials and comedy panel shows like Taskmaster and Have I Got News For You under his belt.</description></item><item><title>Poppy O’Toole, a smoked aubergine salad and an English sparkling wine | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480035/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome young British chef and Potato Queen, Poppy O’Toole.
Michelin-trained internet sensation Poppy Cooks went viral last year and rose to culinary fame when she began posting easy-to-follow recipes on TikTok, including the infamous 15 hour potato. Poppy creates easy-to-follow tutorials which have amassed 300 million views on her channels since April 2020, when she lost her job due to the pandemic. Her debut cookbook Poppy Cooks: The Food You Need, breaks down her fine-dining roots and reimagines them in kitchens at home.</description></item><item><title>Vernon Kay, steak &amp; mushroom stroganoff and a malbec | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480036/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome presenter and proud Northerner, Vernon Kay.
Grimmy and Vernon first met when they presented T4 together back in their TV heydays, and later found themselves on back-to-back, on Saturday mornings on BBC Radio 1 - very challenging time slots for their active social lives. Vernon Kay is best known for iconic TV shows including All Star Family Fortunes, Just the Two of Us and Splash.</description></item><item><title>Annie MacManus, a vodka martini and scallops with lemon butter | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480037/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome DJ, broadcaster, author and one of Nick’s superstar friends, Annie MacManus.
Annie is a force in the music industry. For seventeen years, she was a pillar of BBC Radio, dedicating each show to championing the best in new music on programmes like Radio 1&amp;rsquo;s Future Sounds, Dance Party and, of course, her Sunday evening show with Grimmy - simply called Nick Grimshaw and Annie Mac.</description></item><item><title>Alison Hammond &amp; Dermot O’Leary and a Christmas grazing platter | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480038/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome their favourite TV duo to Casa Grimshaw.
From humble beginnings flipping burgers at Wembley stadium, Dermot O’Leary is now one of the biggest names in UK television. He began on T4, then played Big Brother’s Little Brother before The X Factor came knocking. Other presenting highlights include fronting the National Television Awards for the last ten years and Soccer Aid and the Baftas too. Not confined to one medium, Dermot&amp;rsquo;s dulcet tones can be heard on BBC Radio 2 on Saturday mornings and on his podcast, People just People, available on audible.</description></item><item><title>Hugh Bonneville, Champagne, and Christmas dinner | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Beloved British actor and now author, Hugh Bonneville visits Nick and Angela at casa Grimshaw.
Hugh has appeared in many iconic films opposite some of the greats of Hollywood, Notting Hill with Julia Roberts, Iris with Judi Dench, The Monuments Men with George Clooney, and the Paddington movies with everyone’s favourite bear.
He’s equally celebrated for his portrayal of Robert Crawley in TV drama Downton Abbey and its film adaptations, for which he received Golden Globe nominations, two Emmys and the cast won three SAG Awards for Outstanding Ensemble in a Drama Series.</description></item><item><title>Dame Mary Berry, mulled wine and a chicken, leek and mushroom puff pie | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome their very first Dame to DISH HQ.
The iconic food writer, baker and television presenter is synonymous with Christmas.
Mary Berry trained at the Cordon Bleu in Paris and the Bath School of Home Economics. Her passion for food quickly made her famous and over the last five decades she has been editor of food magazines, penned more than 75 cookbooks and become a much-loved star of the small screen.</description></item><item><title>Marcus Wareing, a Lancashire hotpot and a Chardonnay | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480041/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome Michelin star chef and author Marcus Wareing to DISH HQ. Marcus Wareing is the owner of and head chef at Marcus at The Berkeley Hotel. He was the first person Gordon Ramsay ever employed and, along with Angela, the trio have run some of the UK’s finest restaurants including, the Aubergine, L’Oranger and Pétrus.
You can catch Marcus on Masterchef: The Professionals and on Marcus Wareing: Tales from a Kitchen Garden on the BBC iPlayer.</description></item><item><title>Frankie Bridge, festive baked eggs and an English sparkling wine | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome pop star and Christmas angel Frankie Bridge!
Frankie was a member of not one, but two of the UK’s biggest groups, S Club Juniors and The Saturdays. Frankie’s had 19 UK Top 10 singles which is more than Taylor Swift, Katy Perry and Lady Gaga.
Having appeared on Celebrity MasterChef, I’m A Celebrity…and Strictly Come Dancing, Frankie’s infectious energy has made her a darling of the small screen.</description></item><item><title>Strictly stars Aljaž &amp; Janette and a one-pot paprika chicken &amp; orzo | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Please welcome to the DISH dining-room floor… Aljaž Škorjanec and Janette Manrara!
For eight years, this Strictly Come Dancing husband and wife team waltzed across our TV screens, with the adoring eyes of the nation upon them. Having both taken the decision to step away from Saturday nights, Janette now co-hosts Strictly Come Dancing: It Takes Two with Rylan, and Aljaž has been working on their brand-new stage show.</description></item><item><title>Martin Kemp and a creamy mushroom &amp; cavolo nero pasta | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 08:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Best known as the bassist in Spandau Ballet, Martin Kemp, alongside his brother, Gary, formed one of the most successful Brit pop bands of the 80s selling over 25 million albums worldwide. In the late 90s, Martin swapped the stage for the small screen and joined EastEnders as bad boy Steve Owen.
These days, Martin and his son Roman are regulars on Celebrity Gogglebox and he has just released his brand new book Ticket to the World: My 80s Story, an evocative memoir and joyous celebration of the culture of the decade.</description></item><item><title>Stanley Tucci, a negroni and spaghetti alle vongole | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480045/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome good friend and chicest man alive, Stanley Tucci.
Stanley is an award-winning actor and filmmaker. Nominated for an Oscar, Golden Globe, and BAFTA for The Lovely Bones (2009). The list of his outstanding performances is endless, The Hunger Games, Burlesque, The Devil Wears Prada and Julie &amp;amp; Julia, alongside the inimitable Meryl Streep.
Stanley’s success is not limited to the big screen either as he has won an Emmy for his TV show Stanley Tucci: Searching for Italy and recently starred in Inside Man on the BBC with David Tennant.</description></item><item><title>Dolly Alderton and a Tuscan-inspired fish stew | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480046/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome award-winning author, journalist, columnist, podcaster, screenwriter and foodie Dolly Alderton!
Her first book Everything I Know About Love became a top five Sunday Times bestseller in its first week of publication and won a National Book Award in 2018. She is the former co-host and co-creator of the podcast The High Low. Dolly’s first novel Ghosts was published in 2020 and this year, Everything I Know About Love was adapted into a BBC One TV Series.</description></item><item><title>Russell Howard, a cocido and a Rioja | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480047/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela are joined by stand-up comedian Russell Howard.
Russell is one of the world’s most successful comics. His TV show, The Russell Howard Hour, was once voted BBC 3’s best ever show, and you can catch it now on Sky Max Thursdays at 10.30pm. Tickets are now available for Russell Howard Live, his latest UK tour, which kicks off in March 2023.
As he is dairy and gluten free, Angela cooks Russell a tasty cocido (Spanish stew) with chorizo, white bean &amp;amp; pumpkin.</description></item><item><title>David Harewood, a steak sandwich and fries | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480048/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome another MBE to Dish HQ.
The incredible actor and author David Harewood brings some Hollywood to proceedings this week. Star of stage and screen, he has appeared in major TV shows like The Night Manager with Olivia Colman and Tom Hiddleston, Super Girl and the multi-award winning Homeland with Claire Danes and Damian Lewis. It is on stage, David says that he feels most at home, treading the boards in Othello and King Lear among others.</description></item><item><title>Yotam Ottolenghi &amp; Noor Murad and creamy pasta with chard &amp; lemon | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480049/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome culinary greatness to DISH HQ.
It’s fair to say that this chef, restaurateur and author has transformed the way the world prepares and shares food. Yotam Ottolenghi creates a feast for the eyes (that INSTA grid) and a feast for our tables too. His cuisine is a masterclass in colour and combinations and he champions the humble vegetable like no other. Today he is joined by the esteemed recipe creator and head of his Test Kitchen, Noor Murad.</description></item><item><title>Rylan Clark, a burger and a beer | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480050/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480050/</guid><description>Podcast Description We launch season two with a national treasure…
Everyone’s favourite TV presenter joins Nick and Angela for a meal at DISH HQ.
It’s been ten years since his first appearance on the X Factor and Rylan Clark still has the nation in stitches. He has fronted TV shows like Supermarket Sweep, Ready Steady Cook and currently presents Strictly: It Takes Two with Janette Manrara and Saturday afternoons on BBC Radio 2.</description></item><item><title>Emeli Sandé, garlicky mushroom tagliatelle and a hungry T-Rex | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480051/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480051/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the final episode of season 1, Nick and Angela are joined by one of the UK’s most successful singer-songwriters.
Emeli Sandé’s awards are many and varied. She has number one albums, number one singles, BRITs and an MBE to her name. She released her debut album in 2011, performed at both the opening and closing ceremonies of the London Olympics in 2012 and ten years on, is now one of the UK’s most celebrated female vocalists.</description></item><item><title>Paul Chowdhry and crab, broad bean &amp; lemon pappardelle | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480052/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480052/</guid><description>Podcast Description A stand-up comedian sits down for some laughs with Nick and Angela.
Paul Chowdhry is the first British-Asian comic to sell out Wembley Arena. His show Live Innit was recently named Amazon Prime’s second most-watched comedy special. Paul also starred alongside Patrick Dempsey in hit show Devils on Sky Atlantic and is heading back on the road with his latest offering Family Friendly Comedian - tickets are available now.</description></item><item><title>Grace Dent and a spicy carrot &amp; avocado salad | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480053/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome their first restaurant critic to DISH HQ.
Fine dining is her bread and butter but Grace Dent says she’s just as happy eating quorn sausages with hot sauce. A writer, with 16 novels under her belt, Grace reviews restaurants for the Guardian and brings her food expertise to our TV screens on MasterChef. Catch Grace on her own podcast, Comfort Eating, wherever you get yours.</description></item><item><title>Jamie Laing and a watermelon salad | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480054/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Angela welcome a self-confessed ‘Groomzilla’ to Dish HQ.
Jamie Laing was ‘Made in Chelsea’. Buoyed by 10 years of reality TV, Jamie branched out, creating Candy Kittens, his vegan sweet brand. Since then, he jived his way to 2nd place on Strictly Come Dancing and presents many, many podcasts, including 6 Degrees with Jamie and Spencer and his latest, Nearly Weds with his fianceé Sophie Habboo.</description></item><item><title>Jayde Adams and steak with polenta mash | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480055/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Jayde Adams brings her West Country wit to Dish HQ this week. Dawn French calls her the ‘3rd funniest woman in the world’ and we know why. Her passion for acting, singing and comedy is rivalled only by her fondness for fodder. Jayde was nominated for best newcomer at the Edinburgh Fringe for her debut show (which is almost unheard of), won her first major acting role in 2021 on BBC 2’s ‘Alma’s Not Normal’ and is now on tour with the hilarious, ‘Men, I Can Save You’ - tickets can be found at jaydeadams.</description></item><item><title>Scarlett Moffatt and a speedy coconut &amp; prawn curry | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480056/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Scarlett Moffatt landed in our living rooms in 2014 and has never left. Stars of the smash hit show Gogglebox, the Moffatt family have entertained the nation with their hilarious observations on tv and of course life. Scarlett answered the call of the Jungle and was crowned Queen of I’m a Celebrity in 2016, from there she worked with Ant and Dec on that show and their Saturday Night Takeaway.</description></item><item><title>Singer songwriter Tom Grennan and hake with roast red pepper sauce | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480057/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Grennan is a Bedford boy done good. With a flair for football, he pursued a professional career in his teens until the competition proved too stiff. Taking stock, Tom decided to give his other gift a shot. He began gigging around London and got spotted in a pub by a record label. His songs ‘A Little Bit of Love’ and ‘By Your Side’ (with Calvin Harris) were the second and third most played tracks of 2021 and his new tune ‘All These Nights’ is out now.</description></item><item><title>Actor and comedian Michelle de Swarte and roast lamb with lemon chickpeas | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480058/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480058/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Michelle de Swarte brings lots of laughter to the table at Dish HQ.
Our guest is multi-talented! At 19 she swapped South London for the catwalks of NYC. Struggling to find her voice, Michelle left modelling for journalism and began making documentary films with icon and activist Gloria Steinem. Next, she gave stand-up comedy a shot which led her to Katherine Ryan, who she supported on tour and starred alongside on Netflix (The Duchess).</description></item><item><title>Comedian Ed Gamble and barbecue cauliflower wings | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480059/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ed Gamble is ON MENU at Dish HQ with Nick and Angela.
Comedian Ed is a regular on Mock the Week, a judge on Great British Menu and co-hosts the hugely successful Off Menu podcast with James Acaster. He’s currently touring the country with his stand up show ‘Electric’ (which has just been extended till November 22).
Ed Gamble’s middle name is barbeque and as it’s the season, Angela makes some BBQ cauliflower wings with a zingy coriander mayo, as the trio drill down into the minutiae of outdoor grilling.</description></item><item><title>Strictly Champion Giovanni Pernice and chicken orzo | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480060/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Giovanni Pernice glides into the Dish kitchen for a meal with Nick and Angela.
The dancer and choreographer has been a professional on Strictly for seven years and took home the title and trophy with his partner Rose Ayling-Ellis in 2021. Fun fact: Giovanni holds the Guinness World Record for jive, kicks and flicks! He is currently on tour with his TV dad / big brother Anton Du Beke.</description></item><item><title>Broadcaster James May and a monkfish curry | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480061/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480061/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week James May joins Nick and Angela at Dish HQ.
After presenting Top Gear for 12 years, May now presents Prime Video’s The Grand Tour, as well as a cooking programme entitled “Oh Cook!”, a play on his famous catchphrase. May also hosted a travel series named James May: Our Man in Japan, and following its success, he hits the road again with a journey around the beautiful Italy.</description></item><item><title>Award-winning comedian Sindhu Vee and a pomegranate Margarita | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480062/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sindhu Vee takes a seat at the Dish table with Nick and Angela this week.
After swapping a career in investment banking for comedy, Sindhu has toured the world, has featured on Live At The Apollo, Mock The Week, QI, Have I Got News For You and the critically acclaimed Netflix show Sex Education, to name but a few.
Over some baked cod and cuvée, Sindhu shares what happened when she ate a REALLY spicy chilli, the pros and cons of fish admin and her role in the brand new Matilda movie.</description></item><item><title>Actor and Bridesmaids Director Paul Feig and beef tacos | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480063/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480063/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Nick and Angela are joined by Hollywood’s best dressed filmmaker Paul Feig.
Paul made his name as the creator of the critically acclaimed TV series Freaks and Geeks before directing a number of smash hit comedy films including Bridesmaids, The Heat and Ghostbusters.
Angela prepares some beautiful braised beef tacos as they discuss Paul’s obsession with Martinis, THAT scene in Bridesmaids and how Mexican food saved his life.</description></item><item><title>Ted Lasso’s Hannah Waddingham, Phil Dunster and a sea bass | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480064/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to your dream get-together, hosted by Nick Grimshaw and Michelin star chef Angela Hartnett. It’s time for our first guests to take their seats at Dish HQ.
This week, Angela and Nick are joined by Hannah Waddingham and Phil Dunster from the seven-time (yes, SEVEN) Emmy Award winning comedy-drama Ted Lasso. Hannah and Phil star as club owner Rebecca Welton and footballer Jamie Tartt in Apple’s global hit series, alongside Jason Sudeikis as the American college football coach hired to train a British Premier League team.</description></item><item><title>The starter with Nick, Angela and a risotto | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480065/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Before the guests start arriving, it’s time for our hosts Nick Grimshaw and Angela Hartnett to get to know each other.
Nick gets his first taste of Angela’s cooking and reveals the snack that Simon Cowell got him hooked on in The X Factor. Angela shares stories from Gordon Ramsay’s kitchen and is treated to a gin Bramble from Nick’s cocktail cabinet.
All recipes from this podcast can be found at waitrose.</description></item><item><title>Introducing...Dish | Dish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7895480066/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7895480066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pull up a seat and join Nick Grimshaw and Michelin-star chef Angela Hartnett as they talk food, drink, and entertaining with incredible guests. This is Dish from Waitrose. Available wherever you get your podcasts.
Dish is a S:E Creative Studio production for Waitrose &amp;amp; Partners. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>