<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Up First on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/up-first/</link><description>Recent content in Up First on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 11:10:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/up-first/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Israel-Hamas, U.S. Border Negotiations, Jimmy Lai On Trial | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230145/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 11:10:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin urges a wind-down in Israel&amp;rsquo;s major combat operations. Republicans in Congress seek tighter border controls in exchange for Ukraine and Israel aid. Newspaper founder Jimmy Lai goes on trial in Hong Kong.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Dana Farrington, Ally Schweitzer, and Michael Sullivan.</description></item><item><title>The Sunday Story: Media "Failings" In Covering Trump | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230146/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 08:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today on The Sunday Story host Ayesha Rascoe explores the media&amp;rsquo;s challenge in covering Donald Trump. As he campaigns for a second term as President, Trump is increasingly threatening retribution and violent acts if he&amp;rsquo;s reelected. Rascoe speaks with a journalist and a scholar who both believe the media is failing to convey the danger Trump poses to American democracy.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Israel Kills Gaza Hostages, Deflation, San Antonio Police Indictment | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230144/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 15:17:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230144/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Israeli military said it accidentally killed three hostages held in Gaza. In a statement, the army said it mistook them as a threat and fired. Just because inflation is cooling down doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean prices are also going down - and they won&amp;rsquo;t be any time soon. Two former police officers face murder charges after the fatal shooting of a mentally ill woman last June in San Antonio, Texas.</description></item><item><title>Gaza Post-War Plans, Ohio Prosecutor Misconduct, Comer Shell Company | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230143/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 11:16:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Disagreements emerge between U.S., Israeli, Palestinian and Gulf leaders and activists over who should be in charge of the Gaza Strip after the war. Criminal prosecutors across Ohio broke rules in the courtroom that are supposed to protect the rights of defendants on trial, all in an effort to get convictions. Hunter Biden is being investigated for using his ties to influential people to make business deals and allegedly using shell companies to hide millions of dollars in earnings; GOP congressman James Comer, who is leading the probe, is now accused of doing the same.</description></item><item><title>Putin Year-End Address, SCOTUS Abortion Access, Trump Fraud Trial | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230142/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 11:18:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Russian President Vladimir Putin traditionally ends most years with an extended press conference. What does Putin say as another year ends with his country still at war in Ukraine? The Supreme Court will hear its first abortion case since overturning of Roe v. Wade. Lower courts delivered mixed rulings on mifepristone. What does this mean for women who receive abortion pill in the mail? Also, the civil fraud trial against former President Trump is done.</description></item><item><title>Impeachment Process Vote, Biden and Israel, AL Nitrogen Gas Execution | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230141/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 12:39:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230141/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Republican-controlled House is set to vote on formalizing its impeachment inquiry of President Joe Biden. Biden makes some of his most critical comments to date about Israel&amp;rsquo;s response to the October 7 Hamas attack. And Alabama plans to execute a prisoner in January using nitrogen hypoxia, a process so novel and untested that state officials required the man&amp;rsquo;s spiritual adviser to sign a waiver that said he could be exposed to the deadly gas.</description></item><item><title>Texas Abortion Case, Biden and Zelenskyy, Trump and SCOTUS | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230139/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 11:14:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230139/</guid><description>Podcast Description A Texas woman has left the state, whose highest court ruled she does not meet the exception to the abortion ban, to have the procedure. Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy meets President Biden in Washington as the pair makes a last-ditch plea to Congress for funding. And the Supreme Court has been asked to fast track a case that centers on whether former President Donald Trump should be shielded from criminal prosecution.</description></item><item><title>Arab Leaders on Israel-Hamas, Trump Won't Testify, Argentina Inauguration | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230140/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 11:12:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230140/</guid><description>Podcast Description World policy leaders meeting in Qatar discuss the Gaza war and its impact on regional security. Donald Trump plans to skip testifying for a second time in the New York civil fraud trial against him and his company. And Argentine President Javier Milei is inaugurated after promises of big changes to his country struggling with an economic crisis.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun?</description></item><item><title>The Sunday Story: The Unbearable Weight of Medical Debt | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230136/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 08:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today on The Sunday Story host Ayesha Rascoe explores the growing crisis of medical debt in America. Nationwide, 100 million people have health care debt, according to a KHN-NPR investigation, which has documented a crisis that is driving Americans from their homes, draining their savings, and preventing millions from accessing care they need.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Gaza Detainees, Sickle Cell Breakthrough, Student Debt Reform | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230137/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 14:17:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Images of Palestinian men stripped to their underwear prompt outrage. Genetic editing leads to new treatments for blood ailment. Income-based plan zeroes out payments for millions of borrowers.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hunter Biden Charged, Israel-Hamas War, Antisemitism And Universities | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230138/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 11:33:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230138/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Justice Department has charged President Biden&amp;rsquo;s son on nine counts related to his failure to pay federal taxes. Israeli military soldiers and Hamas militants fight in urban combat. And the presidents of Harvard, MIT, and The University of Pennsylvania face backlash over comments made during a House hearing on campus antisemitism. Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.</description></item><item><title>4th GOP Debate, Alleged Sexual Violence By Hamas, McCarthy To Leave Congress | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230135/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 12:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Republican presidential candidates take to the stage for the fourth primary debate. Israeli officials blast the international community for its response to allegations of sexual violence perpetrated by Hamas. And former House Speaker Kevin McCarthy decides to leave Congress. Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter. Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Megan Pratz and Padma Rama.</description></item><item><title>Aid To Ukraine, Sen. Tuberville and Military Promotions, Fourth Republican Debate | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230134/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 11:12:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Some U.S. lawmakers question whether aid to Ukraine should continue amid a battlefield stalemate. Sen. Tommy Tuberville drops his hold on more than 400 military promotions. And four Republican presidential candidates prepare for a fourth debate in Tuscaloosa, Ala.
Clarification: A previous version of this episode did not make clear that Congressional Republicans have additional border policy requests including proposed requirements for asylum cases and ways to curtail illegal crossings.</description></item><item><title>Ex-Ambassador Charged As Agent, Houthi Attack, Nelson Mandela's Death Anniversary | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230133/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 11:22:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230133/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Justice Department accuses former U.S. ambassador Victor Manuel Rocha of working as a &amp;ldquo;clandestine agent&amp;rdquo; on behalf of Cuba. The Pentagon says that Houthi rebels from Yemen attacked an American naval destroyer and three commercial ships in the Red Sea. And South Africa marks the 10th anniversary of the death of Nelson Mandela.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Kirshnadev Calamur, Andrew Sussman and Miguel Macias.</description></item><item><title>Israel Expands Military Operation, SCOTUS Hears Purdue Pharma Case, Liz Cheney | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230131/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 11:17:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Israel says it expanded its ground offensive against Hamas to all parts of Gaza. This includes the occupied territory&amp;rsquo;s southern areas, where people fled to in the early days of the war. What does this mean for the civilians in Gaza? The Supreme Court on Monday hears arguments for and against a bankruptcy settlement. It involves Purdue Pharma, maker of the pain medication OxyContin. And former Wyoming Congresswoman Liz Cheney warns about the threat of a second Trump presidency.</description></item><item><title>The Sunday Story: All The Only Ones | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230132/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 08:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230132/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week&amp;rsquo;s episode, Ayesha shares the latest series out of NPR&amp;rsquo;s Embedded. In &amp;ldquo;All The Only Ones,&amp;rdquo; Laine Kaplan-Levenson unearths the little-known and often neglected history of trans youth in America. The series follows the lives of young transgender people today and travels back in time to the turn of the 20th century to meet some of the earliest trans youth documented in American history.
You can listen to the 3-part series on the Embedded feed here.</description></item><item><title>Fighting Resumes, Harris At Climate Summit, Remembering Sandra Day O'Connor | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230130/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 14:44:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fighting between Israel and Hamas has resumed after a seven-day pause. Vice President Kamala Harris speaks at the COP28 climate summit in Dubai. Sandra Day O&amp;rsquo;Connor is remembered as a champion of women in the law.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Israel-Hamas Fighting Resumes, Ukraine Aid Holdup, DeSantis vs. Newsom Debate | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230129/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 11:45:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Israeli airstrikes on Gaza resumed on Friday after a weeklong ceasefire. What does the return to war mean for civilians? The White House wants lawmakers to provide additional funds to Israel and Ukraine. House Republicans won&amp;rsquo;t go along, unless they get a concession on their border policy. And Florida&amp;rsquo;s Republican Gov. Ron DeSantis debated California Democrat Gavin Newsom. Up First was edited by Michael Sullivan, Kelsey Snell, Dana Farrington and HJ Mai.</description></item><item><title>Antony Blinken in Israel, George Santos Expulsion Vote, US-India Tensions | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230127/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 12:11:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Israel and Hamas agree to extend a temporary truce by another day. The House weighs whether to expel first-term Republican Congressman George Santos. And the Department of Justice indicts an Indian intelligence officer for allegedly ordering the assassination of a Sikh separatist in New York. Up First is produced by Ana Perez, Ben Abrams, and Julie Depenbrock. Our editors are Michael Sullivan and Kelsey Snell. We get engineering support from Phil Edfors and Arthur Laurent.</description></item><item><title>Blinken in Brussels, Biden in Colorado, COP28 in Dubai | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230128/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 12:01:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230128/</guid><description>Podcast Description U.S. Secretary of State Antony Blinken speaks with NATO foreign ministers in Brussels before heading to the Middle East. President Biden visits Colorado where he&amp;rsquo;s expected to tout his administration&amp;rsquo;s investment in clean energy jobs. And world leaders prepare to begin climate change negotiations in Dubai.
Up First is produced by Ana Perez, Ben Abrams, and Julie Depenbrock. Our editors are Mark Katkov, Dana Farrington, and Sadie Babits. We get engineering support from Phil Edfors Arthur Laurent.</description></item><item><title>Israel-Hamas Extended Truce, Vermont Shooting, Iowa Caucus | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230124/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 11:48:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230124/</guid><description>Podcast Description President Biden says Israel and Hamas have agreed to extend a temporary truce for two more days. Authorities investigate the shooting of three men of Palestinian descent as a hate crime. And the 2024 race for the Republican presidential nominee shapes up.
Up First is produced by Ana Perez, Ben Abrams, and Julie Depenbrock. Our editors are Michael Sullivan, Andrea DeLeon, and Megan Pratz. We get engineering support from Stacey Abbott and Arthur Laurent.</description></item><item><title>The Latest on Israel-Gaza, COP28 in Dubai, Memorials for Rosalynn Carter | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230125/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 11:23:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Israel and Hamas consider extending a four-day pause in fighting. Global climate talks begin later this week in Dubai. And three days of memorial events start in Georgia for former First Lady Rosalynn Carter, who died on Nov. 19 at the age of 96. Up First is produced by Ana Perez, Julie Depenbrock, and Ben Abrams. Our editors are Michael Sullivan, Neela Bannerjee, and Russell Lewis. We get engineering support from Phil Edfors and Arthur Laurent.</description></item><item><title>The Sunday Story: Meeting the Puzzlemaster | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230122/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 08:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today on The Sunday Story host Ayesha Rascoe heads to Westchester County, in upstate New York to meet with The New York Times Crossword editor Will Shortz. The two sit down at the table tennis center Will owns to talk about how he became the Puzzlemaster on Weekend Edition Sunday, his love for all things puzzles and how recently, in his seventies, he has finally found love in his personal life as well.</description></item><item><title>Israel-Hamas Hostage Deal Holds, Riot in Dublin, Paying for Holiday Shopping | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230123/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 16:14:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamas released 24 hostages Friday as Israel freed 39 Palestinian prisoners. Another exchange is expected today. Anti-immigrant sentiment fuels looting and vandalism in central Dublin. Why &amp;ldquo;buy now pay later&amp;rdquo; plans are expected to grow even more common this holiday season.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Israel-Gaza Deal, Progressive Prosecutors, Rosalynn Carter Legacy | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230120/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 11:03:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230120/</guid><description>Podcast Description A four day cease-fire takes effect between Israel and Gaza ahead of the possible release of 50 hostages for 150 Palestinian prisoners. Progressive prosecutors across the country face resistance from police departments that see them as soft on crime. And a journalist remembers the impact Rosalynn Carter had on journalism related to the often neglected subject of mental health. Up First is produced by Ana Perez, Claire Murashima, and Chad Campbell.</description></item><item><title>Israel-Hamas Deal, Black Friday Shopping, Atlanta Police Facility Controversy | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230121/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 11:43:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Israel says the release of 50 hostages in Gaza in return for 150 Palestinians will not start before Friday. Retailers forecast a record numbers of shoppers over the Thanksgiving holiday weekend. Protesters rally against a new, police training facility in Atlanta.
Up First is produced by Ana Perez, Claire Murashima, and Chad Campbell. Our editors are Michael Sullivan, Emily Kopp, Susanna Capeluto. We get engineering support from Gilly Moon, Phil Edfors, and Kwesi Lee.</description></item><item><title>Israel-Hamas Deal, Sam Altman Returns to OpenAI, Wisconsin Redistricting Case | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230119/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 11:43:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Israel and Hamas agree to a deal involving the release of some hostages in exchange for a multi-day cease-fire. Sam Altman returns to OpenAI as CEO after days of turmoil at the artificial intelligence company. And Wisconsin&amp;rsquo;s Supreme Court hears a case related to gerrymandering in the state. Up First is produced by Ana Perez, Claire Murashima and Chad Campbell. Our editors are Didi Schanche, Uri Berliner and Ben Swayse.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine Winter, Jacumba Migrants, Thanksgiving Travel | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230117/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 11:50:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ukraine enters winter with stalled front lines and uncertainty over the West&amp;rsquo;s continued support for its war with Russia. Migrants set up camps in the tiny border town of Jacumba, California without basic necessities or support from aid organizations. And tens of millions of travelers prepare to take to the skies as Thanksgiving nears. Up First is produced by Ana Perez, Chad Campbell and Claire Murashima. Our editors are Michael Sullivan, Andrea DeLeon, and Russell Lewis.</description></item><item><title>Israel-Gaza War, Rosalynn Carter, Argentina Election | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230118/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 11:11:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Officials discuss a possible deal related to the release of some hostages in Gaza in exchange for a pause in fighting. Former First Lady Rosalynn Carter dies at 96 in Plains, Georgia. And Javier Milei wins Argentina&amp;rsquo;s presidential run-off. Up First is produced by Ana Perez, Chad Campbell and Claire Murashima. Our editors are Susanna Capelouto, Michael Sullivan and Tara Neill. We get engineering support from Carleigh Strange and Arthur Laurent.</description></item><item><title>The Sunday Story: Coal's deadly dust | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230116/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 08:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230116/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2011, NPR correspondent Howard Berkes noticed an anomaly in the sidebar of a government report on the Upper Big Branch mine disaster in West Virginia. It suggested that there was an extraordinarily high rate of black lung disease among the coal miners who&amp;rsquo;d been killed in the explosion. And it set him on a decade-long investigation to understand the cause of a hidden epidemic, the toll it took on miners and their families, and why government agencies had failed to prevent it.</description></item><item><title>Gaza Hospital Evacuated, Argentina Elections, Road Runner's Revenge | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230112/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 14:26:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Israeli troops are evacuating Al-Shifa Hospital now that it&amp;rsquo;s under their control. A maverick politician could become Argentina&amp;rsquo;s next president. Why would a movie studio decide against releasing a movie it&amp;rsquo;s already finished?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Gaza Tunnels, GM Contract With UAW Members, Guatemala and Democracy | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230113/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 11:37:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Israel says it is uncovering an intricate network of tunnels used by Hamas in Gaza. Members of United Auto Workers approve a contract negotiated by the union. And prosecutors in Guatemala say they intend to bring charges against President-elect Bernardo Arevalo. Up First is produced by Ana Perez and Shelby Hawkins. Our editors are Michael Sullivan, Emily Kopp and Tara Neill. We get engineering support from Stacey Abbott and Arthur Laurent.</description></item><item><title>Biden and Xi Finally Talk, Israel Raids Gaza Hospital, Veterans Face Foreclosures | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230110/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 12:24:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230110/</guid><description>Podcast Description President Joe Biden speaks about global affairs with China&amp;rsquo;s leader Xi Jinping. Israel raids Gaza&amp;rsquo;s Al-Shifa hospital. And an NPR investigation finds that thousands of U.S. military servicemembers and veterans are at risk of losing their homes. Up First is produced by Ana Perez, Julie Depenbrock, Shelby Hawkins and Ziad Buchh. Our editors are Roberta Rampton, Bob Little and Michael Sullivan. We get engineering support from Stacey Abbott and Arthur Laurent.</description></item><item><title>Biden-Xi Meeting, GOP Tensions, State Department Dissent | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230111/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 11:57:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230111/</guid><description>Podcast Description President Biden aims to restore communications with China&amp;rsquo;s Xi Jinping. Tensions reach a breaking point as the House seeks to avert a government shutdown. And some State Department employees raise objections over U.S. support for Israel. Up First is produced by Julie Depenbrock, Ana Perez, Shelby Hawkins and Ziad Buchh. Our editors are Roberta Rampton, Kelsey Snell, and Larry Kaplow. We get engineering support from Stacey Abbott and Arthur Laurent.</description></item><item><title>Supreme Court Ethics Code, Hamas Military Compound, New Climate Report | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230109/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:11:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230109/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Supreme Court adopts its first code of ethics. Israel says it has evidence of a Hamas military compound beneath a hospital in Gaza City. And the latest National Climate Assessment explains how climate change is affecting our lives. Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Michael Sullivan and Rachel Waldholz. It was produced by Julie Depenbrock, Ana Perez, Shelby Hawkins and Ziad Buchh. We get engineering support from Stacey Abbott and Arthur Laurent.</description></item><item><title>Gaza Hospitals, Biden-Xi Meeting, Looming Government Shutdown | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230108/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 11:12:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Israeli troops advance on Gaza City&amp;rsquo;s Al-Shifa Hospital, where Hamas militants allegedly maintain a command center. President Joe Biden prepares to speak to his Chinese counterpart for the first time in more than a year. Short-term funding for the federal government faces opposition from Democrats and Republicans.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Sunday Story: A Life Worthy of Whalefall | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230106/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 08:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230106/</guid><description>Podcast Description What does it mean to live a life worthy of those we leave behind? On this episode of The Sunday Story, Ayesha Rascoe explores the idea with author Daniel Kraus. Kraus&amp;rsquo; latest novel is Whalefall. It tells the story of Jay Gardiner, a troubled young man burdened by guilt after the death of his estranged father. Jay hopes to redeem himself by diving to recover his father&amp;rsquo;s remains in the ocean off the California coast; instead he is swallowed whole by a whale.</description></item><item><title>Gaza Hospital Crisis, Biden-Xi Meeting, Union Wins And The Car Market | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230107/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 14:09:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Israel says it is &amp;ldquo;closing in&amp;rdquo; on Hamas militants it claims are using hospitals and other civilian infrastructure in Gaza as cover. The American and Chinese presidents are due to talk for the first time in more than a year. It will be difficult for automakers to pass the cost of recent union wins to consumers.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Daily Pauses in Gaza, Manchin Re-Election Decision, Southern Border Surge | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230104/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 11:35:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Israel agrees to daily pauses in areas of northern Gaza, according to Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu. Democratic Sen. Joe Manchin will not seek re-election in West Virginia. And immigration on the US-Mexico border reaches an all-time high. Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Mark Katkov, Megan Pratz and Andrea DeLeon. It was produced by Shelby Hawkins and Ben Abrams. We get engineering support from Stacey Abbott. Our technical director is Zac Coleman.</description></item><item><title>Domestic Pressure on Netanyahu, GOP Debate in Miami, Union Deal with Hollywood | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230103/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 11:47:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Israelis blame Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu for security failures that led to 1,400 deaths by Hamas. GOP presidential candidates take heated shots at the third debate in Miami. And the Screen Actors Guild reaches a tentative agreement with major studios.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Michael Sullivan, Megan Pratz and Rose Friedman. It was produced by Shelby Hawkins, Ben Abrams and Milton Guevara. We get engineering support from Stacey Abbott and our technical director is Zac Coleman.</description></item><item><title>Abortion Rights On The Ballot, GOP Presidential Debate, Syphilis Surge in Babies | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230101/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 11:22:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Abortion access is a winning issue in off-year elections. Candidates vie for the 2024 GOP presidential nomination at a third debate in Miami. And the number of babies born in the U.S. with syphilis is ten times what it was a decade ago. Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Megan Pratz and Scott Hensley. It was produced by Shelby Hawkins, Ben Abrams and Milton Guevara. We get engineering support from Stacey Abbott.</description></item><item><title>One Month Of War in Gaza, SCOTUS Domestic Violence &amp; Guns, Ohio Abortion Vote | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230102/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:22:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Israel and Hamas have been at war for a month and with no sign of relief, it&amp;rsquo;s already the deadliest conflict since Israel&amp;rsquo;s creation 75 years ago. The Supreme Court hears arguments in a case that could give gun rights to people convicted of domestic violence. And, voters in Ohio are deciding whether to establish a constitutional right to abortion in the state.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Mark Katov, Barbara Sprunt, Krishnadev Calamur and Mohamad ElBardicy.</description></item><item><title>Israel's Plan To Replace Hamas, Trump Testifies In Fraud Case, Epic Vs Google | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 11:14:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Israel continues intense bombardment on Gaza and vows to eliminate Hamas with no clear alternative to who might take over. Former President Donald Trump is set to testify in a New York courtroom today on charges of conspiring to falsify his property values. And, Epic Games sues Google in an anti-trust case accusing the tech giant of unfair business practices.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Michael Sullivan, Dana Farrington, Adam Bearne, and Mohamad El-Bardicy.</description></item><item><title>The Sunday Story: Running with testosterone | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230002/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 08:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today is the New York City Marathon. Around 50,000 runners are racing in the men&amp;rsquo;s and women&amp;rsquo;s divisions. And this year, for only the third time in the race&amp;rsquo;s history, a number of runners will be competing in the nonbinary category.
The nonbinary division emerged due to advocacy from trans and nonbinary athletes like Cal Calamia—a rising star in this emerging category. Calamia, who uses both he and they pronouns, is trans and nonbinary, and he started his transition back in 2019.</description></item><item><title>Israel Snubs Pauses, Question Of Aid Goes To Senate, Eyedrop Recall | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230003/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 14:06:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230003/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Israeli government says Hamas must release hostages before any consideration of a pause in its retaliation for the Oct. 7 attacks. The U.S. House passed an aid package unlikely to be agreed to by the Senate. The FDA is recalling more eye drops.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Blinken In Israel, Hezbollah Leader Breaks Silence, FTX Founder Guilty | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230004/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 10:13:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Secretary of State Antony Blinken is back in Tel Aviv today to ask Israel again to prioritize protection of innocent civilians in Gaza following a third day of deadly airstrikes on the densely populated Jabalia refugee camp. The head of the Lebanese militant group, Hezbollah, breaks his silence with a speech addressing the Israel-Hamas war. And, Sam Bankman-Fried, the founder of the cryptocurrency exchange FTX, faces up 110 years in prison for one of the biggest financial frauds on record.</description></item><item><title>Rafah Crossing, Biden Islamophobia Plan, Portland Teachers Strike | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 10:04:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Negotiations are ongoing to allow hundreds more foreign nationals to flee war-torn Gaza through Egypt&amp;rsquo;s Rafah border crossing. The White House plans to combat Islamophobia as frustration mounts among Muslims in America. And, schools in Portland, Oregon, are closed for a second day as the teachers&amp;rsquo; strike continues.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Michael Sullivan, Roberta Rampton, Alice Woelfle, and Mohamad ElBardicy. It was produced by Julie Depenbrock, Shelby Hawkins and Chad Campbell.</description></item><item><title>Gaza War Escalates, Pakistan Deportation Deadline, Trump Organization Trial | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 10:17:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Another phone and internet blackout is hampering rescue efforts after massive airstrikes hit Gaza&amp;rsquo;s largest and most densely populated refugee camp. Donald Trump Jr. takes the stand in New York in a trial charging his family with fraud. And, today is the deadline set by the Pakistani government, for all undocumented immigrants to leave or face deportation. Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Michael Sullivan, Krishnadev Calamur, Alice Woelfle and Mohamad ElBardicy.</description></item><item><title>Gaza Ground Offensive, House Israel Aid Bill, Google Monopoly Trial | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230007/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 10:13:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Israeli tanks and troops have advanced deeper into Gaza as Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu rejects international calls for a ceasefire. House Republicans are proposing a stand-alone bill that would send roughly $14 billion to Israel but doesn&amp;rsquo;t include funding for Ukraine. And, Google will lay out its case in a massive monopoly trail brought by the Justice Department.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Russell Lewis, Kelsey Snell, Uri Berliner and Mohamad ElBardicy.</description></item><item><title>Gaza Crisis, Israel-Lebanon Border Crossfire, Biden AI Executive Order | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 10:16:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230008/</guid><description>Podcast Description People in Gaza face a dire humanitarian crisis as the Israeli military increases airstrikes on the besieged enclave while the ground offensive presses forward. Israel trades fire with Hizbollah forces in southern Lebanon as the war risks opening a new front. And, President Joe Biden issues an executive order for government oversight on AI companies standards on data privacy.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Michael Sullivan, Reena Advani, Roberta Rampton and Mohamad ElBardicy.</description></item><item><title>The Sunday Story: This is what it feels like to be catcalled | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230009/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 07:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Catcalling can be often thought of as playful and harmless, a classic case of boys will be boys. But the reality is anything but harmless. The interactions often leave predominantly women and girls feeling vulnerable and fearful that if they don&amp;rsquo;t respond correctly they can be in danger. Today on The Sunday Story, artist, musician and podcast host Terra Lopez discusses her new podcast series This Is What It Feels Like from CapRadio.</description></item><item><title>Lewiston Shooting Suspect Dead, Israel-Gaza War, Acapulco Devastation | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230010/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 13:12:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230010/</guid><description>Podcast Description A suspect wanted for fatally shooting 18 people in Lewiston, Maine was found dead on Friday. Israel is ramping up its military operations in anticipation of a ground invasion in Gaza as communications are cut off there. Mexican officials say 27 people have died after Hurricane Otis hit Acapulco.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EU Calls For 'Humanitarian Pause', Manhunt for Maine Shooter, Acapulco Hurricane | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230011/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 10:16:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230011/</guid><description>Podcast Description A manhunt continues for the gunman behind a mass shooting in Lewiston, Maine. European leaders call on Israel to stop its relentless bombardment of the Gaza Strip to allow humanitarian aid to reach people who desperately need it. And, Hurricane Otis left a trail of destruction when it struck the Mexican resort town of Acapulco as a Category 5 storm.
Up First is produced by Mansee Khurana, David WestOur editors are Don Clyde, Denise Rios, and Mohamad ElBardicy Our technical director is Zac Coleman And our director is Lilly Quiroz.</description></item><item><title>Mass Shootings in Maine, Gaza Fuel Shortage, New Speaker of the House | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 10:04:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230012/</guid><description>Podcast Description A person of interest in two mass shootings in Lewiston, Maine is still at large as authorities ask locals to shelter in place. Gaza is running dangerously low on fuel to run hospitals and deliver aid, the United Nations says relief operations may halt as early as today. And Republican have finally done it, they unanimously elected Mike Johnson of Louisiana as Speaker of the House. Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Russell Lewis, Tara Neill, Kelsey Snell and Mohamad ElBardicy.</description></item><item><title>Israel's War Strategy, House Votes on Fourth Nominee, Meta's Mega Lawsuit | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:03:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230013/</guid><description>Podcast Description World leaders urge Israel to restrain its attacks on Gaza after 19 days of airstrikes meant to pave the way for a ground invasion. Today, Republicans will vote on their fourth nominee for speaker of the House, Congressman Mike Johnson from Louisiana. And, 41 states are suing Meta for allegedly designing addictive features on Instagram and Facebook that target kids.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun?</description></item><item><title>Hamas Releases Hostages, Eight Candidates Vie for Speaker, Bond Sell-Off Sparks Fear | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 10:15:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230014/</guid><description>Podcast Description As Israeli bombardment continues across Gaza, diplomatic efforts to facilitate the release of more hostages continue after two Israeli women were freed by Hamas. Today, House Republicans will vote between eight candidates hoping to unite a bitterly divided party. And, a sell-off of US Treasury bonds is sparking fears of higher inflation.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.</description></item><item><title>Israel-Gaza War, House Speaker Search, Argentina Elections | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 10:02:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Desperately needed humanitarian aid has begun to trickle into Gaza as Israeli airstrikes intensify on the besieged enclave. Nine Republicans are vying for the gavel of Speaker of the House after Congressman Jim Jordan failed to secure enough votes last week. And, Argentina is heading into a runoff election between far-right populist leader Javier Milei and the ruling party&amp;rsquo;s candidate, Sergio Massa.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun?</description></item><item><title>The Sunday Story: Body Electric | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230016/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 13:03:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230016/</guid><description>Podcast Description For years, medical experts have raised the alarm about the effects of sedentary behavior on the human body. Sitting too much has been linked with numerous health concerns including heart disease, diabetes, cancer, and early death. Days filled with sitting and screen time leave us feeling depleted. So what can we do about it? In a new series called Body Electric, TED Radio Hour host Manoush Zomorodi investigates: how we can change the relationship between our technology and our bodies?</description></item><item><title>Aid Enters Gaza, American Hostages Freed, Resilient American Economy | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230017/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 12:38:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trucks carrying aid entered the Egypt-Gaza border at Rafah on Saturday. The relative of two American hostages freed by Hamas says now is the time for their recovery. The U.S. economy remains very resilient, despite a sharp rise in interest rates, but what does that mean for consumers?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Biden Pushes For Foreign Aid, Russia Detains U.S. Journalist, Voter Fraud Prevention | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230018/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 10:21:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230018/</guid><description>Podcast Description President Biden says supporting Israel and Ukraine is vital for America&amp;rsquo;s national security. But will Congress agree? Russia has detained a second American journalist. Alsu Kermasheva has been charged with failing to register as a foreign agent. And why are Republican-led states leaving a bipartisan group that aims to prevent voter fraud?
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.</description></item><item><title>Israel To Allow Limited Humanitarian Aid, Gaza Hospital Explosion, Jordan Loses Votes | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 10:32:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230019/</guid><description>Podcast Description The war between Israel and Hamas has killed more than 4,000 people - making it the deadliest of all Gaza wars. And things could get even worse once Israel&amp;rsquo;s expected ground invasion begins. Some Western countries are calling for an investigation into the explosion at a Gaza hospital that killed hundreds of people. And Congress remains paralyzed because for the second time Ohio congressman Jim Jordan failed to secure enough votes to become House speaker.</description></item><item><title>Hundreds Die In Gaza Hospital Attack, Biden Visits Israel, Arab Protests | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 10:16:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hundreds of people are dead after an explosion at a hospital in Gaza. Israeli and Palestinian officials are trading blame over who&amp;rsquo;s responsible for the deadly attack. President Biden arrived in Israel on Wednesday morning. There he wants to show solidarity for Israel and prevent any further escalations. And pro-Palestinian protests have erupted across the Middle East following the hospital bombing in Gaza. Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun?</description></item><item><title>Biden Travels To Middle East, Gaza Humanitarian Crisis Worsens, House Speaker Vote | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 10:07:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230021/</guid><description>Podcast Description President Biden on Tuesday will leave for a wartime trip to the Middle East. He will visit Israel, which continues to prepare for a ground offensive against Hamas in Gaza. The humanitarian crisis in Gaza grows worse as supplies are running low. Why is humanitarian aid not getting to the people in need? And the House of Representatives is expected to vote on its next speaker.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun?</description></item><item><title>Gaza Residents Struggle To Get Out, Biden Pushes For More Aid, Polish Elections | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 10:35:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Israel&amp;rsquo;s deadline for civilians to leave northern Gaza has passed. What happens to people who remain behind? President Biden wants more aid for both Israel and Ukraine. But as long as the House is paralyzed, this might not be possible. Also, exit polls suggest Poland&amp;rsquo;s opposition parties won enough votes to form a governing coalition. Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun?</description></item><item><title>The Sunday Story: A 15-minute climate solution attracts conspiracies | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230023/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 07:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230023/</guid><description>Podcast Description 15-minute cities are an urban planning idea growing in popularity. The idea is that you can get to the key places in your life - think work, education, food, recreation - in a 15-minute walk, bike or transit ride. Now mayors from Paris to Cleveland are looking to use them to reduce planet-heating car pollution and improve quality of life.
But they face obstacles - from NIMBYs, to public schools, to death threats for urban planners and politicians.</description></item><item><title>Gaza Evacuation Begins, Israel's Endgame, GOP Nominates Another Speaker | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230024/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 13:29:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Palestinians are beginning to leave northern Gaza as Israel threatens a ground invasion. Past experiences raise questions about whether Israel can control Hamas in the long term. House Republicans tap Rep. Jim Jordan as the next speaker, but he still must be confirmed by whole chamber.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Israel Issues Evacuation Order For Gaza, Scalise Drops Out, Elijah McClain Verdict | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230025/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 10:03:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Israel&amp;rsquo;s military has issued an evacuation order for northern Gaza. It gives the roughly 1.1 million people in that area just 24 hours to get out. Is this the sign that Israel&amp;rsquo;s ground offensive is about to start? House Republicans are once again on the hunt for a new House speaker. Who can unite the party? And a jury in Colorado finds one of two police officers guilty in the 2019 death of Elijah McClain.</description></item><item><title>Gaza Humanitarian Crisis, Steve Scalise Wins GOP Vote For Speaker, AI In Science | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230026/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 10:08:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Israel&amp;rsquo;s bombing campaign in Gaza following the weekend attack by Hamas fighters has plunged the area into darkness. How are civilians trying to survive? House Republicans in an internal vote picked Louisiana Congressman Steve Scalise to serve as the next House speaker. But he doesn&amp;rsquo;t have the required votes in the full House. Scientists from various disciplines will meet in Washington today to discuss the use of artificial intelligence.</description></item><item><title>Israel Prepares Ground Invasion, Biden Confirms Support For Israel, Maui Reopens | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230027/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 10:26:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Israel&amp;rsquo;s military is preparing a ground invasion into Gaza. Authorities believe that about 150 hostages are being held there by Hamas militants. In remarks to the nation, President Biden called Hamas&amp;rsquo; attack on Israel an act of terrorism. And the Hawaiian island of Maui is welcoming back tourists after wildfires this summer leveled the historic town of Lahaina and killed almost 100 people. Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun?</description></item><item><title>Israel Increases Airstrikes On Gaza, Pro-Palestinian Protests, House Speaker Race | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230028/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 10:25:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Israel is increasing its airstrikes on Gaza in retaliation for Saturday&amp;rsquo;s surprise attack. Hamas in return threatens to kill hostages if Israel continues its bombardment. How much is this war targeting civilians? All of this has ignited pro-Palestinian marches in a number of U.S. cities. How do marchers justify Hamas attack? And this latest crisis in the Middle East has also increased the pressure on House Republicans to select a new speaker.</description></item><item><title>Israel At War With Hamas, Intelligence Failure, Earthquake In Afghanistan | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230029/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 10:35:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Israel is at war with Hamas. The militant group launched a surprise attack over the weekend. More than 1,100 on both sides have died so far as Israel retaliates. Hamas&amp;rsquo; unprecedented attack on Israel has also raised questions about Israeli intelligence. Why did Israel and its allies fail to detect any warning signs? And more than 2,000 people have died after a powerful earthquake hit western Afghanistan over the weekend.</description></item><item><title>A Stunned Israel Declares War After Hamas Surprise Attack. What's Next? | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230030/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 12:00:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230030/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this bonus episode of Up First, NPR takes stock of the first day of war between Israel and the Hamas militant group, as the death toll rises into the hundreds on both sides. Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter. Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Olivia Hampton. It was produced by Mansee Khurana.</description></item><item><title>Attacks in Israel, Regional Reaction, Ukraine Aid | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230031/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 13:39:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Israel&amp;rsquo;s prime minister says the country &amp;ldquo;at war&amp;rdquo; after attacks by air and land by Gaza militants. Regional governments are reacting cautiously. And the House Speaker vacancy is complicating additional aid for Ukraine.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Matt Gaetz's District, Ukraine Farmland, Guatemala Political Crisis | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230032/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 10:17:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Florida Republican Matt Gaetz is the man who led the rebellion that pushed out House Speaker Kevin McCarthy. What do his constituents think about what he did? Ukraine is often referred to as Europe&amp;rsquo;s breadbasket. But the ongoing war with Russia has devastated some of its most productive farmland. And Guatemala is dealing with the fallout of August&amp;rsquo;s presidential election. Even though election results are certified, the country&amp;rsquo;s attorney general and others want to challenge the results.</description></item><item><title>House Speaker Candidates, Mediterranean Migrant Deaths, Pakistani Crackdown | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230033/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 10:22:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230033/</guid><description>Podcast Description A House without a speaker is paralyzed to pass spending legislation, including aid to Ukraine. So who can unite Republicans behind them? More than 2,500 people have died this year while crossing the Mediterranean Sea. The reasons why they flee vary, but they all know the journey could be fatal. And starting next month, Pakistan will expel anyone without proper documentation. That includes an estimated 1.7 million Afghan migrants.</description></item><item><title>House Speaker McCarthy Ousted, Catholic Church's Future, China's 'Golden Week' | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230034/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 10:13:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230034/</guid><description>Podcast Description For the first time in U.S. history, the House of Representatives removed its speaker. Who will fill the vacant seat? Roman Catholic leaders are meeting in the Vatican to chart a way forward for the church. And how do Chinese people spend their &amp;ldquo;golden week&amp;rdquo; holiday?
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine Faces Waning Support From Allies, FTX Trial, Laphonza Butler | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230035/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 10:03:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s war is far from over. It&amp;rsquo;s biggest challenge, however, may not be on the battlefield, but in the form of waning support from allies. How are leaders in Kyiv reacting? The man accused of orchestrating one of the largest financial frauds in American history, Sam Bankman-Fried, goes on trial today. What&amp;rsquo;s his defense? And Laphonza Butler is set to be sworn in today as California&amp;rsquo;s newest U.S. Senator.</description></item><item><title>Congress Averts Shutdown, Trump To Appear In Court, Climate Solutions Week | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230036/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 10:16:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lawmakers narrowly avoided a government shutdown by passing a short-term spending measure over the weekend. But to do that the Republican speaker of the house Kevin McCarthy had to work with Democrats. Did he put his job on the line? Former President Donald Trump will appear in court in New York on Monday. This trial, one of many, is a civil trial. He and his company are accused of of fraud.</description></item><item><title>The Sunday Story: The Life And Death Of Elijah McClain | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230037/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 07:10:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230037/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Colorado, the first of two trials is underway in the death of Elijah McClain.
On a late summer night in 2019, McClain, a 23-year-old Black man, was stopped by police in Aurora, Colorado as he was walking home. McClain was put in a chokehold and injected with a high dose of ketamine. He died several days later in the hospital.
Authorities declined to press charges against police and paramedics involved in the incident, insisting &amp;ldquo;they had acted consistently with their training.</description></item><item><title>Government Shutdown Prep, Student Loan Repayments Start, NYC Floods | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230038/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 13:09:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230038/</guid><description>Podcast Description The US government is set to shutdown Sunday after a group of GOP hardliners opposed House Speaker Kevin McCarthy&amp;rsquo;s stop gap proposal. Tens of millions of borrowers will start paying back federal loans on Sunday after a three-and-a-half year suspension, amid a possible government shutdown. New York City tries to get its head above water after a state of emergency is declared because of severe rainfall.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>White House Prepares For Shutdown, Healthcare Worker Strike, FTX Trial | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230039/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 12:15:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230039/</guid><description>Podcast Description With less than 48 hours left to avoid a government shutdown, the White House is already preparing to manage the fallout. NPR&amp;rsquo;s Asma Khalid spoke with White House Chief of Staff Jeff Zients about what those plans are. Another labor dispute looms as tens of thousands of health care workers are on the verge of a nationwide walkout. And Sam Bankman-Fried, the founder of bankrupt crypto exchange F-T-X, is set to go on trial next week.</description></item><item><title>GOP Debate Recap, Biden Impeachment Hearing, Armenia-Azerbaijan Conflict | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230040/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 10:29:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Republican candidates for the presidential nomination finally got around to criticize the frontrunner Donald Trump. House Republicans will hold the first public hearing in their impeachment inquiry against President Biden on Thursday. Democrats have criticized the timing of the hearing, as the government faces a shutdown. And tens of thousands of people have fled their self-proclaimed republic inside Azerbaijan.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun?</description></item><item><title>GOP Debate, FTC Files Antitrust Lawsuit Against Amazon, Slow Vaccine Rollout | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230041/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 10:37:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Seven Republican candidates will be on stage for the second presidential debate in California on Wednesday. Former President Donald Trump will skip the event. U.S. regulators and 17 states have filed an antitrust lawsuit against Amazon, accusing the online retail giant of harming competition. And the rollout of the latest COVID-19 vaccines has been plagued with issues.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun?</description></item><item><title>Biden Joins UAW Strike, Shutdown Negotiations, Election Worker Turnover | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230042/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 10:06:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230042/</guid><description>Podcast Description President Biden will join striking auto workers in Detroit on Tuesday. He has a chance to be the first sitting president to stand on a picket line. Lawmakers in Congress have only days to avoid another government shutdown. But with some right-leaning Republicans continuing to play hardball, can they? And a new report shows that in some states, more than half of election workers have left their jobs since 2020.</description></item><item><title>Hollywood Writers Reach Deal To End Strike, Shutdown Implications, Prison Deaths | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230043/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 10:19:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230043/</guid><description>Podcast Description TV and movie writers have reached a tentative deal with Hollywood studios that could soon end a nearly five-month strike. Union members still have to ratify the deal. Other negotiations, however, aren&amp;rsquo;t go so well. In Washington, a deal to keep the government open beyond the end of this month appears less and less likely. How would a government shutdown affect the U.S. economy? And what&amp;rsquo;s happening inside a North Carolina federal prison?</description></item><item><title>The Sunday Story: NPR challenges U.S. denial of civilian harm in raid on ISIS leader | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230044/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 12:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today on The Sunday Story, NPR&amp;rsquo;s Daniel Estrin talks about his four-year long investigation into the night that Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi, founder of ISIS, died. The Pentagon maintains troops did not harm noncombatants. But Estrin&amp;rsquo;s investigation challenges that account. Now the Pentagon says it will review new information brought to light about the incident.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>UAW Strike Expanded, Government Shutdown, LGBTQ+ In Census Survey | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230045/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 13:03:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230045/</guid><description>Podcast Description President Biden is going to Michigan to support the United Auto Workers&amp;rsquo; union strikes. A government shutdown looms large after members of the House GOP couldn&amp;rsquo;t agree on a temporary spending plan. The Census Bureau plans to test asking people about their sexual orientation and gender identity next year; it says the information will help to fight discrimination.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>BONUS: Zelenskyy Makes Case For More Aid | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230046/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 13:11:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy tells NPR&amp;rsquo;s Steve Inskeep that more foreign aid is necessary to beat back Vladimir Putin&amp;rsquo;s ambitions to expand Russia&amp;rsquo;s influence across Europe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>UAW Strike Latest, Migrants in Italy, Azerbaijan Cease-Fire | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230126/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 10:14:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230126/</guid><description>Podcast Description The UAW is set to expand its strike if automakers fail to meet a deadline, the tiny Italian island of Lampedusa is overwhelmed by more than 11,000 migrants in the past week and Azerbaijan ends an offensive in Nagorno-Karabakh.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Rafel Nam, Mark Katkov, Michael Sullivan and Olivia Hampton.</description></item><item><title>UAW Strike Latest, Migrants in Italy, Azerbeijan Ceasefire | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230047/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 10:14:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230047/</guid><description>Podcast Description The UAW is set to expand its strike if automakers fail to meet a deadline, the tiny Italian island of Lampedusa is overwhelmed by more than 11,000 migrants in the past week and Azerbaijan ends an offensive in Nagorno-Karabakh.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Rafel Nam, Mark Katkov, Michael Sullivan and Olivia Hampton.</description></item><item><title>GOP Spending Rift, Zelenskyy Interview, Louisiana Police Probe | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230048/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 10:06:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230048/</guid><description>Podcast Description House Republicans can&amp;rsquo;t agree on a stopgap government spending bill, NPR&amp;rsquo;s Steve Inskeep speaks with Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky and lawsuits say Baton Rouge police beat detainees.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Krishnadev Calamur, Susanna Capelouto, Ally Schweitzer and Olivia Hampton. It was produced by Shelby Hawkins, Ziad Buchh and Julie Depenbrock.</description></item><item><title>Garland Testifies, Federal Reserve Preview, UAW Strike Consumer Impact | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230049/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 10:39:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Attorney General Merrick Garland faces grilling by House Republicans, the Federal Reserve is widely expected to hold interest rates steady at its meeting today and the long-term consequences of the UAW strike depend on its breadth and length.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Krishnadev Calamur, Rafael Nam and Olivia Hampton.</description></item><item><title>Biden At UNGA, US-Iran Prisoner Swap, Canada Assassination | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230050/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 10:25:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230050/</guid><description>Podcast Description President Biden speaks at the United Nations General Assembly, five prisoners are on their way back to the US after a prisoner swap with Iran and Canada blames the Indian government for the assassination of a Sikh leader in British Columbia in June.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Dana Farrington, Michael Sullivan, Tara Neill and Olivia Hampton.</description></item><item><title>UAW Strike, NY Climate Week, Drew Barrymore Show Pause | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230051/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 10:29:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Auto plants shut down amid a walkout against all Big Three automakers, Tens of thousands of people kick off a week of climate protests in New York and The Drew Barrymore Show pauses over the Hollywood writers and actors strike.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Pallavi Gogoi, Andrea Kissack, Ciera Crawford and Olivia Hampton.</description></item><item><title>The Sunday Story: The Coal Life | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230052/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230052/</guid><description>Podcast Description South Africa has long been one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest consumers of coal. But the country is now in the midst of transitioning its energy supply from coal to renewable sources. But when a country moves away from a source of energy like coal what happens to the towns and communities that were built to support the coal industry. Today on the Sunday Story we bring you a story from Radio Workshop, a podcast in South Africa that works with youth reporters around the continent.</description></item><item><title>Lee Storm Preparations, UAW Strike Continues, Ukraine Latest | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230053/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 13:08:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230053/</guid><description>Podcast Description People in New England prepare as post-tropical cyclone Lee bears down on the region. The United Auto Workers union is still on strike, demanding higher wages and better benefits for new employees. Ukraine hasn&amp;rsquo;t taken back as much land as it wanted since the start of its offensive in June.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>UAW Strikes, Florida Vaccine Guidance, Libya Flooding Recovery | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230054/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 11:12:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Members of the United Auto Workers walked off work at three select plants and are threatening to expand the strike. Florida&amp;rsquo;s COVID vaccine guidance contradicts the CDC&amp;rsquo;s. And officials in Libya say as many 11,000 people have died in flooding there. Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Romney to Retire, Hurricane Lee Prep, Ethics Entaglement | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230055/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 09:55:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sen. Mitt Romney will not run for a second term. States unaccustomed to hurricanes, such as Maine, prepare for Hurricane Lee. And a close advisor to President Joe Biden counseled both a man accused of sexual harassment and the woman who accused him. Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Dana Farrington, Eric Westervelt, Barrie Hardymon and Peter Granitz.</description></item><item><title>Biden Impeachment, Putin and Kim Meet, Libyan Floods | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230056/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 10:19:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Speaker of the House Kevin McCarthy launched a formal impeachment inquiry into President Joe Biden. Russian President Vladimir Putin welcomed North Korean leader Kim Jong Un Wednesday. Is Putin looking for a source of weapons for his war in Ukraine? And floods inundate Libya, where rival factions rule the country.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.</description></item><item><title>International Help in Morocco, Google Antitrust Case, Kevin McCarthy's Bind | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230057/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 10:24:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Moroccan and international teams are working to rescue survivors from the earthquake. The government opens its antitrust case against Google. And the House returns to Washington with Speaker Kevin McCarthy in a bind.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Morocco Earthquake, Covid Boosters, Biden at G20 | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230058/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 10:32:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230058/</guid><description>Podcast Description The death toll from the earthquake in Morocco surpasses 2,100 people. The FDA is poised to green light a new set of COVID boosters. President Biden is wrapping up his Asia trip with a stop in Vietnam.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Michael Sullivan, Scott Hensley, Roberta Rampton and Peter Granitz.</description></item><item><title>The Sunday Story: A rare look inside locked-down Nicaragua | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230059/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 12:00:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today on The Sunday Story NPR correspondent Eyder Peralta travels to Nicaragua. He&amp;rsquo;s the first foreign journalist to make it into the country in more than a year. He traveled to his home country to get an inside look at what life is like for people living under what some call the newest dictatorship in The Americas. He found a country suffocating in fear and he found his own family history repeating.</description></item><item><title>Morocco Earthquake, Trump rally, Antibiotic Resistant Infections | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230060/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 13:08:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230060/</guid><description>Podcast Description A strong earthquake hit Morocco killing hundreds of people and injuring scores more. Donald Trump fundraised in South Dakota last night, accompanied by the state&amp;rsquo;s governor Kristi Noem. Antibiotic resistant infections are causing more and more deaths across the world, and air pollution may be to blame.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Extreme Weather, Ukrainian Nuclear Power, Maui Unemployment | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230061/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 10:29:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can a summer of extreme weather be linked to climate change? Ukraine is the only country that relies on nuclear power while it withstands an invasion. Unemployment lingers in Maui a month after deadly fires.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Andrea Kissack, Michael Sullivan, Katia Riddle and Peter Granitz.</description></item><item><title>Sudanese Refugees, Texas's Floating Border Barrier, Georgia Election Case | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230062/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 10:11:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230062/</guid><description>Podcast Description The United Nations says as many as a million people have fled war in Sudan. NPR&amp;rsquo;s Michel Martin visits refugees in Chad. A judge reeled in Texas&amp;rsquo;s floating border barrier. And prosecutors in the Georgia election case want a four month trial.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by HJ Mai, Eric Westervelt, Ben Swasey and Peter Granitz.</description></item><item><title>Blinken Visits Kyiv, Biden Heads to Asia, Proud Boys Leader Sentenced | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230063/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 10:19:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Secretary of State Antony Blinken is expected in Kyiv to show American support for Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s war effort. President Joe Biden will travel to India and Vietnam as he tries to China&amp;rsquo;s influence in the developing world. And Enrique Tarrio was sentenced to 22 years in jail.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.</description></item><item><title>Senate Returns, Impeachment of Texas AG, Antiterrorism Case in Canada | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230064/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 10:07:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230064/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Senate reconvenes in Washington with a long to-do list. The suspended attorney general of Texas faces an impeachment trial in Austin. And a murder case in Canada is expected to test the country&amp;rsquo;s antiterrorism laws.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Krishnadev Calamur, Liz Baker, Ally Schweitzer and Peter Granitz.</description></item><item><title>Zelenskyy Sacks Defense Minister, Putin Meets Erdogan, Americans Celebrate Labor Day | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230065/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 10:49:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy is replacing his defense minister. Russian President Vladimir Putin will meet his Turkish counterpart to revive the suspended grain deal. And Americans have the day off to celebrate Labor Day. Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Rafael Nam, Mark Katkov and Peter Granitz.</description></item><item><title>The Sunday Story: The Good Enough Job | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230066/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 12:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today on The Sunday Story, author Simone Stolzoff discusses his book The Good Enough Job: Reclaiming Life from Work, about our complicated relationship with work. Stolzoff explains how as jobs have changed over generations, so has the meaning we derive from working. Stolzoff shares his findings on our modern relationship with work and ways we can find more balance in our lives.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Florida Cleanup, Economic Outlook, Congress Returns | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230067/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 12:37:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230067/</guid><description>Podcast Description President Biden is visiting communities in Florida embarking on cleanup efforts after Hurricane Idalia. Unemployment ticked up, counterintuitively due to the continuing strength of the jobs market. Congress heads back to Capitol Hill next week.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Labor Day Weekend Travel, 9/11 Detainee Deal, Job Numbers | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230068/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 10:25:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Idalia could cause delays over the busy Labor Day weekend, settlement talks falter in the 9/11 terrorism case, and the government releases job numbers for August.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Alice Woelfle, Bob Little, Rafael Nam and Olivia Hampton. It was produced by Mansee Khurana, Claire Murashima and Chad Campbell.</description></item><item><title>McConnell Health, Idalia Aftermath, Gabon Coup Fallout | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230069/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 10:12:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Concerns rise over Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell&amp;rsquo;s health, Florida picks up the pieces after Idalia swept through the Gulf Coast and Gabon coup triggers fears of destabilization.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Padma Rama, Russell Lewis, Tara Neill, Michael Sullivan and Olivia Hampton.</description></item><item><title>Idalia Nears Gulf Coast, Proud Boys Leader to be Sentenced, Sexism in Spanish Soccer | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230070/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 10:26:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hurricane Idalia strengthens ahead of its expected landfall. Enrique Tarrio will learn how long he&amp;rsquo;ll serve in prison. And what&amp;rsquo;s to come for women&amp;rsquo;s soccer in Spain amid a standoff over sexism between players and officials?
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Russell Lewis, Krishnadev Calamur, Jason Breslow, Peter Granitz and Olivia Hampton.</description></item><item><title>Florida Braces For Idalia, COVID Cases Rise, Ugandan 'Aggravated Homosexuality' Case | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230071/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 10:18:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Florida braces for Hurricane Idalia. Schools and hospitals recommend masking over rising COVID cases. And a Uganda man faces the death penalty in the country&amp;rsquo;s first &amp;ldquo;aggravated homosexuality&amp;rdquo; case.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Russell Lewis, Jane Greenhalgh, Michael Sullivan and Olivia Hampton. It was produced by Mansee Khurana, Claire Murashima and Chad Campbell.</description></item><item><title>Trump Vote Conspiracy Trial, Jacksonville Shooting, Schools and Heat, Simone Biles | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230072/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 10:04:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trump&amp;rsquo;s election obstruction trial gets a start date, hundreds of people gather to honor three Black people shot and killed at a Dollar General store in Jacksonville, Fla. and millions of students face record temperatures — and no A.C. — in their classrooms. Plus, Simone Biles wins a record 8th all-around national gymnastics title.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun?</description></item><item><title>The Sunday Story: An Afghan climber in limbo | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230073/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 12:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mina Bakhshi learned to climb mountains when she was 17 years old, in her home country of Afghanistan. But when the Taliban captured Kabul, she couldn&amp;rsquo;t see a future for herself anymore. When Mina landed in the U.S., she learned she only had two years of guaranteed stay. She is one of more than 77,000 Afghans who are currently in the U.S. on a status called humanitarian parole. In this episode of The Sunday Story, journalist Lauren DeLaunay Miller digs into the history of humanitarian parole.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine on Prigozhin's Fate, US Official to China, More Songs of Summer | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230074/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 13:00:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ukrainians greet the apparent death of mercenary leader with gallows humor. Commerce Secretary Gina Raimondo seeks to reassure U.S. investors. Selena Gomez and Miley Cyrus release new singles.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trump's Busy Week, Hit Song's Extreme Themes, Wagner Group's Africa Aims | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230075/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 11:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230075/</guid><description>Podcast Description From counterprogramming a GOP debate to posing for a mug shot in Georgia, Donald Trump had a busy week. A chart-topping song holds extreme themes. And Russia&amp;rsquo;s Wagner mercenaries recruit for Africa.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Megan Pratz, Tara Neill, Michael Sullivan, Andrew Sussman, Jan Johnson and Alice Woelfle.</description></item><item><title>GOP Rivals Tangle, Trump To Be Booked, Prigozhin's Plane Crashes | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230076/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 10:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230076/</guid><description>Podcast Description GOP presidential contenders tangle on a debate stage. Trump is expected in Georgia to answer election meddling charges. The head of Russia&amp;rsquo;s Wagner mercenary force is reported dead in a plane crash.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Megan Pratz, Mark Katkov, Jan Johnson and Alice Woelfle.</description></item><item><title>GOP Presidential Debate, New Student Debt Relief, Runway Safety Action | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230077/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 10:15:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eight GOP presidential hopefuls, minus the frontrunner, debate tonight. The Biden administration lays out a school debt repayment plan. Regulators plan safety meetings to deal with runway close calls.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Promise To Maui, Climate Change Backdrop, Emerging Economies Summit | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230078/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 10:20:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230078/</guid><description>Podcast Description President Biden visited Maui, where wildfire survivors worry about finding permanent housing. Climate change forms a backdrop for a summer of extreme weather-related events. And leaders of five emerging economies will talk cooperation and competition at the BRICS summit in South Africa.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Ravenna Koenig, Neela Banerjee, Michael Sullivan, Tara Neill, Jan Johnson, and Alice Woelfle.</description></item><item><title>Life-Threatening Hilary, Guatemalan Reformist's Win, Tennessee Safety Session | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230079/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 10:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Forecasters predicted catastrophic flooding in California from the remnants of Hurricane Hilary. Voters fed up with corruption chose a reformist as the next president of Guatemala. And a special legislative session that was called in response to a school shooting opens today in Tennessee.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Sunday Story: The Quickening | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230080/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 12:01:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today on The Sunday Story, author Elizabeth Rush discusses the book that emerged from her journey to Thwaites Glacier in Antarctica. She explains why Thwaites is under threat and why collaborative problem solving plays a critical role in an era of climate change. The voyage also helped her make an important personal decision: whether or not to become a mother.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hurricane Hilary, Mortgage Rates, Summit Reaction | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230081/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 16:00:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hurricane Hilary is expected to reach Southern California as a tropical storm with damaging winds and rain. A spike in mortgage rates means home shoppers may need to adjust their searches. In Seoul, reaction to the Camp David meeting of leaders from the U.S., South Korean, and Japan.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Camp David Summit, Yellowknife Evacuation, Ecuador Election | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230082/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:25:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230082/</guid><description>Podcast Description President Biden hosts his counterparts from Japan and South Korea at Camp David. The Canadian city of Yellowknife is evacuated as wildfires approach. Ecuadorians prepare for elections.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Larry Kaplow, Roberta Rampton, Ally Schweitzer, and Alice Woelfle. It was produced by Mansee Khurana, Claire Murashima and Lilly Quiroz.</description></item><item><title>Ruling on Abortion Medication, Recovery in Maui, Elections in Guatemala | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230083/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 10:14:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mifepristone remains accessible, for now, after an appeals court ruling Wednesday. Recovery from Maui&amp;rsquo;s wildfires continues. Elections in Guatemala have broad implications for corruption and crime.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Kevin Drew, Larry Kaplow, Ally Schweitzer, Diane Webber, and Alice Woelfle. It was produced by Mansee Khurana, Claire Murashima, and Lilly Quiroz.</description></item><item><title>GOP Polling on Trump, Niger Coup, Conditions at ICE Detention Centers | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230084/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 10:38:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why Republicans seem unbothered by Trump&amp;rsquo;s indictments. Coup leaders in Niger tighten their grip. NPR obtains confidential reports describing &amp;ldquo;barbaric&amp;rdquo; treatment within ICE detention centers.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Kevin Drew, Barrie Hardymon, Ally Schweitzer, Michael Sullivan, Ben Swayse, and Alice Woelfle. It was produced by Mansee Khurana, Claire Murashima, and Lilly Quiroz.</description></item><item><title>Trump Indicted in Georgia, Recovery Continues in Maui, Angola Prison Conditions | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230085/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 10:20:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230085/</guid><description>Podcast Description A Georgia grand jury indicts Donald Trump. Recovery continues in Lahaina after deadly Maui wildfires. A federal court hears allegations of &amp;ldquo;harmful conditions&amp;rdquo; for juveniles jailed in Louisiana.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Susanna Capelouto, Kevin Drew, Ally Schweitzer, Benjamin Swasey, and Alice Woelfle.</description></item><item><title>Maui Recovery, Georgia Election Interference, Alabama Redistricting | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230086/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 10:21:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Recovery continues in Maui after America&amp;rsquo;s deadliest fire in more than 100 years. Georgia prosecutors to present evidence in election interference case. A federal court reviews Alabama&amp;rsquo;s new congressional map.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Krishnadev Calamur, Kevin Drew, Ally Schweitzer, Ben Swayse, and Allison Woelfle.</description></item><item><title>The Sunday Story: Love Commandos | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230087/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 12:00:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230087/</guid><description>Podcast Description In India, intercaste marriage is very rare and marrying for love is not widely accepted. Among those who defy tradition, a small number face threats of violence from their own families. Enter the Love Commandos, a group tasked with protecting these couples under threat. But how do they do it? And why are they controversial? Today on The Sunday Story, Ayesha sits down with Lauren Frayer, the reporter on Rough Translation&amp;rsquo;s new series &amp;ldquo;Love Commandos&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Hawaii Death Toll, Hunter Biden Special Counsel, Wisconsin's Top Court | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230088/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 13:06:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230088/</guid><description>Podcast Description The wildfires in Hawaii have become the state&amp;rsquo;s worst natural disaster in recorded history. David Weiss continues his prosecution of President Biden&amp;rsquo;s son, now as special counsel. The conservative chief justice of the the Wisconsin Supreme Court says the liberal majority has manufactured a &amp;ldquo;coup.&amp;rdquo;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Maui Fire Evacuations, Purdue Bankruptcy Blocked, Poland Moves Troops to Border | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230089/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 10:12:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mass evacuations continue after deadly Maui wildfires. The Supreme Court agrees to review a controversial bankruptcy case involving Purdue Pharma. Wary of Belarus, Poland to send troops to its border.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Kevin Drew, Amra Pasic, Denice Rios, Ally Schweitzer, and Michael Sullivan.</description></item><item><title>Hawai'i Fires, Rising Inflation, Wegovy Clinical Trial | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230090/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 10:11:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Deadly wildfires tear across two islands in Hawai&amp;rsquo;i. The latest inflation report is expected to show rising prices. Clinical trials suggest weight loss drug Wegovy reduces heart attack risks.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Kevin Drew, Rafael Nam, Ally Schweitzer, Alice Woelfle, and Diane Weber.</description></item><item><title>Montgomery Brawl Arrests, Pakistan Elections, Parkland Survivor Launches PAC | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230091/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 10:17:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Three people charged with assault after a waterside brawl in Montgomery, Ala. Pakistan is ramping up for elections while Imran Khan sits in jail. And Parkland shooting survivor David Hogg launches a PAC.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Larry Kaplow, Megan Pratz, Ally Schweitzer, Michael Sullivan, and Alice Woelfle.</description></item><item><title>Ohio Special Election, Biden at the Grand Canyon, Red Cross Blood Donations | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230092/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 10:16:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230092/</guid><description>Podcast Description An election in Ohio has implications for abortion. President Biden heads to the Grand Canyon to tout his environmental policies. The Red Cross allows blood donations from men who have sex with men.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Liz Baker, Dana Farrington, Jan Johnson, Ally Schweitzer and Alice Woelfle.</description></item><item><title>Trump Protective Order, Niger Coup, Ukraine Talks In Saudi Arabia | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230093/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 10:26:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s attorneys have until Monday evening to respond to a request for a protective order against him. Niger&amp;rsquo;s coup leaders close the country&amp;rsquo;s airspace. Ukraine calls Jeddah talks productive.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Dana Farrington, Ally Schweitzer, Michael Sullivan, and Alice Woelfle.</description></item><item><title>The Sunday Story: Hip-Hop Verses That Changed Our Lives | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230094/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:46:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230094/</guid><description>Podcast Description This month marks 50 years since the birth of hip-hop, so our friends at Pop Culture Happy Hour reached out to some NPR colleagues and a few hip-hop luminaries and asked what hip-hop verse changed their lives.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trump in Alabama, No Peace Meeting Invite for Putin, Women's World Cup | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230095/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 12:46:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Following another federal indictment, former President Trump addressed Republicans at a dinner in Alabama and says he&amp;rsquo;s done nothing wrong. Saudi Arabia hosts a peace meeting about the war in Ukraine, but without inviting Russia, and the US team is struggling at the Women&amp;rsquo;s World Cup.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Donald Trump In Court, Monthly Job Report, Alexei Navalny Sentencing | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230096/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 10:04:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former President Donald Trump pleads not guilty to new criminal charges. The Labor Department releases its monthly jobs report. Putin foe Alexei Navalny awaits a verdict on a slew of new charges.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Krishnadev Calamur, Rafael Nam, Amra Pasic, and Ally Schweitzer.</description></item><item><title>Trump Arraignment, Republicans and Climate Change, Russia Strikes Ukrainian Port | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230097/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 10:01:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Donald Trump travels to Washington for his arraignment on new criminal charges. A new poll shows Republicans are turning away from climate change. Russia strikes Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s Danube port.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Amra Pasic, Megan Pratz, Ally Schweitzer, and Michael Sullivan. It was produced by Kaity Kline, Claire Murashima, and Lilly Quiroz.</description></item><item><title>Donald Trump Indicted Over 2020 Election, Conservative Media React, U.S. Bond Rating | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 10:12:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Donald Trump is indicted on felony charges for his efforts to overturn the 2020 election. How conservative media are covering the indictment. Fitch strips the U.S. of its Triple A bond rating.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Krishnadev Calamur, Emily Kopp, Rafael Nam, Ally Schweitzer, and Alice Woelfle.</description></item><item><title>Trump's Staying Power, Oklahoma School Lawsuit, Security in Haiti | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230099/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:32:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s legal woes haven&amp;rsquo;t hurt him in the polls. The ACLU files a lawsuit to block the country&amp;rsquo;s first religious public charter school. Kenya steps in to bolster security in Haiti.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Susanna Capelouto, Megan Pratz, Ally Schweitzer, and Alice Woelfle.</description></item><item><title>A Deadly Blast in Pakistan, Ukraine Counteroffensive, Trucking Firm Yellow Folds | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784230100/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 10:04:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784230100/</guid><description>Podcast Description A bombing kills dozens on Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s border with Afghanistan. Ukraine retakes a small village from Russia. And the trucking company Yellow shuts down after receiving a $700 million government loan. Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun? Subscribe to the Up First newsletter.
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Up First was edited by Amra Pasic, Ally Schweitzer, Michael Sullivan and Emily Kopp.</description></item><item><title>GOP Hopefuls In Iowa, Putin Courts Africa, Auto Sales Strong | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784233180/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 12:24:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784233180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Republican presidential candidates gathered in Iowa for the state party&amp;rsquo;s annual Lincoln Dinner. Russian President Vladimir Putin is trying to turn African nations into allies. Car companies are making large profits despite inflation and high interest rates.</description></item><item><title>U.S. Spending Bill, Heat Exhaustion, Netanyahu on New Powers | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784233181/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 10:00:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784233181/</guid><description>Podcast Description The House and Senate are on radically different paths to approving the annual spending bills, setting up an anticipated September clash that could lead to another government shutdown. What to look out for as extreme temperatures cause more cases of dangerous heat exhaustion. And Israel&amp;rsquo;s Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu defends the overhaul of his country&amp;rsquo;s judicial system.
Want more comprehensive analysis of the most important news of the day, plus a little fun?</description></item><item><title>Hunter Biden's Plea Deal, Niger Coup, New York City's Migrant Shelters | Up First</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8784233179/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 10:38:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8784233179/</guid><description>Podcast Description A plea deal struck between the DOJ and Hunter Biden is on hold after a judge said she wants more information about whether the deal extends to any prosecution related to his business dealings. Soldiers in Niger have announced a coup, imposing a curfew and closing borders in a country that is a key U.S. ally in West Africa. And there are widespread reports of inhumane conditions at a large migrant shelter in New York City.</description></item></channel></rss>