<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Why Files: Operation Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-why-files-operation-podcast/</link><description>Recent content in The Why Files: Operation Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-why-files-operation-podcast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>515: The Search for Noah's Ark | Giants &amp; Aliens in the Book of Enoch | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130130/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Enoch warned the Giants and the Watchers of the world. Repent or feel God's wrath.
They ignored his warning.
The floodgates of Heaven burst forth and water rushed over the Earth, destroying everything. The only thing to survive is a single vessel, a huge ship: the Ark. 5 months later, the waters receded and the Ark made ground on a mountaintop. A man named Noah emerged, and civilization began again.</description></item><item><title>514: DEEP DIVE: The Montauk Project | The Truth is Darker Than You Can Possibly Imagine | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 16:12:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130001/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Montauk Project: The Truth is Darker Than You Think
In 1943, the USS Eldridge was made invisible and teleported from Philadelphia to Virginia. This event was known as the Philadelphia Experiment.
When the Eldridge reappeared, some crew materialized in walls and bulkheads. They died in agony.
But two sailors didn't reappear at all. The two men, who happened to be brothers, were presumed dead or lost.
They weren't dead.</description></item><item><title>513: Mystery in Cisco Grove: Don Shrum’s Encounter with UFOs, Aliens and Robots | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130002/</guid><description>Podcast Description In September 1964, Captain McLeod and Sergeant Barnes were dispatched from Wright-Patterson Air Force base in Ohio. They were sent to investigate a UFO sighting in Northern California.
Wright-Patterson AFB got lots of UFO reports. 99% of them could be explained. And a sizeable percentage of those sightings were hoaxers looking for attention.
The other 1% were classified as UFOs and sent on to Project Blue Book. What happened from there, McLeod didn't know.</description></item><item><title>513: DEEP DIVE: Are Humans the First Civilization? The Silurian Hypothesis | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130003/</guid><description>Podcast Description There are over 7 billion people living on the earth right now. Tens of millions are born and die each year. Every single one of us leaves signs of our existence in the air, water, soil -- even space.
But these signs won't last forever. Our buildings will be gone in a few hundred years. Our stone monuments, plastic, styrofoam, twinkies, even evidence of our inevitable nuclear destruction will eventually be gone.</description></item><item><title>512: Project Looking Glass | The Time Warriors of the 2012 Apocalypse | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130004/</guid><description>Podcast Description You’re not supposed to be alive. None of us are. About 10 years ago, you woke up to an eerie silence. The power was out. You went to check your phone for news but your phone was dead.
Then you realized, everything was dead. Some kind of blackout, you thought.
You looked out your window, confused. It looked like a normal December morning. Holiday decorations were up, though all the Christmas lights were out.</description></item><item><title>511: DEEP DIVE: Smithsonian Cover-Up: Ancient Egyptians and Giants in the Grand Canyon | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 22:55:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130005/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1908, President Teddy Roosevelt wanted to declare the Grand Canyon off-limits to all timber and mining operations. It would take another 11 years for Congress to designate the Grand Canyon a national park.
Sensing a final opportunity for adventure, explorer G.E. Kincaid took a boat down the Colorado River and through the Grand Canyon. The canyon was rich in minerals like gold, silver and copper and Kincaid wanted to see what he could find before the area was closed off for good.</description></item><item><title>510: The UFO Incident That Shocked Ariel School: Telepathic Extraterrestrials | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130006/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 19:34:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130006/</guid><description>Podcast Description September 14th, 1994 was a quiet night in Zimbabwe. Then suddenly, boom! An explosion startled people all over the country. Windows rattled. Doors shook. Shocked and confused, people sheepishly stepped outside to see what happened. Everything looked fine. They went back inside.
But one woman wasn't satisfied. Cynthia Hind drove around the capital city of Harare, searching for the source of the sound but, nothing seemed unusual. But back at home, Cynthia's phone rang relentlessly.</description></item><item><title>509: DEEP DIVE: The Dead Internet Theory | It's ALL Fake | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 23:25:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130007/</guid><description>Podcast Description What if all of our online existence is fake?
You, me, everyone; we're living in a real-life Matrix. Designed to distract us from the truth: that we're just drones in a digital ant-hill. We live, work and die so that the wealthy and powerful can grow more wealthy and powerful.
This is called the Dead Internet Theory. And there's compelling evidence that it's real.
Let's find out why.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>508: Kenny Veach Vanishes on his Quest for the M Cave | Mojave Mysteries Vol. 1 | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 19:15:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130008/</guid><description>Podcast Description o most, the Mojave Desert looks barren. Jagged rock, swirling sand, and scrub brush. But the Mojave is full of life. It’s been home to native tribes for thousands of years.
And the Mojave is also home to many caves; that hold many secrets.
Some caves are reported to be secret entrances to underground bases. And not all of those bases are occupied by humans.
Other caves are rumored to be portals to different places on earth.</description></item><item><title>507: DEEP DIVE: MK Ultra Exposed: We Name the Names behind the CIA's Sinister Mind Control Projects | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 21:27:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130009/</guid><description>Podcast Description MK Ultra, the infamous CIA program shrouded in mystery and controversy. Uncover the chilling truths and unanswered questions that linger around this clandestine project. Was it a mere Cold War strategy or something far more sinister? Navigate through a labyrinth of mind control experiments, secret government operations, and ethical quandaries. This journey into the unknown promises to challenge your perceptions and leave you questioning what lies beneath the surface of historical narratives.</description></item><item><title>506: Backyard Time Machine: The Time Travel Mystery of Mike “Mad Man” Marcum | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mike fired up the box and the lasers came to life.
The machine produced a small circular area of distortion. It was a vortex about eight inches across that looked like ripples above a fire. This was unexpected. Mike didn’t know what the vortex was or if it was dangerous. So he grabbed a sheet-metal screw and tossed it through the field.
It vanished.
Mike just stared and blinked and waited.</description></item><item><title>504: DEEP DIVE: Simulation Theory - Evidence is Everywhere | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 16:11:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130011/</guid><description>Podcast Description PROOF THAT EVERYTHING - IS A SIMULATION (Including God)
Is this reality? Well, we're experiencing ... something right now so maybe the better question is: what is reality?
Could everything we see, everything we experience, everything that exists in our entire universe -- be artificial? Supporters of Simulation Theory believe that not only is it possible that we're living in a simulation; it's likely.
And the more we look for evidence, the more we find.</description></item><item><title>135: Göbekli Tepe and the Prophecy of Pillar 43 | Apocalypse and the Vulture Stone | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 16:18:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130012/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are the descendants of an ancient civilization; one which mastered technology, mapped the cosmos, and understood our relationship with the natural world.
Our ancestors traveled the world and built enormous structures. They scaled their creations into cities.
They shared a common governance and similar religious beliefs.
Our ancestors lived, as we do today, as a global society.
Around 14,500 years ago, this global superpower started to collapse.</description></item><item><title>505: DEEP DIVE: Legend of the Immortal Count of Saint Germain | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 15:39:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130013/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Count of Saint Germain has been called a prophet, a sorcerer, and an immortal.
He's been spotted all over the world for a thousand years. And every time he's seen, he looks exactly the same age.
The Count of Saint Germain advised Kings, Queens and Emperors. He was present at every significant event in European history. And even was an important contributor to America's struggle for Independence.</description></item><item><title>504: 20 And Back - The Super Soldiers Defending the Kuiper Belt | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130014/</guid><description>Podcast Description On April 7, 2016, the team running NASA’s New Horizons mission were waiting nervously. The spacecraft was about to enter the outermost reaches of our solar system.
They'd aimed toward Pluto. Which lives in a region of the solar system called the Kuiper Belt.
Just before arriving at the dwarf planet, the team noticed an object nearby. And it was acting very strange. This object, whatever it was, was spinning faster than everything else around it.</description></item><item><title>503: The Black Knight Satellite | Ancient Craft Watching us From Orbit | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130015/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1957, the Soviet Union launched Sputnik 1. It was the first satellite in Earth's orbit.
Or was it?
For over a hundred years, an object has been seen, heard and photographed by people all around the world. This object became known as the Black Knight Satellite.
The signals coming from the Black Knight Satellite have been decoded.
And if the translation is correct, it's been watching us for 13,000 years.</description></item><item><title>502: Gravity is a Lie, Nothing is Real, the Universe is Electric | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Since grade school, we’ve been taught that gravity is what keeps our feet firmly planted on the ground, but what if that’s all been a lie?
I'm not saying if you jump off a bridge, you fall up, instead of down. But what if Newton and Einstein were wrong and what *really* ties our universe together is not gravity, but electricity?
The Electric Universe Theory says that, instead of gravity, the universe's *true* attractive force comes from invisible electric currents that surround our planet, our solar system, the galaxy and.</description></item><item><title>501: DEEP DIVE: The Adam &amp; Eve Apocalypse Story | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130017/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1966 a well-known engineer released a book with information that could impact everyone on earth. But before anyone could read it, it was classified by the CIA.
We only learned of its existence a few years ago because of a Freedom of Information request.
The CIA only released 57 pages of the original 284-page manuscript. And those pages have been, in the CIA's own words, "sanitized".
Why does the CIA think this book is so dangerous that they had to hide it from the public for 60 years; and continue to hide most of it?</description></item><item><title>132: Time-Slip Artifacts: Modern Objects in the Ancient World - Volume 1 | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130018/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130018/</guid><description>Podcast Description The story of the human race is a story of technology.
One of our ancestors created fire and passed that knowledge along to the next generation. Then the invention of the wheel. Then agriculture, a writing system, mathematics, space travel.
Within our story, empires rise and fall. Technology progresses. Civilizations are born and die. The human race continues to innovate.
All of our innovations are built on previous ones.</description></item><item><title>131: Skyquakes, Upsweeps, Bloops and Sky Trumpets | Terrifying Sounds that Signal the End of the World | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 23:34:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130019/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Book of Revelation says the end of the world will be announced with the sound of seven trumpets. Each blowing of the trumpet brings a new apocalyptic event. After the seventh trumpet: armageddon.
For centuries, people have reported low-frequency hums, the crack of thunder on a clear day and the sound of cannon-fire in the middle of nowhere.
Mysterious sounds have been heard at the bottom of the ocean and in outer space.</description></item><item><title>130: The Horrors of Plum Island | Hybrids, Human Experiments and Weaponized Killer Insects | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130020/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 03:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130020/</guid><description>Podcast Description In July 2008, the carcass of an animal washed up on the beach at Montauk Point Long Island. Local beachcombers are used to seeing dead animals. Seagulls, fish, crabs, even the occasional whale. But they had never seen anything like this.
Animal experts were brought in to identify it. They were stumped. It looked like part dog, part reptile and part rodent - with the beak of a bird.</description></item><item><title>129: The Rendlesham UFO Encounter and the Alien Message from the Future | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130021/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130021/</guid><description>Podcast Description The night after Christmas, 1980, was the last time Airman First Class John Burroughs would ever lead a normal life. He was on patrol at an American-operated Woodbridge Air Force base in southern England. Woodbridge and nearby Bentwaters - called the Twin Bases were rumored to possess nuclear materials. This was the middle of the Cold War, and tensions were high. The threat of nuclear attack, global escalation, and more, sat heavy on the shoulders of Burroughs and his fellow servicemen.</description></item><item><title>Many Worlds Theory: You're Living in a Universe | Can You Visit Your Other Lives? | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130022/</guid><description>Podcast Description So, tell me... how do you like being a movie star? I can't imagine your life. You can't walk down the street without being mobbed by adoring fans. You attend power-lunches with your agent. You pose for pictures on the red carpet on your way to collect your third Academy Award. Your life sounds fun.
Wait, what? You're not a movie star? That's not your life? Well, maybe not in *this* universe, but there is a universe out there where your life is exactly as I described.</description></item><item><title>127: Ghost Lights or Alien Tech? Signals from Beyond the Grave or Beyond the Solar System? | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here’s the scene. You’re driving down a secluded road. The only lights come from your headlights. The only sounds you hear are crickets and the hum of the engine. Suddenly, a mysterious orb of light appears in the distance, floating a few feet above the ground. You get the sense that the light is aware of your presence. It darts around, beckoning you closer.
It can’t be another car.</description></item><item><title>125: The Moon’s Dark Secret: Aliens Harvesting Human Souls | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130024/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Your world is an illusion. Your choices are irrelevant. Your friends, your family, and everyone around you are just manifestations of your mind.
You’re a trapped animal in a cage: a virtual reality created more than 250,000 years ago for a single purpose: to use you as food.
Your emotions are food for those who created the cage. Feelings of happiness and joy are digestible. But those emotions are nowhere near as nourishing as sadness, malice, and especially anger.</description></item><item><title>125: Rise of Atlantis and Fall of the Lemuria: The War that Sank a Continent | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130025/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130025/</guid><description>Podcast Description For thousands of years, the world has been captivated by the mystery of Atlantis. The concept of an ancient city hidden beneath the ocean is fascinating.
But what if there was not just a city, but an entire continent buried beneath the waves?
The continent of Lemuria is a massive landmass believed to have sunk in the Indian Ocean after some ancient, catastrophic event. Atlantis and Lemuria are similar in that they’ve sparked numerous theories, legends and interpretations.</description></item><item><title>124: Solving Cicada 3301: Decoding the Internet's Greatest Mystery | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130026/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Early in the morning of January 4th 2012, a strange message appeared on the internet. Just a few lines of text on an image, posted anonymously. Hello. We are looking for highly intelligent individuals. To find them, we have devised a test.
There is a message hidden in this image.
Find it, and it will lead you on the road to finding us. We look forward to meeting the few that will make it all the way through.</description></item><item><title>123: Ghost Hunting: The Science of the Other Side | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130027/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130027/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1901, Nikola Tesla had the most terrifying experience of his life. As he worked alone in his laboratory at night, he felt a presence.
He created a device to see if he could hear, or pick up any signals from whatever it was that he felt. He called it the “spirit radio”, and it worked.
Tesla wasn’t alone.
Throughout history, famous scientists, who helped shape the technology we used today, have spoken of ghosts and hauntings that shook them to their core.</description></item><item><title>122: Finding Agartha: The Search for the Hidden City in the Center of the Earth | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130028/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cultures around the world have myths that speak of a mysterious underground kingdom that exists deep within the earth, hidden away from the primitive and violent surface-dwellers: which is us.
Picture a society untouched by time, unscathed by war, and unaffected by natural disasters. A culture thriving in the vast open spaces inside the Earth.
Throughout history, many have looked for physical evidence of its existence, tempted by stories of a peaceful but powerful subterranean civilization with advanced technology and ancient knowledge long forgotten by modern man.</description></item><item><title>121: The UFO Incident That Shocked Ariel School: Telepathic Extraterrestrials | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130029/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130029/</guid><description>Podcast Description September 14th, 1994 was a quiet night in Zimbabwe. Then suddenly, boom! An explosion startled people all over the country. Windows rattled. Doors shook. Shocked and confused, people sheepishly stepped outside to see what happened. Everything looked fine. They went back inside.
But one woman wasn't satisfied. Cynthia Hind drove around the capital city of Harare, searching for the source of the sound but, nothing seemed unusual. But back at home, Cynthia's phone rang relentlessly.</description></item><item><title>120: The Moon Landing: Stanley Kubrick's Greatest Film | How NASA and Hollywood Fooled the World | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130030/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stanley Kubrick is considered one of the greatest filmmakers of all time. Of his 13 movies a few are considered classics in their respective genres. Including the black comedy Dr. Strangelove, the highly-quotable anti-war commentary of Full Metal Jacket, and one of the most disturbing and enduring horror films of all time, The Shinning.
But in 1968, Kubrick released "2001 – A Space Odyssey". This is more than a classic.</description></item><item><title>119: Indrid Cold, the Truth about Planet Lanulos and the Mystery of the Smiling Man | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130031/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130031/</guid><description>Podcast Description On November 2nd, 1966, Woody Derenberger was driving home from a business trip when he encountered an extraterrestrial being named Indrid Cold.
Cold communicated with Woody telepathically, and the two went on to be lifelong friends. Other people close to Woody, including family, friends, and even his therapist claimed that they, too, had experiences with Indrid Cold.
Woody wrote and published a detailed account of his experiences, and never went back on his story.</description></item><item><title>118: Artificial Intelligence Out of Control: The Apocalypse is Here | How AI and ChatGPT End Humanity | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130032/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130032/</guid><description>Podcast Description The story of humans began a long time ago.
Three and a half billion years ago protein molecules floated around the ooze called the primordial soup. Then something happened and a molecule made a copy of itself.
And then another copy and another. Soon these molecules arranged themselves into something called a cell.
Then cells clumped together and multiplied. Organisms were created. Over the next three billion years, the organisms became more complicated and more diverse.</description></item><item><title>117: Forbidden Archaeology: Lost Giants of America | The Smithsonian's Biggest Secret | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130033/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130033/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1886, mining engineer John T. Reid was told the Paiute legend
of a giant people defeated by the natives near Lovelock, Nevada. The last of the giants met their fiery end deep within the bowels of a cave.
Reid’s belief in this legend stirred great interest in the secrets held within Lovelock Cave.
Official excavations were undertaken in both 1912 and 1924 by the University of California, with reports telling of thousands of artifacts being recovered.</description></item><item><title>116: The Truth about Roswell: Decoding Decades of Deception | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130034/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 03:00:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130034/</guid><description>Podcast Description It was a sunny afternoon on June 24th, 1947, and Kenneth Arnold was flying his small aircraft over Mineral, Washington. He was heading to Yakima but took a slight detour to look for a lost US Marine Corps plane. If he could find it, he’d collect a nice reward.
Flying near Mount Rainier, he spotted a shiny object in his plane's mirror. Then, he saw multiple flashes of light.</description></item><item><title>115: Operation Mincemeat: The Shadow Catalyst for CIA's Dark Age | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130035/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 03:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130035/</guid><description>Podcast Description On April 30, 1943, in the middle of World War II, a body washed up on the shore of Huelva, Spain. The deceased man was wearing a British military uniform. There was a briefcase strapped to his body containing British and American military secrets. The man was Major William Martin, a British Royal Marine who was the single victim of a fatal plane crash at sea. He had just returned from temporary leave in London, where he had gone to the theater and purchased an engagement ring for his fiancee, Pam.</description></item><item><title>113: Bending Time: The Successful Time Travel Experiments using Kozyrev Mirrors | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130036/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 03:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130036/</guid><description>Podcast Description In December 1990, in a remote village above the Arctic Circle, two Russian scientists embarked on a daring experiment. Their goal was to enhance human “super-perception” or ESP.
They built a device that could shield subjects from electromagnetic interference and amplify their biological energy. The device was a large tube of rolled aluminum with a chair inside.
As soon as the device was built, strange phenomena occurred around the village.</description></item><item><title>113: Aliens &amp; Espionage: Crop Circles and the CIA Coverup | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130037/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 04:00:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130037/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1974 a group of scientists beamed a message into space. The message, meant to be received by an intelligent alien species, described life on Earth.
Written in simple binary code, and using the most powerful radio telescope on the planet, the message was broadcast to a dense cluster of stars in the constellation of Hercules.
This exercise was just ceremonial; a way to demonstrate new technology in radio astronomy.</description></item><item><title>Surviving The Sixth Extinction: Are we too late? | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130038/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 03:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Of all the species that have ever existed on Earth, 99% of them are gone. Most of those were wiped out during what are known as "Mass Extinction Events".
Since life emerged on our planet, there have been five mass extinctions. Sometimes these events last many years. But sometimes a mass extinction can happen very, very suddenly.
Some scientists think we're on the verge of a sixth mass extinction.</description></item><item><title>Varginha UFO Crash: Alien Contact, Government Denial and Coverup | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130039/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 03:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130039/</guid><description>Podcast Description The North American Air Defense Command, known as NORAD, was established in 1958. It was to provide early warning and defense against Soviet bombers and missile launches. But it wasn't long before NORAD would be monitoring skies around the entire planet.
Early in the morning, on January 13th, 1996, NORAD contacted Brazilian Air Defense to report an object entering the Earth's atmosphere about 200 miles Northeast of Sao Paolo.</description></item><item><title>110: Sacred Object or Ancient Weapon? Where is the Ark of the Covenant and what technology did it use? | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130040/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 03:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Even though UFOs are seen everywhere: over the desert, over the ocean, over cities; there's no way to predict when and where they'll show up.
Well, no way except for one: build or detonate a nuclear weapon.
Since the dawn of the atomic age, UFOs have been seen -- and photographed -- during nuclear weapons tests and near nuclear weapons facilities. The Ark of the Covenant is one of the most mysterious artifacts in human history.</description></item><item><title>109: Martian Mysteries: What NASA doesn't want you to know | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130041/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 03:13:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130041/</guid><description>Podcast Description On July 25th, a NASA scientist was studying images of a region of Mars called "Cydonia" when something caught his eye.
He had to take a second to process what he was seeing. He grabbed a magnifying glass.
There was no doubt. On the surface of Mars, 140 million miles from Earth, was a structure in the shape of a human face. It was huge; about a mile wide; and showed two eyes, a nose, and a mouth.</description></item><item><title>Mothman Returns: Point Pleasant Legend to Chicago Terror | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130042/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 03:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130042/</guid><description>Podcast Description This legend beings as so many do. Three gravediggers, working in a cemetery hear something overhead. They look up and see a creature: almost ten feet tall with massive wings perched on a high tree branch; staring at them with glowing red eyes. Then in an instant, it's gone.
Three days later, just a few miles away, two young couples burst into the local police station. Terrified, they report being chased by a tall man with wings and glowing red eyes.</description></item><item><title>Shattering the Illusion: Exorcism and the Truth About Possessions | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130043/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 03:28:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here's how it starts. Maybe it's your mother or maybe your sister. She starts complaining of headaches and strange tingling sensations in different parts of her body.
Her discomfort escalates. She complains of hallucinations; she starts hearing voices. Then the seizures begin. She has trouble walking and eating. And maintaining control of her bladder.
The seizures become violent. She thrashes around her bed for hours. You try to restrain her, but she suddenly has impossible strength.</description></item><item><title>106: America's Secret Space Program and the Alien Connection: SOLAR WARDEN | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130044/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 03:30:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gary McKinnon was obsessed with UFOs; and believed governments were covering up evidence that UFOs exist. In the year 2000, he decided to do a little digging. Gary was a computer expert so what better place to dig than on US government computers?
What he found was so shocking that it sent the entire United States government into a full-blown panic. In fact, the US spent 10 years trying to prosecute Gary.</description></item><item><title>104: What's Hiding Underneath Denver Airport? The Truth about the Strangest Airport in the World | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130045/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 03:00:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130045/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's just a matter of time before it happens. Some catastrophic event that wipes out a large percentage of the Earth's population; and forces the human race to "reset".
Maybe one of the 30,000 "Near Earth Objects" being tracked by NASA finally hit the Earth. Causing an extinction event on par with what wiped out the dinosaurs.
Or Earth's poles finally shift. And, without its magnetic field, the planet is exposed to the raw destructive power of the Sun's radiation.</description></item><item><title>104: The Gateway Process: the CIA's classified Space &amp; Time Travel system that you can learn | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130046/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 03:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130046/</guid><description>Podcast Description The United States military is always looking for new ways to create super soldiers.
They use performance-enhancing and mind-altering drugs. They're currently experimenting with brain implant technology. They've even explored genetic engineering to try and *breed* the perfect soldier.
But those are nothing compared to what happened in 1983; when Lieutenant Colonel Wayne McDonnell submitted a very unusual and detailed report to US Army Intelligence.
It was called "</description></item><item><title>103: CIA Declassified: What Backwards Secrets are you hiding in your Reverse Speech? | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130047/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 03:30:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130047/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1983, David Oates dropped his walkman into the toilet.
If you're under 40 years old, a walkman was a portable cassette player.
If you're under 30, a cassette was how we listened to music in the stone age.
Anyway, after being dropped, David's tape player would only play tapes in reverse.
At first, he found this entertaining. There were lots of songs that contained hidden messages that you could only hear if you played them backward.</description></item><item><title>102: The Emerald Tablet Contains the Secret to Immortality | The Philosopher's Stone from Atlantis | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130048/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 02:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Which would you prefer? Eternal life or unlimited wealth? How about both?
For that, you need The Philosopher's Stone: a substance that can turn base metals into gold, and grant you eternal life.
The Book of Aquarius contains the instructions for The Philosopher's Stone. Although the process can take years, the ingredients are simple. You have them in your home right now.
The Book of Aquarius is derived from many older texts.</description></item><item><title>101: Tesla's Most Destructive Weapon | The Tunguska Event: Comet Impact or Death Ray Experiment? | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130049/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 23:31:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130049/</guid><description>Podcast Description On June 30th, 1908, a mysterious explosion shook the remote Siberian region of Tunguska. The blast flattened 80 million trees across 800 square miles. Every plant, every animal, every insect in the blast radius was vaporized. The shockwave was felt as far away as England.
It looked like a comet impact, yet, no crater was found and no debris was discovered. Scientists still can't explain what happened.
But... at that exact moment, on the other side of the world, Nikola Telsa was conducting his latest experiment: transmitting massive amounts of electricity through the atmosphere.</description></item><item><title>100: Are all the UFOs an invasion or has Project Blue Beam finally begun? | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130050/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 23:36:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Your world is not as it seems. Everything you know to be true is a lie. Hidden behind the façade of our everyday lives is a secret and powerful organization with a dangerous agenda. To manipulate the minds of the masses and usher in a new world order. They call this program "Project Blue Beam".
If the program is successful, we won't see it coming. Borders between nations will be dissolved; all religions will be dismantled; and technology will be turned against us.</description></item><item><title>99: Sergei Ponomarenko : The UFO Time Traveler | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130051/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 01:59:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130051/</guid><description>Podcast Description On April 23rd 2006, a man in his early 20s was seen in Kyiv, Ukraine staring at a high-rise apartment building. Witnesses described him as looking confused and anxious. They thought he might have been a lost tourist.
The man approached two police officers and nervously asked for directions... to a place that no longer existed.
The officers asked the young man for identification. But, there were two problems with his ID.</description></item><item><title>97: Georgia Guidestones Destroyed by a Villain or a Hero? | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130052/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 12:24:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130052/</guid><description>Podcast Description On July 6, 2022, a bomb detonated on a 5-acre plot of farmland in Elberton, Georgia. The explosion destroyed a large monument that had stood on the property for over 40 years.
Known as "The Georgia Guidestones", it was four monolithic slabs of granite, weighing over 230,000 pounds, that contained a set of rules for a more peaceful and orderly society. The identity of the builder was a mystery for 40 years, but today I'll tell you who he was.</description></item><item><title>96: He found Giants then the Government Found Him | What really happened to Andrew Dawson? | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130053/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 12:13:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrew started his TikTok account in July of 2021, and he posted all the typical things. Videos of friends, of work, his girlfriend, his dog, and just him goofing around.
But starting in April, 2022, his posts would take a strange turn; and Andrew Dawson would become the center of one the biggest internet mysteries in years.
Every story I cover on this channel is a suggestion from you and almost every one of them falls into one of a few categories.</description></item><item><title>96: Apollo 20: The Secret Mission to the Moon to Salvage an Ancient Alien Spacecraft | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130054/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 12:48:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130054/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Apollo spaceflight program lasted from 1961 to 1972. Apollo 11 was Neil Armstrong's famous first step. Apollo 17 was the last manned mission to the moon. In all, 20 Apollo flights were planned but Apollo 18, 19 and 20 were canceled.
But in 2007, a retired astronaut blew the whistle and claimed Apollo 18, 19 and 20 *did* happen. But they were highly classified. He knows this because was the commander of Apollo 20.</description></item><item><title>95: CIA Classified Book about the End of the World | The True Adam &amp; Eve Story | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130055/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 08:28:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130055/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1966 a well-known engineer released a book with information that could impact everyone on earth. But before anyone could read it, it was classified by the CIA.
We only learned of its existence a few years ago because of a Freedom of Information request.
The CIA only released 57 pages of the original 284-page manuscript. And those pages have been, in the CIA's own words, "sanitized".
Why does the CIA think this book is so dangerous that they had to hide it from the public for 60 years; and continue to hide most of it?</description></item><item><title>94: The Brooklyn Bridge UFO Abduction | The Weirdest Story You'll Ever Hear | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130056/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 21:40:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nov 30, 1989, just after 3 AM. New York City. Janet Kimball was driving over the Brooklyn Bridge when her car stalled and slowly rolled to a stop.
After a couple of failed attempts to get the car started, Janet was hit by a bright light. Bright enough that she had to shield her eyes. The light was coming from an apartment building. Janet thought maybe someone was shooting a movie.</description></item><item><title>93: Thanks a Million: Year End Wrap and Story of The Why Files | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130057/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 19:37:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Thanks a Million: Year End Wrap and Story of The Why Files
〰〰〰〰〰〰〰〰〰〰〰〰〰〰〰〰〰〰
EXECUTIVE PRODUCERS:
Gino Gentile
Jennifer Gentile
AJ Gentile
Patreon Members
THANK YOU MODS:
Daniel_Van_Auken
jengen13
pratty505
VictoriaY
Jschoop
Zanythos
〰〰〰〰〰〰〰〰〰〰〰〰〰〰〰〰〰〰
🙏 SUPPORT THE WHY FILES 🙏 https://www.patreon.com/thewhyfiles (Fun, Free Perks!)
👽 BUY WHY FILES MERCH 👽
👽 https://shop.thewhyfiles.com (Code: LIZZIDPEEPLE for 10% off first order) 👽
💬 CHAT WITH US ON DISCORD 💬 💬 https://thewhyfiles.com/discord 💬 Support this podcast: https://podcasters.</description></item><item><title>92: Shadow People and The Hat Man | Who are they? What do they want? | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130058/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 00:55:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here's how it happens.
You're drifting off to sleep; or maybe you wake up in the middle of the night. You feel a presence in the room.
You see something out of the corner of your eye. You try to look but you can't move. You try to call out, but you're unable to make a sound. There's an invisible weight on your chest. Even breathing is difficult.</description></item><item><title>91: Smithsonian Cover-Up: Ancient Egyptians and Giants in the Grand Canyon | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130059/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 01:15:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130059/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1908, President Teddy Roosevelt wanted to declare the Grand Canyon off-limits to all timber and mining operations. It would take another 11 years for Congress to designate the Grand Canyon a national park.
Sensing a final opportunity for adventure, explorer G.E. Kincaid took a boat down the Colorado River and through the Grand Canyon. The canyon was rich in minerals like gold, silver and copper and Kincaid wanted to see what he could find before the area was closed off for good.</description></item><item><title>90: The US Military's Secret Flying Saucer Project | Alien Reproduction Vehicles (ARVs) | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130060/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 08:32:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130060/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1988, aerospace designer Brad Sorenson went to Norton Air Force base for the annual air show. The show was the chance for aerospace companies and military contractors to show off new technology to top military and government officials. Brad wanted to network and maybe grab a new client or two.
At some point, Brad got turned around and separated from his group. He hopped into another group and ended up in a large hangar watching a presentation given by a three-star general.</description></item><item><title>89: Proof of Reincarnation | Dorothy Eady: Ancient Egyptian Priestess Reborn | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130061/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 02:33:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130061/</guid><description>Podcast Description 3-year old Dorothy was playing, then accidentally fell down a flight of stairs. She hit her head and was knocked unconscious. When her parents found her, she wasn't breathing.
They called a doctor who rushed over immediately. Dorothy's mother broke down when the doctor said there was nothing he could do. Her little girl was dead.
The doctor left and returned an hour later with Dorothy's death certificate and gently discussed arrangements for the little girl's body.</description></item><item><title>88: From Amityville to Annabelle | The Truth of Ed and Lorraine Warren's Scariest Case | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130062/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 10:20:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130062/</guid><description>Podcast Description From Amityville to Annabelle | The Truth of Ed and Lorraine Warren's Scariest Case
Ed and Lorraine Warren are maybe the most famous paranormal investigators in history.
They've worked on more than 10,000 cases. Some of which have been made into books and movies. The Conjuring films are based on the work of the Warrens.
Today we'll look at a few of their scariest, most disturbing cases and find the truth.</description></item><item><title>86: Project Serpo: The Secret 10-Year Mission to a Planet 40 Million Light Years Away | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130063/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 05:44:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130063/</guid><description>Podcast Description What if you were offered the opportunity to visit another planet?
You get to experience the culture of an alien race, explore a new world; see and use technology that's 5,000 years ahead of ours.
Would you do it?
Before you answer, there are a few catches. You'll be gone for at least ten years. And when you return to Earth, all evidence of your existence will be erased.</description></item><item><title>85: Spontaneous Human Combustion | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130064/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 05:32:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here's the nightmare scenario. You stop by your elderly mother's house to check on her. You grab the doorknob. It's hot to the touch. You ring the bell and knock. No answer.
You fish out your key and open the door. You call out but there's only silence.
The air is warm. There's a sweet, smoky smell. But, nothing looks out of place.
Finally, you go into the living room and you see it.</description></item><item><title>85: ALIEN WAR at The Dulce Underground Base | They Mysterious Death of Phil Schneider | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130065/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 18:55:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130065/</guid><description>Podcast Description ALIEN WAR at The Dulce Underground Base | They Mysterious Death of Phil Schneider
Everyone's heard of Area 51. The top-secret facility in the Nevada desert. But nobody really knows what happens there. We have only rumors.
One rumor is that alien bodies have been recovered from UFO crashes. Those aliens have been autopsied and the subjects of medical experiments for years.
But have you ever heard of Dulce Base?</description></item><item><title>84: Every Event is Secretly Encoded in the Bible even YOUR Birthday (and the Apocalypse) | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130066/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 03:04:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130066/</guid><description>Podcast Description In September 1994, Yitzak Rabin, Prime Minister of Israel received an ominous message. It was a warning that his life was in danger.
The sender of the message said this information was secretly encoded -- in the Bible.
Rabin ignored the warning.
A year later, the Prime Minister was assassinated.
The code hidden within the Bible not only predicted Rabin's assassination, but also predicted the date, and even the name of the killer.</description></item><item><title>83: Alien Probe, Sentient Machine, Nuclear Weapon, or Junk? What is the Betz Mystery Sphere? | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130067/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 15:05:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130067/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the Spring of 1974, a large brush fire swept across the property owned by Antoine and Gerri Betz.
While assessing the damage, they noticed something very out of place.
Lying in the smoldering grass, was a highly polished, metal sphere. This became known as the Betz sphere or the Betz orb.
Terry Betz, Antoine and Jerri's 21-year-old son, went to pick up the sphere. Although it was only 8-inches in diameter, it was extremely heavy.</description></item><item><title>82: Michigan Dogmen, The Beast of Bray Road and True Stories of Werewolves | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130068/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 13:31:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130068/</guid><description>Podcast Description The story always starts the same way. On the side of the road, in a backyard, or in a parking lot; a large dog hovers over a dead animal, quietly eating.
As you approach, the dog looks up. Its eyes shining in the dark.
As you move closer, the dog stands up on its hind legs. It's well over 7 feet tall. It has the body of a man but the head of a dog or a wolf.</description></item><item><title>81: TESLA KNEW The Secret of the Great Pyramid: Unlimited Free Energy to Power The World | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130069/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 22:48:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nikola Tesla believed that he could harness the energy from inside the earth and transmit that power *wirelessly* around the world.
His early experiments were successful. But his research mysteriously vanished after his death.
There is no evidence left of Tesla's wireless power technology.
Or is there?
For years we were taught that the Great Pyramid of Giza was a tomb for a king. It wasn't. It had a different purpose.</description></item><item><title>80: JOHN TITOR: Soldier from the Future | Can this time traveler save us from destruction? | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130070/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 18:08:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130070/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is our future. The United States of America endures a second civil war, killing millions. Immediately after that, a *World* War begins. Nuclear weapons are used. Billions are killed.
The aftermath leaves the earth in ruins. Electric grids are down. Food becomes scarce. Disease is rampant. Society breaks down.
Then, in 2038, all computers go offline. Civilization is set back several hundred years. The world enters a second dark age.</description></item><item><title>77: The Airforce UFO Cover Up That Drove a Man INSANE | The Paul Bennewitz Story | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130071/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 22:22:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Paul Bennewitz lived next to a large airforce base. When he saw colored lights in the sky, he assumed they were experimental aircraft.
Then he started picking up strange radio signals that seemed to be an alien language.
He took his findings to the Air Force. Publicly they denied the UFO/alien story.
But privately, they confirmed Paul's findings. The Air Force even funded his UFO research.
He spent several years gathering evidence and reporting it to the authorities.</description></item><item><title>76: The CIA Assassination of Frank Olson | The Murder that Exposed MK-ULTRA | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130072/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 02:41:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130072/</guid><description>Podcast Description November 28th, 1953. New York City. At 2:30 AM the body hit the sidewalk. A few seconds later, a shower of glass.
The doorman of the Statler Hotel yelled to the lobby that there was a jumper.
The night manager rushed out and saw him. A man, about 40 years old, lying on the pavement. He was on his back, wearing only his underwear and blood started to pool around him.</description></item><item><title>74: The Montauk Project: The Truth is Darker Than You Think | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130073/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 15:44:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130073/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1943, the USS Eldridge was made invisible and teleported from Philadelphia to Virginia. This event was known as the Philadelphia Experiment.
When the Eldridge reappeared, some crew materialized in walls and bulkheads. They died in agony.
But two sailors didn't reappear at all. The two men, who happened to be brothers, were presumed dead or lost.
They weren't dead. They traveled 40 years into the future; in a secret military base on the East end of Long Island.</description></item><item><title>75: Legend of the Phantom Fortress | The Plane that Flew and Landed Itself | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130074/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 23:35:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130074/</guid><description>Podcast Description World War 2 has countless stories of bravery, sacrifice, camaraderie, and heroism.
But the war also has a lot of mysteries. Many of them still unsolved.
Like the legend of the Phantom Fortress.
A B-17 bomber that returned from a mission with no crew aboard; and somehow landed itself.
Let's find out why.
Support this podcast: https://podcasters.spotify.com/pod/show/thewhyfiles/support
Transcript</description></item><item><title>73: Getting to the Bottom of Mel's Hole | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130075/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 21:16:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130075/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Mel Waters' property in the Manastash Ridge, west of Ellensburg, Washington, there is a hole in the ground that looks like a well -- but it's not a well.
Like the owners of the property before him, Mel used the hole as a trash dump. His neighbors used it too. Garbage, broken appliances, old tires, everything went in the hole.
After a while, Mel started to wonder: why doesn't it fill up?</description></item><item><title>72: The Dark Watchers: Silent Guardians of the Pines | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130076/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 23:55:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130076/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Dark Watchers: Silent Guardians of the Pines
The Santa Lucia mountain range runs from Monterey and down the coast of California.
For hundreds of years, stories have been told about entities that keep watch over the mountains. Sometimes seen out of the corner of the eye, always from a distance. Stare too long and they vanish.
If you're ever hiking the wilderness of Big Sur and feel like you're being watched?</description></item><item><title>71: A UFO, the Pentagon and a 3-year Mission to Save the World. The True Story of Valiant Thor | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130077/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 00:47:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130077/</guid><description>Podcast Description On March 16, 1957, at 8 o'clock in the morning, a 300 ft long spacecraft landed in a field in Alexandria Virginia.
Two local police officers arrived on the scene. The door of the craft slowly opened. The officers drew their guns, not sure what to expect.
To their surprise, out walked a normal-looking guy. He smiled at the stunned officers and actually waved hello.
Before the policemen could say a word, the stranger said, in clear English: "</description></item><item><title>THREE STORIES: The Most Mysterious Children in History | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130078/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 12:40:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130078/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 12th century England, two children were found lost in a forest. They spoke only gibberish, wore strange clothing and had bright green skin. When the children finally learned to speak English, they described where they were from. And that's why, after almost 1,000 years, people still talk about The Green Children of Woolpit. In 1828, a teenage boy was shuffling through a public square in Nuremburg. He seemed confused and disoriented.</description></item><item><title>69: An Empty World, A Time Traveler, Another Dimension | Liminal Spaces: The Reality In-between | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130079/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 12:50:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130079/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the past year or so, three internet mysteries popped up that really got my attention. They may seem very different, but trust me, they're connected. The first one is about a girl who found a door in the basement of her AirBnB. She opened it and inside was an abandoned shopping mall. The second story is about Javier aka Unico Sobreviviente, who woke up in a hospital in the year 2027, in an alternate universe.</description></item><item><title>68: The Moon is a Hollow Spaceship | Who built it and why? | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130080/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 12:24:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130080/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Moon is a Hollow Spaceship | Who Built it and Why? Despite it being humanity's constant companion through all of recorded time, the moon is still a mystery. Science hasn't been able to explain how the moon was formed, its unusual orbit, its distance from us, its density, its composition, its structure. These are all still questions. There are theories about the moon that solve some of these puzzles, but not others.</description></item><item><title>67: The Vatican's Secret Time Machine | The Story of the Chronovisor | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130081/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 16:40:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vatican City is an inspirational place. You don't need to be Catholic or even religious to appreciate the architecture, art, and the city's historical significance.
But there is a place within the Vatican that's rarely seen. Hidden beneath the city is an underground fortress. Inaccessible to the public and protected by armed guards and state-of-the-art security. The Secret Apostolic Archives.
Within the stone and steel reinforced walls are vaults, climate controlled rooms and over 50 miles of shelves.</description></item><item><title>66: The Black Knight Satellite - Watching us from orbit for 13,000 years | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130082/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 16:15:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130082/</guid><description>Podcast Description THE BLACK KNIGHT SATELLITE
In 1957, the Soviet Union launched Sputnik 1. It was the first satellite in Earth's orbit. Or was it?
For over a hundred years, an object has been seen, heard and *photographed* by people all around the world. This object became known as the Black Knight Satellite.
The signals coming from the Black Knight Satellite have been decoded.
And if the translation is correct, it's been watching us for 13,000 years.</description></item><item><title>65: Interdimensional Traveler from a Parallel Universe: The Man from Taured | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130083/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 12:35:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Imagine you wake up one morning and notice everything around you is just a tiny bit different. Maybe you're in the same house, but furniture is slightly out of place. Your favorite coffee mug is there, but it has a crack you don't remember. You could have sworn your coffee maker was black, but this one is chrome. Just as you think you're going crazy, you feel a strange tingling sensation; and hear a buzzing in your ears.</description></item><item><title>64: Operation Highjump: Hunting the Secret Nazi UFO Base In Antarctica | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130084/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 12:53:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130084/</guid><description>Podcast Description OPERATION: HIGHJUMP Operation Highjump commenced in August 1946. It was the largest, most heavily armed naval task force ever sent to Antarctica. Leading the mission was Admiral Richard E Byrd, one of the most famous naval officers in history. The official purpose for the expedition was scientific research and military training. But that was just a cover story. Operation Highjump had other goals. One was to extend American sovereignty over Antarctica.</description></item><item><title>63: The Circleville Letters Mystery | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130085/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 19:46:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130085/</guid><description>Podcast Description MYSTERY OF THE CIRCLEVILLE LETTERS
We all keep secrets.
For most of us, these are nothing more than minor embarrassing details about ourselves. But some of us have dark secrets which, if discovered, could destroy lives.
For years, the residents of Circleville, Ohio, received bizarre, threatening letters; from someone who somehow knew every salacious detail of their personal lives.
The letters cost people their jobs, their marriages, their freedom, and sometimes, their lives.</description></item><item><title>62: Sounds from the Hell | The Siberian Drilling Project that went Very Wrong | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130086/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:48:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130086/</guid><description>Podcast Description SOUNDS FROM THE HOLE TO HELL In 1989, Dr. Dimitry Azacov and a group of scientists were working on a borehole drilling project in Siberia. When the drill reached 14.4 kilometers, or 9 miles deep, the drill bit started rotating wildly. It had somehow broken through solid rock and into a hollow area under the earth's crust. This cavity wasn't supposed to be there. When the drill returned to the surface, it was literally glowing red hot.</description></item><item><title>61: Evidence that Reality is a Simulation | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130087/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:48:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130087/</guid><description>Podcast Description PROOF THAT EVERYTHING - INCLUDING GOD - IS A SIMULATION Is this reality? Well, we're experiencing ... something right now so maybe the better question is: *what* is reality? Could everything we see, everything we experience, everything that exists in our entire universe -- be artificial? Supporters of Simulation Theory believe that not only is it *possible* that we're living in a simulation; it's likely. And the more we look for evidence, the more we find.</description></item><item><title>60: How a UFO Caused the Battle of Los Angeles | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130088/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:47:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130088/</guid><description>Podcast Description THE BATTLE OF LOS ANGELES On February 25, 1942, at about 2:30 in the morning, the people of Los Angeles were jolted awake by the sound of air-raid sirens. The city was ordered to blackout and prepare for an attack. Searchlights sprang to life, frantically scanning the sky above the city for enemy aircraft. Finally, the lights converged on a single object. As frightened citizens stepped on to their porches and lawns to get a glimpse of the target, the sky erupted with hundreds of explosions of fire, smoke and steel.</description></item><item><title>58: THE LEGEND of the Immortal: The Count of Saint Germain | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130089/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:46:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130089/</guid><description>Podcast Description CHASING THE IMMORTAL COUNT The Count of Saint Germain has been called a prophet, a sorcerer, and an immortal. He's been spotted all over the world for a thousand years. And every time he's seen, he looks exactly the same age. The Count of Saint Germain advised Kings, Queens and Emperors. He was present at every significant event in European history. And even was an important contributor to America's struggle for Independence.</description></item><item><title>59: Why Ancient People Didn't See the Color Blue | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130090/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:45:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here's a philosophical question for you. If a color doesn't have a name, can we still see it? Many years ago, the human eye evolved to give us the ability to see about a million colors. That's a lot. Then how come, until very recently, nobody saw or even heard of the color blue? Well, it's because blue just -- didn't exist yet. Let's find out why.
Support this podcast: https://podcasters.</description></item><item><title>58: The Most Paranormal Place On Earth - What's Happening on Mount Shasta? | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130091/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:45:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130091/</guid><description>Podcast Description MYSTERIES OF MOUNT SHASTA There is no other place on earth steeped in more mystery than Mount Shasta. Aliens, ghosts, underground bases and interdimensional portals. Check. Lost cities, strange disappearances, bigfoot, gods and demons. Check. Atlantis, Lemuria, reptilian humanoids and giants. Mount Shasta has it all. Let's find out why.
Support this podcast: https://podcasters.spotify.com/pod/show/thewhyfiles/support
Transcript</description></item><item><title>50: Why Superstitions Are Good For You | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130092/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:44:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130092/</guid><description>Podcast Description What do Ponce De Leon, Alexander The Great and Jason Giambi all have in common? Superstitions. What are superstitions? Why do we believe them? Although there are a lot of weird superstitions out there, there may be psychological benefits to believing them. Let's find out why.
Support this podcast: https://podcasters.spotify.com/pod/show/thewhyfiles/support
Transcript</description></item><item><title>55: Another Carrington Event? You Are NOT Prepared for the Coming Solar Storms | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130093/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:43:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130093/</guid><description>Podcast Description WE'RE DUE FOR ANOTHER CARRINGTON EVENT On September 1, 1859, astronomer Richard Carrington was observing a huge sunspot. Suddenly, a flash of intense white light burst from the sun's surface. He had become the first eye-witness of a major Coronal Mass Ejection or CME. And it was headed straight for earth. Seventeen hours later, the night sky in North America lit up like the day. Aurora Borealis, typically only seen near the north pole, were visible as far south as Colombia.</description></item><item><title>49: Alien Bases On The Moon | The Amazing True Story of Ingo Swann | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130094/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:41:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130094/</guid><description>Podcast Description THE MAN WHO SAW ALIEN BASES ON THE MOON Ingo Swann claimed to be a psychic who was employed by the CIA to remote-view the dark side of the moon. Specifically to look for an alien presence. It sounded like science fiction. But in 2006, when the CIA started releasing documents on the Stargate Project, Swann's participation in the program was confirmed. When Swann was asked about the existence of extraterrestrials, he said not only were they already here, but they *are* building something on the far side of the moon.</description></item><item><title>45: It's All FAKE | The Dead Internet Theory | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130095/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:41:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130095/</guid><description>Podcast Description What if all of our online existence is fake? You, me, everyone; we're living in a real-life Matrix. Designed to distract us from the truth: that we're just drones in a digital ant-hill. We live, work and die so that the wealthy and powerful can grow more wealthy and powerful. This is called the Dead Internet Theory. And there's compelling evidence that it's real. Let's find out why.</description></item><item><title>47: Legend of the Moon Eyed People | Before Christopher Columbus? | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130096/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:40:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130096/</guid><description>Podcast Description LEGEND OF THE MOON-EYED PEOPLE Across the Southern Appalachian mountains, from Georgia up through North Carolina, hundreds of unusual stone structures have been discovered. Some date back hundreds of years. Some date back thousands. Archaeologists aren't sure who created these monuments. But the Cherokee people claim they know exactly who built them. The Cherokee say the structures were built by the Moon-Eyed people, a race of fair-skinned, light-haired, bearded humans.</description></item><item><title>42: MIT Computer Predicts the World Will End in 2040 - First Signs Appear in 2020 | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130097/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:39:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130097/</guid><description>Podcast Description COMPUTER PREDICTS WORLD WILL END IN 2040 In 1704, using a series of calculations, Isaac Newton predicted the world would end sometime around the year 2060. Almost 300 years later, in 1973, a computer at MIT made the prediction that life as we know it will end around the year 2040. It also predicted that some of the first signs would be seen in the year 2020. Some of its predictions have come true and scientists are taking this seriously.</description></item><item><title>46: Messages Through Time - A Time Travel Story | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130098/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:38:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130098/</guid><description>Podcast Description THE COMPUTER THAT PROVED TIME TRAVEL | THE DODLESTON MESSAGES In December 1984, Ken Webster, a high-school teacher, was living with his friend Nic and girlfriend Debbie in the small village of Dodleston.
One evening, the three were walking home from the local pub when they saw a pulsing green light emanating from their cottage windows. When they got inside, they saw something that terrified them. Though their computer wasn't connected to any network, and everyone in the house was gone all night, a strange message was written on the screen.</description></item><item><title>43: Civilization Before Humans? Silurian Hypothesis | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130099/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:34:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130099/</guid><description>Podcast Description There are over 7 billion people living on the earth right now. Tens of millions are born and die each year. Every single one of us leaves signs of our existence in the air, water, soil -- even space. But these signs won't last forever. Our buildings will be gone in a few hundred years. Our stone monuments, plastic, styrofoam, twinkies, even evidence of our inevitable nuclear destruction will eventually be gone.</description></item><item><title>41: Paul Amadeus Dienach spent a year in 3906. He wrote down everything he saw. | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130100/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:33:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130100/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1924, Paul Amadeus Dienach had been teaching the German language in Greece. Dying of tuberculosis, he wanted to return home to Switzerland. Before he left, he gave hundreds of pages of handwritten notes to his favorite language student Georgios Papachatzis. Dienach thought translating his notes would help Papachatzis in his study of the German language. They said goodbye and never saw each other again. Papahatzis began translating the pages.</description></item><item><title>40: Atlantis World War Pole Shift - The Terrifying Predictions of Edgar Cayce | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130101/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:33:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130101/</guid><description>Podcast Description ATLANTIS, WORLD WARS AND THE POLE SHIFT Terrifying predictions of Edgar Cayce Edgar Cayce gave over 14,000 psychic readings. He made a number of predictions about future events — many of which have come true. And some of them are terrifying. Some people are worried. Let's find out why.
Support this podcast: https://podcasters.spotify.com/pod/show/thewhyfiles/support
Transcript</description></item><item><title>39: Bigfoot Aliens KGB? Dyatlov Pass explained -- and solved | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130102/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:32:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130102/</guid><description>Podcast Description KGB, BIGFOOT or ALIENS? WHAT REALLY HAPPENED AT DYATLOV PASS? When the helicopter rescue team arrived at the Dyatlov Pass in February 1959, the nine missing hikers had been dead for weeks. The more the investigators tried to piece together what happened, the more the story didn't seem to add up. Their tent had been cut open from the inside and abandoned, but there was no sign of a struggle.</description></item><item><title>36: Project: STARGATE. The CIA, Mars and... Time Travel. | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130103/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:31:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130103/</guid><description>Podcast Description PROJECT STARGATE: CIA, PSYCHICS, MARS AND ... TIME TRAVEL When the first human visits Mars, it will be the biggest scientific breakthrough since landing on the Moon. Probably bigger. But what if I told you the CIA and United States Military have already been to Mars? But they didn't use space-ships to get there. They used psychics. Let's find out why.
Support this podcast: https://podcasters.spotify.com/pod/show/thewhyfiles/support
Transcript</description></item><item><title>35: The Thing Embassy Incident: How Russian children and the KGB trolled America for years | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130104/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:30:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130104/</guid><description>Podcast Description FOR SEVEN YEARS, SOVIET AGENTS SPIED ON THE AMERICAN EMBASSY UNDETECTED In 1945, Soviet children presented the ambassador with a gift to commemorate the friendship of the US and the Soviet Union. A hand-carved wooden replica of the Great Seal of the United States. The ambassador was so pleased with the carving that he hung it in his office at the official ambassador residence in Moscow: the Spaso house.</description></item><item><title>Sonic Weapons, Havana Syndrome and The Fear Frequency | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130105/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:30:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do some horror movies use sounds of a *specific frequency* to amp up the scare factor? Yes. Can infrasound and ultrasound damage the human body? Yes. Has sound been used as a real-world weapon? Yes. Is sound being deployed by America's enemies to cause serious physical harm? Yes. Let's find out why.
Support this podcast: https://podcasters.spotify.com/pod/show/thewhyfiles/support
Transcript</description></item><item><title>33: When will we upload our consciousness to the cloud? | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130106/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:29:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130106/</guid><description>Podcast Description When will we upload our consciousness to the cloud? As long as people have been alive, they've wanted to stay alive. For centuries, explorers have searched for the fountain of youth. And today, scientists are hard at work researching technology that can extend the human lifespan, stop or reverse aging; and even preserve a terminally ill person indefinitely, until a cure for their disease is discovered. But what if -- instead of preserving our *bodies* -- we could preserve our *consciousness*; by uploading it to a powerful computer.</description></item><item><title>34: How Long Can Humans Live Without Their Head? | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130107/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:29:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130107/</guid><description>Podcast Description HOW LONG DO ANIMALS (and people) SURVIVE WITHOUT THEIR HEADS? Does a human head remain conscious after being separated from its body? It sure does. But just how long do you actually survive? Not that long. But, if we look at other animals, some of them can survive for longer than you think. Let's find out why.
Support this podcast: https://podcasters.spotify.com/pod/show/thewhyfiles/support
Transcript</description></item><item><title>31: The Latitude Society - Game, Business, or Cult? (Yes.) | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130108/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:21:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130108/</guid><description>Podcast Description THE LATITUDE. How do you join a cult without knowing it? Here's how it happened to thousands of people in San Francisco just a few years ago. You're with a trusted friend; maybe on a hike, or sitting in a bar or just hanging out. Out of nowhere, your friend asks you: "Can you keep a secret?" Of course you reply that you can. Your friend hands you a small black sleeve, about the size of a credit card.</description></item><item><title>30: The Phantom Time Hypothesis -- The Middle Ages Never Happened | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130109/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:20:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130109/</guid><description>Podcast Description According to a German historian, the year is actually 1724. He says our calendar is a lie and a big chunk of the Middle Ages never happened. Which says that back in 1000 AD, there was a conspiracy between the church and the Holy Roman emperor to change the calendar. The years 614 through 911 were completely made up. Those 300 years just didn't happen. So all that history you learned about Charlemagne and the middle ages.</description></item><item><title>29: Tesla's technology to talk to spirits of the dead | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130110/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:19:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130110/</guid><description>Podcast Description GHOST PHONE vs SPIRIT RADIO. Edison versus Tesla. One of history's greatest rivalries. They would never admit it but as different as these men were, they also had many similarities. For instance, they also both dabbled in paranormal technology. Nikola Tesla was convinced he could invent a device to communicate with the spirit world. And Thomas Edison was convinced he could get there first. Let's find out why.</description></item><item><title>28: NY's Windowless Skyscraper actually a NSA Spy Hub called TITANPOINTE | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130111/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:19:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130111/</guid><description>Podcast Description TITANPOINTE. New York City has skyscrapers of all shapes and sizes. But why does this 500 foot tall, 29-story building have no windows, no lights and no markings at all? Because it's a top-secret NSA spy station built to withstand nuclear war. Officially, this is an AT&amp;amp;T telecommunications building. But thanks to leaked documents, we now know that 33 Thomas Street is actually a top secret NSA mass surveillance hub.</description></item><item><title>27: Area 51 Airline? | JANET: The Secret Government Airline That Doesn't Exist | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130112/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:18:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130112/</guid><description>Podcast Description JANET AIRLINES. Heard of Janet Airlines? No? Good. That's exactly what the US government wants. One of the government's biggest secrets is hiding in plain sight. In Las Vegas. Janet is the top-secret government airline that doesn't exist. Next time you're in Vegas, visit one of the big casinos next to McCarran Airport. I'm talking about Luxor, Excalibur, Mandalay Bay. When you get there, look East at the airport.</description></item><item><title>26: Polybius: The Addictive Mind Control Game That's More Truth than Legend | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130113/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:17:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Was Polybius real? In 1981, an arcade in Portland was the scene of countless gamers coming down with migraines, having heart attacks, seizures and strokes. Local teens were suffering from amnesia and having hallucinations. All due to a mysterious game that seemed to arrive out of thin air. The game was called Polybius. And even though playing the game was dangerous, it was highly addictive and caused some teens to become hyper-aggressive.</description></item><item><title>25: Comparing Earth technology with alien civilizations | The Kardashev Scale | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130114/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:16:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130114/</guid><description>Podcast Description THE KARDASHEV SCALE. We have no idea what an alien civilization would look like. Humans are evolved primates. What if an alien species is reptilian? Or more like an insect? Or a hybrid of these? Or maybe something completely unique that we couldn't even imagine. There is only one set of universal laws that every species must follow. Physics. Specifically energy. One way to measure a civilization is by its energy consumption.</description></item><item><title>24: The Dog Suicide Bridge | Why Have Hundreds of Dogs Jumped? | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130115/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:15:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130115/</guid><description>Podcast Description THE DOG SUICIDE BRIDGE. In Dumbarton, Scotland, there's a 19th-century gothic bridge that crosses a 50-foot ravine. It's *officially* called Overtoun Bridge. But it's *unofficial* name is the "dog suicide bridge." Built in 1895, the ornate bridge leads up to Overtoun House, a 19th century manor built by wealthy industrialist James White on the outskirts of the village of Milton in the Scottish Lowlands. It spans Overtoun Burn, a deep gorge with a small river.</description></item><item><title>23: The Max Headroom Incident. UNSOLVED: The Creepiest TV Hack in History | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130116/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:14:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130116/</guid><description>Podcast Description THE MAX HEADROOM INCIDENT. November 22nd, 1987 was a pretty normal evening for television viewers in Chicago. That night, like every night, Dan Roan was covering sports on WGN-TV, Channel 9. Then suddenly, the signal was disrupted and screens across the city cut to black. Engineers at WGN-TV thought their transmitters were failing. They weren't. A few seconds later, something crazy happened. WGN's broadcast signal had been hijacked in what is now known as "</description></item><item><title>21: Ancient Acoustic Levitation | How The Pyramids Were Built? | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130117/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130117/</guid><description>Podcast Description LEVITATION. The ruins of several ancient civilizations - like the pyramids of Giza, Stonehenge in the UK, and many others - are monuments constructed of massive stones. How the great pyramids of Egypt were built has been the subject of debate for a long time. The fact is, no one really knows for certain exactly how some of these megaliths were constructed. Some researchers think ancient cultures may have mastered levitation through sound which allowed them to easily manipulate massive objects.</description></item><item><title>20: Earthquakes Asteroids Zombies: Predictions of Nostradamus | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130118/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:12:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130118/</guid><description>Podcast Description NOSTRADAMUS. 2022 Predictions: Earthquakes, Asteroids &amp;amp; Zombies? If you believe the predictions of Nostradamus and you enjoyed 2020, you're gonna *love* 2021. While many astrologers, seers and mystics are predicting a hopeful future. If you believe Nostradamus, you better start kissing your mommies and saying your goodbyes. He predicted that 2020 would be a "great trouble for humanity". Well, that was true. And he says a greater trouble is coming in the form of a global famine.</description></item><item><title>19: Stuxnet | The Computer Virus that prevented and started the next world war | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130119/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:12:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130119/</guid><description>Podcast Description STUXNET. The virus that prevented; then started the next world war. Cyberwar is being waged right now in your name. No matter what country you call home, your government is engaged in highly dangerous combat on the Internet. Infrastructure around the world is under siege and everyone is at risk. Even you. In 2010, the Stuxnet virus was discovered in Natanz, Iran and thousands of control systems that operate factories, power plants and nuclear reactors around the world.</description></item><item><title>18: Numbers Stations | Listen to Spy Broadcasts, Audio &amp; Coded Messages | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130120/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130120/</guid><description>Podcast Description NUMBERS STATIONS. Not a relic of the past. Intelligence agencies use shortwave to communicate with spies, agents and assets in the field. Right now. Today. Let's listen to a few and learn how to tune in from home -- for free. Since World War One, numbers stations have been transmitting coded messages to spies around the world using shortwave radio. And they're still transmitting right now. We're going to listen to a few in this episode.</description></item><item><title>17: 9 Time Travel Stories | Is Time Travel Possible? Evidence says yes, it is. | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130121/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:09:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is time travel possible? According to physicists, yes. Time travel *to the future* is not only possible, it's been scientifically proven. But what about traveling to the past? Well, that's a little trickier. BUT, there does seem to be evidence that travelers from the future have visited us in the past; and may be among us right now. The human race has been fascinated with traveling through time ever since, well, ever since the human race understood what time was.</description></item><item><title>16: Aztec Death Whistle | The Scariest Sound You've Ever Heard | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130122/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:07:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130122/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Aztec Death Whistle. If hell has a sound, I bet it sounds alot like the Aztec Death Whistle. The Aztec Death Whistle sounds like a shriek of death mixed with howling wind. It's so unnerving, that the significance of the horrifying sound of the Aztec Death Whistle has fascinated and perplexed scholars for years. I'm going to play the sound of the Aztec Death Whistle for you today.</description></item><item><title>15: The Philadelphia Experiment - The truth about invisibility, teleportation and time travel | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130123/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:05:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130123/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Philadelphia Experiment. It was October 1943. The day the US Navy mastered time travel, teleportation, and invisibility. Actually, they didn't master anything. The experiment had disastrous consequences for the crew of the USS Eldridge. In the summer of 1943, two years after the US entered World War II, American destroyers were being decimated by the infamous German U-boat submarines and German mines were making combat... and commerce dangerous enterprises.</description></item><item><title>13: The Nevada Triangle | 2,000 Planes Mysteriously Crashed &amp; Missing Near Area 51 👽 | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130124/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:05:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Most of us have heard of the Bermuda Triangle, where planes and ships have mysteriously gone missing in the Atlantic Ocean for decades. Did you know there is a similar place in Nevada? The Nevada Triangle. In a region of the Sierra Nevada Mountains in Nevada and California, 2,000 planes have been lost in the last 60 years. In this remotely populated area of more than 25,000 miles of mountain desert, many of the crash sites have never been found.</description></item><item><title>12: What does outer space smell like? (You're not gonna like it.) | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130125/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:04:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130125/</guid><description>Podcast Description What does the moon smell like? Do planets, comets, asteroids and space have their own odors? The smells of the universe are not universal. Different objects in space — comets, planets, moons and gas clouds — all have their own distinctive aroma. Twelve people have walked on the Moon and all of them agree: the Moon smells like gunpowder. According to Space.com, astronaut Jack Schmitt said: “All I can say is that everyone's instant impression of the smell was that of spent gunpowder, not that it was 'metallic' or 'acrid'.</description></item><item><title>11: The Voynich Manuscript Decoded - Have We Finally Solved the Most Mysterious Book in the World? | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130126/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:03:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130126/</guid><description>Podcast Description For 600 years the Voynich Manuscript has stumped scholars, cryptographers, physicists, and computer scientists. Now, a researcher in Germany has claimed to have finally decoded the most mysterious book in the world. The Voynich Manuscript is a 240-page medieval codex written in an indecipherable language, full of bizarre drawings of strange plants, astrological symbols and... lots of... naked women. The Voynich Manuscript defies classification and has also defied comprehension.</description></item><item><title>8: Chicxulub Asteroid Impact - The Day the Dinosaurs Died | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130127/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 14:02:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130127/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Chicxulub Asteroid Impact - The Day the Dinosaurs Died One of the deepest scars on our planet is hidden beneath the Yucatán Peninsula and the Gulf of Mexico. The buried crater, over 90 miles in diameter, was created when a massive asteroid struck the planet 66 million years ago and brought a calamitous end to the reign of dinosaurs. Though dinosaur extinction probably took weeks or months, in just one day, 425 feet of material accumulated where the asteroid hit with the power of 10 billion atomic bombs.</description></item><item><title>7: The Most Secret Places in the World | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130128/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 13:59:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130128/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Most Secret Places in the World - And the wild theories about what really happens inside. In the modern world, places are supposed to be accessible. People move freely around the country they live in and even between countries. However, the most interesting, fascinating and mysterious locations in the world, even today, are strictly off limits to just about everyone. Most of the places on this list are only accessible to those with the proper clearances, but some are not accessible to anyone at all.</description></item><item><title>The Why Files Trailer | The Why Files: Operation Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1243130129/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 18:11:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1243130129/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Why Files
Do you have natural curiosity, interest in scientific mysteries and a great sense of humor? You're in the right place! We cover brainy topics with comedy spin.
I'm AJ Gentile, the Head Nerd In Charge. You might know me from the Discovery Channel, SiriusXM, MTV and the Joe Rogan Experience.
The Why Files is a channel for people who are fascinated (obsessed) with science, science-fiction, bizarre history, weird facts, strange places, conspiracies and unusual people.</description></item></channel></rss>