<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/cautionary-tales-with-tim-harford/</link><description>Recent content in Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 05:01:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/cautionary-tales-with-tim-harford/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How the Radium Girls Fought Back | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700001/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cautionary Book Club: Mollie Maggia's dentist planned to remove a painful abscess from her mouth. But to his horror, her jawbone disintegrated at his touch, crumbling and splintering until it resembled ash. Like hundreds of her colleagues, Mollie had been slowly poisoned by her work with glowing radium dust. Eight months after her first toothache, she was dead.
In the previous episode, Cautionary Tales told the story of the "</description></item><item><title>Glowing Peril: The Magical Glitter That Poisoned a City | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700002/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700002/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Goiânia, Brazil, a junk dealer acquires an old medical device from two scrap-metal scavengers. The device itself isn't useful, but it comes with precious lead which will fetch him good money. There's something else inside the device, too: a curious, crystal-like substance that glows bright blue in the dark.
At first, the dealer is mesmerized by it: he wants to turn it into jewelry for his wife. But, everyone who comes into contact with the magical glitter seems to get sick.</description></item><item><title>George Washington's Beard of Beetles (with The Dollop) | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700003/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cautionary Conversation: Just before Christmas 1799, President George Washington was riding around his country estate, Mount Vernon, when it began to snow. When he arrived home, guests were waiting for him. Known for his punctuality, he hurried to entertain them - still clad in his damp clothes.
The next morning, Washington had a sore throat and a chesty cough. His family decided to take a fateful step: they summoned a doctor.</description></item><item><title>Laser Versus Parchment: Doomsday for the Disc | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700004/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700004/</guid><description>Podcast Description William the Conqueror undertook a remarkably modern project. In 1086, he began compiling and storing a detailed record of his realm: of where everyone lived, what they did and where they came from.
900 years later, the BBC began its own Domesday project, sending school children out to conduct a community survey and collect facts about Britain. This was a people’s database, two decades before Wikipedia. But just a few years later, that interactive digital database was totally unreadable, the information lost.</description></item><item><title>Cautionary Tales Presents The Dream | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 14:35:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700005/</guid><description>Podcast Description On The Dream, host Jane Marie gets to know the life coaches and gurus who claim they know the secret to living our best lives. Is it all in our mindset? Or our privilege? Or are we all under a spell?
Tim Harford is joined by Jane Marie to talk about who coaching works least well for. Turns out it’s the exact people who could benefit most from it, according to the industry.</description></item><item><title>Killers of the Flower Moon: Osage Chief Jim Gray In Conversation | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700006/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Henry Roan has been shot through the back of his head. The local authorities have found his body slumped over the steering wheel of his car. There's no gun at the scene: this is no suicide - it's brutal murder. And the man who ordered Henry Roan's killing? He claims to be his best friend...
Former Principal Chief of the Osage Nation Jim Roan Gray joins Tim Harford to speak about his great-grandfather Henry Roan.</description></item><item><title>Oil and Blood: The Osage Murders | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700007/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Minnie Smith grew sick quite suddenly. She had been young, fit and healthy - and the doctors were baffled when she died. "A peculiar wasting illness," they called it. Then, her sister Anna went missing. Her rotting corpse was found a week later, a bullet hole through her skull. When a third sister, Rita, was blown up in her own bed, a grim pattern was clear: the family was being targeted.</description></item><item><title>DOUBLE BILL: A Monkey For Mayor / A Screw Loose At 17,000 Feet | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700008/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700008/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, we've twice the storytelling fun for you: two Cautionary Tales shorts, previously only available to Pushkin+ subscribers.
A Monkey for Mayor: It was supposed to be a publicity stunt, but when the man who dressed as Hartlepool United’s monkey mascot stood in a mayoral election... he won. Actual politicians predicted disaster - since thousands of workers and millions of dollars were now in the hands of a complete novice.</description></item><item><title>"7000 horses are being flown across space..." - Cautionary Questions #2 | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700009/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why are board games so popular in Germany? What’s Tim Harford’s top tip for productivity? And where do all those sound effects come from? Tim is joined by Cautionary Tales’ very own wizard of sound Pascal Wyse, to read your emails and answer your questions.
Do you have a question for Tim? Please email any queries you might have, however big or small, to tales@pushkin.fm.
Please note that some emails in this episode have been edited for length.</description></item><item><title>Cautionary Tales Presents: Getting out of Dodge from Revisionist History | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700010/</guid><description>Podcast Description The longest running television series of the 20th century was Gunsmoke, a western set in the notorious Dodge City, Kansas. Malcolm sweeps away mountains of legal scholarship to make a bold claim: The simplest explanation for the Supreme’s Court’s puzzling run of gun rights decisions may be that the justices watched too much Gunsmoke when they were growing up. Enjoy this episode from Revisionist History, another Pushkin Industries podcast.</description></item><item><title>A Chorus of Contempt at The Sydney Opera House | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700011/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700011/</guid><description>Podcast Description 1957. Jørn Utzon receives a phone call: he's just won an international competition to design a brand new opera house for the Australian city of Sydney. Utzon is unknown in the field, so this is a triumph. The young architect couldn’t have imagined what a bitter victory it would turn out to be...
The Guggenheim in Bilbao; the Burj Khalifa in Dubai; the Shard in London. These days, everyone seems to want an iconic building.</description></item><item><title>The City That Sold Itself To Wall Street | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700012/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cautionary Book Club: When Morgan Stanley offered to lease Chicago's parking meters for the princely sum of $1 billion, the City Council were convinced that they had struck gold. They hastily signed the deal. But they soon learnt that they hadn't just traded away parking revenue - they had traded away the streets themselves...
In this hybrid episode of Cautionary Tales, Tim Harford first tells the story of the Chicago parking metres fiasco of 2008.</description></item><item><title>General Ludd's Rage Against the Machines | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700013/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700013/</guid><description>Podcast Description 1812. A band of "Luddites" is laying siege to a textile mill in the North of England, under cover of night. They plan to destroy the machines that are replacing their jobs. But mill owner William Cartwright is prepared: he's fortified his factory with skilled marksmen, fearsome eighteen-inch metal spikes and barrels of sulphuric acid.
Today "Luddite" is a term of mockery — a description for someone who's scared of technology.</description></item><item><title>Andy Warhol's Factory of Truth | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700014/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cautionary Conversation: Andy Warhol’s assistant, Gerard Malanga, is facing a long prison sentence in Italy. He’s forged several Che Guevara portraits and tried to pass them off as genuine Warhols. What happens next is a landmark event in the history of art and authenticity…
Tim Harford is joined by Alice Sherwood, author of Authenticity, to discuss truth and fakery in modern times. Today, authenticity seems to matter more than ever — and yet we’re also constantly assailed by people and products that are not what they seem.</description></item><item><title>Poles Apart: How A Journalist Divided A City | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Heroic explorer Frederick Cook has just returned from the very roof of the world, the first man to reach the North Pole. Or so he says. Journalist Philip Gibbs has been watching him, and he’s convinced he’s lying.
When Gibbs publishes that belief, he stands alone. Cook has a gripping manner and an excellent reputation: his winning tale must be true. Diners boo Gibbs at a restaurant, newspapers publish sly-looking caricatures of him, and he even receives threats of violence.</description></item><item><title>The Father of Space Travel | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cautionary Conversation: Did a Nazi put America on the moon? To celebrate the launch of his mini-series on the V-2 rocket, Tim Harford sits down with Pushkin’s resident V-2 expert, Ryan Dilley. They discuss the so-called “Father of Space Travel”, Wernher von Braun, and satirist Tom Lehrer’s musical lampooning of him.
A three-part mini series on the V-2 rocket is available now for Pushkin+ subscribers. We’ll be back again on August 4th with a brand new episode of Cautionary Tales on the main feed.</description></item><item><title>A Fascination with Failure: Death On The Dancefloor (Classic) | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700017/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Henry Petroski is one of Tim Harford's favourite fellow nerds. His study of engineering failures has profoundly influenced Tim's own writing, including the classic Cautionary Tales episode Death on the Dance Floor.
Petroski passed away in June 2023, at the age of 81. This week, in honour of the late great engineer, Tim looks back at the catastrophic Kansas City Hyatt Regency disaster of 1981. The hotel's space-age sky walks -- 60 tonnes of glass, concrete and steel -- crashed down onto the heads of revellers in the atrium below.</description></item><item><title>When Parakeets Plundered New York | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700018/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cautionary Conversation: An invasive parakeet species began spreading in New York City - and the government decided to kill every last bird. Tim Harford is joined by Ben Naddaff-Hafrey, host of The Last Archive, to talk about the great parakeet panic of the 1970s and a history of anxieties about population growth.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Coup, the Poet and the Secret to Winning Wimbledon | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700019/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700019/</guid><description>Podcast Description “If you can make one heap of all your winnings and risk it on one turn of pitch-and-toss..."
Those words - from Rudyard Kipling's poem "If" - were based on charismatic nineteenth century doctor, Leander Starr Jameson. In Britain, Jameson was worshipped as a plucky hero: a bastion of courage and mental fortitude. Ironically, he was also responsible for the Jameson Raid, a South African coup that was an unmitigated disaster.</description></item><item><title>The Man Who Played With Hurricanes | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700020/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 08:54:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, the idea of controlling the weather is controversial. Scientists who research geoengineering have even received death threats. But once upon a time, people were optimistic about remaking the climate in entire regions of the world. They approached this science with a touching faith in the power of human creativity.
Absent-minded genius Irving Langmuir was one such scientist. He dreamt of making deserts bloom and conjuring rain from an arid sky.</description></item><item><title>Cautionary Tales Presents: Lost Hills - The Dark Prince | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we're sharing an episode of the gripping Pushkin series Lost Hills: The Dark Prince. The brand-new season takes a deep dive into the surf world to explore the legacy of Malibu's Dark Prince: Miki Dora. A surfer known for his style, grace and aggression, he ruled Malibu from the 1950s to the 1970s. Celebrated for his rebellious spirit, he was also a conman who led the FBI on a 7-year manhunt around the world.</description></item><item><title>Sonic Poison? The Genesis of Havana Syndrome | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700022/</guid><description>Podcast Description CIA agents in Havana complaining of mental fog, dizziness and ear pain in 2016. Children in Miami in 1974, hyperventilating and wracked with abdominal pain. A medieval outbreak of the “dancing plague”. A chorus of meowing nuns.
These mysterious and seemingly disparate events may have a simple explanation — and one that’s often overlooked when it comes to understanding strange new syndromes.
For a full list of sources used in this episode visit Tim Harford.</description></item><item><title>Airships, AI and Alan Cumming: Tim Answers Your Questions | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why does economics get a bad rap? How did a small Hungarian airline wreak havoc in the 2000s?
What cautionary tales can we glean from Tim’s own life? And what’s his favourite role-playing game?
You sent in your questions and now - with the help of podcasting maestro Jacob Goldstein (What’s Your Problem?) - Tim is answering them.
Do you have a question for Tim? Please email any queries you might have, however big or small, to tales@pushkin.</description></item><item><title>The Man Who Bet His House on a Pop Song - A Eurovision Tale | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700024/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700024/</guid><description>Podcast Description You can gamble on horses or on the turn of a card - but Daniel Gould made a living betting on the outcome of the annual Eurovision Song Contest. Daniel made a profit because he studied the voting history of the competition, as well as the cultural and geo-political factors that predict which songs will triumph and which will score "nil point". In 2018, Daniel was so sure of his system of reducing the risk that he took out a loan on his home and bet it on Israel's song to win.</description></item><item><title>The Dark Money Behind Mother's Day | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700025/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anna Marie Jarvis wanted a national holiday to honor the dedication and sacrifice of America's mothers. She wasn't the first person to propose a Mother's Day - but her campaign caught the imagination of the people and the ears of the politicians.
Congress officially recognised Jarvis's Mother's Day in 1914 - but the indefatigable campaigner had allied herself with businessmen with vested interests in such an annual event. Mother's Day soon span out of its creator's control and caused an embittered Jarvis no end of heartache.</description></item><item><title>The True Scandal of Lydia E. Pinkham’s Vegetable Compound | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700026/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700026/</guid><description>Podcast Description It could cure any 'female ailment' - even cancer - said the adverts. But Lydia E. Pinkham’s Vegetable Compound was, in fact, just a concoction of herbs and alcohol of no proven medicinal merit. That didn't stop desperate American women from buying bottles of the stuff - and writing to Lydia Pinkham for medical advice. Why did her customers shun 'expert' doctors and opt instead for quack medicines? And why, when Lydia Pinkham finally came in for criticism, did no one question the efficacy of her vegetable compound?</description></item><item><title>What if Terrorists Could Weaponize Covid? | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700027/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cautionary Conversation: In 1990, a small extremist group launched a nerve gas attack on passengers riding the Tokyo subway. Thousands of people were hurt, more than a dozen died. At the time, such use of a chemical weapon seemed new and uniquely terrifying.
But advances in biology mean that today it's possible such a group could create a virus like Covid... with the potential to kill millions. What are the dangers and what can we do to combat them?</description></item><item><title>The Vigilante and the Air Traffic Controller | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700028/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Air traffic controllers are meant to stop aircrafts from flying into one another... and if they fail, computer systems are installed to warn pilots of a coming collision. But sometimes these humans and computers give conflicting and confusing advice. Who to believe?
When a cargo plane and a Russian airliner collided in just such a situation, the authorities scrambled to work out how to prevent a repeat of the disaster.</description></item><item><title>America's Mata Hari? The Double Life of Esther Reed | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700029/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cautionary Conversation: When a small-town detective gets a tip about a missing woman, he believes he's uncovered a highly-trained chameleon: a foreign spy. Soon, Esther Reed is on the Secret Service's Most Wanted list, and a nationwide manhunt has commenced. But all is not as it seems.
Jake Halpern joins Tim Harford to talk about the latest season of his Pushkin podcast Deep Cover: Never Seen Again. They discuss the dangers of incrementally increasing lies; how and why certain stories are escalated up the media "</description></item><item><title>Office Hell: the Demise of the Playful Workspace | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700030/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700030/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the early 90s, cutting-edge advertising agency Chiat/Day announced a radical plan, aimed at giving the company a jolt of creative renewal. They would sweep away corner offices and cubicles and replace them with zany open spaces, as well as innovative portable computers and phones. A brand new era of “hot-desking” had arrived.
Problems quickly began. Disgruntled employees found themselves hauling temperamental, clunky laptops and armfuls of paperwork all over the office; some even had to use the trunks of their cars as filing cabinets.</description></item><item><title>La La Land: Galileo’s Warning (Classic) | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700031/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700031/</guid><description>Podcast Description With the 95th Academy Awards just around the corner, Tim Harford looks back at a basic lesson. Galileo tried to teach us that adding more and more layers to a system intended to avert disaster often makes catastrophe all the more likely. This principle has been ignored in nuclear power plants, financial markets and at the Oscars... all resulting in chaos.
For a full list of sources for this episode, go to timharford.</description></item><item><title>The Scientist and the Swindler | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700032/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cautionary Conversation: Celebrated physicist Professor Paul Frampton was on his way to Brussels to meet the love of his life, swimwear model Denise Milani. Or so he thought. When he found himself in jail, he realized he’d fallen prey to a confidence trickster.
Tim Harford is joined by Maria Konnikova - journalist, psychologist and best-selling author - to talk about swindlers: what motivates them; what they look for in their victims; and how to avoid being conned altogether.</description></item><item><title>The Hero Who Rode His Segway Off a Cliff | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700033/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Steve Jobs called It “the most amazing piece of technology since the PC.” According to Jeff Bezos It was not only “revolutionary,” but infinitely commercial. It was a fiendishly clever and massively hyped invention. But in the end It — also known as the Segway — was a failure.
What makes an invention useful and valuable? Jimi Heselden’s pragmatic brainchild the Concertainer might hold the answers. First used to shore up the collapsing walls of a canal, it ultimately solved problems that Jimi had never even imagined.</description></item><item><title>The Mummy's Curse (Classic) | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700034/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700034/</guid><description>Podcast Description A hundred years ago, the Tomb of the Pharaoh Tutankhamun was officially opened - despite the widely held belief that disturbing the remains of the Egyptian pharaohs could incur a deadly curse. Why did a team of archeologists risk inciting the wrath of King Tutankhamun by entering his burial chamber? And how many of them met a premature end for their impudence?
For a full list of sources for this episode, go to timharford.</description></item><item><title>The Final Illusion of the Great Lafayette | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700035/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Golden sparks are raining down on the Great Lafayette’s famous vaudeville show, “The Lion’s Bride”. They look like they’re part of the performance. They aren’t — and soon the theater is ablaze. The manager has to figure out how to save the 3000 audience members, now trapped in a burning building.
Thirty-five years earlier, the Brooklyn Theatre had gone up in flames too. The terrified spectators became a frantic, trampling mass, and hundreds perished in the flames and smoke.</description></item><item><title>LIVE: The Myth of the Million Dollar Tulip Bulb | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700036/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Recorded before an audience at the Bristol Festival of Economics (11/17/2022)
The Dutch went so potty over tulip bulbs in the 1600s that many were ruined when the inflated prices they were paying for the plants collapsed - that's the oft-repeated story later promoted by best-selling Scottish writer Charles Mackay. It's actually a gross exaggeration. Mackay's writings about economic bubbles bursting entertained and informed his Victorian readers - and continue to influence us today - but how did Mackey fare when faced with a stock market mania right before his eyes?</description></item><item><title>DOUBLE BILL: When a Plague Struck World of Warcraft/Blood on the Tracks | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700037/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700037/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a special New Year treat we're presenting two Cautionary Tales Shorts - which have previously only been available to paying Apple and Pushkin+ subscribers. When a Plague Struck World of Warcraft: The makers of WoW wanted to spice up the fantasy computer game by introducing a virtual disease - "Corrupted Blood". It was supposed to be a fun challenge for expert player - but the illness became a pandemic which wiped out villages, cities and then whole realms.</description></item><item><title>"Snow Crashing Into The Metaverse" from Imaginary Worlds | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700038/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700038/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, we’re sharing an episode of Imaginary Worlds. For the last 30 years, the real world has been catching up to Neal Stephenson’s vision of the future in his 1992 novel Snow Crash, which influenced the creators of Google Earth, Second Life, Oculus Rift and more. Now the centerpiece of the novel, a virtual world called The Metaverse, may become a daily part of our lives thanks to Facebook (renamed Meta) and other big tech companies.</description></item><item><title>The Company That Cancelled Christmas | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700039/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700039/</guid><description>Podcast Description More than 100,000 families - many of them amongst the poorest in Britain - put money aside for Christmas gifts and other seasonal treats in a savings club called Farepak. It wasn't a bank, and it wasn't great value for money... and it went bust. Kids went without toys, and festive dinner tables were left bare. Why would someone put their hard-earned money into such a scheme? And what does it tell us about how we often view Christmas as a time for frenzied spending?</description></item><item><title>The Wild Turkeys of Schleswig | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700040/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700040/</guid><description>Podcast Description There are eight American turkeys painted on the walls of Schleswig's Cathedral of St Peter - which is odd... since the frescoes were created two centuries before Columbus even crossed the Atlantic. How did the creatures come to be added to the medieval Biblical scene? Was this proof that the Germans reached the Americas before Columbus? Or do the painted birds tell a different story all together? For a full list of sources used in this episode visit Tim Harford.</description></item><item><title>Cautionary Conversation: The Blitz Spirit and the Blackout Ripper | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700041/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700041/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a crisis most people respond with decency and solidarity. The bombing of British cities in the Second World War did not cause society to crumble as was expected, but proved instead human resilience. That defiant "Blitz Spirit" is still a source of pride for Britons... but have inconvenient facts about that time been ignored?
Alice Fiennes (co-host of the podcast Bad Women: The Blackout Ripper) explains that the chaos and disruption of the bombing allowed some people to commit awful crimes - and especially a trainee RAF pilot who embarked on a vicious killing spree under cover of darkness.</description></item><item><title>The Inventor Who Almost Ended the World | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700042/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Thomas Midgley's inventions caused his own death, hastened the deaths of millions of people around the world, and very nearly extinguished all life on land. Midgley and his employers didn't set out to poison the air with leaded gasoline or wreck the ozone layer with CFCs - but while these dire consequences were unintended... could they have been anticipated?
For a full list of sources used in this episode visit Tim Harford.</description></item><item><title>The Halloween Poisoner | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700043/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Candy laced with cyanide and needles in marshmallows, we've long been warned to be suspicious of the sweet treats handed out by strangers at Halloween. But it seems that most stories of "Halloween sadism" are just that, stories. No child seems to have been killed by adulterated Halloween candy... well... there is one terrible exception. The poisoned Pixy Stix of Pasadena, TX.
For a full list of sources used in this episode visit Tim Harford.</description></item><item><title>Cautionary Conversation: The Conspiracy Theorist Who Changed His Mind | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700044/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Charlie Veitch was certain that 9/11 was an inside job. The attack on the World Trade Center wasn't the work of Al-Qaeda, but an elaborate conspiracy. He became a darling of so-called "9/11 truthers" - until he actually visited Ground Zero to meet architects, engineers and the relatives of the dead. The trip changed his mind... there was no conspiracy. His fellow "truthers" did not take Charlie's conversion well.</description></item><item><title>Cautionary Tales Presents: Warfare, The Life of Anne Frank | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700045/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700045/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, it's an episode from Warfare, a podcast from our friends at History Hit. It's 1942. The year Anne Frank and her family went into hiding during the Second World War. It was there that Anne began keeping a diary that would become one of the most recognisable testimonies of the Jewish war-time experiences. But what do we know of her life before the war? Host James Rogers explores the Franks' lives before the outbreak of war, and why this story is still so relevant today.</description></item><item><title>The Online Date That's Too Good to be True | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700046/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Single and looking for love, Dr Robert Epstein found himself chatting with a slim, attractive brunette online. She seemed perfect... perhaps even too good to be true. Dr Epstein is an expert on artificial conversation - so surely he'd be the last person to fall for a computer? Chatbots fool us more often than we think... especially when they replicate our very worst conversational habits. To read more on this topic try Brian Christian’s “The Most Human Human”.</description></item><item><title>A Leap of Faith From the Eiffel Tower | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700047/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Inventor Franz Reichelt wants to test his novel "parachute suit" from as tall a structure as possible - and the Eiffel Tower seems ideal. Previous trial runs used a mannequin strapped to the chute and have not ended well. Despite this, his plan is to make the Eiffel Tower jump himself. Can he be persuaded to see sense?
Self-experimentation - particularly in the field of medicine - has a long and checkered history.</description></item><item><title>Cautionary Conversation: Flying on Empty | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700048/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700048/</guid><description>Podcast Description A meter is longer than a yard. An ounce is heavier than a gram. We harmlessly mix them up sometimes, but a "unit conversion error" when you're filling up the fuel tanks of an airliner can be fatal. Which is exactly what happened to Air Canada Flight 143. Tim Harford talks to mathematician and comedian Matt Parker about how the aircraft came to take off without the proper fuel load, how no one noticed until it was too late, and why such errors give us an insight into just how important maths is to keeping our complex world working as it should.</description></item><item><title>Tim Talks Bicycles with Patented | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700049/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Invented in the mid-1800s, bicycles have had enduring popularity. Across cultures, they have been embraced, promising freedom and mobility at a lower price point. Tim joins Dallas Campbell on Patented: History of Inventions, to discuss the history of the bicycle, from the invention story through to bicycle booms, the C5 Sinclair and the rise of dockless bike sharing schemes. If you're interested in the stories behind the world's greatest inventions - from the mighty steam train to the humble condom - subscribe to Patented: History of Inventions today.</description></item><item><title>"You’re Not Howard Hughes!" | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700050/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700050/</guid><description>Podcast Description By the 1970s Howard Hughes was the "invisible billionaire”. A business tycoon, a daring aviator and Hollywood Lothario, Hughes had an amazing life story... but hiding away in luxury hotels he wasn't sharing his memories with anyone.
Then the recluse told a respected publishing house - via intermediaries - that he was working on an autobiography. The book would be a blockbuster... only it was all a lie.</description></item><item><title>"Who would you dine with? Scott or Amundsen?" Malcolm Gladwell and Tim Harford in Discussion. | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700051/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Malcolm Gladwell joins Tim Harford to discuss our recent three-part tale about the race to reach the South Pole. There's talk of imperial decline; the power of the underdog; why getting everything you want is actually a handicap; and limes... lots and lots of limes. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>South Pole Race: When the Limeys Get Scurvy | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700052/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Polar exploration is dangerous... but trudging hundreds of miles in subzero temperatures isn't made any easier if you're suffering from scurvy. The deadly vitamin deficiency destroys the body and will of even the strongest and most determined adventurer - and it seems that scurvy stuck down the ill-fated expedition of Captain Scott. But scurvy... in 1912? Hadn't the Royal Navy to which Scott belonged famously cracked the problem of scurvy a century before, with a daily dose of lime juice?</description></item><item><title>The Bowery Boys and the Black Tom Explosion | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700053/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cautionary Tales returns next week, but in the meantime enjoy a story of disaster from The Bowery Boys Podcast. It's July 30th 1916, just after 2am, and a massive explosion rips apart the munitions depot on Black Tom, an island off Jersey City. Tons of debris and jagged shrapnel pepper neighboring Ellis Island and the Statue of Liberty. Thousands of windows across New York are shattered, and millions of residents are awoken wondering what had just happened.</description></item><item><title>South Pole Race: “Mummy, is Amundsen a good man?” | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700054/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Roald Amundsen beat Captain Scott to the South Pole. The Norwegian - using dog sleds and skis - made it look easy... fun, even. He was heading home to safety, while the British party - hauling sleds by hand - were struggling to survive out on the ice.
In this case, to the victor went a spoiled reputation. The British grumbled that Amundsen had somehow cheated, or had at least behaved in an underhand manner.</description></item><item><title>South Pole Race: David and Goliath on Ice | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700055/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700055/</guid><description>Podcast Description 1910: Two men are racing to be the first to reach the South Pole. Captain Robert Falcon Scott heads a well-financed, technologically-advanced expedition - aiming to reach the pole in the "proper" and heroic way... on foot. Roald Amundsen's effort is more modest, relying on cheap sled dogs to carry him to victory. Scott - for all his money, for all his fancy equipment, for all his backing from the mighty Royal Navy - is doomed to failure in the icy wastes of Antarctica.</description></item><item><title>Chicago When It Sizzles | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700056/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700056/</guid><description>Podcast Description July 1995: A deadly heatwave gripped Chicago - bridges buckled; the power grids failed; and the morgue ran out of space - but some neighbourhoods saw more deaths than others.
Sociologist Eric Klinenberg wanted to know why. So he headed to the hardest hit districts and found that social isolation and loneliness played an unsettling role in their heavy deaths tolls. Does the Chicago heatwave teach us that in dealing with climate change we need to consider not just physical infrastructure, but social infrastructure too?</description></item><item><title>The French Knight’s Guide to Corporate Culture | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700057/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700057/</guid><description>Podcast Description France 1346: The army of King Philip VI is Europe's pre-eminent killing machine. It's accustomed to crushing any force stupid enough to oppose it, and now fully expects to annihilate a motley band of English invaders in a field near the village of Crecy. Except as night falls, it is Philip's army that lies broken and bleeding in the mud. What went wrong? The French knights, it seems, had failed to update their corporate culture.</description></item><item><title>Frankenstein Versus the Volcano | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700058/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700058/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Mount Tambora erupted it spewed ash across the globe; blotting out the sun; poisoning crops; and bringing starvation, illness and death to millions. It may also have helped inspire great scientific and cultural advances - including the horror masterpiece Frankenstein. How well do we adapt to catastrophe and what are the limits of our ability to weather even the worst circumstances?&amp;nbsp;
For a full list of sources go to&amp;nbsp;timharford.</description></item><item><title>Bless the Coal-black Hearts of the Broadway Critics | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700059/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700059/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Billy Joel agreed to let dance legend Twyla Tharp turn his songs into a Broadway musical it seemed like a surefire hit. But in previews, Movin&amp;rsquo; Out was panned by the critics. It was soon headed for Broadway and was set to be an expensive and embarrassing failure.So how could Twyla turn things around and avert disaster before opening night?
For a full list of sources go to&amp;nbsp;timharford.</description></item><item><title>Monkey for Mayor from This Day in Esoteric Political History | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700060/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700060/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happens when a monkey gets elected mayor? Well, not really a monkey, but a monkey mascot for a town&amp;rsquo;s football games. Tim Harford joins This Day in Esoteric Political History to discuss a weird moment from UK history in 2002, when the northeastern English town of Hartlepool was gearing up for a mayoral election and ended up voting in&amp;hellip;the local football club&amp;rsquo;s monkey mascot to run their government.</description></item><item><title>When the Autopilot Switched Off | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700061/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700061/</guid><description>Podcast Description An airline captain thought he was giving his children a harmless thrill by letting them "fly" his packed airplane - the young cockpit visitors weren't really in control... the autopilot was doing the real flying. Until it wasn't.&amp;nbsp;
Do safety features actually lull us into a false sense of security - tempting us to take greater risks than we otherwise would?
For a full list of sources go to&amp;nbsp;timharford.</description></item><item><title>Cautionary Tales Presents: World's Greatest Con | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700062/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700062/</guid><description>Podcast Description We'll be back with another story of human error next week, but today we're sharing another podcast you might like. On World's Greatest Con, Brian Brushwood talks about the most audacious con jobs, swindles, and heists in history. In this episode of World's Greatest Con, Brian tells the story of how a game show producer was tempted into upping the ante on his own program by feeding answers to the contestants.</description></item><item><title>Photographing Fairies | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700063/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sherlock Holmes is known for approaching all mysteries with cool logic - and yet when his creator Sir Arthur Conan Doyle saw photographs taken by two young girls purporting to show real life fairies at play... he unwisely declared them genuine.
How did Elsie and Frances fool so many people with their photography... and why did they keep the hoax going for decades?
For a full list of sources go to timharford.</description></item><item><title>Tim Joins ‘No Such Thing As A Fish' | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700064/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700064/</guid><description>Podcast Description ‘No Such Thing as a Fish’ is one of Tim Harford’s favorite podcasts and he was recently invited on as a guest. So here’s a chance to listen to the host of Cautionary Tales chat vital vitamins, stinging schemes, and the practice of pyrography.
Listen to more episodes from No Such Thing as a Fish wherever you get podcasts.
Cautionary Tales will return with the story the greatest photographic hoax in history next Friday.</description></item><item><title>The False Dawn of the Electric Car | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700065/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sir Clive Sinclair was a computer whizz and business mogul to rival Steve Jobs or Bill Gates. He was a visionary who could do no wrong... until he tried to launch an electric vehicle.
The C5 “electrically assisted pedal cycle" doesn't seem so outlandish to us now... but 1985 just wasn't ready for the "aerodynamic bathtub" on wheels. Sir Clive was ridiculed and his business ruined. How did it all go so wrong?</description></item><item><title>The Balloons That Ate Cleveland (A Cautionary Tales Short) | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700066/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 04:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700066/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Disneyland released one million helium balloons to set a new world record, Cleveland, Ohio looked on in envy. Could it top the Magic Kingdom? What did citizens hope to gain from getting into the record books... and at what cost?
This is a special Cautionary Tales Short - a bitesize warning for history. To hear FOUR more Cautionary Tales Shorts (plus other exclusive and ad-free Pushkin content) join Pushkin+ in Apple Podcasts or at https://www.</description></item><item><title>Death on the Dance Floor | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700067/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700067/</guid><description>Podcast Description With its splendid modern architecture, the Hyatt Regency was the place to be seen in Kansas City in 1981. Beneath space-age walkways, guests drank, laughed and danced... not realizing that the 60 tons of of glass, concrete and steel hanging above their heads was about to come crashing down.
One hundred and fourteen people died. But why? Was it cheap materials? Shoddy construction? Or a tiny error that seemed so insignificant that no one paid it any attention?</description></item><item><title>Cautionary Tales Returns Every Other Friday from March 25th | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700068/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700068/</guid><description>Podcast Description The greatest mistakes, disasters and fiascos of the past aren't just gripping stories... they're also warnings from which we all can learn.
Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford returns EVERY OTHER FRIDAY FROM MARCH 25th to chronicle the defeats of mighty armies, the destruction of business empires and the deadly eruptions of fearsome volcanoes. And from amongst the wrecked lives and wrecked egos, Tim finds the simple lessons we can apply in our daily lives.</description></item><item><title>The Mummy’s Curse | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700069/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Disturbing the remains of the Egyptian pharaohs is known to incur a deadly curse, so why did a team of archeologists still risk inciting the wrath of King Tutankhamun by entering his burial chamber? And how many of them met a premature end for their impudence?
Learn more about your ad-choices at https://www.iheartpodcastnetwork.comSee omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Truth About Hansel and Gretel | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700070/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Was the fairy tale of Hansel and Gretel - the story of a woodcutter’s children abandoned in the woods and left at the mercy of a witch - in fact, early true crime? A hit book - The Truth About Hansel and Gretel - said that historical records pointed to the story being based on fact. Are we too quick to dismiss the truth behind tall stories? Or are we always falling for tales that are too good to be true?</description></item><item><title>Do NOT Pass GO! | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700071/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lizzie J. Magie (played by Helena Bonham Carter) should be celebrated as the inventor of what would become Monopoly - but her role in creating the smash hit board game was cynically ignored, even though she had a patent.
Discrimination has marred the careers of many inventors and shut others out from the innovation economy entirely. Could crediting forgotten figures such as Lizzie Magie help address continuing disparities in the patenting of new inventions?</description></item><item><title>Wrong Tools Cost Lives | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700072/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700072/</guid><description>Podcast Description The British Government promised to create a "world-beating" system to track deadly Covid 19 infections - but it included an outdated version of the off-the-shelf spreadsheet software Microsoft Excel. The result was disastrous.
When under pressure or lacking in expertise we can all be tempted to use a tool unsuitable for the job in hand. But whether fitting shelves or trying to halt a pandemic, we need to accept that cutting corners comes at a cost.</description></item><item><title>Fritterin’ Away Genius | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700073/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Claude Shannon was brilliant. He was the Einstein of computer science... only he loved "fritterin' away" his time building machines to play chess, solve Rubik's cubes and beat the house at roulette.
If Shannon had worked more diligently - instead of juggling, riding a unicycle and abandoning project after project - would he have made an even greater contribution to human knowledge? Maybe... and maybe not. Are restlessness and "</description></item><item><title>The Fan Who Infected a Movie Star | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700074/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700074/</guid><description>Podcast Description German measles is a minor illness for most people - but for unborn children it can be devastating. In 1943 - when the link was only just becoming clear - a young US marine decided to break rubella quarantine to meet the movie star Gene Tierney (played by Mircea Monroe). The marine was sick... and Gene was pregnant.
The appalling consequences of that meeting tell us much about how our thoughtlessness can harm those around us - but the kind of tragedy that befell Tierney and her daughter can be averted if we appeal to the better parts of human nature.</description></item><item><title>Whistleblower on the 28th Floor | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700075/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Financial expert Ray Dirks (played by Jeffrey Wright) exposed one of the biggest corporate crimes of all time - and yet he was the one who ended up in front of the Supreme Court.
Whistleblowers often face intimidation from those they bring to justice, but also face hostility from their co-workers, new employers, the authorities and even the public. Why are we suspicious of "tattletales" and what can we do to make vital whistleblowing easier?</description></item><item><title>Masterly Inactivity Versus Micromanaging | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700076/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lady Sale (played by Helena Bonham Carter) was part of a bloody and ignominious British retreat from Afghanistan in 1842. The arrogant colonial invaders had thought intervening in Afghan affairs and dominating the country would be easy - they were wrong. Lady Sale was among the lucky few to escape with her life.
Wiser heads later recommended "masterly inactivity" as a better course of action. In politics, parenting and even medicine - avoiding the temptation to act is a sadly neglected art form.</description></item><item><title>Demonizing Dungeons &amp; Dragons | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700077/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700077/</guid><description>Podcast Description When James Dallas Egbert III was reported missing from his college dorm - one of America's most flamboyant private detectives was summoned to solve the case. "Dallas" had many of the same problems that most teenagers face - but P.I. William Dear stoked fears that he might have fallen under the evil spell of a mysterious and sinister game.... Dungeons &amp;amp; Dragons.
The global panic about the dangers the role-playing game posed to impressionable young minds may seem quaint 40 years on - but again and again we show how fearful we are of creative endeavours we don't quite understand.</description></item><item><title>Number Fever: How Pepsi Nearly Went Pop | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700078/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pepsi twice ended up in court after promotions went disastrously wrong. Other big companies have fallen into the same trap - promising customers rewards so generous that to fulfil the promise might mean corporate bankruptcy. Businesses and customers alike are sometimes blinded by the big numbers in such PR stunts - but it's usually the customers, not the businesses, who end up losing out. Read more about Tim's work at http://timharford.</description></item><item><title>The Curse of Knowledge Meets The Valley of Death | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700079/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why were soldiers on horseback told to ride straight into a valley full of enemy cannon? The disastrous "Charge of the Light Brigade" is usually blamed on blundering generals. But the confusing orders issued on that awful day in 1854 reveal a common human trait - we often wrongly assume that everyone knows what we know and can easily comprehend our meaning.
Starring Helena Bonham Carter as Florence Nightingale.</description></item><item><title>The Dunning Kruger Hijack (and Other Criminally Stupid Acts) | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700080/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700080/</guid><description>Podcast Description The hijackers of flight 961 wanted its pilot to fly them to Australia - and wouldn't listen to his pleas that there simply wasn't enough fuel for the mammoth trip. What would cause them to totally disregard the advice of an expert when the stakes were so very high? The Dunning Kruger effect.
But being too stupid to recognise the limits of your knowledge isn't confined to such prize idiots - it's something we are all guilty of at times and has huge implications for society.</description></item><item><title>Catching a KiIler Doctor | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700081/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Family doctor Harold Shipman got away with murdering his patients for decades. He was one of the most prolific serial killers in history - but his hundreds of crimes largely went unnoticed despite a vast paper trail of death certificates he himself had signed.
Why do we sometimes fail to see awful things happening right under our noses? And how can the systems that maintain quality control in cookie factories be employed to prevent another doctor like Shipman killing with impunity?</description></item><item><title>The Art Forger, the Nazi, and "The Pope" | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700082/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700082/</guid><description>Podcast Description "The Pope" was a revered Dutch art expert - and yet he fell for a not very convincing forgery of a "lost" Vermeer masterpiece. The forger had duped other art connoisseurs too - including the high ranking Nazi Hermann Göring. But perhaps Han van Meegeren's biggest con was to convince the Dutch public that he was a cheeky resistance hero.
We assume knowledge and intelligence can protect us from being duped - but often they are not enough to save us from the fraudster's greatest ally - our own wishful thinking.</description></item><item><title>Florence Nightingale and Her Geeks Declare War on Death | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700083/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Victorian nurse Florence Nightingale (played by her distant cousin Helena Bonham Carter) is a hero of modern medicine - but her greatest contribution to combating disease and death resulted from the vivid graphs she made to back her public health campaigns.
Her charts convinced the great and the good that deaths due to filth and poor sanitation could be averted - saving countless lives. But did Nightingale open Pandora's Box, showing that graphs persuade, whether or not they depict reality?</description></item><item><title>Martin Luther King Jr, the Jewelry Genius, and the Art of Public Speaking | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700084/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700084/</guid><description>Podcast Description One speechmaker inspired millions with his words, the other utterly destroyed his own multi-million-dollar business with just a few phrases.
Civil rights icon Martin Luther King Jr (played by Jeffrey Wright of Westworld, The Hunger Games, and the James Bond films) and jewelry store owner Gerald Ratner offer starkly contrasting stories on when you should stick to the script and when you should take a risk.
Read more about Tim's work at http://timharford.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Why We Believe What Isn't True (with Axios Today) | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700085/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700085/</guid><description>Podcast Description We're no stranger to stories about misinformation or deliberate disinformation. We live in a world where now more than ever, you have to be skeptical. That skepticism can be healthy, but it also can be used to cast more doubt and misinformation on data and statistics that are very real. Tim Harford talks to Niala Boodhoo, from the news podcast Axios Today, about why people believe things that aren't true.</description></item><item><title>The Data Detective | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700086/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cautionary Tales' host Tim Harford has a new book - The Data Detective - setting out ten commandments for understanding the numbers, charts, graphs and statistics that bombard us every day. In this free extract, Tim explains his extra "golden" rule that allows us to observe all his other commandments - be curious. Enjoy.
Cautionary Tales returns February 26.
The Data Detective (Riverhead Books) is published in the US and Canada on February 2.</description></item><item><title>BONUS: Storks, Smoking and the Power of Doubt | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700087/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 13:52:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700087/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's easy to mock statistics or cast doubt on them... but we do so at our peril. Undermining our trust in facts and figures can cause great harm, and even death. We should guard against it.
Tim Harford looks at how the seeds of doubt are planted in this mini-episode of Cautionary Tales to celebrate the release of his latest book.
“How To Make The World Add Up” is out now in much of the world, while listeners in US/Canada can pre-order it under the title "</description></item><item><title>How To End A Pandemic | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700088/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700088/</guid><description>Podcast Description The eradication of smallpox is one of humanity's great achievements - but the battle against the virus was fought by the most unlikely of alliances. How did the breakthrough happen - and can we guarantee that the world is still safe from smallpox?
This episode owes a debt to Stephen Coss’s book The Fever of 1721, Ibram X. Kendi’s book Stamped From the Beginning, and to an article about Dark Winter written by Tara O’Toole, Michael Mair and Tomas Inglesby.</description></item><item><title>That Turn To Pascagoula | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700089/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700089/</guid><description>Podcast Description For years, people had warned that New Orleans was vulnerable - but when a hurricane came close to destroying the city, the reaction was muted. Some people took the near miss as a warning - others, as confirmation that there was nothing to worry about.
So why do we struggle to prepare for disasters? And why don't we draw the obvious lessons from clear warnings?
Sources for this episode include Amanda Ripley's The Unthinkable, The Ostrich Paradox by Howard Kunreuther and Robert Meyer, Margaret Heffernan's Willful Blindness, and Predictable Surprises by Max Bazerman and Michael Watkins.</description></item><item><title>The Village of Heroes | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700090/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700090/</guid><description>Podcast Description It looked like any ordinary roll of cloth, but it brought the dreaded plague to the village of Eyam. First it killed the tailor, then resident after resident succumbed. To stop the spread of the disease to neighbouring towns the people of Eyam agreed to isolate themselves and let the plague run its deadly course. This terrible act of sacrifice is still remembered centuries later - but what does it tell us about how far people will go to save the lives of strangers?</description></item><item><title>The Spreadsheet of Life and Death | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700091/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2020 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Clive had a deadly form of cancer, but fortunately there was a new drug to treat it. Imagine his anger when he was told the treatment was too expensive. He’d entered a world where unique human lives are given a value in a mathematical formula. So how much should we spend to extend or save a life? And are some lives worth more than others?
Read more about Tim's work at http://timharford.</description></item><item><title>A Tsunami of Misery | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700092/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700092/</guid><description>Podcast Description A monstrous wave and then a nuclear disaster forced Mikio and Hamako Watanabe from their home. But being saved from the potential dangers of a radiation leak destroyed their lives in a different way. Why do we overlook the fact that taking action against an urgent danger can also cause longer term ills?
WARNING: This episode discusses death by suicide. If you are suffering emotional distress or having suicidal thoughts, support is available - for example, from the National Suicide Prevention Lifeline.</description></item><item><title>Fire at The Beverly Hills Supper Club | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700093/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Flames are spreading through a Cincinnati hotel. The staff know it, the fire department is coming, and the people in the packed cabaret bar have been told to evacuate… and yet they hesitate to leave. Why don’t we react to some warnings until it’s too late?
Read more about Tim's work at http://timharford.com/
Tim's latest books 'Fifty Inventions That Shaped The Modern Economy' and 'The Next Fifty Things That Made The Modern Economy' are available now.</description></item><item><title>Cautionary Tales Presents: TED Talk Daily | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700094/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700094/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this special episode of Cautionary Tales, we feature Cautionary Tales host Tim Harford's TED Talk Daily from 2018. What can we learn from the world's most enduringly creative people? They "slow-motion multitask," actively juggling multiple projects and moving between topics as the mood strikes -- without feeling hurried. Tim Harford shares how innovators like Einstein, Darwin, Twyla Tharp and Michael Crichton found their inspiration and productivity through cross-training their minds.</description></item><item><title>You Have Reached Your Destination | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700095/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700095/</guid><description>Podcast Description We may mock our ancestors for seeking the advice of oracles, soothsayers and psychics, but today we rely heavily on computer programs and math formulas to help us navigate our world. If we continue to follow them unthinkingly, should we be surprised when we end up in unexpected and dangerous places?
Read more about Tim's work at http://timharford.com/
Learn more about your ad-choices at https://www.iheartpodcastnetwork.comSee omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Bowie, Jazz and the Unplayable Piano | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700096/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700096/</guid><description>Podcast Description It was the biggest concert of Keith Jarrett's career - but the pianist was in for a shock when he entered Koln's opera house. The only piano at the venue was a broken-down wreck. Should he risk humiliation and play anyway or simply walk out? The collaboration between pop superstar David Bowie and arch disruptor Brian Eno offers a lesson that staying in your comfort zone isn't always the best option.</description></item><item><title>How Britain Invented, Then Ignored, Blitzkrieg | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700097/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700097/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1917, a brilliant British officer developed a way to use an emerging military technology: the tank. The British army promptly squandered the idea – but the Germans did not. Blitzkrieg, the devastating advance of German tanks across Europe in 1940, was invented by the British.
This is a common story: Sony invented the forerunner of the iPod, Xerox the personal computer, and Kodak the digital camera. In each case they failed to capitalize on the idea.</description></item><item><title>Buried by the Wall Street Crash | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700098/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Both of the world’s greatest economists, Irving Fisher and John Maynard Keynes, thought they could see into the future and make a killing on the stock market - and then both were wiped out by the Wall Street Crash. One died a pauper, the other millionaire. What does it take to bounce back from ruin? Oh... and UFOs.
Read more about Tim's work at http://timharford.com/
Learn more about your ad-choices at https://www.</description></item><item><title>The Deadly Airship Race | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700099/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700099/</guid><description>Podcast Description A British Lord wanted to build the best airship in the world - and so he had two rival design teams battle it out to win the juicy government contract. Competition is supposed to bring the best out of people, but run in the wrong way it can cause people (and the things they produce) to fall apart in the most horrifying ways.
Read more about Tim's work at http://timharford.</description></item><item><title>La La Land: Galileo's Warning | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700100/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Galileo tried to teach us that adding more and more layers to a system intended to avert disaster often makes catastrophe all the more likely to happen. His basic lesson has been ignored in nuclear power plants, financial markets and at the Oscars... all resulting in chaos.
Read more about Tim's work at http://timharford.com/
Learn more about your ad-choices at https://www.iheartpodcastnetwork.comSee omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Rogue Dressed as a Captain | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700101/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700101/</guid><description>Podcast Description One crisp morning in Berlin, in 1906, a small group of soldiers were led on an extraordinary heist by a man they believed to be a Captain. So how did an ageing nobody in a fake uniform trick them into aiding him in the crime of the century? Some say we humans will obey orders from anyone who dresses the part... but the real reason why we fall for tricksters time and again is far more interesting.</description></item><item><title>DANGER: Rocks Ahead! | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700102/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 05:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Torrey Canyon was one of the biggest and best ships in the world - but its captain and crew still needlessly steered it towards a deadly reef known as The Seven Stones. This course seemed like utter madness, but the thinking that resulted in such a risky manoeuvre is something we are all prone to do when we fixate on a goal and a plan to get us there.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Cautionary Tales | Cautionary Tales with Tim Harford</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6180700103/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 15:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6180700103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Coming November 15 from Tim Harford and Pushkin Industries, Cautionary Tales relates a true story of a time when something did not go according to plan. Some of these true stories are tragic, some are comic, but like the great fables and parables, each of them has a moral. Equipped with the latest research from psychology, economics and the social sciences, Harford explains why things went so awry – and teaches us lessons that we won’t forget.</description></item></channel></rss>