<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Call Chelsea Peretti on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/call-chelsea-peretti/</link><description>Recent content in Call Chelsea Peretti on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/call-chelsea-peretti/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>I LOVE BEING A SPECK OF DUST | Call Chelsea Peretti</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6159910001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6159910001/</guid><description>Podcast Description A mom calls for momtalk. A dude with a deep belly button shares his challenges and triumphs. A discussion of how to get off social media. Car crash alerts. A hematologist calls. An eyeliner rec. Military time. Rubbery pancakes and waffles. Grama impressions and reflections. Food test: gravy. Talking to callers like cute dogs. A barista calls from Alaska. And finally an interview with a couple who replaced their massive grass lawn with a native wildflower garden, thus inspiring their neighbors and the world beyond.</description></item><item><title>YOU ARE NOT THE SAME | Call Chelsea Peretti</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6159910002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6159910002/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode, we dive into the sci-fi world of head injuries and brain problems. Two legendary guests join us: Dr. Langer, Chair of Neurosurgery at Lenox Hill Hospital, and star of two riveting Netflix docu-series "Emergency NYC" and "Lenox Hill," AND: Morgan Murphy, kiss-ready comedian and Abbott Elementary writer extra-ordinaire. Plus calls from various afflicted parties, blithering on with so-and-so and whosy whatsit. Thanks to iHeart music catalog for an exploration of musical nirvana.</description></item><item><title>BEST OF CCP 1 - WEIRDOS, FREAKS, AND OUTCASTS | Call Chelsea Peretti</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6159910004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6159910004/</guid><description>Podcast Description German legend Oliver calls to inquire after his mysterious letter and Chelsea shares with him about the common practices in Hollywood. A baseball player takes us on a party-boi rollercoaster. An Australian caller gives Chelsea a chance to practice her accent. Chelsea's ex "Chance" (nick kroll) - calls and shares about his copycat podcast and tries to get back with Chelsea until she says yes, at which point he's out.</description></item><item><title>PROXY ANIMAL ATTACK STORIES CULMINATING IN ACTUAL ANIMAL ATTACKS | Call Chelsea Peretti</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6159910003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6159910003/</guid><description>Podcast Description A mouse encounter. A lady swims “near” a shark. Two insane girls call. Just another day on the pod until some Brit in the medical profession shares a harrowing dog attack tale. Finally, composer Chris Lennertz calls and details his BEAR ATTACK STORY!!!!! *JACKPOT SOUND EFFECT* Hashtag bear attack. Hashtag Lake Tahoe. Hashtag jackpot sound effect.
Subscribe to Big Money Players Diamond on Apple Podcasts to get this episode ad-free and early access to bonus content: https://apple.</description></item><item><title>A very special CCP: THACHER ISLAND | Call Chelsea Peretti</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6159910005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 19:27:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6159910005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chelsea debuts a new dramatic play-in-progress reading excerpt at Vulture Fest, this time set against the backdrop of a barren island off the coast of Massachusetts. "Thacher Island" features a fisherwoman marooned on an island whose son is mysteriously lost at sea, a seagull named Silver, a dark secret, and a pair of strange visitors who may change things forever... Q&amp;amp;A follows. Starring John Early, Kaitlin Olson, and Xosha Roquemore.</description></item><item><title>CCP CLASSICS: “RAINS COMIN’ IN!“ | Call Chelsea Peretti</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6159910006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6159910006/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a holiday gift, we offer you this classic CCP dramatic play excerpt reading, which many callers claim is a family holiday listening tradition. Written by Chelsea Peretti. With Kate Berlant, John Early, Yassir Lester, Esther Povitsky, Xosha Roquemore, Emily Spivey and narration by Dave King. Q&amp;amp;A follows.
Subscribe to Big Money Players Diamond on Apple Podcasts to get this episode ad-free and early access to bonus content: https://apple.</description></item><item><title>TRENDS, AFFLICTIONS, BAKED GOODS | Call Chelsea Peretti</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6159910007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 21:02:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6159910007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tinseltown MUA Nova Kaplan visits the studio to discuss tiktok makeup trends such as: pumpkin girl makeup, cloud makeup, faux freckles, red carpet looks, and stage makeup, while giving Chelsea a "Latte Girl" beat. Chelsea tries to get her barky dog to bark and learns he is no show-pony. A caller pretends she has old skin. A lass with mild eczema on her knuckles shares her girlfriend's harrowing medical tale.</description></item><item><title>69 AND SHREDDED | Call Chelsea Peretti</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6159910008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6159910008/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Call Chelsea Podcast returns with calls about PEPSI LOVING BEARS! CARROT LOVING HORSES! TUCKED SHEETS! BAKED POTATOES! Featuring ASMR, coffee songs, an analysis of trying to get shredded (including push-up condescension), new sound effects, couture sound effects, a caller named Crisp, and a caller who treats Chelsea like a patient. Cake pops emerge as a super villain. From meandering to over-produced - there’s sure to be something for everyone!</description></item><item><title>CALL CHELSEA PERETTI: THE PREQUEL. IN ANOTHER DIMENSION!!!!! | Call Chelsea Peretti</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6159910009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6159910009/</guid><description>Podcast Description The legendary podcast returns, imagining what happened BEFORE it in time AND space- jk its just a new version of the pod! Now with interviews, live taste tests, special guests, makeovers, video, and stuff like that but still maintaining the integrity of medical and bear fixations. And you: the caller. New episodes starting November 9. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>