<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Normal Women on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/normal-women/</link><description>Recent content in Normal Women on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:01:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/normal-women/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>8. Normal women...are married, divorced and single | Normal Women</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5001960001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:01:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5001960001/</guid><description>Podcast Description The marriage of Queen Victoria to Prince Albert set the template for how we imagine a wedding should be but it wasn’t always about big white frocks. Philippa Gregory explores how married women became the property of their husbands - along with everything they owned and produced. She considers the hidden history of wife sales and female husbands and shines a light on the difficulty women had accessing divorce.</description></item><item><title>7. Normal women...are beyond definition | Normal Women</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5001960002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:01:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5001960002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Men have always claimed that there is such a thing as “female nature” and described it with great authority – but throughout history, women have refused to conform to the strict view of what is masculine and feminine - from fierce jousting medieval ladies to 18th Century French aristocrats who seamlessly slip in and out of male and female roles.
Joining Philippa to discuss whether women have ever fitted the mould are:</description></item><item><title>6. Normal Women...are a weaker vessel | Normal Women</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5001960003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 00:01:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5001960003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bitten, spat on, denounced - in the 1990s newly-ordained women were met with fury by a vocal minority. But women have always played an important role in the Church, as mystics, the heads of religious&amp;nbsp;houses, saints or simply as normal women seeking salvation.&amp;nbsp;
Joining Philippa to tell the story of women's changing place in the Church of England - from 'weaker vessels' in the sixteenth century to women bishops in the twenty-first:</description></item><item><title>5. Normal Women...think about rape | Normal Women</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5001960004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 00:01:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5001960004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Throughout history women have faced the threat of sexual violence and, sadly, it's no different today. Philippa explores how rape was viewed as a crime against a man’s property, how courtly love gave way to brutal desire and the difficulties women face in bringing their attackers to justice.
Joining Philippa to discuss rape - how it has changed through history and how we see it now are:
Joanna Bourke, Professor of History at Birkbeck, University of London and author ‘Rape: A history ’Soma Sara anti-rape activist and founder of ‘Everyone’s Invited’ website and charity</description></item><item><title>4. Normal Women...are underpaid | Normal Women</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5001960005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 00:01:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5001960005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Whether you are on the Board or in the kitchen, a medieval peasant or modern day medic, a Victorian street-sweeper or eighteenth century hand-spinner - if you are a woman, there’s every chance you are underpaid. So why is that? Explanations vary across the centuries from women's lack of upper-body strength to the demands of motherhood and patriarchal oppression,&amp;nbsp;but one thing is certain - the pay gap never closes.</description></item><item><title>3. Normal Women...love women | Normal Women</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5001960006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:01:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5001960006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sapphism, the Cult of the Clitoris, coded diaries and a bower of bliss - Philippa Gregory tells the story of women who love women, and those who tried to stop them.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;We hear from famous lesbians including Queen Anne and Gentleman Jack and less famous lovers rescued from the footnotes of history.
Joining Philippa to discuss the history of women who love women are:
TikTok stars Caitlin and Leah and Professor Laura Gowing, who teaches women's history and queer history at King's College London.</description></item><item><title>2. Normal Women...are angels | Normal Women</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5001960007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 00:01:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5001960007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Just how should women behave? Throughout History, they have so often been expected to act as genteel ladies and confined to the home - often described as the 'angel in the house'. But far from remaining passive, many used their influence to put themselves at the heart of radical social change. In this episode we hear about the anti slavery campaigners - and Philippa introduces us to the hundreds of women who absolutely, under no circumstances wanted the vote.</description></item><item><title>1. Normal Women...riot! | Normal Women</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5001960008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 23:01:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5001960008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Philippa tells the story of women rebels and rioters - from the leaders of the Peasants' Revolt to those arrested at the vigil for Sarah Everard.&amp;nbsp;We hear from&amp;nbsp;'Captain' Ann Carter, leader of a seventeenth century food riot, hanged by the authorities and just one of the thousands of women Philippa&amp;nbsp;has rescued from the footnotes of history and placed at the heart of her book 'Normal Women - 900 years of Making History'.</description></item><item><title>Philippa Gregory's Normal Women - Coming soon | Normal Women</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5001960009/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 08:06:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5001960009/</guid><description>Podcast Description A new eight-part series starts on the 26th October.
Normal Women is a radical retelling of our nation’s story – not of the rise and fall of kings and the occasional queen – but of social and cultural change, powered by the determination, persistence and effectiveness of women– from 1066 to modern times. This is not a podcast about three or four well-known heroines; it is a story about millions of women: those who left records and those who were ‘hidden from history.</description></item></channel></rss>