<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/woman-evolve-with-sarah-jakes-roberts/</link><description>Recent content in Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/woman-evolve-with-sarah-jakes-roberts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>God Moves Only | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550101/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Issa WETV Throwback! SJR caught up with her friend Michelle Williams and sis was candid! She shared what she'd tell her younger self, what led to breaking off her engagement, and what she believes God has called her to do next in her life. Tune in for some edifying girl talk!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Everything Must Go | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550001/</guid><description>Podcast Description When something gets in the way of your relationship with God — it's gotta go. In ”Everything Must Go,” Pastor Sarah Jakes Roberts teaches us to clear away what’s holding us back from being who God created us to be. The things that keep us from God –– bitterness, anger, old mindsets, toxic relationships –– it’s time for them to go.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Her Flaws, My Fight w/ Dr. Jill Waggoneer and Jillian Mitchell | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550002/</guid><description>Podcast Description There is nothing more powerful than showing our children our flaws. What may be even more powerful is showing how we show up in spite of our flaws. Join Pastor Sarah, our new homegirl and honorary doctor - Dr. Jill Waggoneer and her daughter Jillian for our final episode of the "My Mother, My Sister" series. You may want to grab some tissues!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Just Keep Going w/ Erica Campbell | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550003/</guid><description>Podcast Description What to do when you’re starting from the ground up? That’s the question this episode answers. This week W.E. are keeping it raw and real with a woman of resiliency—the faith-filled Erica Campbell who stays making MAJOR moves for the Kingdom! Erica shares with SJR how the desire to win souls &amp; serve Jesus would at times leave her with a residual faith, but even then, she pressed towards the mark.</description></item><item><title>Cultivating Sisterhood w/ Kyndal Banks | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550004/</guid><description>Podcast Description How 'bout W.E. rebuke the spirit of no new friends? Real talk, Sis! The enemy will finesse you into a season of loneliness or toxicity—whole time, you were created for community! Here to tell SJR about finding a tribe of sister-friends, is the Delegation's very own AND creator of Solo2Soul Sisters, Kyndal Banks! This episode is a testament to the power established in coming together &amp; declaring NO WOMAN LEFT BEHIND!</description></item><item><title>Reset Your Priorities w/ Stevi Carter | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sis, set your priorities straight, so W.E. can watch you pop awf! In this throwback episode, newlywed &amp; first-time mom Stevi Carter is teaching us how to rearrange a thing or two. Her main concern is living in a state of gratitude &amp; chile W.E. felt that for somebody! When was the last time you slowed down and prioritized what truly mattered? Ya know…vibin’ with the fam, figuring out those friendships, or building a legacy.</description></item><item><title>Permission Talk w/ Dr. Jackie Greene | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550006/</guid><description>Podcast Description A lot of us are a combined effort of who raised us and who we were influenced by. So, how do we set out on new paths? How do we create better routines? And, how do we make better choices to create change in our health? Check out this week's episode as SJR and Dr. Jackie Greene gives our listeners the permission to live healthier lives! Then head over to access some great finds online at SKIMS.</description></item><item><title>Pace Your Emotions | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550007/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we're throwing it back to that one time W.E.'s surrogate mom, First Lady Serita Jakes, teamed up with SJR to discuss how to rediscover ourselves in a "lost" season. They say a season of being lost hits different when we have the wisdom of another woman to see us through. Tune in as "Mama"/First Lady Serita shares with the Delegation how she's evolved as a woman, navigated the pandemic, and so much more!</description></item><item><title>Leveling Up w/ Morgan DeBaun | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Leveling the playing field is one thing, but leveling ALL the way up is another! And that's what we're on this week thanks to the change agent and multihyphenate herself, Morgan DeBaun! Sis is no stranger when it comes to betting on the underserved and underestimated. Her greatest hope for the generation of women to come, is that we never have to doubt ourselves or the choices we make.</description></item><item><title>Healing Your Mother Wound w/ Alyson Brown | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550009/</guid><description>Podcast Description They say to be the adult you needed when you were younger. But what about those of us traversing emotional injuries created by a generational deficit? YES chile, we're talkin' "mother wounds". As an overcomer of mental and emotional barriers in her childhood, our guest co-host Alyson Brown sits down with SJR to share with listeners how healing is STILL available. Join us as W.E. go inward to become the change we needed and perhaps STILL need to experience.</description></item><item><title>Ascribed Honor in Sisterhood w/ Love McPherson | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sis, you know there’s nothing you can do to earn our love and honor here at Woman Evolve, right? No cap, but W.E. give that out freely! This sisterhood community finds value in EVERY woman W.E. come in connection with! But to help us truly understand the depths of sisterhood relationships, SJR invited Relationship Expert and Certified Marriage &amp; Family Counselor, Love McPherson, on the podcast this week to be a voice of hope!</description></item><item><title>Transparency in Sisterhood w/ Cora Jakes | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550011/</guid><description>Podcast Description If Woman Evolve 23 taught us anything, it’s that truth and transparency will set us free! As sisters, we stood before God and each other in our “nakedness”, witnessing the depths of another woman’s pain. After recognizing a lack of closeness, SJR and her ferocious warrior of a big sister, Cora Jakes, sit down to have an intimate conversation concerning their sisterhood relationship. Tune in as the two explain where they are right now and where they hope to land in due season!</description></item><item><title>Best of Hope Ep. 4 - Hoping to Parent with Intention &amp; Having Hard Conversations | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550012/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550012/</guid><description>Podcast Description When it comes to communicating with the children in your life, are some things better left unsaid? If you're wishing to parent with intention, this drop of hope is just for you! Tune in as SJR and New York Times bestselling author, licensed therapist, and sought-after relationship expert Nedra Tawwab explore the benefits of discussing the "hard" things. Their talk will leave you not only parenting the child that’s in front of you, but healing the inner child within you!</description></item><item><title>Best of Hope Ep. 3 - Hope for Something New | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550013/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550013/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s often times not the surrounding circumstances that prevent us from hoping for something new, but rather our inward inability to hope and expect for more. It is possible to silently hope for things that we would dare not utter out loud for the risk of being disappointed. If WE will allow ourselves to tap into a hope that leaves no room for doubt or disappointment, we position ourselves to not only change our own lives, but the lives of everyone attached to us.</description></item><item><title>Embodied Consistency w/ Fran Medina | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Imagine what would happen if we frequently yielded to our well-being. Here to reveal the fruits of her labor is digital architect Fran Medina! After documenting her health journey online, she quickly cultivated a community of people curious about holistic health and wellness. This week, SJR and Fran connect to explore how a life rooted in intention redefines the markers of success. This episode proves that when it comes to obedience, consistency at even the smallest level makes the difference!</description></item><item><title>Best of Hope Ep. 2 - The Dark Side of Hope | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550015/</guid><description>Podcast Description It can be difficult to hold onto hope, especially when things seem bleak. However, it's important to remember that hope is always the answer. Sometimes, all it takes is a shift in perspective or expectations to see things in a more positive light. That's why we've gathered some inspiring drops of hope from SJR’s sermons and messages that have helped us during our own moments of despair. It is our prayer that by sharing these with you, we're able to provide a boost of hope when you need it most.</description></item><item><title>For Realness Sake with Kieara Pittman | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Issa podcast throwback! Our good Sis stood ten toes down in her truth! But keep it a hunnid, haven't you been in rooms where you chose to become someone else—all to avoid rejection? Kieara explains how the path of self-acceptance led to an encounter with purpose &amp; it's giving Hail Mary vibes! The two discuss lookin' like ya husband’s homeboy, imaginary heaux tales, emotional boundaries, &amp; so much MORE!</description></item><item><title>Best of Hope Ep. 1 - Hope For New Connection | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550017/</guid><description>Podcast Description The hope for new connections can sound scary. It requires a new level of vulnerability and maybe even truth that has yet to be spoken. Sis, we’re evolving over here and it takes all of that and all of you! Lean into trusting yourself so you can learn to trust others with you too. SJR and Andrea Merkyl discuss what new connections require and how they benefit us.</description></item><item><title>Radical Relationships w/ Angela Griffith | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550018/</guid><description>Podcast Description The following episode contains adult themes, sexual content, and strong language not suitable for all audiences. Viewer discretion is advised, so don't say W.E. didn't warn you! Sis, today you are in for a tiiimmmeee with Christian Sex Therapist, Angela Griffith. She teaches women and couples how to break free from toxic purity culture with a twist of humor &amp; a hint of God! Hang onto your wigs and side-eyes as Andrea and SJR take us on an educational journey towards becoming MORE radical—in our bodies, in that marriage, and dare W.</description></item><item><title>A Harmonious Life w/ Tatianna Merritt | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550019/</guid><description>Podcast Description W.E. could either hope for a well-balanced life or truly achieve one! Here to share with our listeners how to maintain harmony is guest co-host Tatianna Merritt. As a wife, mom of four, content creator, and influencer, she tells of the constant need to retreat and seek peace through Christ. Our girl SJR kept it real and said even the "good" things threaten to distract us from who W.</description></item><item><title>A Consistent Discipline w/ LeAnne Dlamini | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Born and raised in Johannesburg, South Africa, LeAnne Dlamini has been on a mission to connect with women from around the world. What started off as a campaign called "End Girl Hate" (EGH), grew into a way of thinking, connecting, and encouraging women and girls to rise above the boundaries we often create amongst ourselves. Tune in as SJR and LeAnne explore how consistency breeds discipline, why team expansion is vital, and what to do during moments of discouragement.</description></item><item><title>Trust Your Light w/ Courtney Sanders | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Look atcha…too busy focusing on your current circumstances that you overlook your future success—but that all stops now! SJR invited her girl Courtney Sanders on the podcast to coach our listeners toward not playing it small &amp; trusting their inner light! Our guest co-host is a digital entrepreneur, speaker, and influencer who puts a fresh spin on business and personal development. So, in this episode, Courtney explains how showing up for yourself IS the same as showing up for others.</description></item><item><title>Reclaim Your Shine w/ Tashara Parker | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550022/</guid><description>Podcast Description The shadows of your past can lead to a bright future, so expect to SHINE no matter what! This week SJR sat down with a boss babe who clearly understood the assignment! Our girl, Tashara Parker, is an Emmy award-winning journalist in Dallas, TX, the founder of a non-profit organization called “Loud Women Lead”, and a national advocate for the natural hair movement known as “The Bun Ministry”. Together they discussed why representation matters, how to navigate unchartered territory, serving the greater good, and family reconciliation.</description></item><item><title>Hope is Here w/ Pastor Sarah Jakes Roberts | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sis, know that when it looks like all hope is gone, a residual faith remains. If you didn't make it to The Hope Revival Tour or just want to re-live the experience, then this throwback episode is for you! While in Maryland, SJR’s past collided with the future she was destined for, and we all recognized that hope was available all along. Listen in on one of the most POWERFUL nights on tour and experience a new-fashioned revival like never before!</description></item><item><title>Trade and Travel w/ Teri Ijeoma | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550024/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Teri Ijeoma of @TradeAndTravel joins SJR to share her story of faith, which led to the teaching of her first students on how to trade and make over $50 Million with her course, "Trade and Travel". Teri covers the common misconceptions about what it takes to get started with investing and developing a knowledge of the financial markets.
Together they go deeper to discuss Teri’s journey from seminary into education as an Assistant Principal at an elementary school.</description></item><item><title>Reigniting the Middle w/ Brita DeBrest | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550025/</guid><description>Podcast Description They say it’s not how you start, it’s how you finish—but what about the middle? Here to empower us towards a path of consistency is Brita DeBrest, CEO of her wellness program TheJumpstartQueen.com! After failing to achieve a series of health goals, Brita explained to SJR how her taste changed as God created a hunger for the conditions of her soul. Sis, you don’t get the life you deserve, you get the life you decide.</description></item><item><title>The Ebbs and Flows of Passion w/ Tiffany Aliche | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550026/</guid><description>Podcast Description The truth about passion is…it changes over time. What sets you ablaze today could very much lose its momentum by tomorrow. And that’s okay, Sis! Here to walk us through the ebbs and flows of life is Tiffany “The Budgetnista” Aliche, an award-winning financial educator, New York Times best-selling author, and founder of the Live Richer Movement. Since losing her husband at the height of her career, Tiffany sits down with SJR to share her grief journey, shed light on Jerrell’s earthly impact, and tell what’s been fueling her lately.</description></item><item><title>Let Truth Be Your Motivation w/ Dr. Natasha Stewart-Gresham | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550027/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sis, do you feel like you’ve reached the end of your rope? Has a certain person, place, or thing rendered you hopeless? Well then, you’ve come to the right place! This week on the podcast, SJR got an expert on the line—Dr. Natasha Stewart-Gresham! As an inspirational speaker, adviser, and life coach, she shares her story of burnout to new beginnings. Sooo…what was her secret sauce for reigniting hope, you ask?</description></item><item><title>Defeating Self-Sabotage w/ Taylor Madu | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550028/</guid><description>Podcast Description This month on the podcast, prepare to R E I G N I T E a flame of hope! Guest co-host, Taylor Madu, provides good insight on how to fill the voids in our life. As a wife, mom, and co-pastor, she explained how to overcome self-defeating behaviors by getting out of our own way. In a breathtakingly beautiful testimony, Taylor revealed to SJR that nothing can separate her from the love of Jesus and W.</description></item><item><title>Our Flaws Exchanged w/ Monyetta Shaw-Carter | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550029/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550029/</guid><description>Podcast Description When was the last time you evaluated your worth, Sis? ‘Cause clearly, you’re PRICELESS! But insecurities have a way of trying to undermine our value. This week, SJR is joined by wife, author, philanthropist, and tv personality, Monyetta Shaw-Carter to normalize being flawed in exchange for hope, healing, and love! Remember, you can choose to acknowledge worth when others see flaws. This co-parenting guru is a class act on how to “Keep It Classy” in her self-help book and personalized planner for unstoppable moms and devoted dads—shop both at MonyettaShaw.</description></item><item><title>Having Tough Conversations w/ Nedra Tawwab | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550030/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550030/</guid><description>Podcast Description W.E. wanna know, are some things better left unsaid? The very thought of opening yourself to a discussion that brings about discomfort is likely to create emotional distress, Sis. That’s why SJR invited New York Times bestselling author, licensed therapist, and sought-after relationship expert Nedra Tawwab on the podcast this week! Whether you’re saying “hard” things or receiving “tough” criticism, accountability is key. Press PLAY to explore how to stop being so offended and just talk about it.</description></item><item><title>New Age Parenting Styles w/ Destini Davis | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550031/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Delegation, what’s that ONE place adults made you “stay in” as a child? Yep, you guessed it—a child’s place. Our girl SJR is clearly in her feelings box, so W.E. got Certified Parent Coach, Destini Davis, on the line to help a sister out! Being a soft place to land for the young people in our lives should be given priority. But don’t get it twisted, they can STILL get these boundaries!</description></item><item><title>Placing Our Hope in God w/ Kirsten Bennett | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550032/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Release the need for control, Sis. It was never yours to begin with. This week’s episode is a gentle reminder to take your hand off the situation and place your hope in God. Advising us how, is Kirsten Bennet, a believer, businesswoman, wife, mom, and advocate for youth and mental health! In openly sharing her life's journey of transitions, Kirsten reveals to SJR what she’s currently trusting God to break in her life and W.</description></item><item><title>The Sex Talk You Never Had w/ Dr. Jill Waggoner | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550033/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Where do W.E. even begin? It all started when SJR took a peek at Dr. Jill Waggoner’s bio. What was full of accolades, distinction, and honor resulted in an open conversation about sex as it relates to the mind, body, and spirit. That’s right! They laid it all out so that you, as a woman, and the teen girls in your life, walk away well-informed and empowered. This episode proves that sex is a covenant, sexuality is not for us to judge, and gender shouldn’t make anyone unlovable.</description></item><item><title>Bigger, Better, and Bolder w/ Jennifer Cohen | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550034/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sis, would you rather walk around with rejection or regret? Here to help us answer this question is best-selling author, international speaker, podcaster, and entrepreneur Jennifer Cohen! She and SJR are urging the girls to take up space and be B O L D! Sure, rejection may hurt for a moment, but regret lasts a lifetime. Therefore, go after the life you want! Today’s episode is about harnessing a skillset to compete with your self-sabotage, self-rejection, and self-doubt—all of which be so quick to count you out of the fight before even steppin’ into the ring.</description></item><item><title>Reigning While Waiting w/ Myleik Teele | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550035/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550035/</guid><description>Podcast Description W.E. wanna challenge you to rethink your “waiting season” as a “sacred pause”. Real talk, Sis! Didn't it feel safer and softer to lean into the idea of a sacred pause? If so, peek into the current reality of boss babe Myleik Teele! In her sit-down with SJR, she speaks on a new way of being that’s rooted in motherhood, abundance, rest, and minding her business—W.E. know that’s right!</description></item><item><title>The Crown Connected to the Man w/ J. Bolin | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550036/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chile, W.E. are well versed in applying pressure. ‘Cause the enemy and all his schemes can get it! But what happens when life succeeds at knocking us to the ground? Is it possible to thrive under such pressure? AND IS—so, chin up, chest out, and crown on! This week, SJR linked up with celebrity fashion stylist, creative director, and entrepreneur J. Bolin, who revealed how to reign while reinventing himself one power move at a time!</description></item><item><title>Reparent Your Perfectionism w/ Tykeia Robinson | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550037/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550037/</guid><description>Podcast Description TRUST…after today’s episode, you’ll want to nurture your relationships with conviction instead of consequence. Here to discuss the idea of reigning over our past is Dr. Tykeia Robinson! She and SJR went down memory lane to trace how their younger selves sought acceptance. And Sis, W.E. all can relate! It would take adulthood, a healthy relationship with God, and therapy for Dr. Tykeia to begin healing from the pain of rejection.</description></item><item><title>Just Keep Going w/ Erica Campbell | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550038/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550038/</guid><description>Podcast Description What to do when you’re starting from the ground up? That’s the question this episode answers. This week let’s wrap up our #ThrowbackPajamaInterviews with a woman of resiliency—the faith-filled Erica Campbell! Sis, we’re no strangers to the role she played in the Kingdom invading our culture. Erica tells SJR how the desire to win souls &amp; serve Jesus would at times leave her with a residual faith, but even then, she pressed towards the mark.</description></item><item><title>Legacy of Authenticity w/ Stephanie Ike | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Would you consider yourself an emotional person? ‘Cause this week Pastor Stephanie Ike has us all journeying towards vulnerability. Yep, W.E. are going there—but in a candid, yet comical kind of way! SJR and Stepanie discuss childhood memories, cultivating trusted spaces, looking back on God’s providence, and so much MORE! Sis, in life you must learn to coach yourself through tough moments instead of shutting down. That way, when you look back over the years, they’ll be a reflection of who God called you to be.</description></item><item><title>Digging Deeper to Find Your Why w/ Olori Swank | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tap in as W.E. throw it back to some candid conversations between SJR and her friends! First, we’re choppin’ it up with fashion stylist, author, and entrepreneur Olori Swank! She tells how her career path took an unexpected turn for the BETTER. That’s right! At times we’re called in a different direction than W.E. prepared for, so knowing your “why” is key. Sis, what makes you bloom and feel alive?</description></item><item><title>Growing in Confidence w/ Sarah Jakes Roberts and Touré Roberts | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550041/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550041/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week W.E. are bringing you a sneak peek episode of Date Night—a Woman Evolve TV series featuring our girl SJR, her hubby PT, and special guests! The single people wanna know, does wholeness stem from self-discovery or by way of Netflix and chill? Shanice Peeples and Reign B. give their take on what today’s dating scene is like. The gag is…our relationship with God grows a confidence that marriage cannot.</description></item><item><title>Lessons in Imperfection w/ Jade Verette | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550042/</guid><description>Podcast Description What if the lessons in imperfection were meant to teach you softness? W.E. tough Sis, but our “Soft Girl Era” is awaiting! This week SJR is choppin’ it up with the homie Jade Verette, a wife, mom, podcast personality, chef, &amp; master mixologist out of Brooklyn, NY. Together they explain the benefits of letting our walls down to receive hope—hope in our relationships, hope for the journey, &amp; hope as a gift from God!</description></item><item><title>Second Chance Grace w/ LaToya Ferguson | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chile, ain’t nothing “regular” about our co-host in today’s episode! LaToya Ferguson is a woman of grace who has relentlessly pursued her future with hope and intentionality. She shared with SJR that losing her mom as an adolescent and not knowing her dad until adulthood proved every day of her life to be a second chance! Sis, did you know that going back to acknowledge a memory or experience can allow you to access healing?</description></item><item><title>Learning to Love Vulnerability w/ Amber Polk | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550044/</guid><description>Podcast Description If loving vulnerability is wrong, then W.E. don’t wanna be right! Our listeners are in for a treat this week as the homie Amber Polk stands flat-footed in her testimony. She joined SJR to discuss how the world’s standards will rob us from the freedom of FULL self-expression every time. Just think about it—how often do W.E. shrink in the presence of others? Amber said she didn’t find herself until she placed herself in environments that produced authenticity &amp; Sis, W.</description></item><item><title>Love Your Life w/ Pastor Sarah Jakes Roberts | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550045/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Love is in the air! But before cupid gets to shuffling, might W.E. interest you in an uplifting message from the Love Your Life Women’s Conference at Lakewood Church? It’s a homegirl moment in the sanctuary you didn’t know you needed! Sis, suffering will teach you lessons that blessings cannot. So, instead of waiting for a perfect life to love…just #TryJesus! And trust, we’re not overlooking the fact that you barely survived ‘the school of hard knocks’—we’ve been there.</description></item><item><title>Hope for a New Perspective of Possibilities w/ Tiara Brown | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550046/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550046/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s co-host is a boss babe straight outta the Delegation! Our girl Tiara Brown is an accountant whose mission is to develop financially literate communities. During this episode, SJR found out that Sis is in her bag, but she's in His Word too! Tiara tells of looking at isolation differently, increasing her visibility in the workplace, redefining self-worth, and launching a business. If you’re in need of a convo to provoke the power of abundant thinking, then look no further!</description></item><item><title>Introducing THE CALLED Podcast | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550047/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Please visit https://lnk.to/thecalledpodcast and subscribe!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hope for a New Level of Self-Awareness w/ Kelly Rowland | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550048/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sis, W.E. on a new level! While many long for momentum to start the year off strong, W.E. hope for an awareness to sustain it. Teaching the girls how to become more self-aware is Grammy award-winning singer, songwriter, actress, and executive producer Kelly Rowland! Yaaasss, this episode has us fangirling &amp; colliding with destiny…chiiillleee! She &amp; SJR were honest about what it takes to show up in marriage, in motherhood, in their careers, and for themselves.</description></item><item><title>Hope for New Connections w/ Andrea Merkl | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550049/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tell a friend, to tell a friend…she’s baaaccckkk! SJR is kickin’ things off with Andrea Merkl, an upcoming author, creative consultant, conscious leader, and exceptional mother. Off grip, our co-host had some explaining to do and Sis did just THAT! As someone navigating life after infidelity and divorce, Andrea offers us hope for NEW connections. In this noteworthy episode, W.E. talkin’ forgiveness, self-abandonment, childhood reckoning, compassion, &amp; so much MORE!</description></item><item><title>Becoming a Partner w/ Pastor Sarah Jakes Roberts | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550050/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550050/</guid><description>Podcast Description W.E. are closing out our #ThrowbackSermonSeries with a bible study message from bestie! And listen, God showed our girl something worth sharing. So, grab your bibles &amp; get into it! SJR explained why you won’t find the right answer if you’re asking the wrong question. Bet, sooo…what exactly should W.E. be asking God? Chile, you know the drill—plug in to find out! In other news Sis, God is NOT your enemy.</description></item><item><title>Wet Wood Still Burns w/ Pastor Sarah Jakes Roberts | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550051/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550051/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a NEW year, SAME God kinda vibe! And Delegation, W.E. couldn’t have made it without your support. In 2023, we’re coming in hot with a flame of hope! So, let’s run it back to a fiery lesson our girl SJR taught at The Potter’s House of Dallas. W.E. wanna know, who’s all been rained on by the storms of life? To the point you forgot what it looks like to be on fire for God?</description></item><item><title>Not for Long w/ Pastor Sarah Jakes Roberts | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550052/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Saints, how y’all feel? Delegation, y’all alright? As W.E. wrap up this year, the bestie SJR wants you to know that the isolation you’re feeling is only temporary. ‘Cause Sis, W.E. coming for you! Clearly, the enemy is B I G mad that you’ve experienced the power of God. So now…there’s a target on your back. But it won’t be long until your bruised heel crushes the serpent’s head!</description></item><item><title>Break the Flow w/ Pastor Sarah Jakes Roberts | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550053/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550053/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re a movement by ourselves, but we’re a force when we’re together—God makes us better! Let’s plug into this prophetic message from our girl SJR at the International Leadership Summit 2018. It’s giving double portion anointing &amp; W.E. want all the scoop! From where to strike our mantle, to how to break the flow. Somebody’s gonna mess around &amp; receive a WORD! Quick question: who minds being pulled on by man in order to be pulled up by God?</description></item><item><title>Worth the Wait w/ Pastor Sarah Jakes Roberts | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550054/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anything worth having is worth waiting for! But chiiillleee, guess Who’s side-eyeing the Saints? In this week's sermon series, SJR declares that God has been waiting long enough…for you, Sis! Perhaps you’ve lost your taste for Him. But NOW is the time to turn that frustration into glory—speak up, adjust your crown, &amp; dream big! The Father highkey desires a relationship with you. So, gone get into alignment with who He says you are!</description></item><item><title>Buried Alive w/ Pastor Sarah Jakes Roberts | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550055/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Whew chile, what a year! How ‘bout W.E. reflect on God’s faithfulness? All month long, join us as W.E. revisit sermons that are powerful and relevant to the times. First up, W.E. are throwin’ it back to a groundbreaking moment from Woman Evolve Conference 2021! The Delegation went H.A.M. for the homie Halimah &amp; liiisssteeen...tear ducts on weak! Then, things got even more real. See, what had happened was…like the Prophet Ezekiel, our bestie SJR began to prophesy over dry bones.</description></item><item><title>Placement of Your Faith w/ Natalie Manuel Lee | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550056/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550056/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s the cross for W.E.! So, what better way to flex for the Kingdom than with the homie Natalie Manuel Lee? Off grip, she accredits her parents for planting a seed of faith. Now look at God…multiplying it &amp; making room for our girl as a producer &amp; host of purpose-driven tv! Sis, do you see yourself as a prodigal daughter or a purpose-filled baddie? Either way, you’re welcome here.</description></item><item><title>Placement of Your Work w/ Ashley Blaine Featherson-Jenkins | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550057/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wobble baby, Gobble baby, Wobble baby, Gobble! Two-step with us this Thanksgiving week as SJR chops it up with Ashley Blaine Featherson-Jenkins. As a Black woman actress and producer in Hollywood, our girl unapologetically places her career in God's hands! ‘Cause what better way to jig to “werk, wurk, don’t stop” if He ain’t jiggin’? Ashley let us in on the journey of actualizing her goals. And the bestie SJR proves that she can be a work in progress while reclaiming her destiny—W.</description></item><item><title>Placement of Your Knowledge w/ Yasmine Cheyenne | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550058/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Don’t call it a podcast, call it an invitation! In this episode, W.E. are inviting listeners to mind their business—Delegation, y’all know how W.E. do—and be curious about what’s happening on the inside. This week SJR teamed up with self-healing educator, author, speaker, and mental wellness advocate, Yasmine Cheyenne! Together they tackle the hot topics of success, healing, empathy, and so much MORE! Sis, healing work is hard work &amp; everybody ain’t bout it, bout it.</description></item><item><title>Wings of Forgiveness w/ Layla Ellaisy | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550059/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Did you know that wielding unforgiveness as a weapon reveals to God that W.E. don’t trust Him to protect us? Liiisteeen…if you can’t say amen, say ouch! This week on the podcast, SJR linked up with the thought-provoking Layla Ellaisy to discuss healing and intimacy with God. You see, Delegation, W.E. gotta do the hard work that goes into living a soft life. Our guest co-host shares her journey of suffering in silence and seeking validation in all the wrong places.</description></item><item><title>Nurturing Your Body w/ Amanda Samuels | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550060/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550060/</guid><description>Podcast Description The category is BODY! That’s right. We’re talkin’ fearfully &amp; wonderfully made! Just ask the homie Amanda Samuels who’s out here revolutionizing her health. Now, who all believe that the way W.E. care for our bodies impacts our relationship with God? W.E. do and the Holy Spirit co-signs! SJR tells of a dissonance experienced when feeling betrayed by the body. And chile, where is the lie? If we’re honest, W.</description></item><item><title>A Father’s Affirmation w/ Bishop T.D. Jakes | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550061/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Back like W.E. never left, here’s the convo you’ve all been waiting for! WTAL Grand Finale—the end of an era or the start of an evolution? Chile, let’s just say one man’s “don’t drop the mic” is another woman’s “turn me up in the microphone”! This week W.E. are thrilled &amp; honored to be kickin’ it with the G.O.A.T. of women’s empowerment, Bishop T.D. Jakes! As a watchman on the wall, he affirms his children and the generation to come in their ability to steward legacy.</description></item><item><title>The Unraveling of a Generational Curse w/ Teya Roberts and Tiffany Mensah | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550062/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Whew chile, wait a minute! Did y’all peep the jaw-dropping trailer of “Angelina”? That NEW Woman Evolve series featuring an intimate view on domestic violence—it’s giving…generational trauma didn’t start with you, but it ENDS with you! With a premiere date of 10/6, SJR sat down with writer and director, Teya Roberts, plus advocate and executive director of the DOVES Network, Tiffany Mensah! This trio is not only raising awareness in faith spaces but making a tangible impact for survivors and witnesses of family violence.</description></item><item><title>Presence of Hope w/ April Daniels | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550063/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Holding onto hope in hard times is a revolutionary act! Just ask our girl April Daniels who, when faced with the devastating loss of her husband, REFUSED to lose faith in God. Sooo…When did resiliency kick in? How did her pep talks with God go? And what should you do when your flesh tries to buck the spirit? Sis, press PLAY for all the deets! April told SJR that she traded her anger for questions and found hope in the promises of God.</description></item><item><title>Presence of Access w/ Shannon Brown | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550064/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Access denied, say what? Sis, throw the WHOLE lie away! As a King’s kid, you’ve been granted exclusive access—not to mention W.E got first dibs on heaven’s resources. And that lil’ detour you’re dealing with is NOT denial! Matter fact, our guest co-host Shannon Brown, a philanthropist for communities of color, might say “been there, done that, TRUST God”! She tells SJR of the permission &amp; possibilities that listeners gain access to once coming into full agreement with God.</description></item><item><title>Presence of Persecution w/ LeToya Luckett | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550065/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chile, leave it to LeToya Luckett to gather the girls while keepin’ it all the way TRILL! As a singer and actress who grew up in the public eye, Sis was exposed to criticism early on. In this episode, She &amp; SJR chopped it up about the insecurities that come from using their gifts. So, if that’s your testimony, tap-tap-tap-in! But one thing for certain &amp; two things for sure, when it comes to a life that pleases God…the Delegation gone step in the face of persecution EVERYTIME—‘cause W.</description></item><item><title>Presence of Restrictions w/ Nona Jones | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550066/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550066/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s something to be said about a woman that restricts her focus on the Lord. Ya know? Drinking her water &amp; minding her business—real bad! This week catch SJR ‘killing comparison’ with author, preacher, &amp; business leader Nona Jones. Our co-host described herself in five words and it gave TOP TIER favor! As a trauma survivor, Nona shares how a fractured identity from early childhood misguided her definition of success.</description></item><item><title>Fire to Trust Jesus w/ Naomi Raine | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550067/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our guest co-host is bringing the heat &amp; W.E. talkin’ fresh, fresh FIRE! Straight outta Maverick City Music &amp; off the Kingdom Tour is prophetic worship leader Naomi Raine! Yaaasss chile, the QUEEN of snatching eyelashes &amp; slaying us in the Spirit! Sis ain’t new to this, she true to this. So, it was only right for Naomi to roll up on SJR and ignite listeners' faith in trusting Jesus.</description></item><item><title>Fire to Work with Crumbs w/ Dr. Pam Ross | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550068/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chile, W.E. love breaking bread with the Delegation! But besides the Canaanite woman, who’s truly measured the weight of glory in a single crumb? Shifting our perspective to strategize with even the smallest of things, is inspirational activist, author, and development coach Dr. Pam Ross. She &amp; SJR testified that God WILL take your crumbs, put them to the fire, and spark a miracle! Yep, if He did it with dirt for Adam, He sho’nuff can do it for the girls!</description></item><item><title>Fire to Stay in the Fight w/ Adrienne Bailon-Houghton | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550069/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yeah W.E. knuckin' and buckin' and ready to fight! You see, our toxic trait is…ANYBODY can get it. But Sis, shouldn't God’s promises fuel the fight? Keepin’ it all the way real is singer, actress, host, &amp; NEW mom Adrienne Bailon-Houghton! She &amp; SJR sparked up a convo on the revolutionary fire to stay in the fight. And Delegation, it's giving the FULL armor of God! Be it flame or ember, you gotta roll with the punches while pursuing the desires of your heart.</description></item><item><title>Fire to Advocate w/ Rev. Alisha Gordon | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550070/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Quick, get Alicia on the keys—'cause THIS girl is on fiyaaa! Our guest co-host, Rev. Alisha Gordon, is out here doing the Lord’s work &amp; it’s LIT! As the founder and Executive Director of TheCurrentProject.org, Sis connects programming and policy to close the social and economic gap for Black single mothers. She &amp; SJR talk pulpits &amp; politics, their lived experiences as single moms in the church, taking on the Goliath of systemic inequalities, plus a life reimagined!</description></item><item><title>Fire to Burn Barriers w/ Joval Webbe | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550071/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 16:33:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last month on the podcast, there was a Master reset! Now, let’s bring the heat with a revolutionary FIRE—God, if the Saints having a Hot Girl Summer just say THAT. As a health strategist, Joval Webbe is co-hosting with SJR and teaching us how to take the limits off our ability to live well. Together they discuss tips on burning down barriers, setting fire to who W.E. once were, &amp; relationships goin’ up in smoke.</description></item><item><title>Reset Your Fears w/ Miss Diddy | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550072/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 13:00:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Liiisteeen, this episode is giving run up, get done up! ‘Cause W.E. woke up and chose violence—against the spirit of fear on today! Like forreal Sis, what you’re afraid of may not even exist. Our girl SJR &amp; boss babe, Miss Diddy, are putting us on game! From how to look at fear…To taking inventory of those worries that never came to pass. Chile, the enemy better count its days playing on our top.</description></item><item><title>Reset Your Values w/ Kourtney Mason | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550073/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chile, yesterday's price is NOT today's price! W.E. are added value in these streets, with a WORTH ethic to prove it. Helping the Delegation instill core values and find fulfillment is SJR’s best friend &amp; corporate baddie, Kourtney Mason! Talk about a revolutionary reset—these two chopped it up about a love language evolved, replacing criticism with compassion, setting boundaries, &amp; so much MORE! Sis, God did His thang when He created you!</description></item><item><title>Reset Your Priorities w/ Stevi Carter | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550074/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sis, set your priorities straight, so W.E. can watch you pop awf! Teaching us how to rearrange a thing or two, is newlywed &amp; first-time mom Stevi Carter. Her main concern is living in a state of gratitude &amp; chile W.E. felt that for somebody! When was the last time you slowed down and prioritized what truly mattered? Ya know…vibin’ with the fam, figuring out those friendships, or building a legacy.</description></item><item><title>Reset Your Esteem w/ Cadedra Burks | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550075/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ladies, W.E. are halfway through the year &amp; hitting the RESET button! ‘Cause why not? Fresh perspective ain’t never hurt nobody. Empowering listeners to rekindle a respect from within, is self-care coach Cadedra Burks! She &amp; SJR unpacked the highs and lows of self-esteem, that ole petty inner voice, along with how to rebuild confidence. Sis, they think you actin’ brand new—whole time, you just protecting the work that God has done in you.</description></item><item><title>Longevity in Sisterhood w/ B. Simone and Megan Brooks | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550076/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550076/</guid><description>Podcast Description When it comes to sisterhood, just know—the Delegation ain’t new to this, W.E. true to this! So, when God slides a bestie in your life who’s ready to square up for the revolution…tag team &amp; OVERTHROW with her! This week, SJR explores the long-standing friendship between comedienne, actress, and boss babe B. Simone and her business partner, Megan Brooks. Their relationship is proof that in our sameness W.E connect, but in our differences W.</description></item><item><title>Cultivating Sisterhood w/ Kyndal Banks | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550077/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550077/</guid><description>Podcast Description How 'bout W.E. rebuke the spirit of no new friends? Real talk, Sis! The enemy will finesse you into a season of loneliness or toxicity—whole time, you were created for community! Here to tell SJR about finding a tribe of sister-friends, is the Delegation's very own AND creator of Solo2Soul Sisters, Kyndal Banks! This episode is a testament to the power established in coming together &amp; declaring NO WOMAN LEFT BEHIND!</description></item><item><title>Faithfulness of Sisterhood w/ Brelyn Bowman and Brittney Borders | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550078/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Be it praying hands or throwing hands, the Delegation gone step! 'Cause like the homies Mary &amp; Elizabeth, W.E. are our sister's keeper. Kick it with SJR, Brelyn Bowman, and Brittney Borders this week for homegirl-time in the sanctuary! After cuttin' up &amp; kee-keein’, an intimate conversation unfolds. Brelyn &amp; Brittney explained how trusting &amp; protecting one another’s faith REVOLUTIONIZED their sibling relationship. Plus, this episode DID what needed to be done for “the strong one”!</description></item><item><title>Seasons of Sisterhood w/ Tommye and Yvette Williams | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550079/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Speaking of #SisterGoals, our guest co-hosts have been in the game for a long time. They're giving ride or die, Ruth &amp; Naomi, 'till the wheels fall off—ENERGY! Straight outta PT's village, W.E. received the love and loyalty that is Tommye and Yvette Williams! The sister-duo sit down with SJR to reflect on their sibling relationship over the years. Whether miles apart, transitioning into a new role, or going through a rough season, trust in God kept them connected by heart.</description></item><item><title>Delicacy of Sisterhood w/ Lori Roberts | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550080/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sis, ain’t no hood like the one W.E. got! All month long, the Delegation is invited to embrace sisterhood in a REVOLUTIONARY way. Ever wondered what happens when women set aside their differences for the greater good? Chile, a bona fide miracle! Read up on the homies Rachel &amp; Leah. Then check out this week’s episode as SJR &amp; Lori Roberts spill the tea on their relationship dynamic. Yep, W.</description></item><item><title>Capacity for Disappointment w/ Marissa Craft | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550081/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Aht, Aht! Disappointment can't be living rent-free in your head Sis. Matter fact, turn SJR &amp; Marissa Craft up in the microphone as they school us on turning our L’s into lessons! Yes, the situation let you down &amp; at times you sense defeat—W.E. validate all that. But girl, you STILL have access! Plot twist: your disappointment and trust in God CAN live in the same place. The bestie SJR opened up about a recent experience where the enemy tried it, but self-compassion had the final say.</description></item><item><title>Capacity for Stress w/ Dr. Thema Bryant | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550082/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chiiillleee, the Saints say W.E. are too blessed to be stressed &amp; too anointed to be disappointed, but the devil is a LIE! This week SJR is joined by Dr. Thema Bryant, an ordained minister, clinical psychologist, author, AND president-elect of the American Psychological Association—yaaasss, put some respect on her name! Together they explore our stress capacity, the need of a sacred pause, intergenerational trauma, &amp; so much MORE!</description></item><item><title>Capacity for Judgment w/ Jay Barnett | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550083/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550083/</guid><description>Podcast Description The doors of the podcast are open &amp; W.E. welcome you to leave your side-eyes at the altar. Here to destigmatize mental health and normalize therapy is author, speaker, &amp; licensed therapist Jay Barnett. Liiisssten, this brotha’s story of emotional invalidation, holistic healing, and spiritual reconciliation is fiya! What W.E. not gone do is…suffer in silence at the fear of being judged. ‘Cause people who live in glass houses shouldn’t cast the first stone…or whatever Jesus said.</description></item><item><title>Strategy of Discernment w/ Milan Harris | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550084/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550084/</guid><description>Podcast Description When it came to making her dreams a reality, Milan Harris understood the assignment! Sooo, what God-given strategy did she dabble in to become the founder &amp; CEO of a luxury streetwear brand? Chiiillleee, the gift of discernment! You see…knowing every role in the business is one thing but being sensitive to divine instruction—bing bong! As a faith &amp; fashion trendsetter, Milan shares with SJR &amp; the Delegation her process of bringing ideas to fruition.</description></item><item><title>Strategy of Favor w/ Touré Roberts | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550085/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550085/</guid><description>Podcast Description The bestie SJR teamed up with her boo thang for this one &amp; W.E. luv to see it! Let’s make some noise for author, entrepreneur, producer, and pastor Touré Roberts! Chile, who knew B A L A N C E was a revolutionary strategy for favor? Plug into this episode as SJR &amp; PT unpack the life of ‘just enough’, the pace of purpose, and the signs of burnout.</description></item><item><title>Strategy of Resources w/ Arian Simone | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550086/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550086/</guid><description>Podcast Description W.E. sayin’ it loud from the church pews to the parking lot—HE ALWAYS PROVIDES! Chile, if that’s your testimony…give Him praise &amp; gone press PLAY. Teaching listeners how to manage their resources with strategy is CEO &amp; co-founder of the Fearless.Fund, our homie Arian Simone! She &amp; SJR discussed finances, human resources, &amp; taking risks...while Eve mentioned a thing or two ‘bout heaux tales. Sis, you serve THEE God who is more than enough!</description></item><item><title>Strategy of Information w/ Caline Newton | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550087/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last month on the podcast, a bunch of baddies reclaimed their power! Now W.E. finna strut into April with a revolutionary strategy! And leading the way is our girl Caline Newton, a certified financial educator &amp; personal finance strategist. Sis, if the math ain’t mathin’ in yo life, TUNE IN for all the deets! SJR &amp; Caline are droppin’ gems about cryptocurrency, financial literacy in relationships, gender equity, entrepreneurship, tithing, &amp; so much MORE!</description></item><item><title>The Revolutionary Power of Authenticity w/ Alexis Skyy | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550088/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550088/</guid><description>Podcast Description W.E. dunno who needs to hear this but…live your ugly truth in a BEAUTIFUL way! Our co-host Alexis Skyy is doing just THAT by stepping away from the social media reputation &amp; into her authentic self. Keepin' it a buck with the Delegation, she shares of falling prey to human trafficking, toxic relationships, &amp; depression. SJR says that your story shouldn’t begin where the pain invaded your soul &amp; whew chile, wait a minute!</description></item><item><title>The Revolutionary Power of History w/ Blessin Giraldo | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550089/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550089/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, SJR is choppin’ it up with Blessin Giraldo, founder of an award-winning step team, actress, &amp; model. Supported by a tribe of women to help reach her full potential, Blessin spills the tea on how to achieve success despite your background. The two discussed powerful lessons of their past, how W.E. get it from our mammas, &amp; passing on generational blessings! Our girl SJR says to R E F U S E the belief that you can't hang in the places where you're called &amp; Sis, W.</description></item><item><title>The Revolutionary Power of Words w/ Sylvia Lloyd | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550090/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550090/</guid><description>Podcast Description You get a Hail Mary! You get a Hail Mary! EVERYBODY gets a Hail Mary! Delegation, join us as W.E. salute everyday women—especially the millions holdin’ it down from the frontlines of this pandemic. This week SJR connects with essential worker Sylvia Lloyd, LMSW who shared her journey &amp; commitment to the helping profession. It would be the words she seldom heard as a child yet laid hold of in adulthood that empowered Sylvia to fulfill her destiny!</description></item><item><title>The Revolutionary Power in Conflict w/ Candice Benbow | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550091/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chiiillleee, this episode is “for church girls who’ve considered tithing to the beauty supply store when Sunday morning isn't enough.” That’s right, Saints—W.E. see your side-eyes &amp; raise you a neck roll…’cause IYKYK! Theologian, essayist, public educator, and author Candice Benbow is co-hosting with SJR &amp; is highkey a force to be reckoned with! She tells of harnessing her power even after internalizing church hurt, losing her mother, and experiencing sexual trauma.</description></item><item><title>The Revolutionary Power in Purpose w/ Khadeen Ellis | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550092/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Women’s History Month to our homegirls! Yaaasss, W.E. finna jigg to 'I'm Every Woman' ALL March long! But hollup…who y’all got—Chaka, Whitney, or boffum? Here to help us take our power back is actress, tv host, youtuber, &amp; podcaster Khadeen Ellis! Sis is kickin’ it with SJR as an authentic representation of what it looks like to be purposeful as a wife, mother, and career woman. TUNE IN &amp; find out how Khadeen is shaping HERstory!</description></item><item><title>Wrong Lanes Have Right Turns w/ Michael Phillips | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550093/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550093/</guid><description>Podcast Description W.E. know the brothas ain't tryna toot their own horn, but...their perspective has been what the girls NEEDED! This week in the driver's seat is author, education advocate, and pastor, Michael Phillips—better known as Dr. Anita's husbae! He pulled up on SJR, explaining how to partner and have dominion, where we anchor our pain, &amp; why men emotional tanks be on E. Life's tension &amp; trauma would land Pastor Michael in the wrong lane.</description></item><item><title>Treasure Hunting w/ Roosevelt Stewart | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550094/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Since the Delegation feelin' these co-ed vibes, let's dive into a convo with worship leader &amp; pastor, Roosevelt Stewart! Straight off the bat, he curbs toxic masculinity &amp; leans boldly into transparency. Our girl SJR posed the question—what can women do to cultivate a safe space that unlocks a man’s heart? That’s right Sis, W.E. got dem keys, keys, keys! And for the future feyoncés who wanna know…if he like it will he REALLY put a ring on it?</description></item><item><title>Table Talk w/ Anthony O’Neal | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550095/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chiiillleee, ISSA special edition podcast series featuring the fellas! The first to pull up a chair &amp; cop a seat at the table is national best-selling author, motivational speaker, financial expert, and podcast host Anthony O’Neal! This week W.E. talkin’ preconceived roles for women (tuh), the depth of a power couple, Black men’s mental health, &amp; so much MORE! Bruh, will you support what God has created her to do?</description></item><item><title>Birthing Purpose w/ Iceis Elliott | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550096/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550096/</guid><description>Podcast Description The bestie SJR, co-host Iceis Elliott, &amp; our homegirl Eve were rollin’ deep on the podcast! But why they started reminiscing on their ratchet days? That was until God said, "act up, you can get snatched up”. This episode talks about motherhood, blended families, and co-parenting revelations. Iceis shares her dream for the future, which proves to be full of purpose! Imagine being pregnant with the possibility of God’s future.</description></item><item><title>Revolutionary You w/ Christina Edwards | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550097/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550097/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the FIRST to ever do it as a college graduate &amp; business owner in her fam, Christina Edwards proves that the revolution will be publicized! TUNE IN as she shares her growth journey &amp; aspires to take you to the next level! From throwing hands to laying hands, when was the last time you decided to back down from a fight? Aht, Aht! Don't be feelin' froggy, Eve, 'cause SJR &amp; Christina explain why every fight is not assigned to your God-given identity.</description></item><item><title>Shoot Your Shot w/ Mya Douglas | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Audacity is at an all-time high &amp; the Saints are here for it! Guest co-host, Mya Douglas, is believing God for her kingdom husband, Youth Anthem Conference 2022, &amp; NEW romance novel! Plus, find out what the bestie SJR is doing this year to target the lingering impacts of trauma. Sis, the idea that your healing is connected to another woman's breakthrough may feel completely out of bounds. But lean in &amp; learn how to pivot!</description></item><item><title>For Realness Sake w/ Kieara Pittman | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550099/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chile, W.E. are bizzack! This week SJR is hangin' with therapist, podcaster, and veteran Kieara Pittman. Our good Sis stood ten toes down in her truth! But keep it a hunnid, haven't you been in rooms where you chose to become someone else—all to avoid rejection? Kieara explains how the path of self-acceptance led to an encounter with purpose &amp; it's giving Hail Mary vibes! The two discuss lookin' like ya husband’s homeboy, imaginary heaux tales, emotional boundaries, &amp; so much MORE!</description></item><item><title>Faith to Finish w/ Marissa Layton | Woman Evolve with Sarah Jakes Roberts</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9138550100/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9138550100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sis, if 2021 tested your gangsta, then 2022 finna catch a fade! Boss up as W.E. strut into this revolutionary year with SJR &amp; global business manager Dr. Marissa Layton by our side! Instead of focusing on the things she can’t control, Marissa has set her sights on a self-compassion rooted in self-care &amp; blank space. Before W.E. knew it, SJR whipped up a snack on scarcity mindsets that blew our wigs back!</description></item></channel></rss>