<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Witnessed: Fade to Black on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/witnessed-fade-to-black/</link><description>Recent content in Witnessed: Fade to Black on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 06:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/witnessed-fade-to-black/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fade to Black | 7. Single White Chase Brandon | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660044/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the late 1990s, the CIA introduced its first Hollywood Liaison Office, a former clandestine services officer named Chase Brandon. Could Gary’s relationship with the Agency, and its Hollywood office, have played a role in his disappearance?
Unlock all episodes of Witnessed: Fade to Black, ad-free, right now by subscribing to The Binge. Plus, get binge access to brand new stories dropping on the first of every month — that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.</description></item><item><title>Investigating the Satanic Panic on ‘Infamous’ | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660043/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Listen to Infamous HERE. For Kelly Michaels, all of history is a Tolkien-like battle between a small number of heroes and villains. Most of us are just hobbits — the in-between folks, just trying to get by. Kelly, who’s getting by working at Wee Care Nursery School in Maplewood, New Jersey, considers herself an ordinary hobbit. That is, until she — like Frodo — gets swept up in a battle, as panic sweeps nation over a surge in Satanism.</description></item><item><title>Fade to Black | 6. Never Ending Story | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660042/</guid><description>Podcast Description How did the disappearance of Gary Devore take such a conspiratorial turn on the internet? And where did these alternative theories originate? Discover how memory and trauma color the truth behind the story and disappearance.
Unlock all episodes of Witnessed: Fade to Black, ad-free, right now by subscribing to The Binge. Plus, get binge access to brand new stories dropping on the first of every month — that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.</description></item><item><title>Fade to Black I 5. Death Is The Most That Can Happen | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660041/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660041/</guid><description>Podcast Description As authorities close their case on Gary Devore, Wendy is plagued by unanswered questions: Why are Gary’s hands missing from his corpse? Is this really his body? Or was this all staged to quiet Wendy and the case?
Unlock all episodes of Witnessed: Fade to Black, ad-free, right now by subscribing to The Binge. Plus, get binge access to brand new stories dropping on the first of every month — that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.</description></item><item><title>Fade to Black I 4. Show Me A Body | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660040/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a year-long disappearance with no leads, Gary’s SUV and skeletonized corpse are discovered in a California aqueduct.
Unlock all episodes of Witnessed: Fade to Black, ad-free, right now by subscribing to The Binge. Plus, get binge access to brand new stories dropping on the first of every month — that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free. Just click ‘Subscribe’ on the top of the Witnessed show page on Apple Podcasts or visit GetTheBinge.</description></item><item><title>Fade to Black I 3. Panama! | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660039/</guid><description>Podcast Description We delve into the script Gary was writing when he disappeared—The Big Steal—set during the US invasion of Panama. What can this script tell us about Gary’s connection to the CIA? And could it be the key to his baffling disappearance?
Unlock all episodes of Witnessed: Fade to Black, ad-free, right now by subscribing to The Binge. Plus, get binge access to brand new stories dropping on the first of every month — that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.</description></item><item><title>Fade to Black I 2. Crocodile Tears | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660001/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a visit from a CIA officer claiming to be Gary’s friend, Wendy starts to wonder: Who was Gary Devore and could he have been leading a double life? The search continues as friends, family, and even Hollywood action stars form their own search party.
Unlock all episodes of Witnessed: Fade to Black, ad-free, right now by subscribing to The Binge. Plus, get binge access to brand new stories dropping on the first of every month — that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.</description></item><item><title>Fade to Black | 1. Pumping Pure Adrenaline | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660002/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the way home from a writing trip in New Mexico, screenwriter Gary Devore disappears in the California desert. After a mysterious last call home, in which he tells his wife Wendy that he’s “pumping pure adrenaline” - she begins to suspect foul play.
Unlock all episodes of Witnessed: Fade to Black, ad-free, right now by subscribing to The Binge. Plus, get binge access to brand new stories dropping on the first of every month — that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.</description></item><item><title>Introducing... Witnessed: Fade to Black | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660003/</guid><description>Podcast Description When LA screenwriter Gary Devore mysteriously disappears in the summer of 1997, weird coincidences lead family and friends to believe he may have been a victim of foul play &amp;ndash; possibly because of his mysterious ties to the CIA. Gary was on the way home from finishing his latest script, which was allegedly going to be based in part on real events that occurred during the American invasion of Panama, and that script vanished along with him and his vehicle.</description></item><item><title>Secret Greek Adoptions Revealed | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660004/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the podcast &amp;ldquo;Born Greek: Made American&amp;rdquo;, hear how Joan and Kathryn were adopted from Greece in 1955 under strange circumstances.
Years later, Joan’s son David discovers an unbelievable secret. His grandfather was a high profile communist who was executed by the Greek State. And there is also another sister, who still lives in Greece. Her name is Effie and she has been looking for Joan and Kathryn her whole life since the three of them were forcefully separated by the police.</description></item><item><title>Lights Out: The Loss of a Lifetime | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660005/</guid><description>Podcast Description From Campside Media and eOne, sports journalist Matt Stanmyre embarks on a journey to examine the stranger-than-fiction twists, life-altering consequences and dramatic mysteries of the most iconic high school football game of all time. For this one New Jersey town it’s the day that changed everything. And decades later, they are still trying to pick up the pieces.
Listen now on Apple Podcasts or the podcast app of your choice!</description></item><item><title>Hidden Crimes, Artful Lies: Exposed | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660006/</guid><description>Podcast Description For years, Helge Achenbach has been among the world’s most successful art dealers. But with one treacherous move, he lands in prison. In Season 6 of Chameleon: Gallery of Lies, host Bijan Stephen sets out on the international trail of the most famous criminal you’ve never heard of. With unprecedented access to an ex-con, Bijan attempts to solve the riddle of who Helge really is—and who he might become.</description></item><item><title>Plumping Profits?: The Kylie Jenner Lip Kit Scandal on Infamous | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 16:52:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660007/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the “Infamous&amp;quot; podcast, when Kylie Jenner launches her lip kits of matching lipsticks and lip liners, it appears the youngest Kardashian-Jenner is suddenly at the helm of a sky-rocketing makeup company — one that catches the interest of Forbes magazine. But what&amp;rsquo;s really happening behind the scenes? Listen to Infamous’s “Plumping Profits?” for never-before-heard recordings of Kris and Kylie from the journalist who found herself at the center of a scandal.</description></item><item><title>Devil in the Ditch | 1. I Would've Remembered a Murder | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660008/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been nearly 20 years since host Larrison Campbell’s 85-year-old grandmother, Presh, was murdered. Detectives say it was probably someone who knew Presh. But in a small Mississippi town, that doesn&amp;rsquo;t exactly narrow it down. Campbell starts at the scene of the crime.
Unlock all episodes of Witnessed, ad-free right now by subscribing to The Binge. Plus, get binge access to brand new stories dropping on the first of every month — that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.</description></item><item><title>Introducing... Witnessed: Devil in the Ditch | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660009/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Just because the police can’t solve a murder doesn’t mean other people won’t find someone to blame. In season 4 of Witnessed: Devil in the Ditch, journalist Larrison Campbell returns to her Mississippi hometown to reexamine one of its most notorious unsolved cold cases – the murder of her grandmother, Presh. What happens when a family and a community suspect one of their own?
Available April 3, 2023, wherever you get your podcasts.</description></item><item><title>Mystic Mother | 8. Seekers | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Life after the Temple.
Want the full story? Unlock all episodes of Witnessed: Mystic Mother, ad-free right now by subscribing to The Binge — All Episodes. All at Once. Plus you’ll unlock brand new stories, dropping every month — that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.
Just click ‘Subscribe’ on the top of the Witnessed show page on Apple Podcasts or visit GetTheBinge.com to get access wherever you listen.</description></item><item><title>Mystic Mother | 7. The Verdict | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660011/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660011/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 48-day trial comes to an end, and the jury reaches a decision.
Want the full story? Unlock all episodes of Witnessed: Mystic Mother, ad-free right now by subscribing to The Binge — All Episodes. All at Once. Plus you’ll unlock brand new stories, dropping every month — that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.
Just click ‘Subscribe’ on the top of the Witnessed show page on Apple Podcasts or visit GetTheBinge.</description></item><item><title>Mystic Mother | 6. The Trial | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660012/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660012/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happens when you represent yourself in your own trial? Tracy’s about to find out.
Want the full story? Unlock all episodes of Witnessed: Mystic Mother, ad-free right now by subscribing to The Binge — All Episodes. All at Once. Plus you’ll unlock brand new stories, dropping every month — that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.
Just click ‘Subscribe’ on the top of the Witnessed show page on Apple Podcasts or visit GetTheBinge.</description></item><item><title>Mystic Mother | 5. The Charges | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660013/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660013/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a search warrant is served on the Temple, more than 30 members face daunting felony charges, and Tracy could face decades in prison.
Want the full story? Unlock all episodes of Witnessed: Mystic Mother, ad-free right now by subscribing to The Binge — All Episodes. All at Once. Plus you’ll unlock brand new stories, dropping every month — that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.
Just click ‘Subscribe’ on the top of the Witnessed show page on Apple Podcasts or visit GetTheBinge.</description></item><item><title>Mystic Mother | 4. Operation Goddess Temple | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660014/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a reporter exposes what really happens during a “whole body healing” session, the Temple unknowingly welcomes in a new kind of seeker, undercover detectives.
Want the full story? Unlock all episodes of Witnessed: Mystic Mother, ad-free right now by subscribing to The Binge — All Episodes. All at Once. Plus you’ll unlock brand new stories, dropping every month — that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.</description></item><item><title>Mystic Mother | 3. The Article | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Temple members fear Tracy’s plan to draw in new seekers could attract unwanted attention.
Want the full story? Unlock all episodes of Witnessed: Mystic Mother, ad-free right now by subscribing to The Binge — All Episodes. All at Once. Plus you’ll unlock brand new stories, dropping every month — that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.
Just click ‘Subscribe’ on the top of the Witnessed show page on Apple Podcasts or visit GetTheBinge.</description></item><item><title>Mystic Mother | 2. Goddess Bless | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660016/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Tracy Elise tries to create a tantric goddess temple in Phoenix, some say it’s not a house of worship, it’s a house of prostitution.
Want the full story? Unlock all episodes of Mystic Mother, ad-free right now by subscribing to The Binge — All Episodes. All at Once. Plus you’ll unlock brand new stories, dropping every month - that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.
Just click ‘Subscribe’ on the top of the Mystic Mother show page on Apple Podcasts or visit GetTheBinge.</description></item><item><title>Mystic Mother | 1. Aphrodite | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660017/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Rebecca discovers a new kind of church, she goes from seeker to goddess.
Want the full story? Unlock all episodes of Mystic Mother, ad-free right now by subscribing to The Binge — All Episodes. All at Once. Plus you’ll unlock brand new stories, dropping every month — that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.
Just click ‘Subscribe’ on the top of the Mystic Mother show page on Apple Podcasts or visit GetTheBinge.</description></item><item><title>Introducing... Witnessed: Mystic Mother | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660018/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660018/</guid><description>Podcast Description For years, the Phoenix Goddess Temple claimed to offer “seekers” healing through sensual touch. But when an outsider exposes what’s happening behind closed doors, the temple unknowingly welcomes in a new kind of seeker—undercover detectives. What some saw as a spiritual home, the state saw as a brothel operating under the guise of religious freedom. So what happens when your beliefs might be against the law? Hosts Katie and Leah Henoch follow the rise and fall of the Phoenix Goddess Temple and tell the story of a community still reckoning with the fallout more than a decade later.</description></item><item><title>Friendly Fire | 8. The Verdict | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660019/</guid><description>Podcast Description The civil trial that will determine whether Marty is liable for killing John John officially begins. We are left with the biggest question of all: Did Lori do the right thing?
A Campside Media &amp;amp; Sony Music Entertainment production.
Find more great podcasts from Sony Music Entertainment at sonymusic.com/podcasts. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Friendly Fire | 7. Pastor Golden and the Outlaw | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Was Marty a corrupt deputy? Is Rick Babb’s story true? Host Sean Flynn toggles between witnesses and investigators to get to the bottom of the story that might be the lynchpin to Lori’s case.
A Campside Media &amp;amp; Sony Music Entertainment production.
Find more great podcasts from Sony Music Entertainment at sonymusic.com/podcasts. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Friendly Fire | 6. Carson County | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660021/</guid><description>Podcast Description A Carson had been sheriff in Scott County for 22 of the previous 30 years— until Marty Carson’s father loses in a landslide. His successor gives a behind-the-scenes look at how the sheriff’s department had been run under Carson’s leadership, and the effect of John John&amp;rsquo;s killing on the community, including the Carson family. Lori learns a staggering theory that could turn her case upside down.
A Campside Media &amp;amp; Sony Music Entertainment production.</description></item><item><title>Friendly Fire | 5. Something Bad is Going to Happen | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660022/</guid><description>Podcast Description If the prosecutor won’t take Marty to court, Lori will. She hires a famous and relentless lawyer to start building a case, one she learns won’t be easy to win. Lori reveals why she believes Marty wanted to get rid of her husband.
A Campside Media &amp;amp; Sony Music Entertainment production.
Find more great podcasts from Sony Music Entertainment at sonymusic.com/podcasts. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>A Q&amp;A with Friendly Fire host Sean Flynn | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Spectacle: True Crime host, Mariah Smith, sits down with Sean Flynn to chat all things about the newest season of Witnessed: Friendly Fire. She puts host Sean Flynn in the hot seat and they dig into true crime – how we report these stories, why we’re so fascinated with them and what this fascination says about us. Mariah gets juicy behind-the-scenes bits from Sean ABOUT reporting Witnessed: Friendly Fire.</description></item><item><title>Friendly Fire | 4. Marty's Side | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marty tells his version of events leading to what officials have deemed a tragic accident. However, some key details don’t add up. The former prosecutor and TBI supervisor confront the inconsistencies and say the investigation was thorough. Does Lori have this all wrong? Do we?
A Campside Media &amp;amp; Sony Music Entertainment production.
Find more great podcasts from Sony Music Entertainment at sonymusic.com/podcasts. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Friendly Fire | 3. He's in Here | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lori decides to conduct her own investigation. She speaks to two witnesses who were there when John John was shot—and they share a different, and troubling, version of events. An innocent man questions why his name was dragged into the case.
A Campside Media &amp;amp; Sony Music Entertainment production.
Find more great podcasts from Sony Music Entertainment at sonymusic.com/podcasts. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Friendly Fire | 2. "An Incident Occurred" | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660026/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lori has two days to plan a funeral for John John. The town anxiously awaits a press conference that will explain how Marty ended up shooting his own partner. But the event leaves Lori with more questions than answers.
A Campside Media &amp;amp; Sony Music Entertainment production.
Find more great podcasts from Sony Music Entertainment at sonymusic.com/podcasts. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Friendly Fire | 1. Officer Down | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660027/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660027/</guid><description>Podcast Description A sheriff’s deputy is shot during a drug bust in Scott County, Tennessee. But who shot him? And how did it happen? The clock ticks as his wife, Lori scrambles for answers. She’s left with a shocking discovery.
A Campside Media &amp;amp; Sony Music Entertainment production.
Find more great podcasts from Sony Music Entertainment at sonymusic.com/podcasts. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Welcome to The Binge - All Episodes, All at Once | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660028/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Want to get all episodes of Witnessed: Friendly Fire now? Subscribe to The Binge - a new podcast channel from Sony Music entertainment.
Unlock all episodes of this show along with the entire network of true crime and investigative podcasts on The Binge. Plus, a brand new story drops every month - that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.
Click “try free” at the top of the Witnessed show page on Apple Podcasts to start your free trial or check out The Binge channel page at apple.</description></item><item><title>Introducing... Witnessed: Friendly Fire | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660029/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660029/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a K-9 officer in the Scott County, Tennessee, Sheriff’s Department winds up shot at the hands of his partner, a grieving widow takes it upon herself to untangle the truth from the lies. Was it just a catastrophic accident? Or an intentional killing? National Magazine Award-winning reporter Sean Flynn returns to Scott County two decades after the shooting to tell the story of one woman’s pursuit of justice—and one community’s enduring reckoning with the fallout.</description></item><item><title>Borderlands | 8. Survival | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660030/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nothing really ends in the borderlands.
Want the full story? Unlock all episodes of Witnessed, ad-free, right now by subscribing to The Binge. Plus, get binge access to brand new stories dropping on the first of every month — that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.
Just click ‘Subscribe’ on the top of the Witnessed show page on Apple Podcasts or visit GetTheBinge.com to get access wherever you listen.</description></item><item><title>Borderlands | 7. Conspiracy | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660031/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660031/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a federal trial comes to a swift end, the community in Far West Texas grapples with the truth.
Want the full story? Unlock all episodes of Witnessed, ad-free, right now by subscribing to The Binge. Plus, get binge access to brand new stories dropping on the first of every month — that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.
Just click ‘Subscribe’ on the top of the Witnessed show page on Apple Podcasts or visit GetTheBinge.</description></item><item><title>Borderlands | 6. Oh Sh*t | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660032/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dale and Kelly hit the jackpot, make their first arrest, and close in on their second.
Want the full story? Unlock all episodes of Witnessed, ad-free, right now by subscribing to The Binge. Plus, get binge access to brand new stories dropping on the first of every month — that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.
Just click ‘Subscribe’ on the top of the Witnessed show page on Apple Podcasts or visit GetTheBinge.</description></item><item><title>Borderlands | 5. The Informant | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660033/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Recently arrived federal agents Dale and Kelly team up to finally get Robert Chambers — then find an unexpected source of help.
Want the full story? Unlock all episodes of Witnessed, ad-free, right now by subscribing to The Binge. Plus, get binge access to brand new stories dropping on the first of every month — that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.
Just click ‘Subscribe’ on the top of the Witnessed show page on Apple Podcasts or visit GetTheBinge.</description></item><item><title>Borderlands | 4. The Door | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660034/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sheriff Thompson tightens his grip on power in Far West Texas, but rumors swirl his reach is even greater than that.
Want the full story? Unlock all episodes of Witnessed, ad-free, right now by subscribing to The Binge. Plus, get binge access to brand new stories dropping on the first of every month — that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.
Just click ‘Subscribe’ on the top of the Witnessed show page on Apple Podcasts or visit GetTheBinge.</description></item><item><title>Borderlands | 3. Just Say No | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660035/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Beloved local sheriff Rick Thompson takes on a starring role as an anti-narcotics crusader in the Reagan Administration&amp;rsquo;s War on Drugs.
Want the full story? Unlock all episodes of Witnessed, ad-free, right now by subscribing to The Binge. Plus, get binge access to brand new stories dropping on the first of every month — that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.
Just click ‘Subscribe’ on the top of the Witnessed show page on Apple Podcasts or visit GetTheBinge.</description></item><item><title>Borderlands | 2. The Outlaw | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660036/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660036/</guid><description>Podcast Description As law enforcement starts to sniff around, Robert steps into the shoes of a legendary drug lord.
Want the full story? Unlock all episodes of Witnessed, ad-free, right now by subscribing to The Binge. Plus, get binge access to brand new stories dropping on the first of every month — that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.
Just click ‘Subscribe’ on the top of the Witnessed show page on Apple Podcasts or visit GetTheBinge.</description></item><item><title>Borderlands | 1. A Wild Place | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660037/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660037/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s the 1970s in Far West Texas, and local bad boy Robert Chambers has always found his way to trouble—women, drugs, rock stars, mountain lions. And when cocaine starts flowing across the Mexican border like never before, Robert dives in headfirst.
Want the full story? Unlock all episodes of Witnessed, ad-free, right now by subscribing to The Binge. Plus, get binge access to brand new stories dropping on the first of every month — that’s all episodes, all at once, all ad-free.</description></item><item><title>Introducing... Witnessed: Borderlands | Witnessed: Fade to Black</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6033660038/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6033660038/</guid><description>Podcast Description The tall-but-true tale of a charismatic outlaw, an iconic small-town sheriff, and the record-setting drug bust that ensnared them both. Set in the rugged Texas borderlands, host Rob D’Amico transports listeners back to the U.S. side of the border for the opening salvo of the War on Drugs … where so much dirty money was swirling across the Rio Grande that even the most incorruptible citizens would be tempted.</description></item></channel></rss>