<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Sound Detectives on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/tags/sound-detectives/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Sound Detectives on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 07:05:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/sound-detectives/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>A Brand New Case | Sound Detectives</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/4832066529/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/4832066529/</guid>
        <description>Podcast Description A mysterious phone call from famed inventor LeVar Burton ropes Detective Hunch into a new case: missing sounds! Hunch prefers to work alone, but when Audie the Ear turns up on his doorstep, he reluctantly teams up to solve their first bubbling sound mystery.
To learn more about Sound Detectives as well as find coloring pages, sound terms, and more, please visit https://www.sounddetectivespodcast.com
Transcript </description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Breaking News: Season 1 Launches Next Week, 11/1! | Sound Detectives</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/4832066530/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/4832066530/</guid>
        <description>Podcast Description A new sneak peek at Sound Detectives, coming November 1st! Sounds have mysteriously gone missing, and everyone is in a panic! Sound Detectives is a fun-filled comedy adventure for the whole family about the magic and mystery of sound. The world famous Detective Hunch teams up with a rookie named Audie – a three foot five inch, walking, talking human ear – to crack the case. They&amp;rsquo;ll need to work together to identify the sounds and nab the nefarious Sound Swindler, all with a little help from LeVar Burton!</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Coming Soon…Sound Detectives | Sound Detectives</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/4832066531/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 23:34:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/4832066531/</guid>
        <description>Podcast Description LeVar Burton presents a serialized kids and family podcast about the mysterious case of missing sounds.
Detective Hunch and his new sidekick, Audie the Ear, are on the case to get the world back its soundtrack. Join the team on this semi-improvised comedy caper to return the mystery sounds before the world falls silent . . . all with some help from LeVar Burton himself!
Transcript </description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
