<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sound Detectives on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/sound-detectives/</link><description>Recent content in Sound Detectives on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 08:05:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/sound-detectives/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>On the Same Wavelength | Sound Detectives</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4832060009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4832060009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hunch and Audie go on a musical adventure and learn that hearing is a spectrum. Audie is in awe of how much – even as an ear – she still has to learn about what it means to be deaf and hard of hearing. LeVar learns something new, too, and wants to add a new exhibit to the museum. Featuring: Matt Maxey To learn more about Sound Detectives as well as find coloring pages, sound terms, and more, please visit https://www.</description></item><item><title>The Stake Out | Sound Detectives</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4832060008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4832060008/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Hunch&amp;rsquo;s suggestion, Audie snoops around LeVar&amp;rsquo;s office and finds a crucial clue! Does LeVar know who stole the missing sounds? And what kind of rude noise is this week&amp;rsquo;s mystery sound?
To learn more about Sound Detectives as well as find coloring pages, sound terms, and more, please visit https://www.sounddetectivespodcast.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hunch Has a Hunch | Sound Detectives</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4832060007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4832060007/</guid><description>Podcast Description After his investigation, Hunch presents Audie with his&amp;hellip; hunch. Audie doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to believe his theory, but there is still a mysterious sputtering sound to return! LeVar seems troubled by a personal matter, but he won’t say what it is. To learn more about Sound Detectives as well as find coloring pages, sound terms, and more, please visit https://www.sounddetectivespodcast.com
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Audie’s Time to Shine | Sound Detectives</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4832060006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4832060006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hunch is ready to let Audie take the lead! Does Audie have what it takes to solve this menacing mechanical missing sound? Meanwhile, LeVar doesn’t seem interested in the latest Sound Swindler clues, but Hunch begins to have his suspicions about the identity of the culprit. To learn more about Sound Detectives as well as find coloring pages, sound terms, and more, please visit https://www.sounddetectivespodcast.com
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We're Gonna Be Famous | Sound Detectives</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4832060005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4832060005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Detective Hunch is busy daydreaming about the glory that will come with solving the case and finding the Sound Swindler, but maybe there&amp;rsquo;s more to solving a case than the fame. LeVar sends them a rhythmically crunchy mystery sound, and asks them to stay focused on the missing sounds.
To learn more about Sound Detectives as well as find coloring pages, sound terms, and more, please visit https://www.sounddetectivespodcast.com</description></item><item><title>Know-How vs. Know-Now | Sound Detectives</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4832060004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4832060004/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Sound Swindler is still at large, and LeVar is anxious for help! Audie is a-buzz about the mystery sound, but Hunch insists that she needs some detective training first. Hunch knows just the thing: Detective Solvall&amp;rsquo;s Handbook for Young Detectives!
To learn more about Sound Detectives as well as find coloring pages, sound terms and more, please visit https://www.sounddetectivespodcast.com
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Brand New Case | Sound Detectives</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4832060001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4832060001/</guid><description>Podcast Description A mysterious phone call from famed inventor LeVar Burton ropes Detective Hunch into a new case: missing sounds! Hunch prefers to work alone, but when Audie the Ear turns up on his doorstep, he reluctantly teams up to solve their first bubbling sound mystery.
To learn more about Sound Detectives as well as find coloring pages, sound terms, and more, please visit https://www.sounddetectivespodcast.com
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Breaking News: Season 1 Launches Next Week, 11/1! | Sound Detectives</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4832060002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4832060002/</guid><description>Podcast Description A new sneak peek at Sound Detectives, coming November 1st! Sounds have mysteriously gone missing, and everyone is in a panic! Sound Detectives is a fun-filled comedy adventure for the whole family about the magic and mystery of sound. The world famous Detective Hunch teams up with a rookie named Audie – a three foot five inch, walking, talking human ear – to crack the case. They&amp;rsquo;ll need to work together to identify the sounds and nab the nefarious Sound Swindler, all with a little help from LeVar Burton!</description></item><item><title>Coming Soon…Sound Detectives | Sound Detectives</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4832060003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 23:34:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4832060003/</guid><description>Podcast Description LeVar Burton presents a serialized kids and family podcast about the mysterious case of missing sounds.
Detective Hunch and his new sidekick, Audie the Ear, are on the case to get the world back its soundtrack. Join the team on this semi-improvised comedy caper to return the mystery sounds before the world falls silent . . . all with some help from LeVar Burton himself!
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>