<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>The Deck Investigates on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/categories/the-deck-investigates/</link>
        <description>Recent content in The Deck Investigates on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 23:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/categories/the-deck-investigates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>The Deck Investigates - 15 of 15: Next in the Investigation</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308800016/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308800016/</guid>
        <description>As of last summer, authorities have Ron Hulse&amp;rsquo;s DNA swab.
They agreed to do a direct comparison test against the partial male profile found on Darlene&amp;rsquo;s blouse.
Not because Ron is a suspect, but because he&amp;rsquo;s her husband.
If that DNA belongs to Ron, then it actually means the profile is kind of useless.
Maybe it was from their hug goodbye that morning when he went to work,
in which case it means that we need to start testing other items while we still can to get a suspect sample.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck Investigates - 14 of 15: A Massive Revelation</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308800015/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308800015/</guid>
        <description>For almost four decades, no one questioned Darlene&amp;rsquo;s cause of death.
And honestly, at first, neither did we.
We didn&amp;rsquo;t set out to debunk the cause of death in Darlene&amp;rsquo;s case, but when we went
through the pathologist&amp;rsquo;s 1984 findings, a few things just didn&amp;rsquo;t make sense.
It wasn&amp;rsquo;t that we thought the report was wrong or that we knew more than a trained
pathologist.
In fact, it was the opposite.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck Investigates - 13 of 15: Untangling Misinformation</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308800014/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308800014/</guid>
        <description>When we made the discovery about the Parson family,
it made us question everything Nelson had told us so far.
And again, Lemon and Parson are pseudonyms
because these guys have never publicly been named suspects by law enforcement.
So to see if this was just some kind of huge mix-up,
we first reached out to a former employee of Nelson&amp;rsquo;s
who Emily had interviewed prior.
She&amp;rsquo;s actually the one who was assigned to be the liaison</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck Investigates - 12 of 15: P.I.&#39;s Best Lead</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308800013/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308800013/</guid>
        <description>About a year before we got involved with Darlene&amp;rsquo;s case,
her family worked with a private investigator, Patrick Zirpoli,
who goes by Zip to those who know him.
Zip spent his career with the Pennsylvania State Police.
He retired in 2015 as a corporal and the unit supervisor
of the Criminal Investigation Assessment Unit.
One of his specialties is cold case homicide investigations,
and after retirement, he&amp;rsquo;s gone on to consult in cold cases.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck Investigates - 11 of 15: Bad Seed</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308800012/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308800012/</guid>
        <description>In any good investigation, you&amp;rsquo;re running down multiple leads at once.
It&amp;rsquo;s not just a time efficiency thing, it&amp;rsquo;s what helps you avoid getting tunnel vision.
So one of the times we met with Nelson, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t just Kenneth McCune Jr.&amp;rsquo;s name that
we brought up.
We also asked him about another name.
We said, hey, what do you know about John Paul Clark?
Did your office ever seriously look at him?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck Investigates - 10 of 15: Look at the Deeds</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308800011/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308800011/</guid>
        <description>Everyone from the current prosecutor to the FBI back in 87 say the same thing.
Look at where her body was found.
Her killer knew the area, knew where he was going to take her.
If that&amp;rsquo;s true, we decided to see what the land would tell us.
So we pulled the deed records for the lot where Darlene was found, and we looked at
parcels around it.
And sure enough, right up the road is McCune Farms, LLC.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck Investigates - 9 of 15: Let&#39;s Go for a Ride</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308800010/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308800010/</guid>
        <description>We&amp;rsquo;re just a mile south of Plymouth on Old 31 headed south to Argus.
Argus is about 15 minutes south of Plymouth, and it&amp;rsquo;s mostly just cornfields and backroads
between the two towns.
Once you turn off of New US 31 onto Old Highway 31, you cross some railroad tracks, and a
few miles south of there, you pass right by Brandi Peltz&amp;rsquo;s old house, where she was
murdered in 1986.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck Investigates - 8 of 15: It All Goes Through One Guy</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308800009/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308800009/</guid>
        <description>In 2016, Kristen was all grown up and a mom of her own when she decided to take her mom&amp;rsquo;s
cold case into her own hands.
It got to a point about seven years ago where I was like, okay, I want to do this.
I was sitting at home with little kids and I just started reaching out like, hey, is
there anything new, anything going on?
Who can I talk to?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck Investigates - 7 of 15: Bring in the FBI</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308800008/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308800008/</guid>
        <description>By January 1987, Marshall County authorities were noticing a pattern emerging.
Here&amp;rsquo;s an excerpt read from Sergeant Dave Yokelet&amp;rsquo;s case summary.
In the past several years, since 1982, this officer has been involved in the investigating
of several violent crimes that have occurred in the extreme southern portion of Marshall
County, Indiana.
Two of those crimes involved homicides, one of which was in 1984, the Hulse Homicide,
the other in 1986, the Peltz Homicide.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck Investigates - 6 of 15: Evil All Around</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308800007/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308800007/</guid>
        <description>Before moving on to other suspects, whose names were coming in via phone calls and letters
from the public, investigators knew what they had to do next—give Ron Hulse another polygraph
test.
I say another because they actually gave him one just three days after Darlene&amp;rsquo;s abduction,
which he passed.
And listen, Ron was never a suspect.
But back then, officers knew that they had to play offense and defense.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck Investigates - 5 of 15: He&#39;s Gunned Down</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308800006/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308800006/</guid>
        <description>On October 25th, 1984, all the way out in Amarillo, Texas,
a 29-year-old man named Ricky Mock went into a convenience store
and held the cashiers and guests at gunpoint, demanding money.
When he got what he was looking for, he took off,
only to be pulled over a few hours later
by an Amarillo officer who noticed his Indiana plates.
Ricky assumed that they knew it was him who robbed the place,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck Investigates - 4 of 15: They Left Town</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308800005/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308800005/</guid>
        <description>Before Darlene&amp;rsquo;s body had even been found, a tip had come in to police.
A man named Jim Garman suggested they check out the home of a woman named Thelma Burns.
He said there were a lot of quote-unquote druggies and creeps who stayed there.
When police went by to talk to him the next evening, this now being after Darlene&amp;rsquo;s body
had been found, Jim Garman&amp;rsquo;s tip had gotten even more specific, and it pointed the finger</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck Investigates - 3 of 15: The Wooded Path</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308800004/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308800004/</guid>
        <description>Walter Grosnickle finally had some free time on Saturday, August 18th, 1984 to make the
hour-long drive from his house in North Manchester, Indiana, to Argus to check out some land that
he&amp;rsquo;d been interested in buying for his timber operations.
This was actually the second time he had driven there to have a look, but he wanted to double
check the trees on the plot before he moved forward with actually buying it.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck Investigates - 2 of 15: A Stranger&#39;s Wrath</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308800003/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308800003/</guid>
        <description>Everett Fish was the reserve officer who passed 20B Road.
The dirt roads off the highway aren&amp;rsquo;t well marked, and it&amp;rsquo;s easy to do.
I even missed it my first time up there.
It took about .2 seconds for him to realize what he&amp;rsquo;d done and make a U-turn back toward the Hulse House,
which was just a stone&amp;rsquo;s throw away from the highway with a cornfield and a barn between.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck Investigates - 1 of 15: Take a Bath</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308800002/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308800002/</guid>
        <description>A little over two years ago, I came across an old news article.
It was about an old unsolved murder that I had never heard of in a tiny Indiana town
that I had only ever passed on my way to somewhere else.
When I reached out to the victim&amp;rsquo;s daughter on Facebook, I had no idea that I would spend
the next two years of my life living and breathing this case, dumping every resource I had into</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Deck Investigates - Darlene Hulse (4 of Hearts, Indiana)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308800001/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308800001/</guid>
        <description>Argus, Indiana is small, more corn stalks than people in 1984.
It&amp;rsquo;s one of those places where neighbor means something different.
Everyone&amp;rsquo;s your neighbor, but each house is a corn or soybean field away.
The home of the Hulse family was just like that,
tucked away off a major road through town with fields to the front and back.
Ron Hulse built the home himself for his wife Darlene and their three daughters.</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
