<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Episode with Richie Sadlier on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/episode-with-richie-sadlier/</link><description>Recent content in Episode with Richie Sadlier on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 12:44:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/episode-with-richie-sadlier/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Episode With Richie Sadlier: Damien Dempsey | Episode with Richie Sadlier</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4257230001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 12:44:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4257230001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's season finale with Damien Dempsey is a beautiful journey through music mixed with some hilarious stories about Shane MacGowan, Ronnie Drew, and a live performance from his kitchen table that blew Richie and Killian away.
In ten days time, Damien will take to the stage at Vicar Street for the first of six of his now iconic Christmas gigs at the venue, concerts which have taken on a huge emotional significance for his fans.</description></item><item><title>Episode With Richie Sadlier: Terence Power of Talking Bollox | Episode with Richie Sadlier</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4257230002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 12:42:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4257230002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Three&amp;nbsp;years ago this month, Terence Power and Calvin O'Brien, two young Dubliners from the inner&amp;nbsp;city, sat down at a kitchen table and recorded&amp;nbsp;a podcast with one of their phones. That initial&amp;nbsp;conversation spawned Talking Bollox, a podcast which quickly gathered huge momentum and has become one of the most popular shows in Ireland.
One of the reasons for the show's success has been Terence and Calvin's frankness about some of the issues affecting their&amp;nbsp;inner city communities, and today Richie sits down with Terence to speak about one of those issues which has&amp;nbsp;been a feature of his life since childhood, addiction.</description></item><item><title>Episode With Richie Sadlier: Zlata Filipović | Episode with Richie Sadlier</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4257230003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 12:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4257230003/</guid><description>Podcast Description In March 1992, Zlata Filipović was an 11-year-old girl growing up in Sarajevo, Bosnia in a normal, middle-class family who kept a diary about all the everyday things a child of her age does: going to school, doing music lessons, visiting her grandparents.&amp;nbsp;
Just one month later, Zlata's diary had begun to transform into an incredibly vivid description of a city under siege as the Balkans War reached her hometown.</description></item><item><title>Episode With Richie Sadlier: John Clarke | Episode with Richie Sadlier</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4257230004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 12:23:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4257230004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s Episode is an extraordinary conversation with John Clarke, the husband and partner of forty years of the late Marian Finucane. It’s an intimate, raw and quite beautiful look at love and loss.
In late 2019, Marian and John agreed that the time was right for her to call an end to her iconic decades-long broadcasting career with RTE. They set to planning their 'sunset walk' together: the trips around the world they hadn't yet got around to making.</description></item><item><title>Episode With Richie Sadlier: Stephen Bradley | Episode with Richie Sadlier</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4257230005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 11:45:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4257230005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Just&amp;nbsp;a few short days ago, Shamrock Rovers manager Stephen Bradley celebrated an historic achievement for the club as he led his team to a fourth League of Ireland title in a row. But although&amp;nbsp;he's our first guest on Episode from the world&amp;nbsp;of sport, today's show is very much not about football.&amp;nbsp;
Instead, it's a love letter from a father to his son. Last year, Stephen and his wife Emma experienced something no parent wants to: they were told their then-eight-year-old son Josh has leukemia, which he continues to be treated for.</description></item><item><title>Episode With Richie Sadlier: Holly Cairns TD | Episode with Richie Sadlier</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4257230006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 11:51:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4257230006/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2018, Holly Cairns was 28 years old and had voted once in her life. In the five years since,&amp;nbsp;she's been elected to Cork County Council, then to Dáil Eireann and in the last twelve months has become leader of the Social Democrats.&amp;nbsp;
Earlier this year, having previously been vocal about the targeted, sexualised abuse she and other female TDs are regularly subjected to, Holly spoke for the first time about that abuse - normally faceless and online - escalating into a real-world situation&amp;nbsp;where a man began showing up at her home in West Cork.</description></item><item><title>Episode With Richie Sadlier: Dr Katriona O'Sullivan, Author of 'Poor' | Episode with Richie Sadlier</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4257230007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:50:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4257230007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Richie first met Dr Katriona O'Sullivan - an academic in Maynooth University's Department of Psychology - about seven years ago but at the time, he had no idea about her backstory: a childhood spent in extreme poverty in England as part of an Irish family in which both her parents suffered from long-term addiction issues.
Despite being surrounded by adults and structures which continuously failed her, Katriona enrolled in Trinity College aged 23 and forged an academic career while raising her young family.</description></item><item><title>Episode With Richie Sadlier: Tommy Tiernan | Episode with Richie Sadlier</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4257230008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4257230008/</guid><description>Podcast Description For the very first show of the series, Richie travels to Galway to speak to Tommy Tiernan, eight months after meeting each other for the first time on Tommy's chat show.&amp;nbsp;
Chatting in his garden studio - The Hen House - Tommy describes how emotions feel like dangerous territory for him, how his complex relationship with his mother continues to evolve years after she took her own life, why psychotherapy has been fruitless for him, and the repercussions of misjudged&amp;nbsp;jokes.</description></item><item><title>Episode with Richie Sadlier: Introduction | Episode with Richie Sadlier</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4257230009/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 15:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4257230009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Richie Sadlier has followed an unconventional career path. He spent his early life as a professional footballer, and is now a psychotherapist and author. Like its presenter, Episode approaches people and subjects in a way that upends expectation.
Having initially struggled to adapt after his football career ended prematurely, Richie started down the path of psychotherapy and today works as a therapist specialising in issues such as relationships, adolescent development and sexuality.</description></item></channel></rss>