<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>In Her Defence on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/in-her-defence/</link><description>Recent content in In Her Defence on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/in-her-defence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Episode 8: Freedom | In Her Defence</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3945350009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3945350009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Did Helen really kill Miles? A burning question remains. As Helen works toward release from prison, we think about what made Miles who he was, and consider the legacy of his violence.
Theme song, “The Fighter,” by Jenn Grant.
Learn more about this podcast and domestic violence in Canada, or sign up for our newsletter at tgam.ca/inherdefence
E-mail the reporter at jpruden@globeandmail.com
If you’re experiencing intimate partner violence and want to talk to someone, you can find resources and your nearest shelter at sheltersafe.</description></item><item><title>Episode 7: Seemed Like a Loser | In Her Defence</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3945350008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3945350008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Appealing a plea deal is a long-shot, but defence lawyer Mona Duckett wants to take it on. The Crown says justice has been served. The Court of Appeal considers Helen’s future.
Theme song, “The Fighter,” by Jenn Grant.
Learn more about this podcast and domestic violence in Canada, or sign up for our newsletter at tgam.ca/inherdefence
E-mail the reporter at jpruden@globeandmail.com
If you’re experiencing intimate partner violence and want to talk to someone, you can find resources and your nearest shelter at sheltersafe.</description></item><item><title>Episode 6: Thanks, Gentlemen | In Her Defence</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3945350007/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3945350007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Helen is sent to prison for the death of her husband. Around the country, people object to her sentence and the way she’s treated in court. In the isolation of prison, Helen wonders whether she’s done something wrong by accepting the deal, and has to consider what to do next.
Theme song, “The Fighter,” by Jenn Grant.
Learn more about this podcast and domestic violence in Canada, or sign up for our newsletter at tgam.</description></item><item><title>Episode 5: The Battered Woman Defence | In Her Defence</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3945350001/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3945350001/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 1987 case of Angelique Lavallee provides a roadmap for the “battered woman defence.” Canada’s first female Supreme Court justice, Bertha Wilson, attempts to expose systemic sexism in the justice system. Helen is charged with first-degree murder, and has to decide whether to accept a plea deal or go to trial.
Elizabeth Sheehy’s book is Defending Battered Women on Trial: Lessons from the Transcripts.
Theme song, “The Fighter,” by Jenn Grant.</description></item><item><title>Episode 4: Responsibility Pie | In Her Defence</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3945350002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3945350002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Helen is interrogated by police officers who say they understand the abuse she’d been living with, and know that something had to happen for her to get free. Someone she loves has betrayed her. Her life – and the lives of her sons – are all on the line. Learn more about this podcast and domestic violence in Canada, or sign up for our newsletter at tgam.ca/inherdefence E-mail the reporter at jpruden@globeandmail.</description></item><item><title>Episode 3: All Hell Breaks Loose | In Her Defence</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3945350003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3945350003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wes Naslund talks about growing up with his father. Miles Naslund is reported missing, but no one seems to care he’s gone. Helen and her family live with a haunting secret. One day in 2017, almost exactly six years after Miles was reported missing, two men show up at Helen’s work.
Learn more about this podcast and domestic violence in Canada, or sign up for our newsletter at tgam.</description></item><item><title>Episode 2: Helen in Hell | In Her Defence</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3945350004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3945350004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Helen Naslund speaks from prison for the first time. Helen describes how she met and married Miles, and the only time she tried to leave. Early one morning in September 2011, two gunshots crack through the house. Learn more about this podcast and domestic violence in Canada, or sign up for our newsletter at tgam.ca/inherdefence E-mail the reporter, Jana Pruden, at jpruden@globeandmail.com If you’re experiencing domestic violence and want to talk to someone, you can find resources and your nearest shelter at sheltersafe.</description></item><item><title>Episode 1: The Ticking Time Bomb | In Her Defence</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3945350005/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3945350005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wes Naslund gets a phone call from his brothers at the farm. Friends and family describe the domestic abuse they suspect was going on in the Naslund house. A fight at the bar leaves Miles seriously injured, and things at the farm reach a breaking point. Learn more about this podcast and domestic violence in Canada, or sign up for our newsletter at tgam.ca/inherdefence E-mail the reporter, Jana Pruden, at jpruden@globeandmail.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: In Her Defence | In Her Defence</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3945350006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 15:52:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3945350006/</guid><description>Podcast Description The first two episodes of In Her Defence will be released on October 10th. Follow now so you don’t miss a new episode.
Theme song, “The Fighter,” by Jenn Grant.
If you’re experiencing intimate partner violence, you can find resources and your nearest shelter at sheltersafe.ca.
Support journalism like this by subscribing to The Globe and Mail. Our listeners get a special discount on new subscriptions at www.globeandmail.com/podcastdeal.</description></item></channel></rss>