<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>British Scandal on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/british-scandal/</link><description>Recent content in British Scandal on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:01:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/british-scandal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Aitken Affair | Face the Music | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jonathan Aitken has created an intricate web of lies, and now he’s placed his own family at the centre of it. If the truth is uncovered, he risks losing his relationships, career and freedom. But journalist David Leigh is onto him and he’s moving fast. He’s just one piece of the puzzle away from bringing Aitken down.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.</description></item><item><title>The Aitken Affair | Lies Under Oath | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480002/</guid><description>Podcast Description The editor of The Guardian has had a tip-off which, if true, is huge: that the cabinet minister Jonathan Aitken is accepting money from senior Saudis. He’s been trying to nail down the story for a month but with no luck. Then one day, he has an idea: call David Leigh, an investigative journalist who MPs with something to hide have learned to fear. Maybe David can find the smoking gun?</description></item><item><title>The Aitken Affair | A Self-Made Man | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480003/</guid><description>Podcast Description With Matt Forde taking some time away from the microphone, comedian and actor Rob Delaney joins Alice Levine to take listeners inside a story of politics, pride and perjury.
Young MP Jonathan Aitken has big ambitions. He wants to make his mark on politics - and on the world. After he catches Prime Minister Margaret Thatcher’s eye, his star is firmly on the rise. But before long, a dark secret threatens to destroy everything he’s worked so hard to build.</description></item><item><title>Listen Now: 'Tis The Grinch Holiday Talk Show | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cuddly as a cactus and charming as an eel, he’s your new favorite snarky talk show host. Join The Grinch (and his faithful dog Max) each week as he rants against Christmas cheer and roasts celebrity guests like chestnuts on an open fire. Starring Saturday Night Live’s James Austin Johnson as the notorious curmudgeon and broadcasting straight from Who-Ville, will The Grinch send these famous folks back down Mt.</description></item><item><title>The Cannabis King | Interview - Julian Peto, close friend of Howard Marks | 4 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matt and Alice sit down with old friend of the notorious drug smuggler, Julian Peto. The pair met as denim-clad Oxford students with long hair and a disdain for academic lectures. Julian takes us inside their raucous university nights, Howard’s magnetic charm, and the Welshman’s surprising resilience in the face of imprisonment and his later cancer diagnosis.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.</description></item><item><title>Listen Now: Legacy | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480006/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Afua Hirsch and Peter Frankopan tell the wild stories of some of the most extraordinary men and women ever to have lived – and ask whether they have the rep they deserve. Should Nina Simone’s role in the civil rights movement be more celebrated than it is? When you find out what Picasso got up to in his studio, can you still admire his art? Was Napoleon a hero or a tyrant - or both?</description></item><item><title>The Cannabis King | The Comedown | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Howard Marks is living a life of luxury in the Mediterranean. But he’s being watched. A federal agent is tapping his phone and following his every move. Craig Lovato has made catching “Mr Nice” his life’s work. And he’s not going to stop until he brings Marks - and his empire - down.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Cannabis King | Bonnie and Clyde | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 16:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Howard Marks has just imported enough Colombian weed to get every person in the UK stoned. He’s at the peak of his trafficking career and he’s never been prouder. Perhaps he’ll even retire. Howard celebrates the win with a sherry. But he’s barely a sip in when a man appears in front of him with some bad news: Howard's under arrest.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>The Cannabis King | The High Life | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480009/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's 1964 and a young Oxford student called Howard Marks develops a habit that will define the course his life. At first, cannabis is simply his escape. But then it becomes his route to making millions. It’s going well - really well - until one misstep sees Howard forced to choose between his family and his freedom.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.</description></item><item><title>Disney+ presents: Wags at War (Sponsored) | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480010/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this special one-off episode, Matt and Alice explore the celebrity saga that gripped the nation. No, it's not Matt Hancock's appearance on I'm a Celeb: it's the iconic court case between former WAGs, Rebekah Vardy and Coleen Rooney. With the help of The Guardian's Media Editor, Jim Waterson, Matt and Alice take listeners right inside Coleen's secret investigation, her stunning Twitter post and the most explosive moments of the trial.</description></item><item><title>Encore: The Hitler Diaries | Interview - Bestselling author Robert Harris | 4 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480011/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matt and Alice speak to Robert Harris, bestselling writer and author of the definitive account of the scandal, 'Selling Hitler'. He tells us why Hitler is one of the least likely historical figures to have kept a diary, and lays bare the impact of the scandal on fake news culture.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Encore: The Hitler Diaries | Hoaxed | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480012/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480012/</guid><description>Podcast Description The stories around the diaries and their authenticity begin to unravel. Streams of people have their reputations and their livelihoods on the line. Who will survive this humiliating scandal? And who, when the dust settles, will still come out on top?
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Encore: The Hitler Diaries | Hitler for Sale | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480013/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Excited by the prospect of the diaries being real, Rupert Murdoch sends famed historian Hugh Trevor-Roper to verify them. Everything is riding on his assessment. What will Trevor-Roper tell the world? Real or fake?
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Encore: The Hitler Diaries | Operation Green Vault | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Journalist Gerd Heidemann is searching for his next story for Stern magazine when the scoop of the century lands in his lap. But is it too good to be true?
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Liz Truss | Alastair Campbell and Joe Lycett on 1 year since Truss | 4 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alastair Campbell - the spin doctor-turned-podcaster - tells Matt and Alice speak why he thinks Liz Truss and Kwasi Kwarteng were a “lethal combination” and describes the moment he felt Truss was really losing the plot. Plus comedian and activist Joe Lycett takes listeners inside his infamous appearance on the Laura Kuenssberg show and tells Matt and Alice why he’s trying (and quite clearly failing) to stop talking about the former leader a year after her tumultuous turn in Number 10.</description></item><item><title>Liz Truss | Liz vs Lettuce | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Liz Truss and Kwasi Kwarteng hit the ground running, scheming ways to revolutionise the government and the economy. But after they announce their shake up, the Truss premiership is on a collision course with an iceberg (lettuce).
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Liz Truss | Hitting The Ground | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Liz Truss’ star is rising in the Conservative party after both Theresa May and Boris Johnson place her at the heart of their cabinets. And when things start to unravel for Boris, Liz sees her chance. It’s time for her to take the lead and unleash the radical revolution she's sure the country desperately needs.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Liz Truss | The Turnip Taliban | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480018/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480018/</guid><description>Podcast Description For as long as she can remember, Mary Elizabeth Truss has been determined to make her mark on British politics. And now it's finally within reach. She’s been handpicked to stand for Parliament in South West Norfolk. But when a story from the past comes to light, her career could be over before it’s even started.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Encore: The Canoe Con | Dead Man Walking | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480019/</guid><description>Podcast Description John Darwin decides to come back from the dead and journalists begin to investigate his mysterious disappearance.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Encore: The Canoe Con | El Dorado | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480020/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480020/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Darwins trick the police into thinking John’s dead and decide they need to flee the country.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Encore: The Canoe Con | Missing | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Prison officer John Darwin finds himself in debt and makes a drastic decision to fake his own death.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Crowded Marriage | Operation PB | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Prince Charles no longer has to live a lie. His divorce with Diana is finalised and his relationship with Camilla is out in the open. But there’s a problem: Camilla remains deeply unpopular with the public and the press. He knows that turning this around will be an uphill battle, so he enlists the help of a wily spin doctor and sets to work. Charles remains adamant that Camilla is his Queen-in-waiting.</description></item><item><title>The Crowded Marriage | Camillagate | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Diana isn’t happy, and she refuses to stay quiet about it any longer. Putting on a brave face for her royal duties is pushing her to the very brink. She begins by confronting the woman she blames for her failing marriage, Camilla Parker-Bowles. But Camilla won’t listen. So Diana goes further with a blistering, tell-all BBC interview, and the Palace is shaken to the core.&amp;nbsp;
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>The Crowded Marriage | Fred and Gladys | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480024/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480024/</guid><description>Podcast Description As England’s future king, Prince Charles knows all too well what’s expected of him: find a virgin bride and fulfil the duties assigned to him at birth. But then he meets Camilla Shand. She’s confident, honest and unlike any woman he’s ever met before. But she’s also deemed wholly unsuitable by the Firm. They would prefer shy, young aristocrat Diana Spencer. So Charles faces an impossible choice: duty or desire?</description></item><item><title>Death of a Rolling Stone | Interview - Prince Stash, close friend of Brian Jones | 4 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480025/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matt and Alice sit down with close friend of Brian Jones, Prince Stash Klossowski de Rola. A fellow musician and socialite at the centre of London’s Swinging Sixties scene, Prince Stash takes us inside the wild nights they spent together in Parisian clubs, and his memories of watching the Stones make magic in the studio. Plus, he tells us what really happened the night he was arrested alongside Brian Jones in a drugs bust that would see Jones found guilty.</description></item><item><title>Death of a Rolling Stone | A Mysterious Death | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480026/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480026/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a difficult few years, things are looking up for Brian Jones. A trip to Morocco opens a whole new world of musical inspiration, and then there’s his collaborations with the likes of Jimi Hendrix. He’s ready to hit the studio and make music he knows the fans will love.
But the other band members don’t want Brian to take the lead. In fact, they don’t want him in the band at all.</description></item><item><title>Death of a Rolling Stone | Love and Other Drugs | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480027/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480027/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Rolling Stones are riding high, topping charts and playing stadiums across the world. But backstage, the relationship between Keith Richards and Brian Jones is rockier than ever. And when an intrepid News of the World journalist stumbles upon the scoop of his career, the Stones need to unite - or their latest single could be their last.
For confidential advice and information about drugs, their effects and the law, call Frank on 0300-123-660 or visit talktofrank.</description></item><item><title>Death of a Rolling Stone | Who's The Leader? | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480028/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brian Jones wants to be a famous blues musician. The only problem is, he hasn’t got a band. When he meets talented upstarts Keith Richards and Mick Jagger, he knows he’s onto something good. Onstage, they’re electric, but behind the scenes a battle ensues to define the soul of The Rolling Stones. Jones put the band together. But as they hit the big time, can he keep hold of the reins?</description></item><item><title>Oscar Wilde | Interview - Wilde's grandson, Merlin Holland | 4 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480029/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matt and Alice speak to Oscar Wilde's only grandchild, Merlin Holland, who has spent more than four decades researching his grandfather's life. He tells us what it's like being connected to a literary icon, and why he believes his grandfather felt untouchable. Plus he takes us inside Wilde's complicated relationship with scandal. Did he court it?
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Oscar Wilde | Exile | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480030/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Oscar Wilde’s reputation is in tatters. His books have been pulled from the printers, his name erased from theatre productions. There's still time to flee. But he would rather be a martyr than a man on the run. He arrives at the trial that will dictate his future determined to put up a fight. Wilde has been called many things, but he won’t be called a coward. And then, the judge delivers his verdict.</description></item><item><title>Oscar Wilde | The Peer and The Poet | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480031/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Oscar Wilde is making waves in London’s literary scene, but he’s heading for disaster. He's been publicly outed by his gay lover’s father, Lord Queensberry. Homosexuality is illegal and Wilde is facing private and public ruin. So he has to make a life-changing choice: fight, or flight?
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Oscar Wilde | Bosie | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480032/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480032/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s 1891 and Oscar Wilde’s star is rising. His book, ‘The Picture of Dorian Gray’, is a bestseller, and his first West End play is about to open. And then he meets Bosie Douglas, a young, handsome and beguiling poet. But homosexuality is illegal and they must keep their relationship secret. When Bosie’s father, the dogmatic Lord Queensberry, finds out, he resolves to do whatever it takes to keep them apart forever.</description></item><item><title>Gazza | Interview | 4 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480033/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matt and Alice speak to Linda Lusardi, former Page 3 model and close friend of Paul Gascoigne. She takes us inside the highs of their raucous nights out, and the lows of his battles with addiction. Plus, she tells us why Gazza’s life wouldn’t be all that different had he never become a footballer.
If you or someone you know is struggling with issues like those touched on in this episode, here are some UK resources:</description></item><item><title>Gazza | Game Over | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480034/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glenn Hoddle has a decision to make. As the England team's new manager, it’s time to select his 1998 World Cup squad. Include Gazza, and he’ll have to take drastic action to stop him going off the rails. But exclude the star player and the country could well turn against him. Gazza played a blinder in the qualifying matches, but will it be enough to get him to France?</description></item><item><title>Gazza | Tabloid Dream | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480035/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480035/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Paul Gascoigne steps out with his new girlfriend, Sheryl, interest in his personal life soars, and the Press takes advantage. Gazza’s alcohol-fuelled benders and turbulent relationship make him easy prey for tabloid journalists seeking headlines. Sheryl befriends one with the hope of turning the narrative around.
If you or someone you know is struggling with issues like those touched on in this episode, here are some UK resources:</description></item><item><title>Gazza | Gazzamania | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480036/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480036/</guid><description>Podcast Description All Paul 'Gazza' Gascoigne has ever wanted to do is play football. So when he’s taken on by Newcastle United, he’s determined to impress. His exceptional talent is obvious to everyone and he quickly becomes the most talked-about player in England. But as his fame grows, so too do his inner demons - and the doubts. Now he's playing for his country on the greatest stage of all: the 1990 World Cup.</description></item><item><title>The Cambridge Spies | Interview | 4 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480037/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alice and Matt sit down with biographer Andrew Lownie, who spent over 30 years researching Guy Burgess and spoke to over one hundred people who knew him personally. He tells us why Cambridge University was a particularly fertile breeding ground for Soviet recruits, how much damage the spy ring wrought on the British establishment and why five people who knew each other should never have become spies in the first place.</description></item><item><title>The Cambridge Spies | The Third Man | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480038/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kim Philby’s job is to uncover other people’s secrets. But now, his oldest friend is on the verge of exposing his own. As two other Cambridge spies are unmasked, Philby’s reputation comes under fierce scrutiny. And Nicholas Elliott is determined to find out whether his old confidante is also a KBG agent. Can Philby wriggle free of Elliott’s sting operation and a government desperate to catch traitors?
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>The Cambridge Spies | The Volkov Affair | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480039/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kim Philby and Guy Burgess are at the height of their power, working as double agents for the Soviet Union. But while their careers are going from strength to strength, their personal lives are in free fall. Destructive habits and paranoia are creeping to the surface. But that's not all... The CIA has just made an explosive discovery - and Philby and Burgess are at the heart of it.</description></item><item><title>The Cambridge Spies | From Students to Spies | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480040/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kim Philby and Guy Burgess are two Cambridge students with a shared purpose: fighting fascism. When they’re introduced to a KGB recruiter in the 1930s, he tells them they could do just that by sharing British secrets with the Soviet Union. So how far will they go to further the cause? As far as betraying their own country?
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>The Great Train Robbery | Interview | 4 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480041/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alice and Matt speak to Colin Mackenzie, the tenacious reporter who managed to track down train robber, Ronnie Biggs, after he escaped prison. A Fleet Street veteran, he takes us back to a golden era in British journalism, and into the whirlwind 48 hours he spent with Biggs in Brazil.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Great Train Robbery | Cat and Mouse | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bruce Reynolds is rich. But he’s also a wanted man. An entire nation wants to know where he is. But there's one person who wants to find him more than any other: Tommy Butler. A relentless detective who’s solved more cases than anyone else in his squad, Butler won’t let anything come between him and the capture of Britain’s biggest thief. And so the hunt begins.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>The Great Train Robbery | Sitting Ducks | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cracks are showing in Bruce Reynolds' 16-man crew and the farm where they’ve been hiding out is a pressure cooker. But today's the day they plan to stage the daring train robbery, and the stakes are far too high to turn back. Can the group hold it together long enough to pull off Britain’s biggest ever heist?
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.</description></item><item><title>The Great Train Robbery | The Ulsterman | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bruce Reynolds is a master of the criminal trade. Canny, well-dressed and suave, he’s transcended his humble origins by taking advantage of London’s illegal underworld. Robbing jewellery allows him to satisfy his taste for the finer things, but now he wants more. His ultimate fantasy is to find an ‘Eldorado’ that will set him up for life. So he concocts a plan more ambitious and much riskier than anything he’s pulled off before.</description></item><item><title>Jeremy Thorpe | Interview | 5 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480045/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alice and Matt talk to Norman Scott, the man at the very heart of our story, whose chance meeting with Jeremy Thorpe in 1961 would lead to an attempt on his life. He describes the first time he caught the former Liberal leader's eye, the painful years living under his control and the terrifying night his life was in the balance. And he delivers his verdict on Hugh Grant’s portrayal of Thorpe in the BBC’s A Very English Scandal.</description></item><item><title>Jeremy Thorpe | Opening The Closet | 4 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480046/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480046/</guid><description>Podcast Description If Jeremy Thorpe’s plan had worked, Norman Scott would now be permanently silenced. But he’s alive and able to tell the world about their affair and the terrifying attempt on his life. For years, Norman has felt shackled by Thorpe. Now it’s Thorpe who could end up behind bars. But will the world believe the powerful former party leader? Or the unknown model with a wild story?
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Jeremy Thorpe | Shoot The Dog | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480047/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeremy Thorpe’s star has risen. As Liberal Party leader, he’s busy tackling the problems of 1970s Britain. But there’s a distraction. Norman Scott is telling his story to anyone who will listen. Thorpe will stop at nothing to keep him quiet, but he can’t do it alone. He takes on a new accomplice: one whose lack of experience will be Thorpe’s downfall - and Scott’s saving grace.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Jeremy Thorpe | The Go-Between | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480048/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeremy Thorpe's political career is on the up. But his personal life is threatening to bring him down. He is one of the brightest stars in Westminster. Perhaps even a future PM. But rumours about his sexuality are swirling. And in 1960s Britain, homosexuality is illegal. Now his former lover, Norman, is preparing to go to the papers to reveal all. And Thorpe decides to risk everything to stop him.</description></item><item><title>Jeremy Thorpe | Simply Heaven | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480049/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ambitious Liberal MP Jeremy Thorpe has a secret. He's got his eye on a handsome but troubled young stable boy. But in 1960s Britain, homosexuality is illegal. Soon he's forced to choose: politics or passion?
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Encore: Archer | Interview | 4 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480050/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alice and Matt talk to Adam Raphael, an author and journalist who, in 1987, was subpoenaed to give evidence for The Daily Star in Archer’s libel trial. He takes us inside the trial, discusses Archer's political skill and compares him to a certain blonde British Prime Minister.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Wondery Presents: Frozen Head | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480051/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hosted by Ash Kelley and Alaina Urquhart from the hit show Morbid.
When 90-year-old Laurence Pilgeram drops dead on the sidewalk outside his condo, you might think that’s the end of his story. But, really, it’s just the beginning. Because Laurence and others like him have signed up to be frozen and brought back to life in the future. And that belief will pull multiple generations of the Pilgeram family into a cryonics soap opera filled with dead pets, gold coins, grenades, fist fights, mysterious packages, family feuds, Hall of Fame baseball legends, and frozen heads — lots of frozen heads.</description></item><item><title>Encore: Archer | From the Penthouse to the Jailhouse | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480052/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeffrey Archer is running for London Mayor and he thinks he can win. But is his web of lies about to unravel?
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Encore: Archer | Mary Vs Monica | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480053/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeffrey Archer takes the witness stand in the libel trial of the century. He has two false alibis and a forged diary to help him prove he never slept with Monica Coghlan. But will the jury believe him, or is his carefully constructed world about to come crashing down?
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Encore: Archer | Lord of the Lies | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480054/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeffrey Archer is a young and up and coming Tory politician. He dreams of becoming Prime Minister. But what happens when a newspaper accuses him of paying for sex?
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
Please support us by supporting our sponsors!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>The Ballad of Yoko and John | Interview | 4 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480055/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matt and Alice talk to Dan Richter, friend and live-in assistant to John Lennon and Yoko Ono in the 1970s. An American who, in his own words, “came along for the ride: a co-conspirator, confidant, assistant and dope-buddy”, Dan gives us a behind-the-scenes glimpse of the private world of John and Yoko. He recalls the making of Lennon's legendary hit 'Imagine', and tells us whether he believes the couple were truly compatible.</description></item><item><title>The Ballad of Yoko and John | The End | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480056/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480056/</guid><description>Podcast Description After the Beatles break up, John's addictions and his bitter jealousy of Paul McCartney threaten to rip his life, and relationship with Yoko, apart. When Yoko sends him away to LA, will their relationship survive?
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Ballad of Yoko and John | All You Need Is Love | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480057/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480057/</guid><description>Podcast Description John Lennon is mesmerized by the strange, thrilling artist Yoko Ono. He has never experienced a collaboration like this with anyone. Not even Paul. But as their relationship deepens, so too do problems in the band. Could this be the end of The Beatles?
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Ballad of Yoko and John | Julia | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480058/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480058/</guid><description>Podcast Description John Lennon has a dream - to make music. So when he enlists George Harrison, Paul McCartney and Ringo Starr to join his band The Quarrymen, he feels like this is the start of something big. But as tragedy strikes, and he faces the perils of newfound stardom, John seeks out new inspiration - an avant-garde, Japanese artist called Yoko Ono.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Boris Johnson | Interview | 6 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480059/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matt and Alice speak to Sonia Purnell, journalist and author of 'Just Boris: A Tale of Blonde Ambition'. She shares her memories of her time working with Boris in Brussels during the 90s. They also discuss his early and crucial reinvention, the Johnson appeal, and whether or not we'll see Boris in British politics again.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Boris Johnson | Them's The Breaks | 5 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480060/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480060/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Partygate story has broken, and it spells disaster for Boris - now, he has to fight for everything he's worked so hard to achieve. But with new scandals emerging, and his government crumbling around him, is this the end of the road for Boris Johnson?
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.</description></item><item><title>Boris Johnson | Winner Takes It All | 4 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480061/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480061/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Teflon PM has successfully delivered Brexit, but his newfound power is threatened by in-fighting between his closest allies. And when Boris faces the biggest challenge of his career so far, the problems begin to pile up - all under the watchful eye of a relentless journalist.
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.</description></item><item><title>Boris Johnson | Leave Means Leave | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480062/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Boris has never been more popular as he leads the successful Leave campaign during the Brexit referendum. He couldn't be in a stronger position to become Prime Minister...until an old ally turns into an adversary. But when new PM Theresa May gives him a surprise top cabinet job, how will Boris use his new position to his advantage?
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening.</description></item><item><title>Boris Johnson | Mayor On A Zipwire | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480063/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480063/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's 2008: Boris is vying for the role of Mayor of London, all the while keeping the top job in his sights. Despite blunders in Beijing, a tumultuous and highly publicized personal life, and that zipwiring incident, Boris seems unstoppable. But with a history-altering referendum on the horizon, Boris faces an existential choice - remain, or leave?
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening.</description></item><item><title>Boris Johnson | Who's The Blondest? | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480064/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alexander Boris de Pfeffel Johnson has one goal: to be king of the world. After all, everyone tells him he's capable of it - his dysfunctional parents, his elite teachers, his affluent friends. But as he faces his first public scandal, will he be able to weather the storm?
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Queen of Clean | Interview | 4 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480065/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matt and Alice speak to David Dimbleby, one of the BBC's most illustrious broadcasters. David reflects on his early years at the BBC, when Mary Whitehouse was beginning her battle against the corporation, and recalls a day he spent interviewing Mary in the 1970s.
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
Please support us by supporting our sponsors!</description></item><item><title>The Queen of Clean | Yes, Prime Minister | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480066/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mary finds an ally in the most powerful person in the country - Margaret Thatcher. But how long will their allegiance last?
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
Please support us by supporting our sponsors!
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Queen of Clean | Courting Disaster | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480067/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mary’s fight moves beyond television to remodeling the whole moral outlook of Britain – via the courtroom. But when she targets the gay community, Mary underestimates the backlash that’s to come. Are Mary Whitehouse's campaigning days over?
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
Please support us by supporting our sponsors!
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>The Queen of Clean | No Sex, Please! | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480068/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480068/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the early 1960s, a housewife from Birmingham is shocked by the changing tide of culture, and decides to do something about it. Mary Whitehouse goes up against her first adversary: the BBC and its liberal Director General, Sir Hugh Carleton Greene. In a battle for the future of the BBC, who will win?
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening.</description></item><item><title>The Spy Who Came Back From The Dead | Interview | 4 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480069/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alice and Matt speak to Julian Hayes, John Stonehouse's grand-nephew and author of 'Stonehouse: Cabinet Minister, Fraudster, Spy'. They discuss the allegations surrounding Stonehouse's involvement with the Czechs, his family's reaction to the disappearance, and the time he tried to egg his grand-uncle.
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
Please support us by supporting our sponsors!</description></item><item><title>The Spy Who Came Back From The Dead | Twister Returns | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480070/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480070/</guid><description>Podcast Description John makes a daring escape - little does he know, police across the world are piecing together his bizarre disappearance. Soon, John's lies and deception begin to unravel: is this the end of the road for Agent Twister?
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
Please support us by supporting our sponsors!</description></item><item><title>The Spy Who Came Back From The Dead | Missing Presumed Dead | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480071/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480071/</guid><description>Podcast Description As John's political, marital and financial woes spiral, he's desperate to find an escape route. Then he reads a book and has a crazy idea...
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
Please support us by supporting our sponsors!
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Spy Who Came Back From The Dead | Agent Twister | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480072/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480072/</guid><description>Podcast Description John Stonehouse is one of the most promising young Labour politicians in England - handsome and charismatic, with the political background to match. But when he catches the eye of the Czech secret service, Stonehouse falls into a dangerous game of cat and mouse.
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
Please support us by supporting our sponsors!</description></item><item><title>Abdication | Interview | 4 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480073/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alice and Matt interview literary agent and biographer Andrew Lownie, author of 'Traitor King: The Duke and Duchess of Windsor in Exile'. He talks about the myth of Edward and Wallace's 'great romance' and his groundbreaking research into the couple's connections with the Nazi party.
A note on names: King Edward VIII was known to his family as David. For clarity, we have called him Edward throughout this series.</description></item><item><title>Abdication | The Traitor King | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480074/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480074/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the late 1930’s, with England turning their back on their former King and World War II looming, the Duke and Duchess of Windsor face an existential choice: stay loyal to Britain, or side with the enemy?
A note on names: King Edward VIII was known to his family as David. For clarity, we have called him Edward throughout this series.
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening.</description></item><item><title>Abdication | The Decision | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480075/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480075/</guid><description>Podcast Description When King Edward VIII announces his intentions to marry Wallis Simpson, politicians, his people and his own family are clear; it's Wallis or the crown. And it’s not just Britain’s government for whom the stakes are high…
A note on names: King Edward VIII was known to his family as David. For clarity, we have called him Edward throughout this series.
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening.</description></item><item><title>Abdication | Wally | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480076/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480076/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Prince of Wales and heir to the British throne, Edward, meets the twice-divorced ‘poor relation’ of Baltimore aristocracy, he’s captivated by her boldness, her confidence and total disinterest in tradition. But his family, and the British government, are determined to put a stop to the match.
A note on names: King Edward VIII was known to his family as David. For clarity, we have called him Edward throughout this series.</description></item><item><title>Hitler Diaries | Interview | 4 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480077/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matt and Alice speak to Robert Harris, best-selling writer and author of the definitive account of the scandal, 'Selling Hitler'. They discuss the scandal's farcical cast of characters, its impact on 'Fake News' culture, and the crudeness of the forgeries themselves.
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
Please support us by supporting our sponsors!</description></item><item><title>Hitler Diaries | Hoaxed | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480078/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480078/</guid><description>Podcast Description The stories around the diaries and their authenticity begin to unravel. For all the people who have their reputations and their livelihoods on the line, who will survive this humiliating scandal? And who, when the dust settles, will still come out on top?
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
Please support us by supporting our sponsors!</description></item><item><title>Hitler Diaries | Hitler for Sale | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480079/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Excited by the prospect of the diaries being real, Rupert Murdoch sends famed historian Hugh Trevor-Roper to verify them. However, as doubts and pressure mount up, what will Trevor-Roper decide to tell the world - real or fake?Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
Please support us by supporting our sponsors!
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Hitler Diaries | Operation Green Vault | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480080/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Journalist Gerd Heidemann is searching for his next story for Stern magazine when the scoop of the century lands in his lap. But is it too good to be true?
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
Please support us by supporting our sponsors!
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Hatton Garden | Interview | 4 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480081/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matt and Alice talk to Martin Brunt, crime correspondent for Sky News. He was the first reporter to reach Hatton Garden after the break in and charted the developing story. He talks about what it was like to report on this case at the time, why it captured the public imagination, and his surprising correspondence with ringleader, Danny Jones.
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening.</description></item><item><title>Hatton Garden | The Diamond Wheezers | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480082/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480082/</guid><description>Podcast Description It seems Reader and his crew have met their match in the form of Detective Sergeant Jamie Day. In a dramatic game of cat and mouse, will 'The Diamond Wheezers' manage to evade capture?
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
Please support us by supporting our sponsors!
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Hatton Garden | The Cabinet | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480083/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Reader and his gang of pensioners make it all the way to the vault but are thwarted at the last minute. Will they walk from the job or come back the next day risking everything to get their hands on the loot?
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
Please support us by supporting our sponsors!</description></item><item><title>Hatton Garden | The Plan | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480084/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brian Reader has a dream – to pull off the biggest burglary in British history. But he can never quite find the right crew to do it. But then he becomes a pensioner and realizes it very well might be now or never.
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
Please support us by supporting our sponsors!</description></item><item><title>Archer | Interview | 4 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480085/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alice and Matt talk to Adam Raphael. He's an author and a journalist and in 1987 he was subpoenaed to give evidence for The Daily Star in Archer’s libel trial. He discusses Archer's character, his political skill and how similar he is to a certain British Prime Minister.
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.</description></item><item><title>Archer | From the Penthouse to the Jailhouse | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480086/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeffrey Archer is running for London Mayor and he thinks he can win. But is his web of lies about to come undone?
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
Please support us by supporting our sponsors!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Archer | Mary Vs Monica | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480087/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeffrey Archer takes the witness stand in the libel trial of the century. He has two false alibis and a forged diary to help him prove he never slept with Monica Coghlan. But will the jury believe him or is his carefully constructed world about to come crashing down?
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.</description></item><item><title>Archer | Lord of the Lies | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480088/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeffrey Archer is a young and up and coming Tory politician. He dreams of becoming Prime Minister. But what happens when a newspaper accuses him of paying for sex?
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
Please support us by supporting our sponsors!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Spy Cops | Interview | 4 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480089/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matt and Alice talk to Alison. She tells the story of meeting a fellow activist called Mark Cassidy and falling in love. Little did she know he was in fact an undercover police officer. She is one of eight women who sued the police – and won – after they were tricked into relationships with members of the Metropolitan Police over the course of 25 years.
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+.</description></item><item><title>Spy Cops | The Other Women | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480090/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 19:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amy has finally exposed Mark for being an undercover police officer. But when she finds out she isn't his only victim she joins a crusade to take down the Metropolitan Police.
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
Please support us by supporting our sponsors!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Spy Cops | The Truth | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480091/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mark moves back in with Amy. But why is he acting so strangely? And what's up with the extra phone she finds in his glovebox.
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
Please support us by supporting our sponsors!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Spy Cops | Undercover | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480092/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mark Kennedy joins a secretive undercover police unit investigating left-wing political groups. But what happens when he gets in too deep?
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
Please support us by supporting our sponsors!
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Maxwell | Interview | 5 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480093/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matt and Alice talk to Roy Greenslade. He edited the Daily Mirror when Maxwell was the owner. He talks about what it was like to have Maxwell as a boss and the reason he thinks Maxwell's death was no accident.
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
Please support us by supporting our sponsors!</description></item><item><title>Maxwell | Legacy Of Lies | 4 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480094/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Robert Maxwell is dead. But how did he die? Was it suicide, an accident or even something more sinister? And will his children ever be able to overcome their toxic inheritance?
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
Please support us by supporting our sponsors!
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Maxwell | Downfall | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480095/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Robert Maxwell's enemies are circling. Can he outrun them or will the Maxwell empire finally come crashing to the ground?
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
Please support us by supporting our sponsors!
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Maxwell | Mirror Man | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480096/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Robert Maxwell buys Britain's second biggest tabloid. Will it help him defeat his rival Rupert Murdoch and give him the power and prestige he's always craved?
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
Please support us by supporting our sponsors!
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Maxwell | The Outsider | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480097/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Robert Maxwell builds himself up from nothing to become one of the most powerful men in Britain. But can he defeat his ultimate rival – the British Establishment?
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
Please support us by supporting our sponsors!
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>The Coughing Major | Interview | 4 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alice and Matt interview the playwright James Graham. He wrote a hit play and tv show about the Ingrams. He talks about what it was like meeting the notorious couple and how he came to question the official narrative of what happened.
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
Please support us by supporting our sponsors!</description></item><item><title>The Coughing Major | From Riches To Rags | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480099/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Charles and Diana celebrate winning a million. But their lives are about to be broken apart when the police come knocking at their door.
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
Please support us by supporting our sponsors!
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Coughing Major | In The Hot Seat | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480100/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Charles is in the hot seat but everyone thinks he will lose early. Little do the production staff or the audience know he has a secret strategy to win a million pounds.
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
Please support us by supporting our sponsors!
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>The Coughing Major | Let's Play Millionaire | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480101/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Diana Ingram is obsessed with tv quizzes. So obsessed she persuades her reluctant husband – army Major Charles Ingram – to try for the Who Wants To Be A Millionaire hotseat. How far will they go in their quest to win a million pounds?
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
Please support us by supporting our sponsors!</description></item><item><title>Encore: The Litvinenko Affair | Interview | 5 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480102/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alice and Matt talk to journalist and author Luke Harding about what The Litvinenko Affair means today. Luke Harding is a foreign correspondent with the Guardian. Between 2007 and 2011 he was the Guardian's Moscow bureau chief. The Kremlin expelled him from the country in the first case of its kind since the cold war. He is the author of A Very Expensive Poison -The Definitive Story of the Murder of Litvinenko and Russia’s War with the West.</description></item><item><title>Encore: The Litvinenko Affair | The Russian Runaround | 4 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480103/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480103/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Litvinenko investigation moves to Moscow. If British police want to interview their chief suspects, they’ll need to get co-operation from the Russian authorities.
Please support us by supporting our sponsors!
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Encore: The Litvinenko Affair | The Polonium Trail | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480104/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Police at Scotland Yard realise they’re not only dealing with the murder of one man…London is facing a full scale nuclear incident.
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App. https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Encore: The Litvinenko Affair | The Mysterious Edwin Carter | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480105/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480105/</guid><description>Podcast Description As Sasha fights a mysterious illness, time is running out for the police to get crucial information about his attackers. The race is on to find out who poisoned him and why.
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App. https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Encore: The Litvinenko Affair | Poisoned | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480106/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Russian dissident Alexander Litvinenko flees Moscow to live in exile in London, but he doesn’t know Russian agents are moving against him and there will be no billionaire to protect him.
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App. https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lord Lucan | Interview | 4 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480107/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alice and Matt talk to Sandra Rivett's son Neil Berriman. He tells them about his decade long mission to get justice for his murdered mother.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lord Lucan | The Closed Circle | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480108/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480108/</guid><description>Podcast Description After the murder of Sandra Rivett the police start hunting for Lord Lucan. Little do they know it's not just Lucan working against them but Britain's aristocracy as well.
There was a publishing issue when this episode was originally released which we quickly resolved. If you are hearing the incorrect audio, here are some things to try:
1. If the episode is downloaded to your app, delete it and re-download 2.</description></item><item><title>Lord Lucan | Murder In Belgravia | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480109/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480109/</guid><description>Podcast Description After walking out on his wife, Lord Lucan has only one goal in mind – to gain custody of his children. But when Veronica fights back, he realizes he will have to go to extreme lengths to get his way.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lord Lucan | Born Lucky | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480110/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lord Lucan and Veronica fall in love. But soon his gambling and her mental health problems threaten their blissful life.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Anarchy In The UK (Sex Pistols) | Interview | 5 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480111/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Malcolm Mclaren's biographer Paul Gorman talks to us about Mclaren's legacy and what it was like meeting the man back in the 1970s.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Anarchy In The UK (Sex Pistols) | Sid And Nancy | 4 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480112/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480112/</guid><description>Podcast Description With John gone Malcolm tries to make Sid the new lead singer. What he doesn't realise is Sid and Nancy's drug addiction and dependency is about to lead to tragedy.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Anarchy In The UK (Sex Pistols) | A Common Enemy | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480113/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480113/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Sex Pistols behaviour becomes more and more erratic and Malcolm Mclaren makes a drastic decision to try and keep the band together.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Anarchy In The UK (Sex Pistols) | God Save The Queen | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480114/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Malcolm Mclaren tries to rock the British establishment by releasing the Sex Pistols shocking new single on the day of the Queen’s Silver Jubilee. Only thing stopping him is the band’s addiction to causing chaos.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Anarchy In The UK (Sex Pistols) | The Wrong John | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480115/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Malcolm Mclaren is bored of his life running a clothes store. And so he decides to try and set up a band – a band, he hopes, who will rock the British establishment to its core.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Canoe Con | Interview: Tony Hutchinson | 4 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480116/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480116/</guid><description>Podcast Description We talk to the Superintendent who led the police investigation into John and Anne Darwin
Listen ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal.
Support us by supporting our sponsors!
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Canoe Con | Dead Man Walking | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480117/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480117/</guid><description>Podcast Description John Darwin decides to come back from the dead and journalists begin to investigate his mysterious disappearance.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Canoe Con | El Dorado | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480118/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480118/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Darwins trick the police into thinking John’s dead and decide they need to flee the country.
Listen ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal.
Support us by supporting our sponsors!
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Canoe Con | Missing | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480119/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Prison officer John Darwin finds himself in debt and makes a drastic decision to fake his own death.
Listen ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal.
Support us by supporting our sponsors!
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Profumo Affair | Interview: Seymour Platt | 6 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480120/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Christine Keeler’s son Seymour Platt joins us to talk about the impact the scandal had on his mum. He also talks about his campaign for her to be pardoned.
Listen ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal.
Support us by supporting our sponsors!
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Profumo Affair | A Man Without Morals | 5 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480121/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480121/</guid><description>Podcast Description A public inquiry into the Profumo affair gets underway, while Stephen Ward’s trial at the Old Bailey begins.
Listen ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal.
Support us by supporting our sponsors!
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Profumo Affair | Get Stephen | 4 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480122/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480122/</guid><description>Podcast Description The British establishment turn against Stephen Ward.
Listen ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal.
Support us by supporting our sponsors! See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Profumo Affair | War Games | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480123/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jack Profumo goes to desperate measures to save his political career, while Stephen Ward tries to stop Christine Keeler selling her story.
Listen ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Profumo Affair | The Smoking Gun | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480124/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Christine Keeler goes from one risky affair to another – with dangerous consequences.
Listen ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Profumo Affair | Sex, Lies and Spies | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480125/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nineteen year old showgirl Christine Keeler meets the cabinet minister John Profumo at a high society pool party. It’s the beginning of their scandalous affair.
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal.
Support us by supporting our sponsors! See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Breaking Barings | Interview: John Gapper | 4 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480126/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480126/</guid><description>Podcast Description How can one man bring down a bank?&amp;nbsp;Financial Times journalist John Gapper covered the Nick Leeson story at the time and co-wrote&amp;nbsp;All That Glitters: The Fall of Barings. He joins Alice and Matt to talk about the phenomenon of the Rogue Trader.
Listen ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Breaking Barings | On the Run | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480127/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Barings Bank discover their most successful trader has left them penniless. The hunt is on to find Nick Leeson.
Listen ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App. https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Breaking Barings | In the Pit | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480128/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480128/</guid><description>Podcast Description The losses in Nick Leeson’s secret account start to get out of hand. It means he needs to start taking even more risks.
Listen ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App. https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Breaking Barings | Under The Water | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480129/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick Leeson rises through the ranks of Barings Bank. When he moves to run the Singapore office, he notices a weakness in the system.
Listen ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App. https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Murdoch Phone Hacking | Phone Hacking Today: Nick Davies Interview | 5 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480130/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480130/</guid><description>Podcast Description The journalist who broke the phone hacking story, Nick Davies joins Alice and Matt to talk about its legacy today. In 2011, Nick Davies reported the key stories that revealed the extent of the ‘dark arts’ at Rupert Murdoch’s newspapers. He is the author of the best selling account: Hack Attack: How The Truth Caught up with Rupert Murdoch.&amp;nbsp;
Listen ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening.</description></item><item><title>The Murdoch Phone Hacking | The Media On Trial | 4 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480131/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rebekah Brooks and Andy Coulson face difficult questions in court. Will justice be done? And how will the inquiry affect the future of Britain’s media?
Listen ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App. https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal. See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Murdoch Phone Hacking | Death Of A Tabloid | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480132/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480132/</guid><description>Podcast Description The news breaks that murder victim Milly Dowler was hacked. It sparks a public outcry. Rebekah Brooks fights to hold on to her job while Rupert Murdoch arrives to try to contain the outrage.
Listen ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App. https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Murdoch Phone Hacking | Turning The Screws | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480133/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rebekah Brooks and Andy Coulson become part of the British power elite. The victims of hacking start fighting back.
Listen ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App. https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Murdoch Phone Hacking | The Dark Arts | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480134/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two ambitious journalists Rebekah Brooks and Andy Coulson rise through the ranks of The News Of The World - Britain’s biggest sunday tabloid. But the culture of ‘dark arts‘ threatens to bring everything down.&amp;nbsp;
Listen ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App. https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Sexed Up Dossier | The Legacy of Iraq Today - Interview with Steve Richards | 4 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480135/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 23:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alice and Matt talk to journalist Steve Richards about the impact of the sexed up dossier row and its legacy today. Steve Richards covered the Blair premiership as a political journalist during the 2000s. He has written about Tony Blair in his new book&amp;nbsp;The Prime Ministers, and in Blair &amp;amp; Iraq: Why Tony Blair Went To War - An Investigation. He also presents the podcast Rock n Roll Politics.</description></item><item><title>The Sexed Up Dossier | The Inquiry | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480136/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480136/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Hutton Inquiry investigates Dr Kelly’s death. The government’s battle with the media comes to a head. Who can the public trust to tell the truth?
Listen ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App. https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Sexed Up Dossier | Harrowdown Hill | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480137/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480137/</guid><description>Podcast Description After tough questioning in Houses of Parliament, UN Weapons Inspector David Kelly goes missing.`
Listen ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App. https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Sexed Up Dossier | 45 Minutes From Doom | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480138/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480138/</guid><description>Podcast Description UN Weapons Inspector David Kelly gets caught in the middle of a controversy over the British case for the Iraq War. He battles to save his reputation against warring factions in the government and the media.
Listen ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App. https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>The Litvinenko Affair | Londongrad Today - Interview with Luke Harding | 5 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480139/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alice and Matt talk to journalist and author Luke Harding about what The Litvinenko Affair means today. Luke Harding is a foreign correspondent with the Guardian.&amp;nbsp;Between 2007 and 2011 he was the Guardian's Moscow bureau chief. The Kremlin expelled him from the country in the first case of its kind since the cold war. He is the author of A Very Expensive Poison -The Definitive Story of the Murder of Litvinenko and Russia’s War with the West.</description></item><item><title>The Litvinenko Affair | The Russian Runaround | 4 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480140/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480140/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Litvinenko investigation moves to Moscow. If British police want to interview their chief suspects, they’ll need to get co-operation from the Russian authorities.
Listen ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal. See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Litvinenko Affair | The Polonium Trail | 3 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480141/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Police at Scotland Yard realise they’re not only dealing with the murder of one man…London is facing a full scale nuclear incident.
Listen ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App. https://wondery.app.link/againsttheodds.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Litvinenko Affair | The Mysterious Edwin Carter | 2 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480142/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480142/</guid><description>Podcast Description As Sashais dying of a mysterious illness, time is running out for the police to get crucial information about his attackers. The race is on to find out who poisoned him and why.
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App.&amp;nbsp;https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Litvinenko Affair | Poisoned | 1 | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480143/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480143/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the first episode of our four part series, Russian dissident Alexander Litvinenko flees Moscow to live in exile in London, but he doesn’t know Russian agents are moving against him and there will be no billionaire to protect him.
Listen early and ad free with Wondery+. Join Wondery+ for exclusives, binges, early access, and ad free listening. Available in the Wondery App. https://wondery.app.link/britishscandal
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Introducing British Scandal | British Scandal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9224480144/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9224480144/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a country obsessed with gossip, the great and the good fear one thing more than any other - scandal.
British scandals change the course of history. They bring down governments, overthrow the rich and cause the mighty to fall. Some are about sex, others about money. In the end, they’re all about power.&amp;nbsp;
But often at the heart of a scandal, there are ordinary human stories, stories of those caught up in the swirl of outrage.</description></item></channel></rss>