<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Psychology of your 20s on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-psychology-of-your-20s/</link><description>Recent content in The Psychology of your 20s on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 23:06:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-psychology-of-your-20s/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>152. Impulse shopping and retail therapy ft. Al from Two Broke Chicks | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 23:06:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Impulse shopping in an experience we've all had, the feeling of buying something you know you don't really need, but you want it desperately in the moment. Often during this decade we begin earning "adult money" for the first time and that means we can begin spending as a way to emotional regulate. Had a bad day? Buy a new pair of shoes. Been through a breakup? Shopping spree.</description></item><item><title>151. Stop getting attached too quickly ft. Lyss Boss | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 23:40:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320002/</guid><description>Podcast Description We all know the feeling of going on a few dates with someone and, suddenly, you're unable to stop checking your phone for messages, wondering when they're free, imagining the wedding, your future kids. And then we are left depleted, ghosted or disappointed. This is what happens when we romanticise the idea of someone, engage in fantasy bonding and it can often end up sabotaging the relationship.
In today's episode we are joined by the wonderful Lyss Boss, host of the Date Yourself Instead podcast to break down how we can take things slow and not get caught up in the idea of someone before we truly know them.</description></item><item><title>150. Sex is mental, not just physical ft. Gina Gutierrez | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320003/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 05:23:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Often when we think about sex, we only think about the physical. We only think about the other person's enjoyment or what sex should look like rather than what it could look like. Many of us have a very outdated understanding of what good, even great sex feels like and even less of an idea around how to achieve greater levels of pleasure and intimacy.
In today's episode, we bring on the incredible Gina Gutierrez, co-founder of the audio erotica app, Dipsea to discuss how we can use story telling, fantasy, self exploration and mental imagery to have better sex in our 20s.</description></item><item><title>149. Confidence will change your life ft. Tiff Baira | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 01:06:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Confidence truly is the secret to a better life: better friendships, better self esteem, better dates, better romance, better career success. Today, we are joined by the iconic, Tiff Baira known best for her show "Street Hearts NYC", her role as a matchmaker and model, as we explore how having certainty in your worth is the key to your dream life. We break down the equation for true, undeniable confidence, treating confidence as a skill you can strengthen and train, the truth behind "</description></item><item><title>148. Understanding ADHD in our 20s ft. Ellie Middelton | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320005/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 02:30:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320005/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2021, Ellie Middelton received a diagnosis of ADHD and autism at the age of 23. It was one of the best things that happened to her. Today, she joins us to discuss why neurodivergence is typically overlooked in women, the misconceptions we have about ADHD and autism, unmasking and how to navigate a diagnosis later in life. She also discusses how to manage neurodivergence in our 20s, why self diagnosis is valid, and why the path people want you to take, may not always be the one for you.</description></item><item><title>147. The psychology of the eldest daughter | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320006/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 01:02:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you ever feel like you need to be perfect, that you are responsible for the emotions of others, you’re the organiser in the friendship group, highly self reliant, an overachiever, constantly being told your mature for your age? I would make a good guess that you are the eldest daughter. In today's episode we break down the psychology behind 'eldest daughter syndrome' and how birth order and gender combines to create a certain personality profile and way of behaving and seeing the world.</description></item><item><title>146. Roommates and sharehouses in our 20s | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 23:48:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Living in sharehouses in our 20s are like their own weird, social experiment. We put together a group of people with different upbringings, personalities, lifestyles and standards under one roof and expect it to work out. Sometimes it does, other times it doesn't and we see social harmony break down. In today's episode we discuss: The four styles of roommates
The Cinderella Roommate The psychology of freeloading The influence of personality
Living with friends The role of communication Conflict, stonewalling and the silent treatment When its time to move out!</description></item><item><title>145. The psychology of pretty privilege and beauty standards | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 01:53:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Attractiveness and beauty is something we all inevitably find ourselves considering. We question whether we would be happier if we lost weight, would find love if our skin was better, would be more successful if we looked more like her or him. Our obsession with beauty is psychological and deeply rooted in our biology and evolution as a species. In today's episode we break down the existence of pretty privilege and beauty standards in our 20s and how they are impacting our mental wellbeing, sense of self worth and even our financial decisions.</description></item><item><title>144. It's okay for your friendships to change | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320009/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 01:56:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320009/</guid><description>Podcast Description In our 20s there are four things we worry about more than anything else: love, money, the future, and our friendships. As we grow and change, the relationships around us will also naturally change and we may begin to notice how we are seeing our friends less and less, watching certain friendships fizzle out or completely outgrowing each other. It's not the same as it once was. This can cause a lot of panic.</description></item><item><title>143. Why do we replay conversations? | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:34:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever had the experience of leaving a conversation and feeling like something you said was off, you sounded weird, you were awkward, worrying about what this person may think of you? This experience is much more common than we think and in today’s episode we break down the psychology behind why we replay conversations, exploring:
Rumination
The illusion of control
Social approval
Hypervigilance
Rejection sensitivity dysphoria
Social anxiety, and more
We often place the perceptions and opinions of others on a pedestal and try to closely manage their judgements of us, but that may not always be helpful.</description></item><item><title>142. The curse of being an overachiever | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320011/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 01:09:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320011/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week's episode we discuss the curse of being an overachiever. Society celebrates us for our successes, for our ability to work hard, push ourselves and constantly be the best. But this sometimes has contradictory consequences whereby the more we invest in our achievements, the less satisfaction and fulfillment we feel. We break down the paradox of being an overachiever and explore: The impact of being labelled a 'gifted child'
Golden child syndrome and family expectations
External validation
The overachiever's identity crisis The burnout cycle Learning your limits and redefining success Listen now!</description></item><item><title>141. How to get over someone you can't stop thinking about | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320012/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 01:33:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320012/</guid><description>Podcast Description We all know the feeling of wanting desperately to move on from someone - an ex, a past love, situationship, someone we know we shouldn't be with - but being unable to stop obsessively thinking about them. In this episode we explore the psychology behind why that is, but also how to get to the next stage of healing where you are free of the past memories, thoughts and your feelings for this person.</description></item><item><title>140. The psychology of envy | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 23:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Envy is ingrained into our human psyche, each and every one of us has, at times, compared ourselves to someone who has more, or possesses a quality or a level of success that we don't, and felt that familiar spike of pain. In today's episode we break down the psychology behind envy, and why it reflects a deeper insecurity in ourselves we are not ready to recognise. We explore: The prevalence of envy in our 20s
The primal origins of envy
Envy vs.</description></item><item><title>139. How to have better first dates! | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:28:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dating in our 20s can feel like a minefield, a lot of people don't know what they want, what they like, we get ghosted, we get stood up, and then there are the first dates. First dates can feel intimidating but today we are breaking down my 10 tips to have the best first dates of your life. By adopting the mindset that you are there to learn more about yourself and have a fun experience, we take first dates off a pedestal and lower the stakes.</description></item><item><title>138. We need a new approach to anxiety ft. Dr David Rosmarin | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 01:46:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr David Rosmarin is an Associate Professor at Harvard Medical School and the founder of the Centre for Anxiety. Today he joins us on the podcast to discuss how we are getting anxiety WRONG as we break down a new approach to managing our anxiety, rather than approaching it with fear. For anyone who is anxious or has battled anxiety in their 20s and beyond, join us for a vulnerable conversation of how anxiety may actually be your superpower and how it has even created stronger relationships for me, personally.</description></item><item><title>137. I'm putting too much pressure on myself | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 01:30:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we're having a candid chat about how I'm going. How I'm really going! We discuss imposter syndrome, why I've been putting way too much pressure on myself as of late and in the lead up to 2024 and why that has manifested in some serious burnout and illness (don't mind my Covid voice). I also break down my struggles with being disliked, particularly online and how we can manage and redirect the opinions of others to ensure they do not interrupt our journey to being our most authentic selves.</description></item><item><title>136. The psychology of procrastination | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 23:04:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Putting off a task to the last minute might feel good in the moment, but it often leads to a lot of long term consequences and stress. In today's episode we discuss the psychology behind why we procrastinate. Procrastination is often confused with laziness and poor time management, but its so much more than that. Many of us are chronic procrastinators because of factors like: Boredom
Perfectionism and overthinking Poor impulse control The pleasure principle
Anxiety regulation
Enjoying the urgency, adrenaline and pressure of doing things last minute We break down all those causes of procrastination, alongside my SIX crucial tips for managing your chronic procrastination, from chunking, to the 80/20 rule, self imposed deadlines and using social accountability.</description></item><item><title>135. Emotional eating | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320018/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 00:31:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our relationship with food is so much more psychological then it appears to be, and the evidence for that can be seen with emotional eating. Sometimes we eat as a way to process or regulate our emotions, rather than from actual hunger. This can disrupt our relationship with food and lead us to develop unhealthy coping mechanisms. In today's episode, we discuss: The psychology behind emotional eating
Why we emotionally eat
The impact of our hormones and stress response How diet culture is putting food in control The truth about intuitive eating Tips to manage your emotional eating
And more!</description></item><item><title>134. The psychology behind the "ick" | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320019/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 00:48:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320019/</guid><description>Podcast Description You're dating someone new and suddenly, they show up to a date wearing crocs, or wear goggles to the beach and you get the ick. You immediately lose all attraction to them, you feel the immediate need to end the relationship, why is that? In this episode we break down some of the surprising psychology behind the ick, including the links to our intuition, emotional unavailability, rejection sensitivity and more, but also why the ick isn't always a death sentence.</description></item><item><title>133. Feeling lost after university and career anxiety | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320020/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 01:15:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320020/</guid><description>Podcast Description The post graduation blues can leave us feeling incredibly anxious, aimless and stuck, battling with the question of 'what next'? We are faced with a number of significant changes and transitions such as increasing distance between us and our friends, financial anxiety and having to make significant career decisions. All of this can culminate is a sense of choice overload and paralysis, but also a overwhelming sense of nostalgia to return back to the 'good old days'.</description></item><item><title>132. The psychology of Taylor Swift | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 22:50:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Taylor Swift is possibly the most famous person in the world right now, beloved by millions, streamed by billions, her eras tour may have even saved the US economy. What is it about her as an artist, a celebrity and a person that is so uniquely captivating? How has she continued to reach new heights, new fans and achieve such career longevity? And why do so many of us feel an emotional connection to her and her music, despite never having met her?</description></item><item><title>131. Why does life feel boring? | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 04:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320022/</guid><description>Podcast Description We have all had that experience of feeling bored with our everyday life, whereby we look around and our daily experiences have lost some of the colour and excitement. Why is that the case? Psychology can provide some explanations including: A lack of novelty and new experiences
Seasonal affective disorder Overstimulation from our phones and social media Social comparison The benefits of a dopamine detox
We discuss all these reasons and more, as well as what we can do to change that!</description></item><item><title>130. Relationship anxiety and being 'forever single' in your 20s ft. Katy Bellotte | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 00:06:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320023/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today's episode we bring on the wonderful, Katy Bellotte, to discuss everything love, dating and relationship in our 20s. We discuss what it feels like to have never had a relationship in your 20s, the milestone anxiety and societal pressure that makes us to feel like we need to settle for someone we're not fully committed to, feeling behind and what it feels like to finally find the one.</description></item><item><title>129. The psychology of oversharing | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320024/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 00:48:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320024/</guid><description>Podcast Description We all know the feeling of oversharing at a party or work function and feeling the sting of embarrassment and shame the next day. So why do we feel the need to overshare with others, even though it has emotional and mental consequences? In this episode we explore the psychology of oversharing, from the difference between trauma dumping and authenticity, why oversharing soothes our social anxiety or can be used subconsciously to fast-track a relationship.</description></item><item><title>128. When it's time to walk away from a relationship | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320025/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 00:16:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320025/</guid><description>Podcast Description One of the hardest dilemmas we have to face is when it's time to walk away from someone you still love because you know the relationship isn’t right for you. We can often find ourselves stuck in a constant battle between knowing what is right, and what our heart wants us to do. In this episode we break down the five key signs its time to walk away, particularly for those of us in our 20s, and why these reasons matter the most, exploring ideas of: Fatal Attraction Theory
The biology behind our 'gut instinct' The Reciprocity Principle Equity Theory Sunk costs Expectant thinking Fear of being lonely or of the unknown
We also explore why we find it so difficult, the reasons that hold us back, including as the stigma around being the one to initiate the breakup and feeling like a failure for your relationship not working out.</description></item><item><title>127. Can we be too self aware? | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320026/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 05:29:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320026/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a question I have been asking myself a lot recently as someone who is VERY invested in the self-help space. Have we reached a point where we are too aware of our problems, faults, thoughts, actions and behaviours? Self awareness can free us from so many mental restrictions, it allows us to make better decisions, be a better friend, a better person, invest in our dreams and values.</description></item><item><title>126. How to heal a fear of abandonment | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320027/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 01:08:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Many of us battle with a deep-rooted fear and anxiety that those we love will leave us. Maybe we have been hurt in a past relationship, or witnessed a messy divorce or the passing of ones we love and we have unconsciously learned to associated vulnerability, intimacy and love with pain and disappointment. This fear of abandonment can cause us to sabotage otherwise perfectly healthy relationships or to push people away out of an irrational fear they will leave us, only to end up just as alone as if they had.</description></item><item><title>125. The psychology of dating apps ft. Bumble | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320028/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 23:26:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320028/</guid><description>Podcast Description The new reality of dating in your 20s is that the majority of us who are single are on the dating apps. Tinder, Hinge and Bumble have completely changed how we approach dating by expanding our options, making dating convenient and accessible and are increasingly becoming the way many of us meet our partners. A study conducted by the Pew Research Centre found that almost half of us between 18 and 29 have used a dating app.</description></item><item><title>124. Moving to a new city in our 20s | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320029/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 02:10:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320029/</guid><description>Podcast Description A lot of us in our 20s feel the urge to upend everything and move to a new city - maybe for work, for a partner or just for the pure adventure of a new experience and environment. So in this episode we're going to break down why our 20s are perhaps the best time to make this major life change, from the lack of external responsibilities to the psychological benefits it brings, including self reflection, promoting a growth mindset and realising our ideal selves.</description></item><item><title>123. A life update - healthy love, moving overseas, dealing with online criticism | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320030/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 03:29:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320030/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's been a while since my last life update so I thought we would take a bit of a breather and sit down for a nice chatty episode, just for you all the loyal podcast listeners, discussing all the recent changes and surprises that have been transpiring in my life as of late. From discovering what a healthy relationship looks like after years of tragic dating stories, the end of my single era, to moving to NYC and writing a book (!</description></item><item><title>122. The pressure to be exceptional in our 20s | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320031/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 00:13:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Increasingly, those of us in our 20s are facing an exceeding pressure to be exceptional and have a million accomplishments and accolades under our belt. If we are not successful, what are we worth? Examples like the Forbes 30 under 30, the wunderkind phenomena and young success stories all make us feel like we're not achieving enough or are falling behind. Today we're going to break down exactly why we feel this way, using theories around self determination, observational learning and social comparison.</description></item><item><title>121. Befriending your social anxiety | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320032/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 01:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each of us deals with feelings of embarrassment, awkwardness and feeling social self conscious every now and then. But social anxiety can cause us a level of emotional, mental and physical discomfort that disrupts out ability to build authentic connection and can hold us back. In this episode we break down the psychology of social anxiety, particularly deconstructing the belief that everyone is judging us or that the opinions of others matter.</description></item><item><title>120. Understanding your ego | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320033/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 22:37:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320033/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week's episode we discuss the psychology of your ego and what its trying to tell us! Ego can feel nasty and entitled but it comes from a place of deep insecurity that we need to unpack before we can truly understand ourselves. We look at the 6 signs your ego is in control, where ego comes from and how to replace it with self esteem and humility.</description></item><item><title>119. How to make the most of your 20s pt.2 | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320034/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 07:31:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Love, dating and friendships can feel like a black box in our 20s when we're trying to make the most out of our formative years. None of us have the answers or a guide to some of our biggest questions - how do I actually make new friends, how many friends should I have, should I be settling down this early or exploring my options? In part two of this series we breakdown how to make the most out of our personal relationships during this decade.</description></item><item><title>118. How to make the most of your 20s pt.1 | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320035/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 07:18:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320035/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do we actually make the most of our 20s? Career anxiety, feeling stuck, taking risks and managing our money (do we spend or save) are all big concerns we have in this period. So how do we manage these dilemmas and choices to create our dream life in our 20s, and what does that dream life even look like? In part one of our mini series, we examine the major decisions we make during this decade around our future and how we can approach them to get the best outcome.</description></item><item><title>117. The psychology of trauma ft. Dr MC McDonald | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320036/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 01:03:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trauma seems like a bit of a black box at times, something that we all experience as part of our life journey as humans but surrounded by a lot of misinformation. In this episode, we are joined by our guest, Dr MC McDonald, author of The Trauma Response Is Never Wrong to break down all of the science and psychology behind why we react to trauma the way we do, suppressed memories, what actually counts as 'traumatic' and the impact of trauma on our body.</description></item><item><title>116. Is it love, or are you just attached? | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320037/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 00:04:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Love and attachment feel very similar, and it's very easy to confuse the two especially in the early stages of dating when we are overwhelmed by infatuation and the novelty of a new relationship. However, they are very different. Whilst love is a deliberate choice, mutual, selflessness, and long lasting, attachment is unconscious, can be one-sided and based on what serves our needs. Confusing these two feelings can cause us to pursue the wrong people, invest too quickly and, at times, end up hurt and disappointed.</description></item><item><title>115. Let's talk about depression in our 20s | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320038/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320038/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, I want to talk about depression. And not just from a psychological and scientific perspective but also from a personal perspective, sharing parts of my story. It's not something I've talked about much on the podcast but recently I've really come to terms with my own shame and stigma and I want to discuss where I'm at now, the journey I've been on and how its impacted the life I've created for myself in my 20s.</description></item><item><title>114. Healing your inner teen | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320039/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 02:26:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Everyone is talking about healing our inner child, but what about our inner teenager? We experience certain things in adolescence that we don't experience as children and these can manifest in different behaviours, defence mechanisms and emotional wounds that continue with us into adulthood. Whilst the inner child is seen as gentle and vulnerable, the inner teen may be angry, misunderstood and lonely. So in this episode we break some some of the psychology and theories behind healing your inner teen, including the interactions with our hormones, certain life experiences and the impact of our first romantic encounters and sexual experiences.</description></item><item><title>113. Forgiving yourself for past mistakes | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320040/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 01:05:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320040/</guid><description>Podcast Description All of us are going to mess up. In our 20s and every decade thereafter. But its what we choose to do with those mistakes that's important. In this episode we explore why we often regret past decisions and actions, looking at the development of our brain and personality, we also explore the distinction between regret and guilt and why both emotions may actually be protecting us from future pain.</description></item><item><title>112. Your ex moved on - now what? | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320041/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 01:30:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320041/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s something we all inevitably experience in our dating lives, the pain of a break-up, saying goodbye to someone we loved and then, one day, the realisation that your ex has moved on and is with someone new. It can be incredibly confronting and painful, so today we're going to explore exactly why it hurts, even if deep down, we know we were never going to work. We will dive into the psychological ideas and theories behind rosy retrospection, social comparison, our self worth and the emotional and psychological closure that occurs when our ex moves on.</description></item><item><title>111. The healing power of nature | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320042/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 02:52:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320042/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we're discussing the secret and the science behind the healing powers of nature. Our generation has become increasingly detached from the outdoors and our wild roots, with over 90% of our days spent indoors or on a screen, often at the expense of our mental wellbeing, sense of self, psychological and spiritual connection with the land and overall physical health. In this episode we explore ideas around nature deficit disorder, recent longitudinal studies on the impacts of green spaces on our mental health and practices such as forest bathing, forest schools, water therapy and what we can learn from the deep connection that Indigenous groups have with the land.</description></item><item><title>110. The psychology of hyperindependence | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320043/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 02:20:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Independence is highly regarded as an admirable personality trait - we are obsessed with people who are self made, who solo travel, pay their own bills and don't seem to need anyone. However, our sense of independence can become problematic when we approach the point of hyper-independency. Hyper-independence refers to an excessive sense of self sufficiency and self reliance, in which we deny the help of others, prefer doing things on our own and avoid emotional vulnerability.</description></item><item><title>109. Why are we so hard on ourselves? | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320044/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 04:25:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320044/</guid><description>Podcast Description So often in life, we are our own worst enemies. The meanest and loudest voice in our head is our own. So why are we so hard on ourselves? In this episode we break down the psychological underpinnings behind our inner critic, from the proposed evolutionary role of negative self talk, to the influence of our upbringing including the distinction between conditional and unconditional positive regard, parental expectations and childhood bullying.</description></item><item><title>108. The psychology of gaslighting | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320045/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:39:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320045/</guid><description>Podcast Description The term 'gaslighting' has grown in popularity in recent years and become part of our shared psychobabble, giving our generation the language to describe a pattern of behaviour that has existed for centuries. This week on the podcast, we explore a recent story in the media on gaslighting and dive into what gaslighting actually means from a psychological perspective. We explore the origins of the term, how it references pop culture, the six behavioural patterns adopted by gaslighters and the links to narcissism and pathological lying.</description></item><item><title>107. How to get out of a rut | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320046/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 04:17:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320046/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week's episode we discuss why we fall into a so called 'rut' and how to pull ourselves out of it and rekindle our sense of self! Our 20s represent a transition into adulthood where we can find ourselves more and more detached from ourselves, uninspired, unmotivated, unexcited by life. The reasons for why this occurs varies, from the transition to full-time work, experiencing failure, the monotony of daily routine and even chronic stress.</description></item><item><title>106. Overcoming trauma and complex PTSD ft. Amy B Chesler | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320047/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 09:05:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320047/</guid><description>Podcast Description TW: Domestic violence, sexual abuse. In her early 20s, Amy suffered an unimaginable loss. Her mother was murdered at the hands of her brother. But what came next is an even more incredible story of growth, advocacy and overcoming adversity and trauma. In this week's episode, we speak to Amy about trauma in our 20s and how we can push through grief and loss. We discuss the power of positive self talk, the psychology of complex PTSD, unlearning generational trauma and how to use your pain to help others.</description></item><item><title>105. The stigma of being single | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320048/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 03:08:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Being single has never been more common, with more people being single than ever before in history. And yet, we still experience a great degree of social and internal stigma, and even shame, around our relationship status. From the comments of family or friends saying that "you'll find someone soon", to the movies where marriage and partnership is the happy ending, sometimes we feel the need to settle in order to be happy or live up to societies expectations.</description></item><item><title>104. The psychology of overthinking and indecision | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320049/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 02:11:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Overthinking can sometimes feel like an endless mental maze that we're trapped in. This tendency to overthink can also lead to chronic indecisiveness and obsessive acknowledgement of the opinions of others. But overthinking is much more common that when we think, and may actually indicate a greater sense of self awareness and emotional intelligence. In this episode we explore why we have a tendency to overthink, from the illusion of control, to perfectionism, childhood learning and the link to ADHD and depressive rumination.</description></item><item><title>103. How to be completely unique | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320050/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:20:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320050/</guid><description>Podcast Description The desire to be unique and individual is one that we all feel, especially in our 20s as we begin to establish our 'adult' identity and make efforts to distinguish ourselves. In this weeks episode we discuss seven major tips and strategies for being the most interesting and unique person in any room - from embracing unconventional thinking, rejecting the herd mentality of trends and the desire to be the "</description></item><item><title>102. Queer identity in our 20s ft. Claud Bailey | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320051/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 04:47:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320051/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we sit down for an intimate conversation with the incredible Claud Bailey, a queer film director and queer youth advocate based in Sydney, Australia to discuss what our gender and sexuality means for our 20s. We dive into the meaning of community, gender expression, the beauty of queerness and how to navigate coming of age as a queer person in the 21st century, along with the role of being a responsible and compassionate ally.</description></item><item><title>101. The psychology of ghosting | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320052/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:58:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we're discussing the increasing prevalence of ghosting in modern dating. The use of dating apps has created a sense of choice overload, whilst social media has simultaneously allowed us a sense of online anonymity and diminished our ability to communicate, resulting in a rise in ghosting. Being ghosted can leave us craving emotional closure and feeling a sense of rejection. However, there are a number of psychological motivations behind why people ghost us, including emotional unavailability, emotional intelligence, the Dark Triad of narcissism, psychopathy and machiavellianism, but also people pleasing tendencies and convenience.</description></item><item><title>100. What I've learned from 2 years of podcasting | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320053/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 06:43:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320053/</guid><description>Podcast Description HAPPY 100th EPISODE! In this week's episode, we are celebrating two very special milestones - 100 episodes of The Psychology of your 20s and the 2 year anniversary of the show. I decided to sit down and answer some of your questions around what I've learned from this experience, what advice I would give, how I'm going, my future plans, why heartbreak gave me the best gift I could have asked for and give some lighting round advice to my most asked questions.</description></item><item><title>99. The myth of the 5-year plan | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320054/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 05:51:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320054/</guid><description>Podcast Description In our 20s we can often feel like we have to have a plan for our lives or a 5 year vision for where we want to be. This can cause us to be boxed in and blind to the surprises opportunities that life throws our way. The idea of a 5 year plan is a myth and in today's episode, we are going to break down why. From societal conventions of a 'good' life, the butterfly effect, the psychology behind impulsive decisions and goal setting and the need for a sense of control over the chaos of our 20s, we explore all that and more to uncover why your school counsellor was wrong and you DON'T need a five year plan for your life.</description></item><item><title>98. The psychology of self sabotage | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320055/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 03:11:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sometimes our biggest enemy isn't others, it's ourselves. Self sabotage is a complicated psychological experience whereby we unconsciously undermine our own goals and wellbeing because of an implicit belief that we don't deserve our success, are afraid of failure, or cannot allow ourselves to be happy. From dating people we shouldn't, to procrastination, indecision, doom scrolling and self destructive behaviours, it all comes down to our unconscious beliefs about our self worth.</description></item><item><title>97. The long distance dilemma | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320056/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 02:17:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Long distance in any relationship can be hard, so why do we choose to do it? In our 20s our relationships take on an increased level of seriousness, but at the same time we are also presented with so many wonderful decisions to travel, move new places, try new positions and jobs and figure out what we want from our lives. However, our partners don't always make the same decision.</description></item><item><title>96. I feel ugly | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320057/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 02:18:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Recently I've been feeling, as the episode title says, ugly. My relationship with my body and sense of 'attractiveness' has always been complicated and in the past few months, certain events and experiences have only exacerbated a lot of the insecurities I've had since childhood. So I wanted to talk about it, because I know I'm not the only one. Our 20s involve a lot of self growth, coming into our own identity and reframing our mindset on appearance and our relationships with our bodies.</description></item><item><title>95. Dating with intention in our 20s | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320058/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:55:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dating in our 20s can feel like an uphill battle, and many of us are seeking an alternative to casual relationships and meaningless flings or hookups. This week on the podcast, we discuss how we can adopt an intentional approach to our romantic life and dating decisions, in particular, how this can free us from some of the pressure and stress that accompanies dating in our 20s. We discuss the psychology and research behind self awareness, value and goal orientation, self concept, understanding what others want and how to lower your expectations and meet people organically so that we can embrace the excitement and fun of meeting new people and forming meaningful connections.</description></item><item><title>94. Chronic illness and overcoming adversity ft. Bradley Dryburgh | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320059/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 18:22:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320059/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2020, Bradley found himself questioning death. He was 24 and lying in hospital bed with bleeding lungs caused by his condition, cystic fibrosis. Three years later, he has run multiple marathons, left behind his successful career as a realtor and is now running his podcast 'A Lot To Talk About', sharing his story. This week we break down his journey, including his philosophy towards overcoming the adversity we all face in our 20s, whatever that may be.</description></item><item><title>93. How to build consistency | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320060/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 06:55:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320060/</guid><description>Podcast Description All of us in our 20s have some goal or ambition that we are striving for and whatever that may be, consistency is the key to our success. On this episode we break down how we can use the psychology behind consistency and motivation to help achieve our goals, from microhabits to delayed gratification, self compassion, a monthly routine and incremental reinforcement. We also examine some of the science and social psychology behind productivity and how society has dictated the ways in which we pursue our goals and why we might have it wrong.</description></item><item><title>92. The psychology of platonic soulmates | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320061/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 05:43:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Platonic soulmates represent the idea that our deepest relationships and our strongest bonds don't have to be romantic, sexual or based on attraction, they can be between us and our friends. This idea of platonic soulmates has been on the rise, however, it's not a new phrase. Plato, the ancient greek philosopher, was one of the first people to identify this feeling of deep connection and understanding between two individuals that appears to be inexplicable or spiritual.</description></item><item><title>91. Overcoming milestone anxiety in our 20s | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320062/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 00:43:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320062/</guid><description>Podcast Description In our 20s, we face an increasing sense of pressure to reach certain important, life milestones, such as getting into our first relationship, graduating university, finding our career path, getting engaged and so many more. When we don't meet the expectations or the timeline that society gives us, we can feel like failures and begin to self sabotage or ruminate on our faults and flaws. This week we're going to explore the psychology behind milestone anxiety - the experience of stress and unease when we haven't achieved certain milestones by a certain age - why it occurs, the influence of social comparison and conditioning, how we can combat this feeling, practice self compassion and be excited by our own journey through life, and our 20s.</description></item><item><title>90. The psychology of open relationships | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320063/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 04:08:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we're diving into the psychology behind open relationships in our 20s - why people are attracted to the idea of non-monogamy, how they operate, the boundaries that are set, how to navigate sexual jealousy and whether they actually work? Open relationships have become an increasingly popular alternative to traditional monogamy, but they are not a new concept. Why are some people more curious when it comes to open relationships?</description></item><item><title>89. Maintaining your identity in a relationship | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320064/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 03:07:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320064/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, I'm joined by the fabulous Al and Sal, the hosts of Two Broke Chicks, to discuss how we can maintain our identity in a relationship, especially in our 20s. Our romantic relationships are fundamental elements of our identity and we all crave the warm and fuzzy feelings that accompany dating someone wonderful. But how do we ensure that our partners and relationship do not take over our lives, our identity and our independence?</description></item><item><title>88. The psychology of dreams | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320065/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 03:36:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320065/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast we are breaking down the psychology of our dreams - why we dream, the role of our brain, what our dreams mean, repressed desires, nightmares and even the role of daydreaming for our mental wellbeing. If you've ever wondered about your weird dreams, some of the scientific theories and whether you are a maladaptive daydreamer, this episode is for you as we jump into the fascinating science and psychology behind these imaginative, colourful hallucinations.</description></item><item><title>87. Should you quit your 9-5? | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320066/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 04:51:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Many of us in our 20's have become disillusioned with the 9-5 lifestyle and the reality of working an office job for the rest of our lives. Psychology shows us that the 9-5 job is not only inefficient but unnatural, leaving us feeling burnt-out, unmotivated, detached from the things that matter and searching for an alternative that offers both freedom and flexibility. This week, I talk about my own journey of leaving behind my 9-5 job and pursuing the podcast full time; from why I made my decision, what the transition has been like and my advice and tips on how you can do the same.</description></item><item><title>86. Perfectionism and academic anxiety | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320067/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 02:50:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Perfectionism is on the rise amongst young people, and in this episode we break down exactly what it means to have perfectionist tendencies. We examine the theories of personality, our upbringing, links to OCD and ADHD and what it means for academic performance and anxiety. We also dive into some of the methods for minimising our perfectionism, including visualisation, the 80-20 rule, cognitive behavioural therapy and positive self talk to show how life isn't perfect, so you don't have to be either.</description></item><item><title>85. 'Daddy issues' and dating in your 20s ft. Violet Benson | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320068/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320068/</guid><description>Podcast Description This Friday we sit down with the wonderful Violet Benson, host of the podcast Almost Adulting, also known for her famous meme account, Daddy Issues, as we discuss everything dating in our 20s, specifically the truth about daddy issues, healing childhood trauma and parental relationships and how to reestablish your boundaries and standards. That, and so much more. Listen now!
Follow Violet everywhere: Almost Adulting podcast - https://open.spotify.com/show/7IY1Gjc1uktmDCmNLA0HXo?si=14792ff30f75463e</description></item><item><title>84. Loneliness is not your enemy! | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320069/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 05:56:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320069/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we break down the psychological, biological and evolutionary underpinnings of loneliness and break down some of the stigma around feeling lonely in your 20's. This decade is full of a number of significant life transitions and changes that can lead us to feel isolated and detached, but loneliness sometimes get's a bad wrap. We explore how we can cultivate a better relationship with loneliness by understanding the instinctual urges behind this feeling, embracing solitude and reframing the narrative around exactly how common it is to feel lonely in your 20's.</description></item><item><title>83. The psychology of 'lucky girl syndrome' | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320070/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 02:06:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320070/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode we break down the science and psychology of the internet and TikTok sensation of "lucky girl syndrome". We explore the ideas and theories behind self fulfilling prophecies, confirmation bias, goal-oriented behaviour, brain anatomy and the power of positive affirmations on shifting our mindset to reveal whether lucky girl syndrome is fact or fiction, and where ideas of privilege and personality come in. Listen now! See omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>82. The psychology of emotional unavailability | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320071/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 11:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320071/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we are discussing the science and psychology of emotional unavailability and breaking down the misconceptions and myths about emotional unavailability in our 20's, particularly when it comes to dating people who won't commit. We’re going to break down exactly what emotional unavailability versus availability looks like and how it manifests in relationships, what emotional unavailability means on a personal, individual level, the difference between men and women when it comes to this concept and how to develop emotional availability and grow closer to the ones we love and attract those who are equally emotionally available.</description></item><item><title>81. Date yourself instead ft. Lyss Boss | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320072/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 12:52:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320072/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we are joined by Lyss Boss, the host of Date Yourself Instead, to discuss dating in our 20's, particularly what it means to deliberately choose to be single, how we can learn from past relationships and heal our attachment styles. Alongside this we dive into the psychology behind karmic relationships, repeating toxic patterns in relationships and learning to move on through authenticity and creativity. Listen now! See omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>80. Why you should take risks in your 20’s | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320073/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320073/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we discuss the psychology behind why we all should be prepared to talk risks and push beyond our comfort zone in our 20’s. This topic has a lot of personal relevance for me right now, which I share in this episode, but there is also a lot of science and psychology that is incredibly compelling and persuasive as to why taking a risk is a good thing!</description></item><item><title>79. The psychology of breakups | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320074/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Breakups and heartache are a universal experience in our 20’s. But what exactly happens to our minds, our bodies and our emotions at the end of a relationship? This week we will break down the psychology and the science behind breakups, heartbreak and moving on. We will explore the theory of withdrawal, stages of grief, conditioning and the psychology behind why ‘no contact’ really does work to hopefully provide some solace to all the heartbroken out there on what exactly a breakup does to our psychology.</description></item><item><title>78. Let’s talk about eating disorders | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320075/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320075/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode we break down the psychology behind eating disorders - from anorexia to bulimia and binge eating disorder. Amalie Lee, the Host of the Recovery Talk podcast joins us to discuss her own experience with anorexia and as an eating disorder recovery coach as we break down the triggers and origins of eating disorders, the misconceptions, how they impact our psychological and emotional well-being and the journey to healing and recovery.</description></item><item><title>77. Why do we worry about the future? | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320076/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320076/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast we discuss the experience of worrying and overthinking the future. From anticipatory anxiety, the the illusion of control, paradox of choice and self preservation, anxiety about the future has a lot of psychological origins that we will unpack in todays episode to try and find freedom from future spiralling and embrace the moment.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>76. Hookup culture and casual dating in your 20’s ft. Louise Rumball | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320077/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320077/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we dive into the psychology behind hookup culture and casual dating in our 20’s. We are joined by the host of The Openhouse Podcast, Louise Rumball, as we discuss the cultural and societal changes that have contributed to this sexual liberation, what happens to our brain during and after a hookup, empowering ourselves through pleasure but also healthy boundaries and the science and personal stories behind why casual dating may not be for everyone.</description></item><item><title>75. Healing your inner child! | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320078/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320078/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the show we dive into what it really means to heal your inner child. From reparenting to relearning your attachment style, the power of play and protecting your inner childlike wonder and curiosity, we discuss the psychology and everyday practices we can enact to connect and heal our inner child wounds and bring that joy and vulnerability to our adult lives. Listen now!See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>74. Outgrowing friendships | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320079/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320079/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the show we deep dive into why we outgrow our friendships as we enter our 20’s. We often have a romanticised idea that friendships last a lifetime, but during this decade we realise that it’s a lot more nuanced. We explore the main factors behind the friendship “fizzle”, why it’s a normal part of growing up, how we can handle the emotions that come along with and learn to value solitude and be selective when it comes to our friendships.</description></item><item><title>73. The complete guide to therapy in your 20’s | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320080/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320080/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we deep dive into everything there is to know about therapy in our 20’s. From identifying when you need therapy, to finding the right therapist, the different types of therapy that are available, some of the misconceptions about therapy and the details of your first session, this episode provides all the information to remove some of the mysticism and stigma behind getting some help for your mental health in your 20’s.</description></item><item><title>72. Attachment styles, non-negotiables and dating men ft. Chidera Eggerue | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320081/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 11:29:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320081/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week I am joined by Chidera Eggerue, otherwise known as the Slumflower, host of the Slumflower Hour and author of the Number 1 Sunday Times Bestsellers What a Time to be Alone (2018) and How to Get Over a Boy (2020) to discuss attachment styles, how to set boundaries and non-negotiables when dating men. We discuss the own hard lessons we’ve learnt through our intimate relationships, how to reclaim your power, the psychology behind why we accept the bare minimum and so much more.</description></item><item><title>71. The secret to self confidence | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320082/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320082/</guid><description>Podcast Description This weeks episode we deep dive into the psychology self confidence and how we can master our sense of confidence and self assurance to be the best versions of ourselves. We discuss the elements that make up confidence, the impact of nature versus nurture and the difference between self confidence and arrogance. We also explore some of the evidence-based strategies that we can use to improve our self esteem and why “faking it till you make it” is more than just a saying.</description></item><item><title>70. The psychology of gossip | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320083/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 23:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320083/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this weeks episode we discuss the evolutionary and psychological reasons behind why we gossip. We explore the origins of gossip, the different forms of gossip and how it influences our 20’s, particularly our social connections and sense of community. We also dive into the downsides of rumours and slander, how gossip has evolved with social media and discuss how we can break free of the cycle of gossip in our lives and create more positive conversations and relationships.</description></item><item><title>69. Codependent relationships in our 20’s | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320084/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 00:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320084/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we discuss codependency and how it can manifest in our friendships and relationships in our 20’s. We break down some of the misconceptions around codependency, the origins of the terms and early signs our relationships may be codependent. We also dive into the difference between healthy dependency and maladapative codependency and how we can recenter and restore balanced and mutual relationships with those in our lives. Thank you to today’s sponsor, Athletic Greens.</description></item><item><title>68. The myth of the “dream job” | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320085/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320085/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we discuss the idea of the dream job, whether it is fact or fiction? We discuss where the idea of the “dream job” comes from, why we feel so much pressure around deciding what we want to do with our lives, career anxiety and how to rebalance our relationship with our professional lives in our 20’s. Listen now to learn more. Thank you to today’s sponsor, Athletic Greens.</description></item><item><title>67. Embracing your authentic self | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320086/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 01:23:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320086/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we discuss the psychology of authenticity and how we can discover and therefore embrace our authentic selves. We discuss what it is to be authentic, why we suffer when we are disconnected from our true selves and the daily practices we can incorporate to live authentically, be vulnerable and consistent with our core self and values. Thank you to todays sponsor Athletic Greens. Please use the following link for a FREE one year supply for immune supporting vitamin D and five free travel packs at www.</description></item><item><title>66. Dating in our 20’s - why we date the wrong people | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320087/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 21:47:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320087/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week I bring on a special guest and a close friend, artist Sydney Farey, to discuss the horrors and surprises of dating in our 20’s. We discuss the psychology behind why we are attracted to the wrong people, the impact of our childhood and early relationships on our romantic lives and how to prioritise yourself whilst we date during our 20’s.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>65. The psychology of New Years Resolutions | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320088/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320088/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we break down the psychology of New Years resolutions, the significance of the new year for making goals and promises to ourselves, why we set New Years resolutions, the typical reasons we tend to fail and how to be successful. We explore self efficacy, personal development theory and the psychology behind failure to understand how we can achieve our 2023 goals.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>64. Tis the season to feel lonely | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320089/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 07:16:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320089/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we discuss loneliness, particularly around the holiday season. Why is it that we feel so lonely during that period between the holidays and the new year, whether we are surrounded by family or spending our time alone and what are some of the explanations for this feeling. We discuss the benefits and downsides of solitude, how to overcome loneliness and why the holiday season can be so difficult.</description></item><item><title>63. Setting boundaries and sticking to them | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320090/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 12:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320090/</guid><description>Podcast Description With the holiday season I thought it would be a great time to discuss how we can set boundaries within our closest relationships. From emotional, physical, financial to spiritual boundaries, how can we establish realistic and sustainable boundaries in our lives and what do we do when someone violates these. Thank you to todays sponsor Athletic Greens. Please use the following link for a FREE one year supply for immune supporting vitamin D and five free travel packs at www.</description></item><item><title>62. Navigating a quarter life crisis and feeling lost | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320091/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 12:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320091/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we discuss our quarter life crisis! Whilst it may be a normal experience for those of us in our 20’s, the experience can be incredibly scary and stressful. We dive into how to navigate a quarter life crisis, the characteristics of this period, why it’s important for our growth and how to move through this experience and come out the other side as successful and healed individuals.</description></item><item><title>61. Why we compare ourselves to others | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320092/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 10:14:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320092/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we discuss social comparison, the good, the bad, the psychology. We talk about why it is that we compare ourselves to others, the impacts of social comparison and how to break the cycle of judging our attributes and characteristics compared to others.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>60. Seasonal depression and the ‘winter blues’ | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320093/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 08:22:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320093/</guid><description>Podcast Description With many of us entering the colder, winter months, understanding what seasonal depression is and how it impacts our mood, energy levels, appetite and mental well-being is crucial. This week we break down the science and psychology behind seasonal affective disorder and how we can overcome the ‘winter blues’ brought on by the colder months.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>59. The psychology of diet culture and embracing our bodies | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320094/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 22:59:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320094/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we discuss the insidious nature of diet culture and how it convinces us we need to change our bodies to be happier. We discuss how diet culture has become so influential through normalisation, repetition across social media, social approval and early learning in childhood. Finally we talk about how to push back against the negative beliefs and behaviours ingrained in us by diet culture and embrace our bodies.</description></item><item><title>58. Can ex’s be friends ft. My Ex-Boyfriend | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320095/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 08:19:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320095/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week I have invite on a special guest to chat about whether exes can be friends. Our conclusion, well … you’ll have to listen. We talk through how we fell in love, why we broke up and whether we could get back together. Thank you to todays sponsor Athletic Greens. Please use the following link for a FREE one year supply for immune supporting vitamin D and five free travel packs at www.</description></item><item><title>57. The psychology of toxic parents | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320096/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 10:30:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320096/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode we discuss the characteristics of toxic parents and the impact they have on our development and adulthood. We dive into narcissistic parental abuse, intergenerational trauma, overcoming a toxic upbringing and how to establish boundaries.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>56. Why am I so unhappy? | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320097/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 11:19:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320097/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do we explain the feeling where we have everything we could want, but we still feel so unhappy and dissatisfied? In this episode we explore some of the reasons for unhappiness in the face of success and everything we have ever wanted to dispel some of the stigma around sadness, depressive episodes and the normalcy of feeling unhappy.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>55. Dealing with rejection | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 02:21:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rejection can be such a blow to our self-esteem, whether it’s romantic, with friends, at work or during our studies. Rejection can be a painful experience, but psychology can explain many of the reasons why we look to avoid rejection and how we can overcome experiences of rejection, especially in our 20’s. Thank you to todays sponsor Athletic Greens. Please use the following link for a FREE one year supply for immune supporting vitamin D and five free travel packs at www.</description></item><item><title>54. Single, happy and alone in our 20’s | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320099/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 19:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320099/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we discuss how to be happy being alone and all the amazing benefits that come with single hood in our 20’s! How can we cultivate a life we love despite being single and why do we crave love even when we are happy being alone?See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>53. The power of microhabits | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320100/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 10:05:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320100/</guid><description>Podcast Description BONUS EPISODE. This week we discuss the power of micro habits and how we can integrate them into our everyday lives to create the lifestyle changes we are after in our 20’s.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>52. Career anxiety, disillusionment and feeling stuck | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320101/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 04:14:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our careers and work can be a major point of stress in our 20’s and we try to figure out what exactly we’re doing and where we want to go. In this episode we discuss career anxiety, feeling lost and when it’s time for a change. Thank you to this weeks sponsor, Athletic Greens. Please go to athleticgreens.com/Jemma to redeem you offer of 1 year do free vitamin C and 5 free travel packs.</description></item><item><title>51. Overcoming childhood trauma | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320102/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 00:53:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320102/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we discuss trauma in childhood, the way it effects our brain and chemistry, our behaviours and our relationships in adulthood.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>50. Let’s talk about death ft. A Mortuary Technician | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320103/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 23:56:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320103/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are joined this week by Laura, a student mortuary technician in Australia to discuss her experiences and role and how she thinks about death and the meaning of a good life on this special guest episode.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>49. Financial anxiety, money and relationships | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320104/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:21:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320104/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week I’m joined by Lindsay, a Financial Therapist who runs Mind Money Balance to discuss how we manage anxiety and emotions around money in our 20’s. From healing our childhood relationship with money to dealing with financial boundaries in relationships, we explore the intersection between money and our 20’s in this special, guest episode. Lindsay Bryan-Podvin (she/her) is a biracial financial wellness expert, speaker, and author of the book &amp;ldquo;The Financial Anxiety Solution.</description></item><item><title>48. Identity Crisis! | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320105/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 10:56:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320105/</guid><description>Podcast Description What does identity really mean? And how do we know when we’ve found it, can we ever truly embody our ‘true selves’? In this episode we discuss what it means to undergo massive shifts in our identity and come out of it the other side and how we might assist that journey.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>46. Making friends in your 20’s | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320106/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 10:23:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320106/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we discuss how to make new friendships in our 20’s. We all can recognise how hard it is to make friends as we enter adulthood but what does psychology actually say about this struggle and why is it so difficult as we move beyond our school years into work and the real world.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>45. Soulmates and twin flames | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320107/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 09:01:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are soulmates real? And how do we know if we’ve met the one? This week we discuss the idea of twin flames and soul mates and alternative explanations for the deep connection and chemistry we feel with some people and whether we are destined to meet.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>44. The history and psychology of hormonal birth control | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320108/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 01:09:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320108/</guid><description>Podcast Description How does the pill and hormonal birth control impact our psychological well-being and experiences in our 20’s? This week we discuss the history and origins of the pill and how it interacts with our body and systems. Are the benefits worth the risks and what about the dark history behind the emergence of this common form of female birth control?See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>43. Hustle culture and burnout | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320109/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 12:25:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320109/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week talk about the cultural phenomenon of hustle culture, the rise and grind age of work and professional success. We also discuss the role of burnout in this relationship and how we can recentre our lives to avoid this type of exhaustion and free ourselves of the stress and pressures of the need to always be hustling.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>41. Situationships - boundaries, vulnerability and wanting more | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320110/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 11:41:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320110/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we discuss the tricky topic of situationships in our 20’s - the grey space between casual and committed. How do we establish good boundaries in these relationships or avoid them to begin with? And when do we know it’s over?See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>40. When you feel directionless | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320111/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 10:57:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320111/</guid><description>Podcast Description What can we do when we feel lost and directionless in our 20’s? It’s a common feeling and one shared by many but when you’re in a rut it can be hard to get our. In this episode we discuss actions we can take to recentre ourselves and our vision or mission in life and make big changes to push us forward.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>39. Alcohol and hangxiety | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320112/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 08:17:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320112/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode we talk about the interactions between alcohol and the brain. Alcohol can be a huge part of our lives in our 20’s, as can anxious feelings the morning after drinking so it’s important to understand why our body (and our brain) reacts this way to alcohol and how we can remedy those feelings of stress the next day.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>38. Healing unhealthy attachment styles | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320113/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 10:27:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320113/</guid><description>Podcast Description We discuss the four attachment styles and their implications for the relationships we have in our 20’s. Where did the idea of attachment come from, how relevant are they and can we heal disordered patterns of attachment? Listen in for the answers to those important questionsSee omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>37. How to develop emotional intelligence in your 20’s | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320114/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 10:45:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320114/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we discuss the secrets and successes of emotional intelligence and how to cultivate and grow your EQ in your 20’s. Why is it so important? What are the benefits? And how can we be the most emotionally intelligent versions of ourselves?See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>36. The Psychology of Grief | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320115/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 09:25:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320115/</guid><description>Podcast Description What do we do when we’ve lost someone we’ve loved? In this weeks episode we talk about the confusion and anger, the safeness, following the loss of a loved one. How do we move on and continue to hold the memory of them close?See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>35. BONUS EPISODE: “Don’t talk about us on the podcast” | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320116/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 21:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320116/</guid><description>Podcast Description The girls are back for an episode on love, friendship, first impressions and stereotypes
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>34. Antidepressants | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320117/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 08:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why I went on antidepressants, my experience and the stigma around medication and mental illness.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>33. Social attraction, being ‘cool’ and in-groups | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320118/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 12:20:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320118/</guid><description>Podcast Description What does it mean to be ‘cool’ and why does it matter? In this weeks episode we discuss the importance of social acceptance and why being authentic is actually the key to being socially attractive.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>32. BONUS EPISODE: Girl Talk | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320119/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 03:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320119/</guid><description>Podcast Description A bonus episode of our new segment, Girl Talk. We have three (!!) special guests on to talk life transitions, five year plans and all the goings on of life for us at the moment.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>31. The Anxious Mind | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320120/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 12:21:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320120/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode we discuss anxiety in our 20’s. We talk about the body on anxiety, different anxiety disorders and the unique triggers in our 20’s.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>30. Heartbreak - hurting, healing and thriving ❤️‍🩹 | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320121/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 12:14:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320121/</guid><description>Podcast Description We discuss the biology behind those awful breakup feelings, how to truly let someone go, the stages of grief and whether it’s possible to be friends with you ex.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>29. Loneliness | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320122/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 08:07:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why you’ve been feeling lonely recently because I have been too! We talk about how to embrace loneliness, why your best relationships are just around the corner and the power of gratitude.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>28. Are love languages real? | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320123/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 05:39:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320123/</guid><description>Podcast Description We discuss love languages, what are they, are they real and where did the idea come from? We also talk about recent research done by Hinge on the most common love languages and the modified quiz which now includes two additional love languages.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>27. Is social media corrupting your brain? | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320124/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 05:28:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320124/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we discuss the psychology of social media: how it controls our behaviours, social comparison and the what makes tiktok so addictive.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>26. People pleasing - how to say NO! | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320125/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 02:46:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320125/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we discuss people pleasing: what it is, where it comes from and some interesting links to trauma and gender. We also discuss some strategies for learning how to say no and putting yourself first!See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>25. Conquering failure in your 20’s | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320126/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 01:35:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320126/</guid><description>Podcast Description What does psychology have to say about our fear of failure and how can we change our mindset to one that embraces the mistakes we are inevitably going to make? This week we discuss failure of many sorts in our 20’s: relationships, academic, in the workplace. Tune in!See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>23. Toxic Relationships - Our Experiences ft. Claudia Grenfell-Uijalnd | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320127/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 05:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320127/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode I bring on Claudia as we discuss our experiences in toxic relationships in our 20’s. This is part one of a two part episode.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>22. What are we fighting for - The Psychology of Conflict | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320128/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 10:56:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why do we fight and how can we resolve conflict in a healthy manner? We’re talking about interpersonal conflict today and answering some of the big questions around fighting with those we love.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>21. Catastrophic thinking - When the worst case scenario happens | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320129/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 02:58:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320129/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happens when the worst case scenario happens? Whilst that rarely happens, today we break down catastrophic thinking and why we always expect the worst case scenario.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>20. The Psychology of Lasting Friendships | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320130/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 04:19:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320130/</guid><description>Podcast Description We bring on the longest and nearest friend to talk about how our friendship has lasted for almost a decade, the lessons we’ve learned in 2021, home buying and so much more.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>19. The Psychology of Forgiveness | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320131/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 00:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320131/</guid><description>Podcast Description We start our new year off RIGHT with a view into what psychology has to say about forgiveness and why it is the life changing philosophy we need in our 20’s. We discuss skills, strategies, set backs and benefits in our last episode of 2021 as we start the new year with a clean slate and fresh heartsSee omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>18. The Psychology of Big Life Changes | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320132/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 12:23:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320132/</guid><description>Podcast Description The psychology of the big life changes that we all experience in our 20’s: moving cities, graduations and job changes, it’s that time of the year. But where does the anxiety of big life changes come from? How do we deal with the fear of loneliness and adjustment disorder? Listen to find out.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>17. The Psychology of Cheating | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320133/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 07:54:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why do people cheat? Is the phrase once a cheater, always a cheater correct? Where do conceptions of monogamy come from? Learn in this episode.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>16. BONUS EPISODE: Love Line | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320134/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 01:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320134/</guid><description>Podcast Description We answer some of your pressing love questions and conundrums alongside some special guests - Jack and Meg!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>15. The Psychology of Attraction | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320135/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 09:51:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why do we feel a “spark” for some people and not others? What creates attraction and what is our ‘love map’? Listen in to find out why we are attracted to some people over others and how we can transform passionate love into something stable and long term.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>14. The Psychology of Narcissism | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320136/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 06:35:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320136/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, we talk about narcissism and how to identify narcissists in our own lives. We talk about how their behaviours may make relationships particularly hard, the origins of this personality disorder and whether a cure is possible!See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>12. Let’s Get Friendly with Jack - creativity, life paths and the next great Australian novel | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320137/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 06:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we’re bringing in a special guest, someone very close to the show and my heart. The wonderful Jack - one of our co-writers and podcast inspos - joins the podcast to talk creative pathways, reflecting on your younger years, our inner child and our concepts for the next greatest Australian novels.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>11. The Psychology of Friendship Breakups - the fizzle, toxic people and forgiveness | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320138/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 00:35:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320138/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode we are discussing the psychology behind friendship breakups - why we need to move on from people, the types of toxic friends to look out for, the best way to breakup with a friend and more! Tune in for some juicy psychology and lessons for our 20’s.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>10. The Psychology of Climate Anxiety with Tenaya | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320139/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 01:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we are discussing the psychology of climate anxiety especially in light of recent announcements of a code red for humanity due to climate change. I’m joined by Tenaya, our in house expert on all things sustainability, to discuss how climate anxiety manifests, the psychology of climate denial and how to take care of yourself when faced by dread about the future of the planet. References / things talked about: The IPCC report: https://www.</description></item><item><title>9. The Psychology of Lockdown - a quick check-in and tips and tricks ✨ | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320140/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 05:18:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Howdy! This week we have a little lockdown snapshot where I delve into the psychology behind why lockdowns can be such a killer for our mental health. Indulge in some of my tips abs tricks for staying sane and as always, get vaccinated and stay COVID safe.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>8. The Psychology of Unrequited Love - why we love those who don’t love us back. | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320141/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2021 02:40:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320141/</guid><description>Podcast Description This weeks episode is a deep and highly personal one. Hold onto your horses. We discuss unrequited love - why we feel it, how to fix it and whether it is truly what we can call love ❤️😢See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>7. Would Maddy, Meg and Jemma get into Oxford? | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320142/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 09:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320142/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a bit of a different episode this week! We decided to take the all souls Oxford College entrance exam and answer some of the hardest questions in psychology that are asked of potential students. What are our answers? Listen in to find out.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>6. The Psychology of Jealousy - why we feel so insecure, lessons from polyamory and more | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320143/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2021 03:03:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320143/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we discuss jealousy - the green monster - and break down where jealousy originated from, it’s emotional core and how we can address these feelings.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>5. Let’s Get Friendly with Phoebe - emotional labour, high integrative complexity and boundaries | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320144/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 00:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320144/</guid><description>Podcast Description The second instalment of our let’s get friendly episodes with the glorious Phoebe, here to talk about situationships, setting healthy boundaries and climate anxiety.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>4. The Psychology of FoMO | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320145/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2021 04:38:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320145/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode we discuss the fear of missing out - where FoMO comes, why it feels so shit and potential solutions to stop worrying about what you’re missing out on.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>3. The Psychology of the 9-5 | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320146/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 04:26:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320146/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we talk about the transition to full time work in our 20’s and why the 9-5 is not conducive to a well rounded lifestyle. Special guest Erin also joins us to give her expert opinion.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>1. The Psychology of Imposter Syndrome - why do you feel like such a fraud?? | The Psychology of your 20s</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6973320147/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 00:14:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6973320147/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode we discuss imposter syndrome; where it comes from, why we feel it and why society wants to convince women it’s a gendered problem.See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>