<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Planet Money on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/planet-money/</link><description>Recent content in Planet Money on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:58:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/planet-money/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to be better at hybrid work, according to research | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500360/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:58:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500360/</guid><description>Podcast Description The research keeps coming in on remote work. New evidence suggests working from home, at least full-time, may not be as productive as we once thought. Economist Jose Maria Barrero and his co-authors have reviewed this and other studies for a recent paper. In this episode, we hear about the challenges that come with working fully remote and some best practices for hybrid work. This episode was first published as a bonus episode for our Planet Money+ listeners.</description></item><item><title>What econ says in the shadows | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500359/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 02:31:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500359/</guid><description>Podcast Description Economics Job Market Rumors is a website that&amp;rsquo;s half a job information Wiki, where people post about what&amp;rsquo;s going on inside economics departments, and half a discussion forum, where anyone with an internet connection can ask the economics hive mind whatever they want. All anonymously.
People can talk about finding work, share rumors, and just blow off steam. And that steam can get scaldingly hot. The forum has become notorious for racist and sexist posts, often attacking specific women and people from marginalized backgrounds.</description></item><item><title>Why '90s ads are unforgettable | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500358/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 02:46:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500358/</guid><description>Podcast Description Maybe she&amp;rsquo;s born with it, maybe it&amp;rsquo;s __________.
The best part of waking up, is _______ in your cup!
Got ____?
If you can identify these brands based on tagline alone, it&amp;rsquo;s possible you&amp;hellip; are a 90s kid.
The &amp;rsquo;90s were arguably the peak moment of advertisers trying to make an impression on us that could last for decades. They got us to sing their jingles and say their slogans.</description></item><item><title>The U.S. economy's biggest superpower, explained | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500357/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 20:03:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500357/</guid><description>Podcast Description What if you could borrow money on the cheap and use it to pay for just about anything? The U.S. government can, and does, with U.S. Treasuries. But the market for Treasuries might be more fragile than we know. In this episode, Yesha Yadav of Vanderbilt Law School explains why. This episode was first published as a bonus episode for our Planet Money+ listeners. Today we&amp;rsquo;re making it available for everyone.</description></item><item><title>Why do doctors still use pagers? | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500356/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 23:28:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500356/</guid><description>Podcast Description Remember pagers? They were huge in the 80s — these little devices that could receive short messages. Sir Mix-A-Lot even had a song about them! But then cell phones came along, and pagers more or less became obsolete.
Except there&amp;rsquo;s one group of people who still carry pagers: medical doctors. At a surprisingly large number of hospitals, the pager remains the backbone of communication. Need to ask a doctor a question?</description></item><item><title>Two food and drink indicators | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 23:01:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today on the show, we have two episodes from our daily podcast, The Indicator, about things we spend a lot of time thinking about this time of year: food and drink. First up, we explore how changes in economic conditions led to one of the U.K.&amp;rsquo;s iconic (and affordable) staple foods becoming a luxury.
Then, the story of one Indigenous woman whose small business went head-to-head with Coca-Cola over a trademark dispute.</description></item><item><title>Why are we so bummed about the economy? | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500002/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 23:11:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Would you say that you and your family are better off or worse off, financially, than you were a year ago? Do you think in 12 months we&amp;rsquo;ll have good times, financially, or bad? Generally speaking, do you think now is a good time or a bad time to buy a house?
These are the kinds of questions baked into the Consumer Sentiment Index. And while the economy has been humming along surprisingly well lately, sentiment has stayed surprisingly low.</description></item><item><title>So you want to sell marijuana across state lines | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 23:44:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500003/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the state of Oregon, there is a glut of grass. A wealth of weed. A crisis of chronic. And, jokes aside, it&amp;rsquo;s a real problem for people who work in the cannabis industry like Matt Ochoa. Ochoa runs the Jefferson Packing House in Medford, Oregon, which provides marijuana growers with services like drying, trimming and packing their product. He has seen literal tons of usable weed being left in marijuana fields all over the state of Oregon.</description></item><item><title>A very Planet Money Thanksgiving | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 23:33:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here at Planet Money, Thanksgiving is not just a time to feast on turkey, stuffing, mashed potatoes, green bean casseroles and pie(s). It&amp;rsquo;s also a time to feast on economics. Today, we host a very Planet Money Thanksgiving feast, and solve a few economic questions along the way.
First: a turkey mystery. Around the holidays, demand for turkey at grocery stores goes up by as much as 750%. And when turkey demand is so high, you might think that the price of turkey would also go up.</description></item><item><title>Economic fact in literary fiction | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500005/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 00:48:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Some of the most influential and beloved novels of the last few years have been about money, finance, and the global economy. Some overtly so, others more subtly. It got to the point where we just had to call up the authors to find out more: What brought them into this world? What did they learn? How were they thinking about economics when they wrote these beautiful books? Today on the show: we get to the bottom of it.</description></item><item><title>China's real estate crisis, explained | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 23:33:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500006/</guid><description>Podcast Description China&amp;rsquo;s economic growth for the past few decades has been extraordinary. And much of that growth was fueled by real estate – it was like this miraculous economic engine for the country. But recently, that engine seems to have stopped working. And that has raised all kinds of questions not just for China but also for the global economy. Today on the show, we look at what&amp;rsquo;s happening inside China&amp;rsquo;s real estate market.</description></item><item><title>The alleged theft at the heart of ChatGPT | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500007/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 23:54:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500007/</guid><description>Podcast Description When best-selling thriller writer Douglas Preston began playing around with OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s new chatbot, ChatGPT, he was, at first, impressed. But then he realized how much in-depth knowledge GPT had of the books he had written. When prompted, it supplied detailed plot summaries and descriptions of even minor characters. He was convinced it could only pull that off if it had read his books.
Large language models, the kind of artificial intelligence underlying programs like ChatGPT, do not come into the world fully formed.</description></item><item><title>Never have I ever | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 23:38:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500008/</guid><description>Podcast Description The world of economics has these two different sides. One one side, there are the economists in their cozy armchairs and dusty libraries, high up in their ivory towers. On the other, there&amp;rsquo;s the messy world we&amp;rsquo;re all living in, where those economics are actually playing out. Sometimes, researchers will write about something that they themselves have never actually experienced. Sure, they&amp;rsquo;ve thought about it, theorized, come up with smart analyses&amp;hellip;but that&amp;rsquo;s not the same as getting out of that armchair and into the real world.</description></item><item><title>FTC Chair Lina Khan on Antitrust in the age of Amazon | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500009/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 21:45:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500009/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Lina Khan was in law school back in 2017, she wrote a law review article called &amp;lsquo;Amazon&amp;rsquo;s Antitrust Paradox,&amp;rsquo; that went kinda viral in policy circles. In it, she argued that antitrust enforcement in the U.S. was behind the times. For decades, regulators had focused narrowly on consumer welfare, and they&amp;rsquo;d bring companies to court only when they thought consumers were being harmed by things like rising prices.</description></item><item><title>Antitrust in America (classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 23:25:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Earlier this fall, the Federal Trade Commission filed a high-stakes lawsuit against Amazon.
In that suit, the FTC claims Amazon is a monopoly, and it accuses the company of using anti-competitive tactics to hold onto its market power. It&amp;rsquo;s a big case, with implications for consumers and businesses and digital marketplaces, and for antitrust law itself. That is the highly important but somewhat obscure body of law that deals with competition and big business.</description></item><item><title>All you can eat economics | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500011/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 22:23:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500011/</guid><description>Podcast Description You might expect to find economic concepts in the pages of an economics textbook. But you know where you can really see a lot of economic concepts in action? Buffets.
Here at Planet Money we believe there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of economics going on at the all-you-eat buffet, tucked in between the mountains of brisket and troughs of mashed potatoes. From classic concepts like adverse selection, sunk costs, diminishing marginal returns, to more exotic economic mysteries, like the flat rate pricing bias.</description></item><item><title>Cutting school... by 20% | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 00:08:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Right now, a lot of school districts across the country are making a pretty giant change to the way public education usually works. Facing teacher shortages and struggling to fill vacant spots, they are finding a new recruitment tool: the four-day school week.
Those districts are saying to teachers, &amp;ldquo;You can have three-day weekends all the time, and we won&amp;rsquo;t cut your pay.&amp;rdquo; As of this fall, around 900 school districts – that&amp;rsquo;s about 7% of all districts in the U.</description></item><item><title>How unions are stopped before they start | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500013/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 23:47:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Union membership in the U.S. has been declining for decades. But, in 2022, support for unions among Americans was the highest it&amp;rsquo;s been in decades. This dissonance is due, in part, to the difficulties of one important phase in the life cycle of a union: setting up a union in the first place. One place where that has been particularly clear is at the Volkswagen plant in Chattanooga, Tennessee.</description></item><item><title>Indicator exploder: jobs and inflation | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 21:33:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500014/</guid><description>Podcast Description When someone says &amp;ldquo;the economy is doing well&amp;rdquo;—what does that even mean? Like, for workers, for employers, for the country as a whole? According to what calculation? How do you put a number on it?
The world of economics is filled with all sorts of &amp;ldquo;measuring sticks.&amp;rdquo; GDP. Inflation. Unemployment. Consumer sentiment. Over time, all kinds of government agencies, universities and private companies have come up with different ways to measure facets of the economy.</description></item><item><title>Maria Bamford gets personal (about) finance | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 23:26:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Note: There is swearing in this episode.
In 2017, The University of Minnesota asked comedian Maria Bamford to give their commencement speech. But the University may not have known what it was in for. In her speech, Bamford told the crowd of graduates how much the university offered to pay her (nothing), her counteroffer ($20,000), and the amount they settled on ($10,000), which (after taxes and fees, etc.) she gave away to students in the audience to pay down their student loans.</description></item><item><title>Why the price of Coke didn't change for 70 years (classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 20:22:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Prices go up. Occasionally, prices go down. But for 70 years, the price of a bottle of Coca-Cola didn&amp;rsquo;t change. From 1886 until the late 1950s, a bottle of coke cost just a nickel.
On today&amp;rsquo;s show, we find out why. The answer includes a half a million vending machines, a 7.5 cent coin, and a company president who just wanted to get a couple of lawyers out of his office.</description></item><item><title>A man, a plan, wind power, Uruguay | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500017/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 18:48:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500017/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2007, Uruguay had a massive problem with no obvious fix. The economy of this country of 3.5 million people was growing, but there wasn&amp;rsquo;t enough energy to power all that growth.
Ramón Méndez Galain was, at the time, a particle physicist, but he wanted to apply his scientific mind to this issue. He started researching different energy sources and eventually wrote up a plan for how Uruguay&amp;rsquo;s power grid could transition to renewable energy.</description></item><item><title>The flight attendants of CHAOS | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 23:28:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500018/</guid><description>Podcast Description When contract negotiations between Alaska Airlines and their flight attendants&amp;rsquo; union broke down in 1993, the union had a choice to make.
The union — The Association of Flight Attendants-CWA — knew that if they chose to strike, Alaska Airlines could use a plan. While Alaska Airlines technically couldn&amp;rsquo;t fire someone on strike, they could permanently replace the striking flight attendants with new workers. Essentially, if the union went on strike, they could risk thousands of people&amp;rsquo;s jobs.</description></item><item><title>A trucker hat mystery, the curse of September and other listener questions | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500019/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 21:18:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ba-dee-yah! Say do you remember? Ba-dee-yah! Questions in September!
That&amp;rsquo;s right - it&amp;rsquo;s time for Listener Questions!
Every so often, we like to hear from listeners about what&amp;rsquo;s on their minds, and we try to get to the bottom of their economic mysteries. On today&amp;rsquo;s show, we have questions like:
Why is September historically the worst month for the stock market?
How did the Bass Pro Shops hat get so popular in Ecuador?</description></item><item><title>The natural disaster economist | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 21:18:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500020/</guid><description>Podcast Description There seems to be headlines about floods, wildfires, or hurricanes every week. Scientists say this might be the new normal — that climate change is making natural disasters more and more common.
Tatyana Deryugina is a leading expert on the economics of natural disasters — how we respond to them, how they affect the economy, and how they change our lives. And back when Tatyana first started researching natural disasters she realized that there&amp;rsquo;s a lot we don&amp;rsquo;t know about their long-term economic consequences.</description></item><item><title>A black market, a currency crisis, and a tango competition in Argentina | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500021/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 03:34:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500021/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Nobel-prize winning economist Simon Kuznets once analyzed the world&amp;rsquo;s economies this way — he said there are four kinds of countries: developed, underdeveloped, Japan&amp;hellip; and Argentina.
If you want to understand what happens when inflation really goes off the rails, go to Argentina. Annual inflation there, over the past year, was 124 percent. Argentina&amp;rsquo;s currency, the peso, is collapsing, its poverty rate is above 40 percent, and the country may be on the verge of electing a far right Libertarian president who promises to replace the peso with the dollar.</description></item><item><title>"Based on a true story" | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 21:41:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500022/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a group of amateur investors rallied around the stock for GameStop back in 2021, the story blew up the internet. News outlets around the world, including us here at Planet Money, rushed in to explain why the stock for this retail video game company was suddenly skyrocketing, at times by as much as 1700% in value, and what that meant for the rest of us.
When movie producer Aaron Ryder saw the GameStop story — an army of scrappy underdogs, banding together to strike back against a financial system they felt was rigged against them — he knew it had the makings for a great movie.</description></item><item><title>How to launder $600 million on the internet | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500023/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 00:11:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Erin Plante is a private detective who specializes in chasing down stolen cryptocurrency. In March of 2022, she got the biggest assignment of her career: Hackers had broken into an online game called Axie Infinity and made off with over $600 million worth of digital money.
It was the largest crypto heist in history. And now it was Erin&amp;rsquo;s job to find that money and get it back. Erin&amp;rsquo;s investigation would lead her to face off against some of the world&amp;rsquo;s most formidable digital money launderers, whose actions would soon raise alarms at the highest levels of government — even threaten the nuclear security of the entire planet.</description></item><item><title>China's weakening economy in two Indicators | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 21:50:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500024/</guid><description>Podcast Description In China, data on the economy is sometimes difficult to come by. The Chinese government has put a pause on releasing some of its official economic data. But many of the stories emerging from the country paint a clear picture: the second largest economy in the world is struggling.
Today, our friends at The Indicator share some of their recent reporting on China. First up, it&amp;rsquo;s a special edition of the Beigie Awards focused entirely on China.</description></item><item><title>Is economists' favorite tool to crush inflation broken? | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500025/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 21:00:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500025/</guid><description>Podcast Description When economists and policymakers talk about getting inflation under control, there&amp;rsquo;s an assumption they often make: bringing inflation down will probably result in some degree of layoffs and job loss. But that is not the way things have played out since inflation spiked last year. Instead, so far, inflation has come down, and unemployment has stayed low.
So where does the idea of this tradeoff – between inflation and unemployment – come from?</description></item><item><title>The prince of prints and his prints of Prince | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 21:48:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500026/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1981, photographer Lynn Goldsmith took a portrait of the musician Prince. It&amp;rsquo;s a pretty standard headshot — it&amp;rsquo;s in black-and-white, and Prince is staring down the camera lens.
This was early in his career, when he was still building the pop icon reputation he would have today. And in 1984, shortly after Prince had released Purple Rain, he was chosen to grace the cover of Vanity Fair. The magazine commissioned pop culture icon Andy Warhol to make a portrait of Prince for the cover.</description></item><item><title>How to fight a patent pirate | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500027/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 22:18:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Back in the 1990s, Dr. Raghunath Mashelkar was in his office in New Delhi when he came across a puzzling story in the newspaper. Some university scientists in the U.S. had apparently filed a patent for using turmeric to help heal wounds. Mashelkar was shocked, because he knew that using turmeric that way was a well known remedy in traditional Indian medicine. And he knew that patents are for brand new inventions.</description></item><item><title>Summer School 8: Graduation and the Guppy Tank | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 23:35:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Congratulations to the Planet Money Summer School Class of 2023! Today, you become masters of business administration&amp;hellip; spelled with lower-case letters for legal purposes. Your diploma is waiting for you just across the stage.
But first, there&amp;rsquo;s one final skill to impart: the pitch. We wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be doing our job as a half-baked parody of a business school if we didn&amp;rsquo;t leave you with the confidence and opportunity to stand in front of an investor and ask for money.</description></item><item><title>The secret entrance that sidesteps Hollywood picket lines | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500029/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 00:08:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Across Hollywood right now, writers and actors are picketing in front of studio lots. They&amp;rsquo;re walking back and forth, holding up signs demanding concessions on things like pay, how many writers work on projects, and the use of AI in TV and movies.
But, on some of these lots, there are these strange alternate entrances where there are no picketers. Here drivers can come and go as they please without ever encountering any sign of a strike.</description></item><item><title>Summer School 7: Negotiating and the empathetic nibble | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500030/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 21:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500030/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do you get the best deal? How do you know you&amp;rsquo;re getting the best deal? Whether you&amp;rsquo;re talking down the price of a car or talking up your salary, you don&amp;rsquo;t have to be a jerk to get what you want. Negotiations can be win-win – if you know what to ask for and how to grow the pie.
We have three stories in today&amp;rsquo;s episode about how to negotiate tactically.</description></item><item><title>Vacation, and why the U.S. takes so little of it | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500031/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 20:36:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you work more for more money? Or work less for more time? For some, this is the ultimate economic choice.
Every single worker in the European Union is guaranteed four weeks of paid vacation. No matter how long they&amp;rsquo;ve been at a company. No matter how low paying the job is. Vacation is a right.
In fact, all but one of the richest countries in the world guarantees paid vacation, except: the U.</description></item><item><title>Summer School 6: Operations and 25,000 roses | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500032/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:15:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500032/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s difficult to control everything,&amp;rdquo; says our guest professor for this week, Santiago Gallino. &amp;ldquo;What is not difficult is to plan for everything.&amp;rdquo; Today we venture into the sphere of business that masters the planning, and backup planning: operations management.
It&amp;rsquo;s more than just predicting a bottleneck and imagining a solution, because there&amp;rsquo;s always a bottleneck to clear. It&amp;rsquo;s about modeling, and weighing the costs of messing up vs.</description></item><item><title>The new Biden plan that could still erase your student loans | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500033/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 21:43:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500033/</guid><description>Podcast Description This summer, the Supreme Court struck down Biden&amp;rsquo;s plan to forgive student loan debt for millions of borrowers. Except, on the same day Biden first announced that plan, he also unveiled another, the SAVE plan. And though SAVE sounded less significant than Biden&amp;rsquo;s big forgiveness pledge, it&amp;rsquo;s still alive and could erase even more student debt.
SAVE is officially a loan repayment plan. But through a few seemingly minor yet powerful provisions, many more low-income borrowers will end up paying little or nothing until, eventually, their loans will be forgiven.</description></item><item><title>Summer School 5: Tech and the innovator's dilemma | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500034/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 17:43:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500034/</guid><description>Podcast Description For anyone running a business, technology is both threat and opportunity. Today, we run through techniques entrepreneurs can use to take advantage of new tech or defend against the dangers. It&amp;rsquo;s not just about the product you&amp;rsquo;re selling. It&amp;rsquo;s about consumer psychology, and ethics, and taking calculated risks to navigate uncertainty.
But, since this is Planet Money Summer School and we want to set your business on the path to riches, we&amp;rsquo;re going to talk about how to use tech to dream big.</description></item><item><title>A tarot card reading for the U.S. economy | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500035/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 23:20:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Predicting the future of the economy is always a dicey proposition. That is especially true after more than three years of pandemic-related economic weirdness. No one quite knows what will happen next.
Will the Fed be able to pull off a soft landing and bring down inflation without causing either a recession or a big jump in unemployment? Or will we end up with a hard landing, in which inflation comes down, but at the price of the country&amp;rsquo;s economic health?</description></item><item><title>Summer School 4: Marketing and the Ultimate Hose Nozzle | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500036/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 22:05:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500036/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this session of Planet Money Summer School, we are getting the word out about your brand. How do you convince consumers to buy your product, even if they are only just hearing about it? It&amp;rsquo;s time for sales and marketing!
If you&amp;rsquo;ve watched a show like Mad Men or The Office, you know the importance of a strong pitch. It&amp;rsquo;s precision-crafted to show how what you&amp;rsquo;re selling can solve a problem your customer needs solved.</description></item><item><title>Tackle your medical debt with Life Kit | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500037/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 23:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500037/</guid><description>Podcast Description There&amp;rsquo;s an estimated $195 billion of medical debt in America. But just because a medical bill comes in the mail doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean you have to pay that exact price. In this special episode from our friends at Life Kit, you&amp;rsquo;ll learn how to eliminate, reduce or negotiate a medical bill.
If you liked this episode, you can check out more Life Kit here. They have episodes on how to choose a bank, and how to save money at the grocery store.</description></item><item><title>Did two honesty researchers fabricate their data? | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500038/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 08:15:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan Ariely and Francesca Gino are two of the biggest stars in behavioral science. Both have conducted blockbuster research into how to make people more honest, research we&amp;rsquo;ve highlighted on Planet Money. The two worked together on a paper about how to &amp;ldquo;nudge&amp;rdquo; people to be more honest on things like forms or tax returns. Their trick: move the location where people attest that they have filled in a form honestly from the bottom of the form to the top.</description></item><item><title>Summer School 3: Accounting and The Last Supper | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 22:17:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Usually, the first class that an MBA student takes is accounting. That involves, yes, equations and counting widgets&amp;hellip;but it&amp;rsquo;s more than that. Inside the simple act of accounting is a revolutionary way of thinking not just about a business, but about the world. A universe where all the forces are in balance. Accounting gives you a sixth sense–one that can help you determine whether your business will survive or fail.</description></item><item><title>Planet Money Paper Club | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500040/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 22:55:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500040/</guid><description>Podcast Description We here at Planet Money love economics papers. And that is also the case for so many of the economists we speak with. For them, new research can explain something they have always wondered about, or make them see something they have never noticed before. And it inspires their own work. So, to bring that same sense of discovery to you, the listener, today we are dedicating our show to a special experiment.</description></item><item><title>Summer School 2: Competition and the cheaper sneaker | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500041/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 21:28:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500041/</guid><description>Podcast Description For episode 2 of Planet Money Summer School, we are talking strategy. You have your million dollar business idea, and maybe some money in your pocket to get it up and running. But now you enter into a crowded market. You have to deal with competition. So, what can you do to make sure your product is a success? That was the conundrum facing the Starbury. It was a basketball shoe with a celebrity endorsement, that had to go up against THE basketball shoe with THE celebrity endorsement: the Air Jordan.</description></item><item><title>Surprise, you just signed a contract! How hidden contracts took over the internet | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500042/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:28:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500042/</guid><description>Podcast Description When you make an account online or install an app, you are probably entering into a legally enforceable contract. Even if you never signed anything. These days, we enter into these contracts so often, it can feel like no big deal.
But then there are the horror stories like Greg Selden&amp;rsquo;s. He tried to sue AirBnB for racial discrimination while using their site. But he had basically signed away his ability to sue AirBnB when he made an account.</description></item><item><title>Summer School 1: Planet Money goes to business school | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 23:11:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Find all episodes of Planet Money Summer School here.
Planet Money Summer School is back! It&amp;rsquo;s the free economics class you can take from anywhere&amp;hellip; for everyone! For Season 4 of Summer School, we are taking you to business school. It&amp;rsquo;s time to get your MBA, the easy way!
In this first class: Everyone has a million dollar business idea (e.g., &amp;ldquo;Shazam but for movies&amp;rdquo;), but not everyone has what it takes to be an entrepreneur.</description></item><item><title>The quest to save macroeconomics from itself | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500044/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 23:13:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500044/</guid><description>Podcast Description When it comes to big questions about the economy, we&amp;rsquo;re still kind of in the dark ages. Why do some economies grow so much faster than others? How long is the next recession going to last? How do we stop inflation without wrecking the rest of the economy? These questions are the domain of macroeconomics. But even some macroeconomists themselves admit: While we have many theories about how the economy works, we have very few satisfying answers.</description></item><item><title>Two Indicators: After Affirmative Action &amp; why America overpays for subways | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500045/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 23:35:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two stories today.
First, as we start to understand post-affirmative action America, we look to a natural experiment 25 years ago, when California ended the practice in public universities. It reshaped the makeup of the universities almost instantly. We find out what happened in the decades that followed.
Then, we ask, why does it cost so much for America to build big things, like subways. Compared to other wealthy nations, the costs of infrastructure projects in the U.</description></item><item><title>Supply, demand, extinction | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500046/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 22:03:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Back in the 90s, Ivan Lozano Ortega was in charge of Bogota&amp;rsquo;s wildlife rescue center. And he kept getting calls from the airport to come deal with&amp;hellip; frogs. Hundreds of brightly colored, poisonous frogs.
Ivan had stumbled upon the poisonous frog black market. Tens of thousands of frogs were being poached out of the Colombian rainforest and sold to collectors all around the world by smugglers. And it put these endangered frogs at risk of going extinct.</description></item><item><title>Planet Money Live: Two Truths and a Lie | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500047/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 20:51:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500047/</guid><description>Podcast Description The shocks of the pandemic economy gave us a bunch of enormous natural experiments, which helped to prove or disprove conventional economic thinking.
Take, for example, the bullwhip effect, the idea that the further away from the customer you are in the supply chain, the more volatile your orders are likely to be. This theory played out at an enormous scale, in the pandemic. Consumers and companies overreacted to the risk of shortages by ordering more products and hoarding them, causing massive shifts in the supply chain – just like the theory says.</description></item><item><title>Mike The Mover vs. The Furniture Police | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500048/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 22:15:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500048/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1978, a young man named Mike Shanks started a moving business in the north end of Seattle. It was just him and a truck — a pretty small operation. Things were going great. Then one afternoon, he was pulled over and cited for moving without a permit.
The investigators who cited him were part of a special unit tasked with enforcing utilities and transportation regulations. Mike calls them the furniture police.</description></item><item><title>Twins (classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500049/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 18:36:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Twins are used to fielding all sorts of questions, like &amp;ldquo;Can you read each other&amp;rsquo;s minds?&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Can you feel each other&amp;rsquo;s pain?&amp;rdquo; Two of our Planet Money reporters are twins, and they have heard them all.
But it&amp;rsquo;s not just strangers on the street who are fascinated by twins. Scientists have been studying twins since the 1800s, trying to get at one of humanity&amp;rsquo;s biggest questions: How much of what we do and how we are is encoded in our genes?</description></item><item><title>The 60-day job race | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500050/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 18:28:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500050/</guid><description>Podcast Description People come from all over the world to work in U.S. tech. And during the tech boom years, the industry relied heavily on foreign workers. This is how we built Silicon Valley – with great minds coming from everywhere to work in the U.S.
But when the industry started to shrink, all of these people who moved here for work are finding that linking their jobs to their residency is really complicated.</description></item><item><title>Two Indicators: The economics of innovation | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500051/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 22:09:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Innovation is crucial for game-changing advancements in society, whether it&amp;rsquo;s treatments for serious diseases, developments in AI technology, or rocket science.
Today on the show, we&amp;rsquo;re airing two episodes from our daily economics show The Indicator. First, a new paper suggests that breakthrough innovations are more likely at smaller, younger companies. We talk to an inventor who left a big pharmaceutical company to start afresh, leading to some incredible treatments for serious diseases.</description></item><item><title>The town that changed economics | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500052/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 22:45:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500052/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the early 90s, when a young economist named Michael Kremer finished his PhD, there had been a few economic studies based on randomized trials. But they were rare. In part because randomized trials – in which you recruit two statistically identical groups, choose one of them to get a treatment, and then compare what happens to each group – are expensive, and they take a lot of time.</description></item><item><title>The Spider-Man Problem (update) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500053/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 22:28:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500053/</guid><description>Podcast Description (Note: This episode originally ran back in 2022.)
This past weekend, Spider-Man: Across the Spider-Verse had the second largest domestic opening of 2023, netting (or should we say webbing?) over $120 million in its opening weekend in the U.S. and Canada. But the story leading up to this latest Spider-Man movie has been its own epic saga.
When Marvel licensed the Spider-Man film rights to Sony Pictures in the 1990s, the deal made sense — Marvel didn&amp;rsquo;t make movies yet, and their business was mainly about making comic books and toys.</description></item><item><title>AI Podcast 3.0: Dial M for Mechanization | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500054/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 22:32:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500054/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s the thrilling conclusion to our three-part series on AI — the world premiere of the first episode of Planet Money written by AI. In Part 1 of this series, we taught AI how to write an original Planet Money script by feeding it real research and interviews. In Part 2, we used AI to clone the voice of our former colleague Robert Smith.
Now, we&amp;rsquo;ve put everything together into a 15-minute Planet Money episode.</description></item><item><title>AI Podcast 2.0: The host in the machine | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500055/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 23:32:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500055/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Part 1 of this series, AI proved that it could use real research and real interviews to write an original script for an episode of Planet Money.
Our next task was to teach the computer how to sound like us. How to read that script aloud like a Planet Money host.
On today&amp;rsquo;s show, we explore the world of AI-generated voices, which have become so lifelike in recent years that they can credibly imitate specific people.</description></item><item><title>AI Podcast 1.0: Rise of the machines | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500056/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 21:42:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500056/</guid><description>Podcast Description We used to think some jobs were safe from automation. Though machines have transformed industries like agriculture and manufacturing, the conventional wisdom was that they could never perform what&amp;rsquo;s called &amp;ldquo;knowledge work.&amp;rdquo; That the robots could never replace lawyers or accountants — or journalists, like us.
Well, ever since the release of artificial intelligence tools like ChatGPT, it feels like no job is safe. AI can now write essays, generate computer code, and even pass the bar exam.</description></item><item><title>Green energy gridlock | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500057/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 23:15:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lyle Jack wants to build a wind farm on the Pine Ridge Reservation in South Dakota. But to make the project work, he has to connect that wind farm to the electric grid. Which is easier said than done. On today&amp;rsquo;s show - how the green energy revolution may live, or die, by bureaucrats trying to untangle a mess of wires. This episode was produced by Willa Rubin. It was edited by Sally Helm, fact-checked by Sierra Juarez, and engineered by Katherine Silva.</description></item><item><title>Predictions: Jobs! | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500058/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 22:57:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500058/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s time for another installment of &amp;hellip; Planet Money Predictions! air horn Last year, we invited two economic forecasters to tell us what they saw coming for jobs, the housing market, and inflation. And now they&amp;rsquo;re back. Which means it&amp;rsquo;s time to find out whose predictions were more on the money, and send the victor to the next round, where they face off against a new forecasting phenom. Since our last game, housing and inflation have cooled, but the job market keeps going strong.</description></item><item><title>How AI could help rebuild the middle class | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500059/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 23:37:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500059/</guid><description>Podcast Description For the last four decades, technology has been mostly a force for greater inequality and a shrinking middle class. But new empirical evidence suggests that the age of AI could be different. We speak to MIT&amp;rsquo;s David Autor, one of the greatest labor economists in the world, who envisions a future where we use AI to make a wider array of workers much better at a whole range of jobs and help rebuild the middle class.</description></item><item><title>Inflation and the Profit-Price Spiral | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500060/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 23:59:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Economists say that inflation is just too much money chasing too few goods.
But something else can make inflation stick around.
If you think of the 1970s, the last time the U.S. had really high sustained inflation, a big concern was rising wages. Prices for goods and services were high. Workers expected prices to be even higher next year, so they asked for pay raises to keep up. But then companies had to raise their prices more.</description></item><item><title>The Day of Two Noons (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500061/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 21:59:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500061/</guid><description>Podcast Description (Note: this episode originally ran in 2019.)
In the 1800s, catching your train on time was no easy feat. Every town had its own &amp;ldquo;local time,&amp;rdquo; based on the position of the sun in the sky. There were 23 local times in Indiana. 38 in Michigan. Sometimes the time changed every few minutes. This created tons of confusion, and a few train crashes. But eventually, a high school principal, a scientist, and a railroad bureaucrat did something about it.</description></item><item><title>How to fight a squatting goat | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500062/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 01:37:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Back in 2005, Burt Banks inherited a plot of old family land in Delaware. But when it came time to sell it, he ran into a problem: his neighbor had a goat pen, and about half of it crossed over onto his property. Burt asked the goats&amp;rsquo; owner to move the pen, but when neighborly persuasion failed to get the job done, he changed his strategy. He sued her.</description></item><item><title>Two Indicators: the influencer industry | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500063/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:54:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500063/</guid><description>Podcast Description When you were little, what did you want to be when you grew up? An astronaut, a doctor or maybe a famous athlete? Today one of the most popular responses to that question is influencer – content creators who grow their following on Tik Tok, Instagram and YouTube and monetize that content to make it their full-time job.
In a lot of ways influencing can seem like the dream job - the filters, the followers, the free stuff.</description></item><item><title>Financial advising while Black | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500064/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 20:52:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500064/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a successful career in advertising, Erika Williams decided it was time for a change. She went back to school to get an MBA at the University of Chicago, and eventually, in 2012, she got a job at Wells Fargo as a financial advisor. It was the very job she wanted.
Erika is Black–and being a Black financial advisor at a big bank is relatively uncommon. Banking was one of the last white collar industries to really hire Black employees.</description></item><item><title>The zoo economy (classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500065/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 22:04:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Note: This episode originally aired in September, 2014.
Zoos follow a fundamental principle: You can&amp;rsquo;t sell or buy the animals. It&amp;rsquo;s unethical and illegal to put a price tag on an elephant&amp;rsquo;s head. But money is really useful — it lets you know who wants something and how much they want it. It lets you get rid of things you don&amp;rsquo;t need and acquire things that you do need.</description></item><item><title>The quest for the factory-built house | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500066/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 22:47:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Imagine if we built cars the same way we build houses. First, a typical buyer would meet with the car designer, and tell them what kind of car they want. Then the designer would draw up plans for the car.
The buyer would call different car builders in their town and show them the blueprints. And the builders might say, &amp;ldquo;Yeah, I can build you that car based on this blueprint.</description></item><item><title>Tax Code Switch | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500067/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 20:26:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500067/</guid><description>Podcast Description This past January, researchers uncovered that Black taxpayers are three to five times as likely to be audited as everyone else. One likely reason for this is that the IRS disproportionately audits lower-income earners who claim a tax benefit called the earned income tax credit. And this, says law professor Dorothy Brown, is just one example of the many ways that race is woven through our tax system, its history, and its enforcement.</description></item><item><title>The life and possible death of low interest rates | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500068/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 02:06:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Right now, the economy is running hot. Inflation is high, and central banks are pushing up interest rates to fight it. But before the pandemic, economies around the world were stuck in a different rut: low inflation, low interest rates, low growth. In 2013, Larry Summers unearthed an old term from the Great Depression to explain why the economy was in this rut: secular stagnation. The theory resonated with Olivier Blanchard, another leading scholar, because he had made similar observations himself.</description></item><item><title>Two innovation market indicators | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500069/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 23:26:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Right now, the economy is all over the place. And when things get confusing, we look to basic economic indicators to help explain what&amp;rsquo;s going on. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re bringing you two episodes of our daily show The Indicator that focus on the bond market.
The market for U.S. treasury bonds is generally safe, predictable and pretty boring. Recently, though, it&amp;rsquo;s been anything but. We look into the fluctuations in bond prices and the yield curve (one of our favorite indicators) to try to help us understand where the economy stands right now.</description></item><item><title>Your banking questions, answered | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500070/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 00:21:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500070/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s been a month since the collapse of Silicon Valley Bank touched off the worst episode of banking turmoil since 2008. While the financial system appears to have stabilized, we&amp;rsquo;re still reckoning with what happened. Regulators are getting dragged before Congress. The Federal Reserve and the FDIC have promised reports on what went wrong with bank oversight. And judging by our inbox, you, our listeners, have a lot of lingering questions.</description></item><item><title>The battle for Puerto Rico's beaches | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500071/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 21:05:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Puerto Rico&amp;rsquo;s beaches are an integral part of life on the island, and by law, they&amp;rsquo;re one of the few places that are truly public. In practice, the sandy stretch of land where the water meets the shore is one of the island&amp;rsquo;s most contested spaces.
Today we&amp;rsquo;re featuring an episode of the podcast La Brega from WNYC Studios and Futuro Studios, a show about Puerto Rico and the Puerto Rican experience.</description></item><item><title>The safety net for banks | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500072/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 00:30:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500072/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the first half of March, three banks - Silicon Valley Bank, Signature Bank, and Silvergate - all had relatively classic bank runs and collapsed. Which sparked some major banking stress. As a result, the Federal Reserve got a lot of requests to use one of its oldest and most important tools for soothing such troubles: the discount window.
The discount window is like a safety net for banks.</description></item><item><title>A Great Recession bank takeover | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500073/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 01:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Earlier this month, we saw the largest bank collapse since the 2008 financial crisis. For many of us, seeing Silicon Valley Bank&amp;rsquo;s meltdown brought us right back to that time 15 years ago, at the beginning of what would become the Great Recession. In early 2009, one or two banks were failing every week. That&amp;rsquo;s when Planet Money reporter Chana Joffe-Walt went inside one of those banks: the Bank of Clark County, in Washington State.</description></item><item><title>The battle over Osage headrights | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500074/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 02:01:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Richard J. Lonsinger is a member of the Ponca tribe of Oklahoma, who was adopted at a young age into a white family of three. He eventually reconnected with his birth family, but when his birth mother passed away in 2010, he wasn&amp;rsquo;t included in the distribution of her estate. Feeling both hurt and excluded, he asked a judge to re-open her estate, to give him a part of one particular asset: an Osage headright.</description></item><item><title>Inside a bank run | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500075/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 05:33:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sometimes you hear these stories about an airplane that suddenly nosedives. Everyone onboard thinks this is it, and then the plane levels out and everything is fine. For about 72 hours, people and companies that had deposited millions of dollars at the Silicon Valley Bank — many of whom were in the tech industry — thought they had lost absolutely everything to a bank collapse.
Two weeks later, the situation at Silicon Valley Bank has leveled off.</description></item><item><title>Planet Money Records Vol. 3: Making a hit | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500076/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 01:04:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Since we started Planet Money Records and released the 47-year-old song &amp;ldquo;Inflation,&amp;rdquo; the song has taken off. It recently hit 1 million streams on Spotify. And we now have a full line of merch — including a limited edition vinyl record; a colorful, neon hoodie; and 70s-inspired stickers — n.pr/shopplanetmoney. After starting a label and negotiating our first record deal, we&amp;rsquo;re taking the Inflation song out into the world to figure out the hidden economics of the music business.</description></item><item><title>How Silicon Valley Bank failed | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500077/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 00:35:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Silicon Valley Bank was the 16th largest bank in America, the bank of choice for tech startups and big-name venture capitalists. Then, in the span of just a few days, it collapsed. Whispers that SVB might be in trouble spread like wildfire through group texts and Twitter posts. Depositors raced to empty their accounts, withdrawing $42 billion in a single day. Last Friday, after regulators declared that SVB had failed, the FDIC seized the bank.</description></item><item><title>Dude, where's my streaming TV show? | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500078/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 01:08:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the past year, dozens of shows have been disappearing from streaming platforms like HBO Max and Showtime. Shows like Minx, Made for Love, FBoy Island, and even big budget hits like Westworld have been removed entirely.
So why did these platforms, after investing millions of dollars in creating original content, decide not just to cancel those shows, but to make them unavailable altogether?
We dive into the economics of the television industry looking for answers to a streaming mystery that has affected both fans and creatives.</description></item><item><title>The value of good teeth | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500079/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:23:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500079/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a kid, Ryanne Jones&amp;rsquo; friend accidentally hit her in the mouth with a hammer, knocking out her two front teeth. Her parents never had enough money for the dental care needed to fix them, so Ryanne lived much of her adult life with a chipped and crooked smile. Ryanne spent a while as a single mom working low-wage jobs, but she had higher aspirations: she interviewed dozens of times a year for higher-paying roles that she was more than qualified for.</description></item><item><title>Seinfeld-onomics | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500080/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 23:09:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500080/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 90s sit-com Seinfeld is often called &amp;ldquo;a show about nothing.&amp;rdquo; Lauded for its observational humor, this quick-witted show focussed on four hapless New Yorkers navigating work, relationships&amp;hellip;yada yada yada.
Jerry, George, Elaine &amp;amp; Kramer set themselves apart from the characters who populated shows like Friends or Cheers, by being the exact opposite of the characters audiences would normally root for. These four New Yorkers were overly analytical, calculating, and above all, selfish.</description></item><item><title>CBOhhhh, that's what they do | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500081/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 23:28:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500081/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you are a congressperson or a senator and you have an idea for a new piece of legislation, at some point someone will have to tell you how much it costs. But, how do you put a price on something that doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist yet?
Since 1974, that has been the job of the Congressional Budget Office, or the CBO. The agency plays a critical role in the legislative process: bills can live and die by the cost estimates the CBO produces.</description></item><item><title>Meow Money Meow Problems | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500082/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 01:18:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500082/</guid><description>Podcast Description More than 20 years ago, something unusual happened in the small town of Dixfield, Maine. A lady named Barbara Thorpe had left almost all of her money—$200,000—to benefit the cats of her hometown. When Barbara died in 2002, those cats suddenly got very, very rich. And that is when all the trouble began.
Barbara&amp;rsquo;s gift set off a sprawling legal battle that drew in a crew of crusading cat ladies, and eventually, the town of Dixfield itself.</description></item><item><title>Hollywood's Black List (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500083/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 23:10:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500083/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode originally ran in 2020.
In 2005, Franklin Leonard was a junior executive at Leonardo DiCaprio&amp;rsquo;s production company. A big part of his job was to find great scripts. The only thing — most of the 50,000-some scripts registered with the Writers Guild of America every year aren&amp;rsquo;t that great. Franklin was drowning in bad scripts &amp;hellip; So to help find the handful that will become the movies that change our lives, he needed a better way forward.</description></item><item><title>Jay &amp; Shai's debt ceiling adventure | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500084/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Every year, the U.S. government spends more money than it takes in. In order to fund all that spending, the country takes on debt. Congress has the power to limit how much debt the U.S. takes on. Right now, the debt limit is $31.4 trillion dollars. Once we reach that limit, Congress has a few options so that the government keeps paying its bills: Raise the debt limit, suspend it, or eliminate it entirely.</description></item><item><title>Two Indicators: Inside the Fed, then and now | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500085/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:35:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500085/</guid><description>Podcast Description A lot of the time, economic policy can seem pretty impersonal — cold, hard, data-driven. But at the heart of the Federal Reserve are people: fallible, complicated people who are just doing their best to steer the economy in the right direction. Often, we remember them just for their economic decisions. But today, we&amp;rsquo;re airing two episodes from our daily economics show The Indicator that profile the people inside the Fed.</description></item><item><title>Our 2023 valentines | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500086/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 00:11:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Every Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day, we at Planet Money consider the things that we love, the things that we can&amp;rsquo;t stop talking about, the things that get our hearts racing&amp;hellip;in a good way. And we give them valentines!
This year our valentines go out to:
ImportYeti, a website that lets you see exactly where U.S. companies are importing goods from.
Economic data revisions, those tweaks to the data that make things like the jobs numbers even more accurate.</description></item><item><title>The ice cream conspiracy | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500087/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 23:14:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Take a look in any supermarket ice cream freezer section and you may see a mystery. There are big containers of the typical ice cream brands: Breyers, Turkey Hill, and Edy&amp;rsquo;s. And there are specialty brands that make gelato, low-fat and vegan ice creams. And then there are the fancy pints: which is mostly Ben &amp;amp; Jerry&amp;rsquo;s and Häagen-Dazs.
Häagen-Dazs has flavors like vanilla, chocolate, pistachio—the sort of flavors that run smooth.</description></item><item><title>Baby's first market failure | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500088/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 21:53:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anyone who has tried shopping for day care knows that it is tough out there.
For one, it is hard even to get your hands on information about costs, either online or over the phone – day cares will often only share their prices after you have taken a tour of their facilities. Even once you find a place you like, many day cares have waitlists stretching 6 months, 9 months, a year.</description></item><item><title>Groundhog Day 2023 | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500089/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 23:44:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500089/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s Groundhog Day, and once again, the eyes of the nation have turned to a small town in Western Pennsylvania. Every February 2nd, the only story anyone can talk about is whether or not Punxsutawney Phil will see his own shadow. If he does: six more weeks of winter. If he doesn&amp;rsquo;t: spring is on its way.
This year, in a cruel twist of fate reminiscent of the 1993 movie Groundhog Day, two Planet Money hosts have found themselves facing a curse.</description></item><item><title>To all the econ papers I've loved before | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500090/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 21:47:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500090/</guid><description>Podcast Description A great economics paper does two things. It takes on a big question, and it finds a smart way to answer that question.
But some papers go even further. The very best papers have the power to change lives.That was the case for three economists we spoke to: Nancy Qian, Belinda Archibong, and Kyle Greenberg.
They all stumbled on important economics papers at crucial moments in their careers, and those papers gave them a new way to see the world.</description></item><item><title>The story of "Monopoly" and American capitalism | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500091/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 01:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Monopoly is one of the best-selling board games in history. The game&amp;rsquo;s staying power may in part be because of strong American lore — the idea that anyone, with just a little bit of cash, can rise from rags to riches. Mary Pilon, author of The Monopolists: Obsession, Fury, and the Scandal Behind the World&amp;rsquo;s Favorite Board Game.
But there&amp;rsquo;s another origin story – a very different one that promotes a very different image of capitalism.</description></item><item><title>Charles Ponzi's scheme | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500092/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Some of history&amp;rsquo;s biggest financial scams owe their name to Charles Ponzi. Here&amp;rsquo;s the story of the man behind the eponymous scheme.
Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Big Rigged (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500093/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 23:49:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Driving a truck used to mean freedom. Now it means a mountain of debt.
Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Indicators: The 2% inflation target | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500094/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 23:55:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500094/</guid><description>Podcast Description If the Fed had a mantra to go along with its mandate, it might well be &amp;ldquo;two percent.&amp;rdquo; We look into how that became the target inflation rate, why some economists are calling for a change and how the inflation rate becomes unanchored.
Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Planet Money Movie Club: It's a Wonderful Life | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500095/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 22:55:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to the Planet Money Movie Club, a regular series from Planet Money+ in which we watch an economics-related movie and discuss! On today&amp;rsquo;s episode, Kenny Malone, Wailin Wong, and Willa Rubin talk about Frank Capra&amp;rsquo;s 1946 classic &amp;lsquo;It&amp;rsquo;s A Wonderful Life.&amp;rsquo; They discuss CPI adjustments, how a copyright lapse helped make the film more popular, and what exactly a &amp;lsquo;Building and Loan&amp;rsquo; is.
Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.</description></item><item><title>The economics lessons in kids' books | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500096/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 22:24:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500096/</guid><description>Podcast Description All sorts of lessons (even about economics) can be learned from kids&amp;rsquo; books. On today&amp;rsquo;s show, we visit an elementary school to try to teach third graders econ using some beloved childrens&amp;rsquo; classics. And, along the way, we learn a few things ourselves.
Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Rest of the Story, 2022 | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500097/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 00:12:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500097/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s that time of year again! Our annual year-end tradition of checking in on previous stories to hear what happened after the microphones stopped running.
We&amp;rsquo;ll hear from a CEO who was trying to get her company out of Russia amidst the war in Ukraine, check in with an organizer who was trying to turn his community into a city, follow-up on our experiment in polling, and get the latest from our record label — Planet Money Records.</description></item><item><title>Which economic indicator defined 2022? | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 21:43:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500098/</guid><description>Podcast Description 2022 was a year of big economic changes. But what economic story most defined the year? Our hosts from Planet Money and The Indicator battle it out over what should be crowned the indicator of the year. Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney
Transcript</description></item><item><title>In defense of gift giving | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500099/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 00:50:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cold economic reasoning says, supposedly, that gifts are inefficient transfers of wealth. But Planet Money host Jeff Guo believes in the economic virtues of gift giving. On today&amp;rsquo;s show, Jeff tries to win over Planet Money&amp;rsquo;s resident Scrooge, Kenny Malone, by going on a quest to find him the perfect gift. Along the way, they&amp;rsquo;re visited by the spirits of three Nobel prize-winning economic theories that can explain why gift-giving is actually good.</description></item><item><title>Two Indicators: The fight over ESG investing | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500100/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 22:59:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500100/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;ESG&amp;rdquo; investing – Environmental, Social, Governance – has attracted a lot of attention from investors, and from Republican politicians who call it &amp;ldquo;woke investing.&amp;rdquo; On today&amp;rsquo;s show, what the fight over ESG reveals about the potential and limitations of sustainable investing.
Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The sports ticket price enigma | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500101/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 22:32:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Inflation is making prices go up, except not for&amp;hellip;sports tickets? So, we set out on a daylong sporting event marathon to learn why.
Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Spam call bounty hunter | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500102/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 23:43:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Telemarketing calls are not only annoying; in some cases, they are illegal. Congress even gives you the right to sue scofflaw telemarketers for $500 a call. Today, the story of one man who collected a surprising amount of money bringing telemarketers to justice. Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The case of the missing cheese racks | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500103/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 23:45:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jelle Peterse&amp;rsquo;s company ships cheese all over the world, but they don&amp;rsquo;t always get their cheese racks back. In this episode, we try to fix a supply chain problem. Gouda grief!
Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>When women stopped coding (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500104/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 22:53:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500104/</guid><description>Podcast Description A lot of computing pioneers were women. For decades, the number of women in computer science was growing. But in 1984, something changed.
Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>My Favorite Tax Loophole | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500105/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 03:20:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500105/</guid><description>Podcast Description There&amp;rsquo;s a big difference between tax avoidance and tax evasion. But sometimes even avoiding taxes (legally) can feel like you&amp;rsquo;re getting away with something. Today, we share some of our — and your! — favorite loopholes in the U.S. tax code.
Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Messi economics | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500106/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 02:14:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Soccer star Lionel Messi is currently hoping to lead Argentina to victory in the World Cup. His path to global fame was shaped by a crisis in Argentina&amp;rsquo;s economy.
This episode was made in collaboration with NPR and Futuro Studios&amp;rsquo;s The Last Cup podcast.
Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney
Transcript</description></item><item><title>One economist's take on popular advice for saving, borrowing, and spending | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500107/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 21:45:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500107/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode was first released as a bonus episode for Planet Money+ listeners last month. We&amp;rsquo;re sharing it today for all listeners. To hear more episodes like this one and support NPR in the process, sign up for Planet Money+ at plus.npr.org. Planet Money+ supporters: we&amp;rsquo;ll have a fresh bonus episode for you next week! &amp;ldquo;Save aggressively for retirement when you&amp;rsquo;re young.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;The stock market is a sure-fire long-term bet.</description></item><item><title>How the cookie became a monster | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500108/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 02:17:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500108/</guid><description>Podcast Description 30 years ago, Lou Montulli set out to solve a fundamental problem with the internet, and accidentally created an entirely different one. On today&amp;rsquo;s show, how the cookie went from an obscure piece of code designed to protect anonymity, to an online advertiser&amp;rsquo;s dream, to a privacy advocate&amp;rsquo;s nightmare.
Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sam Bankman-Fried and the fall of a crypto empire | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500109/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 01:03:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Bankman-Fried built a reputation as the one reliable crypto bro. But within the span of days, his empire came crashing down. What the rise and fall of crypto&amp;rsquo;s 30-year-old elder statesman says about the story of crypto so far.
Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The E-Book Wars | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500110/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 23:23:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500110/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2019, a group of librarians (quietly) stormed the offices of a major publisher, Macmillan, to protest a controversial policy on e-books. On this show, how a tiny change - a book on a screen - threw an industry into war with itself.
Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoneya
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Peak Sand (classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500111/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 23:26:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sand. It&amp;rsquo;s in buildings, windows, your cell phone. But there isn&amp;rsquo;t enough in the world for everyone. And that&amp;rsquo;s created a dangerous black market.
Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Planet Money tries election polling | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500112/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 23:44:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Polling is facing an existential crisis. Few people are answering the phone, and fewer people want to answer surveys. On today&amp;rsquo;s show, we pick up the phones ourselves to find out how polling got to this place, and what the future of the poll looks like.
Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Indicators shaking China's economy | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500113/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 22:58:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Xi Jinping recently secured his third term as China&amp;rsquo;s president – so we&amp;rsquo;re looking at two shocks to the world&amp;rsquo;s second-largest economy. First: How China&amp;rsquo;s housing boom turned into a real estate crisis. Second: How the recent U.S. ban on selling advanced semiconductor chips to China could affect China&amp;rsquo;s technology industry.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Planet Money Records Vol. 2: The Negotiation | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500114/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 03:20:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500114/</guid><description>Podcast Description We got our hands on the long-lost &amp;ldquo;Inflation&amp;rdquo; song, and now it&amp;rsquo;s time to put it out into the world. So, we started a record label, and we&amp;rsquo;re diving into the music business to try and make a hit.
This is part two of the Planet Money Records series. Here&amp;rsquo;s part one and part three.
Update: We now have merch! We released a line of Inflation song gear — including a limited edition vinyl record; a colorful, neon hoodie; and 70s-inspired stickers.</description></item><item><title>Planet Money Records Vol. 1: Earnest Jackson | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500115/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 00:15:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500115/</guid><description>Podcast Description We try to start a real record label. Just to put one song out there. It&amp;rsquo;s a song about inflation, recorded in 1975&amp;hellip; and never released. Until now.
This is part one of the Planet Money Records series. Here&amp;rsquo;s part two and part three.
Update: We now have merch! We released a line of Inflation song gear — including a limited edition vinyl record; a colorful, neon hoodie; and 70s-inspired stickers.</description></item><item><title>The high cost of a strong dollar | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500116/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 00:25:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500116/</guid><description>Podcast Description When it comes to international trade and finance, everyone pretty much speaks one language: the U.S. dollar. So when the Federal Reserve hikes interest rates and the dollar suddenly gets strong, it can cause huge headaches all over the world.
Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The money fixers (classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500117/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 20:56:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500117/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do you mend a broken bill? On this classic episode, we visit the Mutilated Currency Division.
Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney
Transcript</description></item><item><title>You asked for coupons, Delaware, and the truth about goldfish | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500118/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 00:42:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500118/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today&amp;rsquo;s show, we&amp;rsquo;re answering listener questions from the Planet Money inbox. Like, who really benefits from retail coupons? And why are goldfish so cheap?
Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Indicators: back to school | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500119/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 22:16:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500119/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s fall, so on this episode, we&amp;rsquo;re taking you back to school. First, what sorority rush can teach us about a particular kind of market. Then, how two economists fixed the way macroeconomics was taught in high schools. It&amp;rsquo;s econ, inside and outside the classroom.
Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Forging Taiwan's Silicon Shield | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500120/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 23:56:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Taiwan is at the center of a global feud. Its main defense may be what some call its &amp;ldquo;Silicon Shield&amp;rdquo; — its powerful semiconductor industry. On today&amp;rsquo;s show, the story of how one economic hero helped to transform Taiwan&amp;rsquo;s economy and create the &amp;ldquo;Taiwan Miracle.&amp;quot;
Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Economic anarchy in the UK | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500121/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 23:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Liz Truss, the new Prime Minister of the UK, was determined to change the British economy. Instead, her government&amp;rsquo;s mini-budget helped kick off a mini-financial crisis.
Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Would you like a side of offshoring with that? | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500122/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 21:22:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500122/</guid><description>Podcast Description A lot of restaurants took a hit during the pandemic. And when they struggled to find workers, some found surprising solutions. On today&amp;rsquo;s show, what happens when you offshore cashiers.
Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The miracle apple (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500123/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 23:06:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today on the show, how we got from mealy, nasty apples to apples that taste delicious. The story starts with a breeder who discovered a miracle apple. But discovering that apple wasn&amp;rsquo;t enough.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Econ's Brush with the Law | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500124/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 22:44:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500124/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happens when you take some of the most powerful people in America — federal judges — and teach them economics? We look at the swanky econ retreats that may have changed American law forever.
Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Midnight Connection | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500125/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 22:47:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Texas&amp;rsquo;s energy grid is largely disconnected from the rest of the U.S. That led to disastrous consequences last year when the state&amp;rsquo;s grid was overloaded during a winter storm. Back in the 1970s, one company attempted to change the system in a secret, middle-of-the-night operation. Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Vibecession Vibes Session | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500126/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 01:16:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500126/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;re not in a recession, but why are the vibes feeling so off? We put the question to an economist and one expert on &amp;ldquo;vibes&amp;rdquo; and also hire a jazz band to take a pun way too far.
Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Good, the Bad, and the Uggly | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500127/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 03:33:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eddie Oygur is an Australian businessman who&amp;rsquo;s sold sheepskin ugg boots for years. But one day, he was hit with a lawsuit for breaking American trademark law. On today&amp;rsquo;s show — what&amp;rsquo;s in the name ugg? Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Indicators: unlikely economic relationships | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500128/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 21:00:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500128/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today&amp;rsquo;s show - how your social circle is one of the strongest predictors of economic mobility and how pop music reflects the economy.
Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The salvage car Silk Road | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500129/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 00:15:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500129/</guid><description>Podcast Description A practically brand new Lexus with a New Jersey inspection sticker lands on an auto body lot in Turkmenistan. How did it get there? To find out, we journey into the bizarro economy for misfit cars. And we follow a very different kind of journey – of the auto body repairman from Turkmenistan who brought us this story in the first place. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.</description></item><item><title>Breaking down the price of gasoline | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500130/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 00:15:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500130/</guid><description>Podcast Description High gas prices have fueled speculation and investigations — is anyone raising prices and keeping prices high for profit? To find out, we break down the price of gas, piece by piece, to show you how we get to the price we see at the pump and how much everyone profits at each step of the way. | Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney.</description></item><item><title>SUMMER SCHOOL 8: Productivity &amp; Getting Lit | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500131/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 22:40:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Productivity is our economic measure for how far our work goes, as individuals and as a society over all. It plays an important role in determining our quality of life, the prices of our goods and services, and, to some extent, the amount of free time we have. Today, we explore how thousands of years of productivity advancements transformed something now so standard that we take it for granted: light.</description></item><item><title>Wake up and smell the fraud | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500132/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 22:31:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sometimes online shopping can feel a little unsavory. There are the listings that make you question if you&amp;rsquo;ll really be getting exactly what&amp;rsquo;s advertised. And there&amp;rsquo;s no worse feeling than paying for something and then not getting it. But when Nina Kollars ordered coffee pods and got WAY more than she asked for, it made her feel just as uneasy. Her quest for answers and what it teaches us about a new generation of online fraud.</description></item><item><title>SUMMER SCHOOL 7: The Fed &amp; Volcker's Socks | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500133/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 23:33:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500133/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Federal Reserve plays a very important role in the economy. When things start to look uncertain, the central bank is tasked with stepping in to restore people&amp;rsquo;s confidence in the economy. But how do they do it? On today&amp;rsquo;s episode we dive deep on monetary policy and the role of the fed. |At this Summer School, phones ARE allowed during class&amp;hellip; Check out this week&amp;rsquo;s PM TikTok! | Listen to past seasons of Summer School here.</description></item><item><title>Inflation Reduction Actually | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500134/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 23:48:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Congress just passed the biggest, most ambitious climate bill in history. And it&amp;rsquo;s called &amp;hellip; the Inflation Reduction Act of 2022. What&amp;rsquo;s with that branding? And what can the bill teach us about actually fighting inflation? | Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SUMMER SCHOOL 6: Trade &amp; The Better Life | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500135/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 22:46:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500135/</guid><description>Podcast Description International trade is the web of cross-border relationships that binds economies together. Because of trade we have access to cheaper, higher-quality goods, and we get to benefit from other countries&amp;rsquo; cultures. Economics tells us trade makes society, overall on average, better off, but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean everyone wins. Today, the good and bad of trade through the eyes of workers in developing economies who make the things sold around the world.</description></item><item><title>Carried interest wormhole | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500136/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 00:56:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500136/</guid><description>Podcast Description The carried interest tax loophole is a way that wealthy Americans – often the people who manage hedge funds or private equity firms – avoid paying billions of dollars worth of taxes. It has been one of the most controversial yet durable features of the U.S. tax code. But where did it come from? Today we romp through space and time to piece together the origins of this loophole.</description></item><item><title>SUMMER SCHOOL 5: Car Parts, Celery &amp; The Labor Market | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500137/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 00:38:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500137/</guid><description>Podcast Description You can learn a lot about a person from their job. The same can be said of an economy. The market for jobs can us a lot about how the economy is doing, but more importantly, it is where we look to see who the economy is working for, and who is left behind. In today&amp;rsquo;s lesson we&amp;rsquo;ll visit two workplaces each facing a different labor puzzle. At one end, there&amp;rsquo;s the question of when to replace a worker with a robot, and what it is like to be that worker waiting for the robots to come.</description></item><item><title>A new way to pay for college (Update) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500138/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 20:46:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500138/</guid><description>Podcast Description College has gotten incredibly expensive. And some colleges are offering students a new way to pay. It&amp;rsquo;s not a scholarship. It&amp;rsquo;s not quite a loan. It&amp;rsquo;s more like the students are selling stock in themselves. We check in on how income share agreements at one school have been working. | Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SUMMER SCHOOL 4: Inflation &amp; Drinking Buddies | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500139/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 00:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Inflation can be one of the scariest forces in the economy. As prices rise and your dollar doesn&amp;rsquo;t go as far, you feel poorer, and it&amp;rsquo;s all out of your control. To better understand inflation, we turn to the story of Brazil, where, in the 90s, hyperinflation threatened to derail the whole economy until the country turned to a group of unlikely heroes: four drinking buddies. | Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.</description></item><item><title>We Buy a Superhero 8: Micro-Face: The Musical | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500140/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 09:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500140/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode, Micro-Face: The Musical. A full concert recording of a one-of-a-kind Planet Money superhero musical, taped during our recent live show at the Roulette Theater in Brooklyn, New York. Here&amp;rsquo;s more from our project We Buy A Superhero.
Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two recession Indicators | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500141/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 21:55:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500141/</guid><description>Podcast Description So are we in a recession or not? The jury is still out, but there are some warning signs. GDP is down and inflation is up. But how much do we know about the &amp;lsquo;indicators&amp;rsquo; that tell us how the economy is doing? Today, the stories of two of our most important indicators, the Consumer Price Index and GDP, and what they can and can&amp;rsquo;t tell us about our current economic predicament.</description></item><item><title>SUMMER SCHOOL 3: Booms, Busts &amp; Us | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500142/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 02:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Life has its ups and downs. Same for the economy. Today we ask, can the business cycle be tamed? Two stories of recession and techniques for moderating the ferocity of booms and busts. Plus, how bankruptcy is a secret weapon of the American economy. | Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney. | At this Summer School, phones ARE allowed during class&amp;hellip; Check out this week&amp;rsquo;s PM TikTok!</description></item><item><title>Little House on the Blockchain | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500143/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 23:38:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500143/</guid><description>Podcast Description It has great bones, three bedrooms and one and half baths, and it comes with its own machine that mines cryptocurrency. But in a year of reckoning for crypto, how interested are potential buyers? | Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SUMMER SCHOOL 2: GDP &amp; What Counts | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500144/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 01:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500144/</guid><description>Podcast Description What even is &amp;ldquo;the economy&amp;rdquo;? And how do you measure it? Our path out of the economic darkness and into the light has been guided in large part by one single statistic: GDP. This week: the origins, history, and problems with the economic indicator to rule them all. | At this Summer School, phones ARE allowed during class&amp;hellip; Check out this week&amp;rsquo;s PM TikTok! | Listen to past seasons of Summer School here.</description></item><item><title>Best by, sell by, use by | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500145/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 02:08:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wait, wait&amp;hellip;don&amp;rsquo;t throw that out! What if much of what you&amp;rsquo;ve been told about food expiration dates is&amp;hellip; wrong? | Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SUMMER SCHOOL 1: Recessions &amp; Rap Battles | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500146/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 02:42:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500146/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s macro time! Today: Keynes vs. Hayek. Season 3 of summer school is here asking the biggest economic questions about what makes an entire economy grow or contract? Things like, is there a &amp;ldquo;right&amp;rdquo; level of unemployment? Who gains from trade? What rhymes with &amp;lsquo;paradox of thrift&amp;rsquo;? Also, inflation, we&amp;rsquo;ll get to inflation. Episode 1 begins with the rise of macroeconomics as a field, with one of the great economic debates of the 20th century: what causes booms and busts, and what can the government do about it?</description></item><item><title>A tale of two cityhoods | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500147/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 23:22:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500147/</guid><description>Podcast Description There&amp;rsquo;s a movement underway in Georgia. More and more communities around Atlanta are choosing to keep their tax dollars very local, and become their own cities. It&amp;rsquo;s a story about equity and exclusion – and also potholes. | Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two crypto crash Indicators | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500148/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 21:09:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two stories of consternation from inside the crypto world. Can a crypto crash spread to the wider economy? How does contagion work? And &amp;hellip; why has crypto had such appeal with Black investors? | Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Suitcases, secret lists, and Citizens United | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500149/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:05:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500149/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today&amp;rsquo;s show: the Watergate scandal you haven&amp;rsquo;t heard about – that led directly to Citizens United and multi-billion dollar elections. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here. Transcript</description></item><item><title>When Subaru came out (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500150/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 22:40:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500150/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the early 90s, Subaru was struggling to stand out in a crowded automobile market. In their greatest time of need, they turned to an unlikely ally: lesbians | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Recession referees | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500151/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 01:38:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Whenever the economic data start to look rough, we&amp;rsquo;re forced to confront a familiar question: Are we in a recession, or about to be? But there are actually only eight opinions in the country that officially matter. Today on the show, we meet the committee that calls recessions. | Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The tale of the Onion King (Update) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500152/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 23:50:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500152/</guid><description>Podcast Description How one man&amp;rsquo;s quest to dominate the onion market changed commodities trading, and potentially how much you pay at the grocery store, forever. | Subscribe to Planet Money+ in Apple Podcasts or at plus.npr.org/planetmoney.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The debate over what's causing inflation | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500153/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 22:57:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500153/</guid><description>Podcast Description The last few months have made us acutely aware of inflation. We all agree that it&amp;rsquo;s making our lives harder, but economists disagree about what&amp;rsquo;s causing it. | Fill out our listener survey: npr.org/podcastsurvey Transcript</description></item><item><title>Let them eat lunch | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500154/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 00:23:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500154/</guid><description>Podcast Description For many Americans, desk lunches are the norm. You might even be having one right now. But what if it didn&amp;rsquo;t have to be this way? | Fill out our listener survey here Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Gecko Effect | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500155/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 00:10:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Years ago advertising was dominated by cars and beer. Today on the show, how a simple slogan and a talking gecko helped the insurance industry become one of the most dominant forces in advertising. Now, we&amp;rsquo;re all living with the consequences. | Fill out our listener survey here
Transcript</description></item><item><title>On the case: Recession, formula, and greenbacks | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500156/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 00:25:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500156/</guid><description>Podcast Description It was just another day at the office. Then the phone started ringing and the caseload kept growing&amp;hellip;on today&amp;rsquo;s show, your favorite Planet Money gumshoes investigate your listener questions. | Fill out our listener survey here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Homer Simpson vs. the economy | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500157/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 22:28:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500157/</guid><description>Podcast Description When the beloved Simpsons family made its TV debut in 1989, it squarely represented middle-class America. Today &amp;hellip; not so much. That house, those two cars, those three kids all on one salary doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem so believable anymore. Today we examine the changing reality of what middle-class means in America through the Simpsons. It&amp;rsquo;s a wild, musical journey into the heart of the US economy. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.</description></item><item><title>The bank war (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500158/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 22:20:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500158/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the 1800s, populist president Andrew Jackson went head-to-head with the most powerful banker in America over who should control the country&amp;rsquo;s money. This clash ended in disastrous results.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We Buy a Superhero 7: Collectibles (Live Show!) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500159/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 00:49:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500159/</guid><description>Podcast Description What transforms a regular object into a collectible? At our live show earlier this month, we went on a journey through collectibles history. And we had a goal: to turn our Micro-Face comic book into the most collectible item of all time. | Bid on our collectible Micro-Face comic book here!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The NRA's Secret Tapes | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500160/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 02:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500160/</guid><description>Podcast Description Soon after the mass shooting at Columbine High School in 1999, leaders of the National Rifle Association held a conference call to craft their response. Secret tapes from this call obtained by NPR&amp;rsquo;s Investigations team reveal how the NRA developed what would become their standard response after decades of school shootings. | Listen to the original Up First episode: n.pr/nratapes
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Investing in mediocrity | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500161/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 23:09:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500161/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is the key to success in financial markets a matter of luck or skill? One former bond manager shares his strategy: Win big by avoiding winning. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How the burrito became a sandwich (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500162/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 22:03:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500162/</guid><description>Podcast Description A sandwich is generally defined as something delicious slapped between two slices of bread. New York tax code would beg to differ. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Buy now, pay dearly? | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500163/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 00:45:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500163/</guid><description>Podcast Description A wave of companies that allow customers to pay for items from their favorite stores in four interest-free installments has taken over the country. But is &amp;ldquo;buy now, pay later&amp;rdquo; lending too good to be true? | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A 12-year-old girl takes on the video game industry (UPDATE) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500164/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 21:19:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500164/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Maddie Messer was 12 years old, she noticed an unfair dynamic in the video games she loved: playing as a man was often free, but she had to pay to play as a woman. So &amp;hellip; she decided to take on the video game industry. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The day Russia adopted the free market | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500165/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 00:24:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500165/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the early 90s, American economist Jeffrey Sachs was a part of a team that tried to transform Russia&amp;rsquo;s economy. It did not go as planned. He tells us what he thinks went so wrong. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Escheat show (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500166/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 23:20:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500166/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for money you&amp;rsquo;ve forgotten about, there&amp;rsquo;s a chance the government might have it. The good news is that you can get it back. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Planet Money book club | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500167/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Behind every Planet Money episode is a ton of reading. Today, we share some of our favorite books from along the way. Here are our picks:
From Mary, American Bonds: How Credit Markets Shaped a Nation by Sarah L. Quinn
From Erika, The End of Globalization: Lessons from the Great Depression by Harold James
From Alexi, The Sixth Extinction: An Unnatural History by Elizabeth Kolbert
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Risky business | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500168/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 22:49:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two stories on how businesses are using insurance to navigate new kinds of risks. First, how music venues are handling pandemic-related risks. And how Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine is affecting cyber insurance. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We Buy a Superhero 6: The Comic Book | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500169/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 23:34:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500169/</guid><description>Podcast Description After many, many delays, the Micro-Face comic book is here! And we answer the burning question: Why did it take so long to make a comic book? | Come see Planet Money Live in NYC on May 10th! One night only. Tickets on sale here. And buy our now-ready Micro-Face comic book.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>TikTok to the top | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500170/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 01:01:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Thanks to TikTok, Tai Verdes went from struggling musician to Top 40 hitmaker. But first, he had to crack the algorithm of how to go viral. | Come see Planet Money Live in NYC on May 10th! One night only. Tickets on sale here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The student loan paaaaauuuuuse | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500171/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 20:47:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500171/</guid><description>Podcast Description The pause on federal student loan payments was just extended for the sixth time in two years. So&amp;hellip;what&amp;rsquo;s that been like for the borrowers, and what&amp;rsquo;s in store for them when the system eventually restarts? | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here. | Planet Money TikTok has been nominated for a Webby award! Cast your vote for us here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Peanuts and Cracker Jack (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500172/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 21:48:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ballpark vendors share their strategies and other secrets to selling the most hot dogs at baseball games. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How manatees got into hot water | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500173/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 23:41:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500173/</guid><description>Podcast Description While on the brink of extinction in the 1970s, manatees found sanctuary in the warm waters of Florida power plants. Now, they&amp;rsquo;re hooked on fossil fuels. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Turkey's runaway inflation problem | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500174/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 22:08:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500174/</guid><description>Podcast Description Turkey is facing really high inflation, over 60 percent. Its president is taking an unorthodox approach to dealing with it. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>When bricks were rubles | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500175/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 23:48:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500175/</guid><description>Podcast Description For a brief, strange period after the U.S.S.R. collapsed, &amp;ldquo;real&amp;rdquo; money was less valuable than tradeable objects like bricks or towels. We look back at the Russian barter economy and we see the nature of money and value underneath all currency. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Bond King | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500176/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 22:07:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500176/</guid><description>Podcast Description Investing legend Bill Gross revolutionized the bond market, built an empire, and lost it all. Our very own Mary Childs talks about her new book, The Bond King. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Fashion Fair's makeover | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500177/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 23:28:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500177/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fashion Fair was the first big national brand to make makeup for Black women, but it slowly faded into obscurity. Now that it&amp;rsquo;s relaunched, can it compete in an industry it helped create? | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two inflation Indicators: Corporate greed and mortgage rates | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500178/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 00:21:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500178/</guid><description>Podcast Description Corporate profits are soaring. So are prices. Can corporations just not raise prices? Would that fight inflation? We examine this theory making the rounds. Then, we go inside the pipes of the economy to see how mortgage rates connect to that recent rate hike by the Federal Reserve. | Subscribe to our sister podcast, The Indicator from Planet Money. It&amp;rsquo;s daily, and always less than 10 minutes.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tech giants and tiny dogs | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500179/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 23:44:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500179/</guid><description>Podcast Description What a business that makes ramps for wiener dogs teaches us about the massive power of tech giants. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Escape from Russia | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500180/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 23:13:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500180/</guid><description>Podcast Description An American business owner with employees in Russia extracts her colleagues from the country. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Grocery delivery wars | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500181/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 22:38:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Behind the scenes at a new kind of grocery store that promises delivery in minutes. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The dollar at the center of the world (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500182/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 00:32:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500182/</guid><description>Podcast Description After World War II devastated the global economy, there was a push for a new universal currency. This is the story of how the U.S. dollar won. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Of oligarchs, oil and rubles | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500183/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 02:32:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500183/</guid><description>Podcast Description Three stories about how the sanctions imposed on Russia are playing out – for regular Russian people, for Russia&amp;rsquo;s super-rich, and for Russia&amp;rsquo;s energy exports. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>'Fortress' Russia put to the test | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500184/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 23:37:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500184/</guid><description>Podcast Description The U.S. is putting Russia&amp;rsquo;s defense plan against sanctions to the test. Meanwhile, Russia&amp;rsquo;s role as a huge exporter of oil and natural gas could cause ripple effects throughout the global economy. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Putin's big bet: Sanction-proofing Russia | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500185/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 20:14:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500185/</guid><description>Podcast Description The U.S. is imposing economic sanctions on Russia to punish it for invading Ukraine. But Russia has spent years trying to make its economy immune to sanctions. So, will these new sanctions be enough? | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How bad is inflation? | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500186/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 00:33:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500186/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two stories about the effects of inflation on the economy. We meet a gig worker who&amp;rsquo;s seen an increase in wages, but because of inflation, how much of that increase in earnings is an illusion? Then, we break down how the Federal Reserve is planning to fight inflation. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Predictions: Inflation! | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500187/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 23:50:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500187/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s time for another round of &amp;ldquo;Planet Money Predictions!&amp;rdquo; Economic forecasters square off to predict the future of inflation and explain what&amp;rsquo;s going on in the economy.| Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SPAM strikes back | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500188/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 00:29:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500188/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hormel Foods makes SPAM, and for generations, the company also created jobs for families in Austin, Minnesota. Today, the story of a labor strike that threatened to tear one small town apart. (This episode was made in collaboration with The Experiment podcast.) | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Waste land (Bonus) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500189/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 23:03:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500189/</guid><description>Podcast Description Recycling most plastic doesn&amp;rsquo;t work. It never has. In 2020, we ran an episode showing how big oil companies misled the public into thinking plastic would be recycled. That episode just won a duPont-Columbia award. Here it is. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Our Valentines 2022 | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500190/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 23:03:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500190/</guid><description>Podcast Description We profess our love for our curiosities, obsessions, and the things we wish we&amp;rsquo;d thought of first. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A SWIFT getaway | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500191/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 00:29:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500191/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2016, thieves tried to steal nearly a billion dollars from the Bank of Bangladesh&amp;rsquo;s reserves without ever entering the building. And six years later, justice hasn&amp;rsquo;t been so SWIFT. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Uncle Sam wants YOU to fight inflation | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500192/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 00:07:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500192/</guid><description>Podcast Description How war bonds, controlled prices, and a national network of nosy neighbors helped beat inflation during WWII. Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The M&amp;M anomaly (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500193/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 19:59:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500193/</guid><description>Podcast Description Despite costing the same price, a pack of peanut butter M&amp;amp;M&amp;rsquo;s weighs 0.06 ounces less than a pack of milk chocolate M&amp;amp;M&amp;rsquo;s. A trade secret explains why. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Spider-Man Problem | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500194/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 01:06:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500194/</guid><description>Podcast Description Spider-Man isn&amp;rsquo;t the first film franchise to be rebooted over and over again. But the infamous off-screen drama between Marvel Studios and Sony Pictures explains why it happens so frequently. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two indicators: supply chain solutions | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500195/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 22:27:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500195/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two stories about people trying to overcome supply chain challenges. We follow a ship that is forced to get creative to bypass clogged ports, and we visit a warehouse that is running out of space. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>'Soul Train' and the business of Black joy | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500196/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 22:35:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500196/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Soul Train first launched in 1970, Black audiences weren&amp;rsquo;t understood as a viable target market. Don Cornelius changed that forever with his weekly TV dance show. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Patent racism (classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500197/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 22:08:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500197/</guid><description>Podcast Description Economist Lisa Cook has been nominated to serve on the Federal Reserve board. In 2020, she talked to us about proving that racism stifles innovation. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The rapid testing show | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500198/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 02:38:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500198/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Planet Money team fans out across the nation with one goal: to get a Covid test in 24 hours. It is easier said than done. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>No such thing as a free return | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500199/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 00:29:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500199/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lenient policies have shoppers making more returns than ever — around half a trillion dollars worth of products. Today, we find out the fate of some of those returned goods.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>HBO 2.0 | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500200/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 00:29:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500200/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happens when the iconic symbol of your brand no longer makes sense? Today, HBO tries to evolve their sonic brand. This episode was adapted from the podcast Twenty Thousand Hertz. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The rest of the story, 2021 | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500201/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 22:46:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500201/</guid><description>Podcast Description On protests, pasta and forgiven payments. Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The holiday industrial complex (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500202/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 05:10:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500202/</guid><description>Podcast Description Where do holidays like National Potato Chip Day and Argyle Day come from? We trace the roots of one made-up holiday until we find out who is running the global holiday machine. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The economic indicator of the year | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500203/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 01:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500203/</guid><description>Podcast Description Will it be inflation? Striketober? The supply chain? Our hosts make their case, and the choice is up to you.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bell wars (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500204/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 21:30:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500204/</guid><description>Podcast Description The two biggest handbell companies in the world have been locked in a feud for decades. Why? | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Planet Money's Supply Chain Holiday Extravaganza | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500205/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 05:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500205/</guid><description>Podcast Description Planet Money&amp;rsquo;s Supply Chain Holiday Extravaganza Did the supply chain wreck your holiday shopping? Planet Money comes to the rescue. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>No shortages of labor stories | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500206/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 00:47:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500206/</guid><description>Podcast Description We asked for your dispatches from the labor market, and boy did we hear back. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We buy a lot of Christmas trees (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500207/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 22:40:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500207/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Robert head to the world&amp;rsquo;s largest Christmas tree auction with $1,000 and a truck. And get schooled in the tree market. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two music indicators | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500208/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 01:06:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500208/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ticket scalping frustrates fans, but it fascinates economists. It&amp;rsquo;s been a favorite topic of ours in the past. This time, Darian turns to friends and experts to navigate the world of concert tickets like an economist who is also a music fan. Then we find out just how big Adele is on vinyl. So big her latest album disrupted the whole market for vinyl, the material itself. | These stories come from our daily podcast The Indicator.</description></item><item><title>Is a Stradivarius just a violin? (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500209/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 23:17:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500209/</guid><description>Podcast Description Many music aficionados will tell you that violins and violas made by legendary craftsman Antonio Stradivari represent the pinnacle of the instruments. But what if it&amp;rsquo;s all just an example of really good branding? | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Consider the lobstermen | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500210/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 03:01:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500210/</guid><description>Podcast Description A tense conflict between Indigenous fishermen and commercial lobstermen flared up in Nova Scotia in the fall of 2020. Today, how it all got started and how the Canadian government added fuel to the fire. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A locked door, a secret meeting and the birth of the Fed (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500211/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 00:35:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500211/</guid><description>Podcast Description The story of the back-room dealings that created America&amp;rsquo;s central bank. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Day of the Debt | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500212/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 05:10:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500212/</guid><description>Podcast Description We make a loan to the U.S. government, and it does not go the way we thought it would. Plus: the story of that one time the U.S. defaulted. Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>You asked for real raises, free shipping, and a special delivery | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500213/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 01:13:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500213/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s listener question time. We&amp;rsquo;ve got answers about &amp;ldquo;free&amp;rdquo; shipping, full employment, when a raise isn&amp;rsquo;t a raise, Taylor Swift, crypto seizures and our very own Micro-Face comic. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A trunk full of truffles (Update) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500214/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 04:58:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500214/</guid><description>Podcast Description Truffles are one of the most expensive and sought after ingredients in the world. Today, we look back at our NYC adventure with a truffle smuggler and how the market has changed since we last talked to him. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Of boats and boxes | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500215/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 21:19:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500215/</guid><description>Podcast Description We take a trip to ports on the east and west coasts to ask what&amp;rsquo;s on everyone&amp;rsquo;s mind: why are they so clogged? And how can we fix it? | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Auction fever (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500216/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 23:44:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500216/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we go on a Planet Money roadtrip to learn the secrets of the auction world. We find some amazing bargains, some shady strategies and a giant big digger. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here. Transcript</description></item><item><title>Planes, trains and bad bridges | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500217/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 01:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500217/</guid><description>Podcast Description The $1.2 trillion infrastructure bill has passed Congress, but what exactly is in it? Today, the important, surprising, delightful line items. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Moonshot in the arm | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500218/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2021 23:39:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500218/</guid><description>Podcast Description COVID-19 prompted the quickest vaccine development in history. An inside look at how the government and pharmaceutical companies joined forces to make it happen.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Wheat Whisperer | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500219/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 23:40:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500219/</guid><description>Podcast Description Southeast Asia is one of the biggest growth markets for American wheat. Where did this taste for wheat come from and who is responsible?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Night of the living inflation | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500220/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 22:42:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500220/</guid><description>Podcast Description We look at a hidden form of inflation affecting our economy — we&amp;rsquo;re calling it &amp;ldquo;skimpflation.&amp;rdquo; The Indicator tells a spooky tale about the inflation demon. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nice work week, if you can get it | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500221/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500221/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 40 hour work week has been the standard for 80 years. What will it take to lower that? | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two indicators: Congressional Game Theory and the Debt Ceiling | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500222/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 23:50:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500222/</guid><description>Podcast Description We bring you two stories from The Indicator on the recent battles being fought in Congress. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Burnout (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500223/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 00:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500223/</guid><description>Podcast Description All types of companies are struggling with burnout. Many try to fix it. Most of them fail. One exception: A 26-year-old call center manager, with stress balls and costumes in her arsenal. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Janet Jackson's 'Control' | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500224/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 22:44:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500224/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the 35th anniversary of Janet Jackson&amp;rsquo;s first No. 1 Billboard Hot 100 hit, our friends at It&amp;rsquo;s Been A Minute look back at Control, her career-defining album that changed the trajectory of pop music in the late &amp;rsquo;80s and &amp;rsquo;90s.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hire power | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500225/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 21:49:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500225/</guid><description>Podcast Description Noncompete agreements have become an integral part of job contracts. A show about what they are and how we got here. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Do You Feel? (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500226/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 23:47:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500226/</guid><description>Podcast Description We tend to think of economists as cold, unfeeling, attempting to be as rational as possible. But once a month, economists pick up the phone to just&amp;hellip; check in with us. How are we feeling? Good, bad, worse than a year ago? It&amp;rsquo;s a very specific phone call with very specific questions and a few years ago we looked into the origins of this very important survey that factors into economic decision making.</description></item><item><title>LIBOR pains | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500227/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 01:27:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500227/</guid><description>Podcast Description For decades, banks used one rate to help set all other rates: LIBOR. After it came out that it&amp;rsquo;d been rigged, regulators said: no more. Now it&amp;rsquo;s a race — and a road trip — to find an alternative. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We set up an offshore company in a tax haven (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500228/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 23:24:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500228/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Pandora Papers released this week reveal how many world leaders allegedly hold wealth through the use of shell companies. We listen back to when we set up our very own Planet Money shell companies.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Rent Help Is Too Damn Slow | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500229/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 00:37:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500229/</guid><description>Podcast Description Congress created a massive pile of money to help people pay rent during the pandemic. Why have so few people gotten help? We follow the money. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>When The U.S. Paid Off The Entire National Debt (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500230/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 23:01:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500230/</guid><description>Podcast Description There was one time the U.S. federal government stopped borrowing and paid off every penny of national debt. It did not end well. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>When Luddites Attack (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500231/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 23:12:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500231/</guid><description>Podcast Description A couple centuries ago, a group of English clothworkers set out to destroy the machines that had been taking their jobs. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Original Sign | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500232/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 01:45:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500232/</guid><description>Podcast Description A request for dozens of stop signs flummoxes a town and angers a resident. A show about infrastructure, decision making and stop signs. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Indicators: Women And Work | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500233/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 00:35:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500233/</guid><description>Podcast Description Women start a lot of businesses, but when it comes time for them to grow, many hit a wall, or the women founders end up losing control. Why? We bring you two indicators on women and work from our daily podcast The Indicator. Also, Amanda and Stacey go on a picnic to prove a point. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Afghanistan's Money Problem | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500234/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 23:57:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500234/</guid><description>Podcast Description Afghanistan&amp;rsquo;s economy changed — almost overnight — after the Taliban retook control of the country | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Flood Money (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500235/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 22:23:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500235/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bill Pennington&amp;rsquo;s house floods a lot: Three times over the course of three years. And every time his house floods, the government pays to help him repair the damage. Is something wrong here? | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>This Is Your Brain On Drug Ads | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500236/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 00:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500236/</guid><description>Podcast Description Apologies to listeners who received two episodes in their feed today. The U.S. is one of two countries in the world that allows pharmaceutical companies to advertise prescription drugs directly to consumers. Why? And what does that do to us Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Indicators: Water Pressure | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500237/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 23:15:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500237/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s another extremely dry, hot summer for the American West. Our daily podcast, The Indicator from Planet Money, brings us two stories about the water shortage in the West with economic ideas that may help. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SUMMER SCHOOL 6: Crypto &amp; Commencement | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500238/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 00:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500238/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the last class of Planet Money Summer School Season 2, we cover one more important market — cryptocurrency. If you&amp;rsquo;re thinking about investing in crypto, do you know exactly what it is that you&amp;rsquo;re buying? Or how it should (if at all) fit alongside the rest of your investments? | Watch this Tik Tok to learn more and subscribe to our weekly newsletter here. | Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to take the Summer School Final Quiz.</description></item><item><title>The Lost Archives of Sadie Alexander | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500239/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 21:28:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500239/</guid><description>Podcast Description The work of our first Black economist was lost to history. Professor Nina Banks set out on a quest to find it. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SUMMER SCHOOL 5: Bubbles, Bikes, &amp; Biases | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500240/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 23:50:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500240/</guid><description>Podcast Description Investing during a bubble can leave you bust. But how to tell the difference between a bubble before it bursts and an investing rocket ship taking off? We&amp;rsquo;ll run through a historical example and look inside our own thinking to find the mental biases that can contribute or exacerbate bad bubble thinking. | Watch this Tik Tok to learn more and subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Indicators: Will Remote Work Kill The Office? | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500241/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 23:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500241/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s Stacey vs Greg in a face off on the future of the office. Each takes a side, armed with studies, historical examples, theories on efficiency and happiness and from their closet studios, they bring their indicators for the future of the office. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here. And our daily podcast The Indicator hosted by Stacey here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SUMMER SCHOOL 4: Bonds &amp; Becky With The Good Yield | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500242/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 23:44:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500242/</guid><description>Podcast Description A few years back, Cardiff asked for an unusual Christmas present: a junk bond&amp;hellip; Parallel to the stock market, the bond market offers different levels of risk and reward. In this class, what is a bond, how do they differ from stocks, and how do they help companies grow? | Watch this Tik Tok to learn more and subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Big Little Ideas | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500243/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 00:40:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500243/</guid><description>Podcast Description There are a lot of fancy terms for the things we experience — but are they really useful? Yes! We explain four social-science terms that can help us understand our world. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SUMMER SCHOOL 3: Smooth Spending &amp; The 401K | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500244/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 22:58:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500244/</guid><description>Podcast Description Even if you don&amp;rsquo;t own stocks, there are a lot of reasons to care about investing. We meet some of the folks left out of the stock market who deploy sophisticated economic thinking, even creating their own alternate financial systems. Our professors help us understand how consumption smoothing and life-cycle hypothesis apply to personal finance. And we meet the creator of the 401(k). | Watch this Tik Tok to learn more and subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.</description></item><item><title>Mobile Home Parked | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500245/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 22:46:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500245/</guid><description>Podcast Description We find out what happens when big investors spend billions of dollars buying mobile home parks and make them less affordable for the people who live there. Then we learn how the government helps them do it, with super low-cost loans that were meant to support affordable housing. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SUMMER SCHOOL 2: Index Funds &amp; The Bet | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500246/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 21:08:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500246/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2006, Warren Buffett bet a million dollars that the most brainless, boring investment around would do better than the researched, handpicked investments of some of the smartest hedge fund managers in the world. The second class of Summer School looks at how that bet played out, the origins of the index fund, and why it&amp;rsquo;s so hard to beat the market. Returning to the underlying theme of risk and reward, we also discuss how diversification reduces risk.</description></item><item><title>Three Reasons for the Housing Shortage | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500247/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 22:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500247/</guid><description>Podcast Description America&amp;rsquo;s housing shortage has been decades in the making. A lot of people blame Baby Boomers — but is it really their fault? We unpack three big reasons for the shortage. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SUMMER SCHOOL 1: The Stock Market &amp; Penelope The Cow | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500248/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 23:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500248/</guid><description>Podcast Description The first class of Planet Money Summer School starts off with a field trip. With the help of a cow, two economists, and three cute animals, we learn what a stock is and how stocks are priced, and we begin to see the psychological forces that make prices move up and down on the stock market. Keep an eye out throughout for our big theme for the course this summer: risk and reward.</description></item><item><title>Banque Worms | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500249/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2021 01:44:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500249/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last year, one of the biggest banks accidentally paid off a client&amp;rsquo;s loan to its lenders — a $900 million mistake. Some of the recipients wouldn&amp;rsquo;t give the money back. And then a surprising court ruling affirmed their no give-back. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Video Gaming The System | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500250/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 23:54:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500250/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two groups of people who would never meet in real life collide in a world of wizards and dragons. They battle it out in a low-tech video game, and it shakes the lives of a lot of real people living in a collapsing economy. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Great Inflation (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500251/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2021 06:31:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500251/</guid><description>Podcast Description For much of the 1970s inflation was bad. Prices rose at over 10 percent a year. Nothing could stop it — until one powerful person did something very unpopular. Today&amp;rsquo;s show: How we beat inflation. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>100 Years Since Sadie Alexander | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500252/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 22:48:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500252/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1921, Sadie Alexander became the first Black person in America to receive a PhD in economics. Then, she was functionally shut out of economics jobs, got a law degree, and became an attorney instead. A century later, economics has made notably little progress bringing Black women into the field. We work with The Sadie Collective to bring you three stories from three eras of recent history that show us how the field has changed, where it still falls short, and the unique joys of being a Black woman and loving economics.</description></item><item><title>Of Memestocks and Milk Bags | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500253/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 03:18:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500253/</guid><description>Podcast Description We answer your questions about memestocks, milk in bags, the size of cereal boxes, and products exclusive to the rich, but not for long? | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Indicators: Clogged Ports And Corporate Vets | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500254/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 23:51:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500254/</guid><description>Podcast Description We bring you two stories from The Indicator on two industries that are undergoing rapid change: vets and container shipping. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Rest Of The Story, Summer 2021 | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500255/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 21:31:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500255/</guid><description>Podcast Description We follow up on takeout cocktails, college athletes at the Supreme Court, bankrupt Hertz, and the new shape of pasta. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What's A Bubble? (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500256/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 00:42:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500256/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can you tell if the economy is in a bubble? How? And why do bubbles happen? Robert Shiller and Eugene Fama shared the economics Nobel back in 2013 despite fundamentally disagreeing over the meaning of a bubble. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bobby Bonilla Day | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500257/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 00:38:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500257/</guid><description>Podcast Description How the worst deal in baseball explains one of the most important concepts in economics. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Corporate Fugitive: Carlos Ghosn | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500258/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 21:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500258/</guid><description>Podcast Description Japan once served sushi in the shape of Carlos Ghosn&amp;rsquo;s face. Then Japanese authorities arrested the celebrity CEO who remade Nissan. We bring you first hand accounts of his spectacular rise, sudden fall and dramatic escape. | This episode is a collaboration with HBR IdeaCast.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Predictions! | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500259/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 21:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500259/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two forecasters predict the future of the U.S. economy — and promise to come back on the show to see who was right, and who was wrong. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Uncle Jamie Broke Jeopardy (Update) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500260/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 21:01:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500260/</guid><description>Podcast Description James Holzhauer took a math degree, a gambling career, and a buzzer, and turned it into a fortune on a game show. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Used Car Talk | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500261/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 20:30:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500261/</guid><description>Podcast Description How supply and demand stalled out the used car industry. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Stuff Gets Cheaper (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500262/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 21:59:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500262/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the world of consumer electronics, it pays to be cheap. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Amateur Hour at the Supreme Court | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500263/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 22:50:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500263/</guid><description>Podcast Description College athletes are considered amateur players. And amateurs don&amp;rsquo;t make any money. But can they get more education paid for at least? | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Black Wall Street | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500264/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 20:25:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500264/</guid><description>Podcast Description 100 years ago, Black Wall Street was destroyed. But how was it built? And what does it take to get restitution? | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>One Hack to Fool Them All | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500265/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500265/</guid><description>Podcast Description How a single hack pried open the networks of giant corporations and the U.S. government itself. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Runaway Recommendation Engine | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500266/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 23:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500266/</guid><description>Podcast Description Recommendation systems have changed how we choose what we want. But are they choosing what we want? | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Big Government Cheese (CLASSIC) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500267/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 21:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500267/</guid><description>Podcast Description That time the U.S. government accidentally created a cheese surplus so large it had to be stored in a ginormous cave. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Get The Vaccine, Lose The Skinny Jeans | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500268/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 23:04:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500268/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two stories from our Indicator team about the sometimes-unlikely people who shape what we buy and what we do. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Blood Money | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500269/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 20:32:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500269/</guid><description>Podcast Description The United States is one of the few countries that lets companies pay people for their blood plasma. Why? | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hot Cheetos | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500270/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 03:18:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500270/</guid><description>Podcast Description A janitor walks out of a chip factory with a bag of dustless Cheetos and changes the global snack game forever. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Emission Impossible | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500271/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 22:09:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500271/</guid><description>Podcast Description Carbon offsets have become a popular tool to combat climate change. But how effective are they? | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>DIY Reparations | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500272/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 21:10:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500272/</guid><description>Podcast Description Some Vermonters were tired of waiting around for reparations. So they decided to take matters into their own hands. | This episode was produced with our friends at Invisibilia. Check out their new season here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We Buy A Superhero 5: Hollywood | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500273/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 01:06:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500273/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the last and greatest chapter to our superhero saga, Micro-Face tries to make the jump from comic books to movies. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The $100 Million Deli | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500274/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 22:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500274/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why is a single New Jersey deli worth so much? And what does it tell us about how the stock market works? | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We Buy A Superhero 4: Sellout | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500275/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 22:59:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500275/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two months ago, Planet Money got its own superhero. Today, we sell him out. | Find the full Planet Money Superhero series here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Writers Revolt (UPDATE) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500276/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 22:34:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500276/</guid><description>Podcast Description We have a winner in an epic Hollywood story. A couple years back, 7,000 TV writers across the U.S. fired their agents. All on the same day. It was part of a battle over how creative work gets valued and compensated in TV and film. Now, we have the dramatic resolution. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>India, Farming, and the Free Market | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500277/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 23:26:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500277/</guid><description>Podcast Description For decades, India has shielded its agricultural sector from the free market. Now, the government wants to let it in. Millions and millions of farmers are not happy about it. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Workin' 9 To 5 | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500278/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 18:16:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500278/</guid><description>Podcast Description The movie &amp;ldquo;9 to 5&amp;rdquo; used humor to highlight the struggles of women in the workplace 40 years ago. Where are we now? | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>About Your Extended Warranty | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500279/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 22:37:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500279/</guid><description>Podcast Description Calls about &amp;ldquo;extended auto warranties&amp;rdquo; blow up our phones over and over. But what are these robocalls actually offering? | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Jacob Loud's Land Was Lost | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500280/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 21:25:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500280/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today&amp;rsquo;s show: the arcane laws that have cost Black landowners their property, and the lawyer who is trying to fix those laws. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Two Indicators: Boomtown &amp; Bye Bye | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500281/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 21:18:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500281/</guid><description>Podcast Description We look at housing prices in Montana, an oil market milestone, and give a fond farewell. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Curse Of The Black Lotus (Update) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500282/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 19:40:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500282/</guid><description>Podcast Description When the popular card game Magic: The Gathering entered a speculative bubble, its creators found a way to keep it from bursting. We check in to see if their strategy is still working. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Socialism 101 | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500283/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 18:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500283/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today on the show: The critics of capitalism. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>You Asked For Shots, Tuna, Metal, and Money | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500284/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 21:56:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500284/</guid><description>Podcast Description Listeners send us questions every day. It&amp;rsquo;s about time we answer a few of them. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The New Shape Of Pasta | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500285/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 22:18:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500285/</guid><description>Podcast Description What do you do when you can&amp;rsquo;t find the perfect pasta shape? You invent a new shape. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Even More Minimum Wage | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500286/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 18:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500286/</guid><description>Podcast Description The tipped minimum wage hasn&amp;rsquo;t changed for decades. Is now finally the time? | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The $69 Million JPEG | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500287/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 04:28:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500287/</guid><description>Podcast Description An artist called Beeple just sold a piece at Christie&amp;rsquo;s for millions. But it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a painting&amp;hellip; it was a kind of crypto. We speak with him and the others behind the first NFT auction. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nigeria, You Win! (Update) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500288/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 22:41:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500288/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nigerians heard a radio ad offering millions of dollars for people with business proposals. They thought it was a scam. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Marriage Pact | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500289/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 00:12:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500289/</guid><description>Podcast Description They say true love is hard to find. Whoever says that isn&amp;rsquo;t an economist. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Happy Fed Independence Day (Update) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500290/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 22:36:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500290/</guid><description>Podcast Description The story of the day the Federal Reserve got its independence and the fight — an actual physical fight — to keep it. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We Buy A Superhero 3: Resurrection | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500291/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 01:07:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500291/</guid><description>Podcast Description We have found the perfect superhero. Now we just have to make him our own. | Find the full Planet Money Superhero series here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bond Voyage | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500292/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 20:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500292/</guid><description>Podcast Description The government used to be afraid to borrow too much money. Today, it borrows hand over fist. And it&amp;rsquo;s &amp;hellip; fine? | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We Buy A Superhero 2: Loophole | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500293/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 23:56:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500293/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marvel was not interested in selling us Doorman. But there is another way to jumpstart our superhero empire. | Find the full Planet Money Superhero series here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why Printers Are The Worst | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500294/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 18:33:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500294/</guid><description>Podcast Description The real money is in the ink. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We Buy A Superhero 1: Origins | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500295/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 00:11:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500295/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marvel has 7,000 characters, many of them forgotten. We want to buy one from their vault and launch our own little Planet Money franchise. | Find the full Planet Money Superhero series here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Can't Let It Go | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500296/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 20:39:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500296/</guid><description>Podcast Description Irrational decisions. Things we can&amp;rsquo;t let go. Friend of the show Sam Sanders comes by to talk obsessions. We turn to economics for advice, clarity and comfort. | Subscribe to Sam&amp;rsquo;s podcast, It&amp;rsquo;s Been A Minute. Transcript</description></item><item><title>Fine and Punishment | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500297/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 20:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500297/</guid><description>Podcast Description When you get out of prison, you have to start paying off fees. Some are related to committing a crime. Others are not. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Robinhood's Very Bad Day | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500298/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 23:16:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500298/</guid><description>Podcast Description How the stock trading app works. And why it almost broke last week. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Can't Stop GameStop | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500299/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 02:26:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500299/</guid><description>Podcast Description Video game stores. Hedge Funds. Reddit forums. How this mad lib resulted in the biggest short squeeze in years. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The World's Biggest Battery (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500300/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 20:19:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500300/</guid><description>Podcast Description California has a ton of solar power. But as soon as night falls, it&amp;rsquo;s gone. Today on the show: how to bottle the sun
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Desi Invented Television | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500301/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 00:55:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500301/</guid><description>Podcast Description The television was invented by Philo Farnsworth in 1927. TV was invented by Desi Arnaz in 1951.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Modern Monetary Theory (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500302/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 18:21:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500302/</guid><description>Podcast Description We rethink everything we know about government spending, taxes, and the nature of money.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Great Gatsby | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500303/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2021 00:08:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500303/</guid><description>Podcast Description All of it. Read by the staff of Planet Money.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nervous TikTok | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500304/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 03:00:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500304/</guid><description>Podcast Description The U.S. was going to ban TikTok&amp;hellip; and then it didn&amp;rsquo;t. We break down the beef with TikTok, and see what life would have been like without it. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Planet Monet (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500305/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 22:19:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500305/</guid><description>Podcast Description Investors are pouring money into art, but a lot of it is disappearing into storage. We find out why. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Bees Go To California (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500306/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 23:23:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500306/</guid><description>Podcast Description Almonds taste great. And the logistics behind pollinating almond trees are un-bee-lievable. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chaos At The Capitol | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500307/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 02:22:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500307/</guid><description>Podcast Description With an insurrection at the Capitol, we interrupt Planet Money and turn the feed over to tonight&amp;rsquo;s episode of the NPR Politics podcast. | Subscribe to Planet Money&amp;rsquo;s weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bitcoin Losers (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500308/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 22:57:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500308/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Bitcoin market is still crazy, but a lot of people can&amp;rsquo;t even find their Bitcoins. We go looking for lost billions. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Rest Of The Story, 2020 | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500309/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 22:49:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500309/</guid><description>Podcast Description We check in on The Fed, a vaccine scientist, and the mixed martial arts. Oh, and a bunch of escheaters. So long, 2020! | Support our show here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How To Stop An Asteroid (UPDATE) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500310/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2020 22:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500310/</guid><description>Podcast Description Some smart people say we should be doing more to protect the Earth from asteroids. The technical issues are relatively easy. The economics — figuring out who&amp;rsquo;s going to pay — are much harder. | Support our show here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Fork The Government | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500311/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 03:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500311/</guid><description>Podcast Description A global pandemic might not be the best time to try something new with technology. But Taiwan decided to do it anyway. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Mixtape Drama | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500312/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2020 00:40:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500312/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mixtapes were the heart of hip-hop culture in the 90s. Until an arrest in 2007 brought it all down. | Today&amp;rsquo;s episode is from our friends at Louder Than a Riot.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Case Against Facebook | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500313/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 01:21:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500313/</guid><description>Podcast Description The government just filed one of the largest antitrust cases in history against Facebook. Why now? And what will it mean? | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We Buy A Lot Of Christmas Trees | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500314/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 22:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500314/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Robert head to the world&amp;rsquo;s largest Christmas tree auction with $1,000 and a truck. And get schooled in the tree market. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Stolen Company (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500315/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:28:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500315/</guid><description>Podcast Description When an American company named ABRO learns their goods are being counterfeited in China, they start their own trade war. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How The Rat Blew Up | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500316/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 00:36:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500316/</guid><description>Podcast Description Unions have been putting giant inflatable rats in front of businesses for years. Now businesses are trying to deflate them, in court. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Before The Shot In The Arm | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500317/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 02:45:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500317/</guid><description>Podcast Description Inventing a vaccine for COVID-19 was hard, but getting billions of doses to billions of people is going to be even harder. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hot Dog Hail Mary (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500318/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 22:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500318/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Falcons are trying something radical: Making their food cheaper. It could break stadium economics.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Swamp Gravy (UPDATE) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500319/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 23:47:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500319/</guid><description>Podcast Description Colquitt, Georgia, was struggling. And then musical theater came along. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>All Your Genes Are Belong To Us | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500320/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 01:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500320/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who owns your genes, anyway? For a while, Big Biotech patented 20% of the human genome. Then a lawyer took them to the Supreme Court. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trade Show (UPDATE) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500321/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 23:56:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500321/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s been a rough four years for free trade. Today on the show, we present 244 years of trade in 22 minutes. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Biden Time | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500322/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 22:24:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500322/</guid><description>Podcast Description Four things Joe Biden can do as president — even if the Democrats don&amp;rsquo;t control Congress. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Worst. Tariffs. Ever. (Classic) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500323/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 21:55:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500323/</guid><description>Podcast Description One of the few things a new president has a lot of control over is tariff policies. But it wasn&amp;rsquo;t always that way. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hacking The Perfect Auction | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500324/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 22:57:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500324/</guid><description>Podcast Description A Nobel-Prize winner spent years designing an auction to sell off the airwaves, which are owned by the public. But Wall Street found a tiny flaw. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What's Next for the Economy? | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500325/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 21:10:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500325/</guid><description>Podcast Description A research group at Harvard came up with a faster way to check the economy&amp;rsquo;s pulse. It may change how we fight recessions. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What Economy Are You Voting For? | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500326/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 21:25:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500326/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two candidates. Two very different ways of thinking about the economy. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Who Gets To Vote In Florida? | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500327/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 23:30:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500327/</guid><description>Podcast Description Angel Sanchez was 17 and in prison when he learned felons couldn&amp;rsquo;t vote in Florida. When he got out, he tried to change that. It was working – until money got involved.| Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Frame Canada | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500328/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 21:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500328/</guid><description>Podcast Description For years, Wendell Potter ran a campaign to terrify Americans&amp;hellip; about health care in Canada. Now he explains how he did it, and why. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hey Google, Are You Too Big? | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500329/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 00:23:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500329/</guid><description>Podcast Description The government just filed an antitrust lawsuit against Google. In this episode, we talk about why, and why it matters. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Opening Schools And Other Hard Decisions | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500330/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 23:47:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500330/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily Oster wanted to understand the risks of opening schools. So she started a massive data collection campaign. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Caste Arrives In Silicon Valley | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500331/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 20:22:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500331/</guid><description>Podcast Description For some Indian employees of big U.S. tech companies, caste discrimination is real. To combat it, first people have to talk about it. That&amp;rsquo;s hard. | Today&amp;rsquo;s episode is from our friends at Rough Translation.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Political Ad Nauseam | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500332/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2020 22:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500332/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s presidential election season, and that means it&amp;rsquo;s political ad season. But who do ads target, anyway? | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rethinking Black Wealth | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500333/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 21:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500333/</guid><description>Podcast Description Homes in Black neighborhoods are valued lower than homes in white neighborhoods. Why? This episode, Dr. Andre Perry flips the narrative of the racial wealth gap. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Call Center Call Out | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500334/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 23:17:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500334/</guid><description>Podcast Description We visit life on the other side of your customer service call and get a glimpse into the troubling future of work in America. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trump's Tiny Taxes | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500335/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 01:05:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500335/</guid><description>Podcast Description A totally refreshing 20 minutes or so of infotainment related to Trump, taxes and toy wooden arrows. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sell Me Your Climate Bombs | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500336/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 22:41:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500336/</guid><description>Podcast Description There are tanks all over the U.S. that are like little climate change time bombs, ticking away. Today on the show, getting to them before they go off. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>REDMAP (Update) | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500337/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 21:53:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500337/</guid><description>Podcast Description The result of national elections is shaped in a big and underappreciated way by very local elections. This is the story of the man who shaped many, many local elections to tip the national scales. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Apple v Everybody | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500338/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2020 22:01:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500338/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Epic Games CEO Tim Sweeney sued Apple over its App Store, it started a war about antitrust and the internet.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>After The Plague | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500339/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 21:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500339/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Black Death was one of the worst catastrophes to ever hit humanity. But it also helped upend feudal hierarchies, redistribute wealth, and make daily life better for a lot of medieval Europeans.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Waste Land | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500340/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 23:33:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500340/</guid><description>Podcast Description Recycling plastic has never worked very well. So who convinced us this was a good idea? In this episode, we might have the answer. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We Buy A Junk Bond | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500341/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 20:07:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500341/</guid><description>Podcast Description Team Indicator buys Cardiff a surprise present. A terrible, extremely risky, but wildly interesting investment. Then it gets interesting. The company that issued the junk bond declared bankruptcy. But that wasn&amp;rsquo;t the end of the story. | Subscribe to our daily podcast, The Indicator here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Murderer, The Boy King, And The Invention Of Modern Finance | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500342/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2020 00:08:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500342/</guid><description>Podcast Description John Law killed a man in a duel, brought the first paper money to France, and became one of the richest people in the world. Then it all collapsed.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SUMMER SCHOOL: Graduation! | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500343/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 22:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500343/</guid><description>Podcast Description Summer School graduates take the stage to show us how we can all see our everyday world through the beautiful lens of economics. | Take the final exam and get your diploma here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Old Rules Were Dumb Anyway | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500344/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 22:49:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500344/</guid><description>Podcast Description When the pandemic hit, the old rules went out the window. What rules will stay broken when things go back to normal?Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SUMMER SCHOOL 8: Risk &amp; Disaster | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500345/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 21:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500345/</guid><description>Podcast Description Inside one insurance policy is a world of incentives and bad behaviors. Take the final exam and get your diploma here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Crisis At The Post Office | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500346/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 02:05:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500346/</guid><description>Podcast Description The United States Postal Service is in the middle of a political firestorm. What happened, and can it be fixed? Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SUMMER SCHOOL 7: Advertising &amp; Race | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500347/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 18:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500347/</guid><description>Podcast Description A Black ad executive figures out how to reach diverse audiences.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Big Rigged | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500348/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 19:31:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500348/</guid><description>Podcast Description Driving a truck used to mean freedom. Now it means a mountain of debt. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SUMMER SCHOOL 6: Taxes &amp; Donald Duck | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500349/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 20:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500349/</guid><description>Podcast Description The surprisingly entertaining history of the income tax. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mask Communication | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500350/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 20:58:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500350/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why won&amp;rsquo;t some people wear masks? Is there anything we can do to convince them? We look to behavioral economics for help. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SUMMER SCHOOL 5: Trade &amp; Santa | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500351/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 20:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500351/</guid><description>Podcast Description The economics of free trade and what happens when governments get involved. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>College Fails | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500352/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 23:32:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500352/</guid><description>Podcast Description The pandemic is transforming college from a can&amp;rsquo;t-miss into a can&amp;rsquo;t-attend experience. Can colleges survive? | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SUMMER SCHOOL 4: Scarcity &amp; Pistachios | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500353/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 22:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500353/</guid><description>Podcast Description Class 4 brings us an economic conundrum: how do you efficiently share a scarce resource? | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rest of the Story, Pandemic Edition | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500354/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 20:48:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500354/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rest of the Story, Pandemic Edition We check in on the people we&amp;rsquo;ve met and stories we&amp;rsquo;ve covered since this whole thing started. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SUMMER SCHOOL 3: Profit &amp; Cocaine | Planet Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3020500355/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3020500355/</guid><description>Podcast Description In our third class, we take all that we&amp;rsquo;ve learned about decisions and markets and bring it to a former drug kingpin. | Subscribe to our weekly newsletter here.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>