<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sh**ged Married Annoyed on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/shged-married-annoyed/</link><description>Recent content in Sh**ged Married Annoyed on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 01:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/shged-married-annoyed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ep 248. Breaded Ham | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770001/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770001/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast - there’s a sickness bug in the Ramsey household… plus Chris and Rosie discuss fancy nursery food and trying to eat healthily on tour. QFTPs include an ALLEGED horse attack victim, a mistaken identity in the cookie aisle and some very funny job interviews. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 247. Incense Sisters | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770002/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:45:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770002/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s a lot to get through on this week’s podcast, and it’s hot one! Chris and Rosie discuss the ongoing saga of Elf on the Shelf, why Rosie is thinking about having another baby(!) and general bin problems. QFTP’s involve a couple of icks, a very accidental man and a story involving a reed diffuser that will really stay with you!&amp;nbsp;
Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Ep 246. A new low | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770003/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 01:23:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770003/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Ramsey&amp;rsquo;s return for tour chat, fresh beefs and some massage based chat that leads to various questions. The brilliant QFTP&amp;rsquo;s which involve misheard dirty talk, a bag for life and a school rumour. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 245. Serial Sanitiser | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770004/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 01:34:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770004/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week the Ramsey&amp;rsquo;s record the podcast on the road! The tour is in full swing but Rosie is still getting to grips with the geography of where they are exactly. The pair manage some tour beef and they also discuss the pros of having parties when there&amp;rsquo;s no kids allowed. All of this plus some brilliant QFTP&amp;rsquo;s including a story about women, a flip flop and some serious exhibitionism.</description></item><item><title>Ep 244. *QFTP Special* | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770005/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 01:01:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770005/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Shagged Married Annoyed tour is in full swing so this week The Ramsey&amp;rsquo;s bring you a Question From the Public (Public Public PPPPPP Public) Special! There&amp;rsquo;s strippers, pet shops, fun times up a mountain and a trip to Ayia Napa! Enjoy this week&amp;rsquo;s special episode and Chris and Rosie will be back in your ears next week. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>Ep 243. Bag of Bricks | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770006/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 01:28:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770006/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week&amp;rsquo;s Shagged Married Annoyed Chris and Rosie chat about the upcoming tour and how Chris was nervous about a particular delivery turning up at the house. The pair share their horror at a student story and there is a Rosie&amp;rsquo;s Mystery that blows both their minds. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 242. Beloved Sponge | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770007/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 01:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770007/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast, Chris and Rosie have received a halloween card from Robin. They’ve both been ‘reading’ and they discuss sibling debts. This week&amp;rsquo;s beefs involve an incident with a protein bar and a homework pyramid. QFTPs include a bath time sibling story and an unconventional treatment for a mountain biking injury. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Ep 241. Air Biscuit | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770008/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:00:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770008/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast, Chris and Rosie are preparing themselves for Robin’s birthday party - and in the process, Rosie has found something very interesting for sale on the internet…&amp;nbsp;Chris reveals a milk story from his past and there are lollipop and bruise related beefs. QFTPs include a brilliant nickname and more milk-related trauma.
Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Ep 240. Duvet Lasagne | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770009/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 00:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770009/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast Chris and Rosie discuss warming up for the tour and unconventional duvet arrangements. There is a diet related beef - and Chris has a special request for Rosie. QFTPs include a frisky book club, an unusual fragrance and some more tales from the swinging community. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 239. Talk less, smile more | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770010/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 00:53:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770010/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast Chris and Rosie discuss smelly towels, saying the wrong thing and Designated Survivor. Chris has a new job for his CV and the beefs cover falling asleep and smelly bins. Rosie is on a mission to make the Nana trolley fashionable and the pair are told about an anonymous Whatsapp Group. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Ep 238. Open Sesame | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770011/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 00:15:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770011/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week&amp;rsquo;s podcast Chris has a fashion crisis and Rosie is keen to know some secrets. There&amp;rsquo;s a discussion about Airplane v Aeroplane and Rafe shows Rosie up in the queue for Ice Cream. All of this plus a phantom sandwich poker and a man who tries to perform a sex act on himself. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Ep 237. Dinner Ladies Best Mate | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770012/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 00:22:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770012/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week&amp;rsquo;s podcast the Ramsey&amp;rsquo;s talk rats, homework, nest parenting and a Would You Rather that gets personal! Rosie gets nostalgic for Dinner Ladies and she explains the pooh corner to Chris. QFTP&amp;rsquo;s involve presents, a mother and son interaction and some icks! All of this plus some juicy beefs! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 236. Rosie and Ramsey FM | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770013/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 00:03:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770013/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week's podcast Chris and Rosie discuss Cribs, changing room debacles, cinema codes, childhood lies and there is even an office poll! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 235. Egg, toast, wine and… | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770014/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 00:19:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Prepare yourselves for a mini IQ test on this week&amp;rsquo;s podcast. It gets tense! The Ramsey&amp;rsquo;s talk about The Great North Run and why they will or won&amp;rsquo;t do it and Chris discusses UFO&amp;rsquo;s and Rosie has a rare requested shout out. There&amp;rsquo;s beefs and of course QTFP&amp;rsquo;s which get heavily musical in a rude way! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Ep 234. Triple D | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 00:07:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris and Rosie have been at the NTA&amp;rsquo;s and they share all the gossip from their night! Also this week Rosie learns the names of her fingers and Chris explains his problem with inside toys being outside. QFTP&amp;rsquo;s include a Bat or Bird dilemma and an unfortunate toilet based school story. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 233. 4pm Fight Time | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 00:55:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770016/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week&amp;rsquo;s podcast Chris and Rosie discuss 90&amp;rsquo;s parenting, the Loch Ness monster, and Alabama hot pockets which disturbs Chris to no end! Rosie has some holiday observations and there&amp;rsquo;s a family beef. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 232. Four Eighths | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770017/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 00:30:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770017/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Ramsey&amp;rsquo;s are back from their holidays and not without some stories! There was a hospital trip and some fast food on the plane home. Rosie has been getting to know her fractions whilst Chris has been spreading the Cuddle Club word. There are some holiday beefs plus QFTP&amp;rsquo;s involving stinky cleavage, a home birth and sex on the wedding night. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Ep 231. Obligatory Trebles | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770018/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 00:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770018/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast, The Ramseys are about to go on holiday - but this time, they haven’t told Robin. Rosie gets an enlightening lesson about the equator from Chris. There’s a fake tan related beef and a QFTP about a very embarrassing return. Also there&amp;rsquo;s a stinky Would You Rather and some very exciting news! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>What's that on your prom dress?... A short message from Chris &amp; Rosie | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 12:15:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770019/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Chris and Rosie Ramsey show has been shortlisted for an NTA. Thank you all so much for voting! We now need you to vote again! Visit nationaltvawards.com/vote and you'll find us in the TV Interview Category. Thanks Smas and Das! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 230. Daytime MILF Event | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770020/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770020/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week, Chris went too hard climbing a mountain and Rosie remembers the best Christmas present she ever received. Chris has a beef about Rosie&amp;rsquo;s cooking habits - and the QFTPs teach us all about &amp;lsquo;reclaiming&amp;rsquo;. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 229. No Capping | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770021/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 00:43:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770021/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Chris has a quiz for Rosie to check how down with the kids she is! There&amp;rsquo;s also some beef but only from Chris as Rosie has been off gallivanting again. There is a couple of car based QFTP&amp;rsquo;s and an ex ick. All of this plus some a Carl Hutchinson on tour story! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>Ep 228. Roll In The Woods | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770022/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week, The Ramseys are back from their holiday and they’re also celebrating their anniversary! The beefs include a packing conundrum and someone’s sent in a bizarre egg-related turn on. QFTPs include a bin incident, wedding day jujitsu and the worst photo of all time. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 227. Double Bunny Ears | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770023/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week, The Ramsey&amp;rsquo;s are bracing themselves for the school summer break and they&amp;rsquo;re very close to cancelling their holiday. The beefs include cereal hypocrisy and Chris has a UFC-related ick. QFTPs include an hospitalisation and a one-night-stand who has a way with words. Plus, a listener might have an answer for the supermarket closing time conundrum. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Ep 226. Whiskers | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770024/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 00:56:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770024/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week The Ramsey&amp;rsquo;s talk tantrums, kids performances, comic timing and pool etiquette. The beefs are packing based and QFTP&amp;rsquo;s are pretty filthy but spark a fun new games! Plus a listener gets in touch about the man who drank the cat milk! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 225. Yolo | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770025/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 00:36:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris and Rosie talk soft parenting, celebrities taking part in combat sports and if it&amp;rsquo;s okay to be using YOLO as a greeting! Also this week they try an answer a snail conundrum and have a shared beef! And as a special treat, friend of the podcast Carl Hutchinson makes a rare appearance! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 224. Double Wipe | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770026/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 01:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770026/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Rosie shares some stories from her holiday which involve a rogue pooh and some intimate sun cream application. The beefs are podcast related and the QFTP&amp;rsquo;s involve an ick, a misheard name and some kinky behavior. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 223. Hot Heat | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770027/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:55:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rosie is on holiday so this week so as well as some pre-holiday beef, we have put together some QFTP&amp;rsquo;s they have never made it to the podcast! There&amp;rsquo;s hamsters, icks, a would you rather and lots more bizarre and wonderful contributions from the Smas and Das. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 222. Double Cap | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770028/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 02:42:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris and Rosie are feeling the heat on this week&amp;rsquo;s podcast (well just Chris actually), so much so one of them is doing it in their underwear! They discuss sun cream, water bottles, holidays and lullabies. Beefs are train based and QFTP&amp;rsquo;s involve a massage, tennis and wrong dog Rick. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 221. Lego Destruction Pending | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770029/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 02:45:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770029/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week&amp;rsquo;s podcast Rosie and Chris are revisiting the realities of very early mornings and they have a catch up after Rosie destroyed Chris&amp;rsquo; Lego on the TV show. There&amp;rsquo;s beef, icks, a sore bum crack and everything in between! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 220. Good Optics | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770030/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 02:16:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris and Rosie talk trampolining techniques, parenting lessons, Subbuteo and sun cream icks. Sandra is in Rosie&amp;rsquo;s bad books after borrowing Rosie&amp;rsquo;s clothes and Chris reveals a new character - Captain Cuddle. QFTP&amp;rsquo;s include cock rings, embarrassing Mum behavior and rude signs! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 219. Nice Coat Lee | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770031/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 02:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770031/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week's podcast the pair catch up after a few days at home and a trip to the beach. There's a breaking wind confession and some Power Rangers chat. Beefs are okay, or are they? QFTP's cover office fridge politics, a scented candle, nicknames and a love egg. To vote for The Chris and Ramsey Show at the NTA's visit: https://www.nationaltvawards.com/vote
Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.</description></item><item><title>Ep 218. Pity Click | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770032/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 01:48:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770032/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Ramsey&amp;rsquo;s have so much to discuss on this week&amp;rsquo;s podcast! They have been in London seeing a West End show and they presented a BAFTA&amp;hellip; but not without some embarrassing moments of course! Rosie has had underwear malfunctions and Chris has beef about hotel breakfasts. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 217. kiss my flower | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770033/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770033/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Chris and Rosie talk about some of the train drama they&amp;rsquo;ve been seeing while out on the road. They discuss the headache of children wanting songs on repeat and there&amp;rsquo;s the latest beef! QFTP&amp;rsquo;s covers voice notes from dates, a beery night for fun and being hypnotised. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 216. Open! | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770034/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 01:04:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770034/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Chris and Rosie have oven problems and there is some charger based beef. They discuss the pitfalls of espresso martinis and get nostalgic over hot tubs. QFTP&amp;rsquo;s cover some petite crime, dirty sheets and an unfortunate photo mishap. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 215. Cold Hearted Father | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770035/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 02:01:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770035/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week's podcast Rosie gets the ick after Chris books a hotel over the phone which also ends with Chris having a new name. The pair talk about Rosie's funny turn while the pair were away and they also question if anyone enjoys sex standing up... there's some fainting based beef and an retro xfactor ick from a listener. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Ep 214. Spirito Di Punto | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770036/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 02:12:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770036/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week&amp;rsquo;s podcast Chris and Rosie get nostalgic for 90&amp;rsquo;s adverts and have to get siblings involved for some clarity. There is some fantastic missed heard lyrics, a sample fiasco and a terrapin story. All of this plus the couples weekly beefs. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 213. Skip Cap | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770037/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 02:30:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770037/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week&amp;rsquo;s podcast Chris is feeling itchy and neither he or Rosie can figure out why. Rosie spent an evening at a David Bowie tribute act and reveals her technique for singing along when she doesn&amp;rsquo;t know the words. The beefs are on the dry side and there&amp;rsquo;s a snoring special in QFTP&amp;rsquo;s! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Ep 212. Five Fold Sunnies | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770038/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 02:00:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770038/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Rosie and Chris discuss Chris' new ick worthy sunglasses, sex toys and Rosie's battle with Catholicism.&amp;nbsp;
Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 211. FAGDA | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770039/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 02:00:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770039/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Rosie and Chris discuss Chris' slide record, Reality TV and Rosie aversion to seeing people in the shade. They take a deep dive in to medieval torture devices and Rosie reveals Chris' bad sleeping habits.&amp;nbsp;Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 210. Pear of Anguish | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770040/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 03:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770040/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Rosie and Chris discuss Rosie’s dental problems, Sandra’s Birthday and Chris’ trip to the wrestling. They take a deep dive in to medieval torture devices and Rosie reveals her disgust in Chris’s feet. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 209. Biggest Loser | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770041/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 03:37:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770041/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week&amp;rsquo;s podcast Rosie reflects on her appearance on The Wheel and why she thought a hamper was needed. Chris gets annoyed about stray snacks and the pair agree to do more kissing after Rosie watched a TikTok video. All of this plus some brilliant QFTP&amp;rsquo;s involving a practical joke, some icks and a strange massage technique. Enjoy! Mars bar anyone? Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.</description></item><item><title>Ep 208. Cowboy | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770042/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 03:05:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770042/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Chris and Rosie discuss ice baths, American reality TV and if they have ever been truly full. There is some classic print beef and Chris is annoyed at how Rosie is brushing her teeth. Also on the podcast is a clothes carrying ick, a frisky flight and a strange way of eating food. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>Ep 207. Ham Dumpling | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770043/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 03:53:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770043/</guid><description>Podcast Description A lot gets covered on this week&amp;rsquo;s podcast - does Rosie trust Chris and should Chris take up meditation? The pair discuss retirement, how French kids look healthier and why mid-week swimming is always a treat! All of this plus a Fireman&amp;rsquo;s Pole story and an unlikely use for a Mars Bar. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 206. What film am I thinking of? | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770044/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 03:30:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770044/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week&amp;rsquo;s podcast Chris and Rosie discuss The Comedy Awards and what went on afterwards. They chat buffet etiquette and why you should never put a baguette in a toaster. Rosie develops a new board game and Chris attempts to explain Alternate Universes&amp;hellip;All of this plus a call with Sister Kate, a brilliant Rosie&amp;rsquo;s Mystery and a story that will never see the light of day. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.</description></item><item><title>Ep 205. Pass the Shoe | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770045/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 03:20:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770045/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast Chris returns to Rosie&amp;rsquo;s jotters to discuss Rosie&amp;rsquo;s early creative writing ambitions. They marvel at whisking, they chat about Chris&amp;rsquo; athleticism and there&amp;rsquo;s an old age beef that rears it&amp;rsquo;s ugly head. All of this plus some strange family habits and a brilliant case of mistaken identity. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 204. Three blind wipes | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770046/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 03:21:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770046/</guid><description>Podcast Description The podcast this week covers all sorts! From pelvic floor exercises to spittoons to a unusual talent from a 12 year old. All of this plus Beefs, a record breaking ick and and update on Rosie&amp;rsquo;s jotters! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 203. Nurse Damp | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770047/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 02:27:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770047/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week&amp;rsquo;s podcast Chris and Rosie have a lot to get through! They answer all your Midnight Gameshow questions, discuss their trip to London and make a return to Rosie&amp;rsquo;s Jotters. There is some quick fire beef, a few icks and a new (questionable) business idea for Rosie. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 202. Ding dong the crust is gone | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770048/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 03:59:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770048/</guid><description>Podcast Description The podcast starts this week with some self tan beef or is Rosie just melting? The pair catch up and discuss yet another hobby that Chris has taken up and Rosie is NOT happy. Chris revisits Rosie's jotters and the pair chat through some listener icks, an unfortunate pooh incident in a car and a seriously gross search story. Enjoy Smas and Das! To vote for the podcast and The Chris and Rosie Ramsey Show in this year's National Comedy Awards visit www.</description></item><item><title>Ep 201. Don’t tug at your girdle | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770049/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 04:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770049/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast Chris &amp;amp; Rosie discuss the highs and (big) lows of fancy dress. There’s an update on what Sandra Christmas gifts and Chris reveals what he attempted to change his name to. Beefs get musical and QFTP's involve a new phenomenon that will put you off your yogurt-based deserts. &amp;nbsp;
Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Extra! Extra! | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770050/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 12:36:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hello Smas and Das,
We hope you enjoy this bonus episode! Extra Extra is our fortnightly bonus episode that our SMA+ subscribers receive!
For January &amp;amp; February you can subscribe to our Lucrative Lucrative Sponsor Tier on SMA+ and get 50% off for 3 months. No adverts and fortnightly bonus content for half the price!
Just use the code BEEF .
Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Ep 200. AD/BC | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770051/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 05:30:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770051/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Ramsey's are back and it's the 200th episode! There's a quiz, there's beefs, a Rosie's Mysteries and even a Strictly debrief!
Enjoy Smas and Das and thanks for listening for 200 episodes!
Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 199. Christmas Special: What would Jackie do? | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770052/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 05:06:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770052/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's the last podcast of the year from Chris and Rosie and it's a Christmas bumper edition *sleigh bells included*. The couple discuss recycling, festive chauvinist pigs and Rosie's hat habit. QFTP's are Christmas themed including an extreme PDA, magical reindeer and a living legend. To all the Smas and Das, thank you so much for listening to the podcast and sending in your brilliant stories. Merry Christmas and we'll be back in your ears in 2023!</description></item><item><title>Sh**ged Married Annoyed at Footprints Community Café | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770053/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 06:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770053/</guid><description>Podcast Description What a lovely festive morning the Ramsey’s had thanks to the staff at The National Lottery supported Footprints Community Café. Chris and Rosie caught up with the team and found out about the amazing work they do all year round to help support their local community. And of course, in true Sh**ged Married Annoyed style, they even got some beefs! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Ep 198. Strip Search | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770054/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 04:31:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770054/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Ramey's are getting festive and in particular Chris shares the joys of Christmas Markets. Rosie enjoys part two of the Countries quiz and she also shares some Strictly moments! Beefs are gassy and Chris is still going strong with the protein bars. QFTP's involve some unusual icks, trading cards and a solitary tomato. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Ep 197. Magnum XL | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770055/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 05:30:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770055/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast Chris and Rosie discuss billionaires, the etiquette of buying teacher&amp;rsquo;s presents and why taking a toddler to a Christmas shop can be tricky. The beefs involve Chris getting locked out and QFTP&amp;rsquo;s cover condoms, loose teeth and an indoor gilet. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 196. Centrifugal Force | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770056/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 05:20:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770056/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week&amp;rsquo;s podcast Chris and Rosie discuss centrifugal force and what life would be like as a worm&amp;hellip; all the big topics! They also catch up on Rosie&amp;rsquo;s excitement over Strictly and Sewing Bee and what she is enjoying most about the Football. QFTP&amp;rsquo;s involve a tanning salon, a brace journey and some swapsies in a car park. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>Ep 195. Glib, Glab, Glob | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770057/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 05:14:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770057/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast Chris &amp;amp; Rosie discuss sleeping arrangements, phone updates and the down side to bubble gum ice cream. Rosie gets annoyed about Chris’ sticker addiction and Chris has some possible names for Rosie’s band. QFTP’s include sleepwear, a skater boy and a bad bikini wax experience. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 194. Preekend | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770058/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 05:00:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770058/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Chris and Rosie wish Kate a Happy Birthday and they discuss preekends and the protocol when taking a sick day. The beefs have taken a healthy turn, protein bars and treadmill etiquette are both on the table. QFTP&amp;rsquo;s involve a messy dream, a make believe squirrel and a wonderful Rosie&amp;rsquo;s Mystery! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Ep 193. BeanFest | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770059/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 05:04:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770059/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week&amp;rsquo;s podcast Rosie tells all about her trip to London to see The Backstreet Boys. Chris has been busy at home, or has he? The beefs include arguments of car boots and general couple rage. There&amp;rsquo;s a couple of icks and of course some QFTP&amp;rsquo; which this week involve a terrible Best Man, baby feeding and a worrying foam party. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.</description></item><item><title>Ep 192. Dirty knit witted yellow livered | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770060/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 04:56:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770060/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week&amp;rsquo;s podcast Chris ad Rosie get nostalgic for their younger days. Robin has his own beef with Chris and Halloween costumes take quite the battering. Gilets are revisited again in the beefs and pumps get mentioned more than a couple of times. QFTP&amp;rsquo;s involve a toilet roll substitute, a promiscuous son and a change of heart over a sex position. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.</description></item><item><title>Ep 191. Gilet Incorporated | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770061/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 04:14:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770061/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Chris names himself head of gilets and Rosie isn’t happy about it! There’s some bowl licking, a car related ick, and some dancefloor shenanigans. All of this PLUS a member of the Beef family return with a Barry update. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 190. Just be chill | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770062/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 04:14:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770062/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Ramey&amp;rsquo;s are back and Rosie wants to know why Chris &amp;lsquo;can&amp;rsquo;t be more chill?&amp;rsquo;&amp;hellip; There&amp;rsquo;s vasectomy chat, a safe lucrative sponsor and some hypothetical life planning for Chris. The QFTP&amp;rsquo;s involve a strange choice of sex toy, a bad smell and some misinformation on pubes. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 189. House Shoes | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770063/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 04:33:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770063/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Chris and Rosie discuss ways to clean a radiator (that&amp;rsquo;s covered in sick), Chris&amp;rsquo; choice of shoe and Rosie&amp;rsquo;s response to a text. QFTP&amp;rsquo;s cover bin juice, pile cream and an unusual use for lego. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 188. Mars Cha Cha | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770064/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 04:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770064/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week&amp;rsquo;s podcast Chris and Rosie discuss frubes, strictly, facial recognition and loads more&amp;hellip; plus they are joined by a film crew, can you tell? The beefs cover mishearing and of course bins! QFTP&amp;rsquo;s involve a stripper, drinking from a bottle and a filthy dog grooming habit. All of this and some wonderful icks. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Ep 187. Born to Fight | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770065/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 04:17:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770065/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week&amp;rsquo;s podcast there&amp;rsquo;s some singing, misplaced chewing gum, stripper stories and a new (and improved?) name for a glove compartment. All of this plus beefs, icks and some smelly QFTP&amp;rsquo;s. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 186. Kegs full of Kaka | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770066/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 04:22:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770066/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Chris and Rosie chat bingo, holidays and what happens if you have a bathroom accident in ASDA. There&amp;rsquo;s a quiz devised especially for Rosie and the QFTP&amp;rsquo;s are particularly filthy! Expect stories of swingers, underwear, icks and getting caught in the act! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 185. Anchor Pants | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770067/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 04:01:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770067/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s a &amp;lsquo;Questions from the Public&amp;rsquo; Special! Chris and Rosie catch up on some of your questions! There are icks, a revengeful DJ, a sad story about a goldfish and some unsavoury student accommodation. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 184. Beat the Letter | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770068/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 04:28:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770068/</guid><description>Podcast Description The school holidays are finally over and Chris and Rosie are enjoying some normality. This week on the podcast they get nostalgic over calculators and kids games. They have some snack based beef and a position based ick. All of this plus Rosie updates the smas and das on her recent garden furniture purchase. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Ep 183. Water is blue | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770069/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 04:14:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770069/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Ramsey&amp;rsquo;s are back with beefs, icks and QFTP&amp;rsquo;s but this week there is a little something extra, Rosie&amp;rsquo;s jotters! Chris gets to the bottom of some of Rosie&amp;rsquo;s teenage musings that he found in the loft&amp;hellip;enjoy everyone and remember, water is blue. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 182. A little bit sexy | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770070/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 04:12:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770070/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Ramsey's return and yes it's still the summer holidays! Chris and Rosie talk funfairs and the law according to American movies. Rosie almost brings her acting skills to the beefs and the icks have their very own designated spot. QFTP's involve cling film, chicken wings and great balls of...something.
Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 181. The glove | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770071/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 04:00:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770071/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week it&amp;rsquo;s roasting hot and Rosie&amp;rsquo;s loving it. Chris took Robin on a mini break, and the Ramsey&amp;rsquo;s went to the beach. There&amp;rsquo;s garlic bread beef and it&amp;rsquo;s a specials week for questions from the public. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 180. Sommelier summer camp | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770072/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 04:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770072/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s still the summer holidays and Chris and Rosie have taken time off to spend it with the boys. Big mistake. Chris is into a new sport. Rosie&amp;rsquo;s had a wardrobe malfunction and there’s possibly the most horrific hotel find ever. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 179. Pokethon | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770073/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 04:17:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770073/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week the Ramsey&amp;rsquo;s manage to record a podcast, despite the summer holiday madness! Chris has been getting competitive with a 6 year old, Rosie has a sci fi related ick and they both discuss Robin&amp;rsquo;s latest practical joke. QFTP&amp;rsquo;s cover a sibling shock, an unusual work break snack and a unfortunate incident on holiday. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Ep 178. Oh wow | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770074/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 04:10:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770074/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Ramsey’s have had a busy week (separately!). Chris has been at the UFC and Rosie has been singing at Ladies Day. It’s a plonkcast so the beefs are pretty rich. QFTP’s cover icks, a questionable spag bowl, an unusual breakfast and some peeling skin&amp;hellip; oh wow! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 177. Summer holiday special | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770075/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 03:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770075/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Ramsey's are back from holiday and they're more knackered than when they left. Chris has been reading tips on how to stay cool this summer and Rosie's been deep diving into TikTok. Plus there's some holiday special questions from the public.&amp;nbsp;
To subscribe to ad free episodes and bonus content visit shaggedmarriedannoyed.com Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 176. Out of Office | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770076/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 04:11:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770076/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast Chris &amp;amp; Rosie share some unused QFTP’s and they do not disappoint! There&amp;rsquo;s a slightly disturbing holiday story, a bouji hairdresser, a sex egg and a stinky drawer. Enjoy Smas and Das! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 175. Double Muggins | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770077/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 04:26:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770077/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Rosie reveals a new musical talent in the family and Chris becomes a Golf Guy. There&amp;rsquo;s a truth bomb from Sandra and beefs that get Rosie very animated! QFTP&amp;rsquo;s involve some dirty dishes, a hairy meal and a gross ear wax habit. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 174. Co-ords | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770078/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 04:40:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770078/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast Chris &amp;amp; Rosie discuss co-ords, free gifts, farting in Asda and whether it&amp;rsquo;s okay to attend a date topless. All of this plus some slippery beef and a couple of icks for good measure! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 173. Hot Potato | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770079/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 04:12:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770079/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast the couple discuss urban myths, street names and Kids TV. As well as serving up some beef Chris is also busy eating some carb based humble pie! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 172. But what about the pool table? | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770080/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 04:27:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770080/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week&amp;rsquo;s podcast Chris and Rosie talk hair treatments, massages and builders mugs. The beefs take an interesting turn and the QFTP&amp;rsquo;s cover care packages, a sad ick, lube and a misheard saying. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 171. Meet you in my dreams | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770081/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 04:23:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770081/</guid><description>Podcast Description As well as serving up some brilliant beefs and icks there is also dream analysis and a surprise gift from Sandra. QTFP&amp;rsquo;s involve social etiquette, a not so nice desert bowl and a memory for Chris to revisit. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 170. The 80’s door handle | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770082/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 04:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770082/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week&amp;rsquo;s podcast the Ramsey&amp;rsquo;s try and wrap their heads around the Jubilee! Rosie get&amp;rsquo;s nostalgic for 80&amp;rsquo;s door handles and Chris gets accused of shouting. The beefs mount up and QFTP&amp;rsquo;s involve data apps, icks, and the class pet. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 169. Dacious | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770083/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 04:08:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770083/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week&amp;rsquo;s podcast the Ramey&amp;rsquo;s discuss their new TV show, a kids party that Rosie attended and how Chris&amp;rsquo; lack of socks seems to have caused a real stir! They share their beefs which involve an emotional sports day and the QTFP&amp;rsquo;s go veggie and even include a mistaken urinal situation. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 168. The Worst Smell in The World | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770084/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 04:35:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770084/</guid><description>Podcast Description As well as discussing their new TV show Chris and Rosie share their weekly beefs and their new official ‘ick’ section. They chat passive aggressive waiters, behind the scenes strictly rituals and their thoughts on thongs. QFTP’s include strange contraception choices and some pretty expensive, albeit, dirty sheets. All of this PLUS an exciting announcement! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Ep 167. Killer extensions | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770085/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 04:16:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770085/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week (and much to Chris’ dismay) the couple discuss Rosie’s hair extensions and why she used to call psychic hotlines. There’s some observations and an update on the TV show. Beefs get medical and QFTP’s cover an eventful French exchange, a unfortunate cab journey and frozen prawns. PLUS the pair get to the bottom of who their Disney crush was. Become a member at https://plus.</description></item><item><title>Ep 166. Hip hip... | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770086/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 04:34:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770086/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week&amp;rsquo;s podcast Rosie delivers some more observations and even has some audio evidence to prove it! Chris has been feeling ill after catching the kids germs and shares his stomach bug woes from the tour. There&amp;rsquo;s the weekly beefs and QFTP&amp;rsquo;s that cover service stations, eating in supermarkets and manscaping. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 165. Rude Awakening | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770087/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 04:15:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770087/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Chris and Rosie share their traumatic few days after both Rafe and Robin came down with a stomach bug. There are towel forts, bucket techniques and even a QFTP along the same theme. As well as this the pair share their beefs and go deep with the icks plus there's an update on the reality of hotel shenanigans. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.</description></item><item><title>Ep 164. The Best Walker | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770088/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 04:20:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770088/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week’s podcast Chris and Rosie discuss Easter Eggs, VPL, hand towels and some more ick! There’s an awkward zoom funeral moment and an elaborate name for a pot washer! Enjoy smas &amp;amp; das! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 163. Good Friday plonkcast | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770089/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 04:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Good Friday! It&amp;rsquo;s a plonkcast, Rosie&amp;rsquo;s got pre-beef, Chris remembers a story that&amp;rsquo;s been on his mind, Barry has a word and one listener wants relationship advice. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 162. Three words | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770090/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770090/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s the podcast that loves dogs! (Well Chris does anyway). Chris and Rosie play a word game, Sandra&amp;rsquo;s treated herself to a new robe and watch out for the list of things to do that&amp;rsquo;ll keep you single. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 161. How long you staying? | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770091/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 04:09:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770091/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Chris and Rosie have some serious Cocomelon beef and land line issues. They discuss Team leaders, keyholders and why people should mind their own business when it comes to luggage! QFTP&amp;rsquo;s cover hired Kilts, auto correct gone wrong and some unsavoury behaviour with a Dorito dip. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 160. Round Robin | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770092/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 05:30:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770092/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week the podcast was recorded in London and Chris &amp;amp; Rosie got a taste of office life! The pair discuss a recent photo shoot, an incident on a train and bad customer service. There&amp;rsquo;s some Sandra gossip, the weekly beefs and outstanding QFTP&amp;rsquo;s. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 159. Free Roam | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770093/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 05:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770093/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Chris &amp;amp; Rosie discuss family traits, fart shaming, free roam pets and they play an alternative to &amp;lsquo;would you rather&amp;rsquo;. There&amp;rsquo;s some urinal compliments and an annoying expression&amp;hellip; beg your pudding?? Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 158. These boots aren’t made for walking | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770094/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 05:25:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris and Rosie return with their (National Comedy Award Winning) podcast and share their mishaps from the night. They answer all the big questions such as - is there more doors or wheels in the world? The beefs are juicy and the QFTP&amp;rsquo;s involve a camera phone, an acrobatic role and some playground shenanigans. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Ep 157. Purple reigns | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770095/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 05:16:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770095/</guid><description>Podcast Description The podcast is swing heavy this week, or is it swung? The pair come together over their garden plans as well as sharing their weekly beefs. QFTP&amp;rsquo;s involve lies, a punchy request and some toe sucking action. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 156. Bathroom Teaspoon | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770096/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 05:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rosie and Chris have been nominated for the national comedy awards&amp;hellip;and there might just be an apple sour in it if you vote. They remember what they were wearing and what they were saying at the Millennium. And Sandra&amp;rsquo;s got tote bag fever. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 155. The Pitt's | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770097/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 05:08:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770097/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Chris &amp;amp; Rosie discuss Brad Pitt&amp;rsquo;s relationship status, past lives and storm facts. The beefs involve a real time print count and Rosie shares how life is with Chris on the road. QFTP&amp;rsquo;s cover bean bag trays, a foreign object in food and menstrual cups. All of this plus the couple ask the age-old question&amp;hellip;do Americans use electric kettles? Become a member at https://plus.</description></item><item><title>Ep 154. Stain of regret | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770098/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 05:08:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770098/</guid><description>Podcast Description There&amp;rsquo;s a fair few food based topics up for discussion this week - from Hot Dogs to burnt Jacket Potatoes. Robin has suggested a new career for Chris &amp;amp; Rosie whilst Rafe is enjoying the joys of Cbeebies. Rosie&amp;rsquo;s mysteries returns and Chris brings some fun facts. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 153. Record Breakers | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770099/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 05:19:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770099/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast his week Chris and Rosie discuss Record Breakers, birdwatching and bad breath. The beefs get personal and the QFTP&amp;rsquo;s involve swinging, flossing and a coughing incident. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 152. Do Buy | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770100/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 05:30:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770100/</guid><description>Podcast Description There is a sleep war brewing in the Ramsey household! The pair discuss tupperware, sneezing and baby bathwater. Belinda is back and the beefs get shouty. QFTP&amp;rsquo;s cover a kids birthday party, an unlucky sister and a different kind of rate and review system. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 151. Timber | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770101/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 05:12:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770101/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Rosie has some Rafe beef, Chris has some wood problems and the pair share the weekly grievances with each other. There&amp;rsquo;s some Facebook Market place discussion and QFTP&amp;rsquo;s involving sexting, mistaken identity and Christmas trees. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 150. Tony doesn't live here | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770102/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 05:12:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770102/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast Chris &amp;amp; Rosie record a podcast and keep it extra real with some live interruptions. If anyone sees Tony, tell him they have his parcels! There&amp;rsquo;s weekly beefs plus one for Netflix, Rosie suggests a unique way of having children and QFTP&amp;rsquo;s cover butt plugs, guinea pigs and an unfortunate incident with a wet phone. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Ep 149. Dipped in fat | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770103/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 05:00:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770103/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s 2022 and Rosie and Chris are celebrating with fireworks, sort of. Sandra&amp;rsquo;s Christmas presents get a shout out and Rosie has beef with Chris&amp;rsquo;s cold. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 148. Christmas Special | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770104/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 05:33:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770104/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's the last SMA of the year and the Ramsey's are feeling festive! There's singing, festive beef and some christmassy QFTP's. All of this plus we here why Rosie is on the naughty list and how Chris is messing with new family traditions.
We hope all the smas and das have a Merry Christmas and a Happy New Year!
Chris and Rosie will be back in your ears on January 7th.</description></item><item><title>Ep 147. Find a happy place | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770105/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 05:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770105/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Ramsay's are buzzing from their tour but they're not talking to each other in January. Chris has a history lesson and Rosie takes part in a new game against her will.&amp;nbsp;
Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 146. Liquid Gold | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770106/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770106/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week’s podcast Chris and Rosie have forgone the beefs for just some old school bickering! Rosie has been to a Panto and Chris has some tour gripes he wants to share. As well cracking QFTP’s there’s some informative phone calls with Rosie’s siblings. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 145. Sorry Dad | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770107/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770107/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Chris and Rosie discuss NFTS (!?), smart ovens and Storm Arwen. PLUS Rosie reveals a new listener! There’s some meaty beefs and the QFTPs involve some confusion at a funeral, friction burn and a pretty gross ‘would you rather?’! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 144. Licence to snooze | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770108/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770108/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Chris &amp;amp; Rosie chat about sharing the sofa with Will Smith and Chris’ train ride after. There’s a surprise visit from Belinda Beef who’s a bit confused to say the least and the QFTP’s range from fetish weeks to missing contraception. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 143. How’s Christine? | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770109/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770109/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Chris and Rosie get nostalgic over renting movies and discuss parenting in the 21st Century… are they bringing up posh kids? There’s a throwback beef and some brilliant QFTP including a car key itch and a wild weekend in Watford. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 142. Classic Borisina | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770110/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770110/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week the pair chat about Rosie’s trip to London, mistaken identity at Chris’ gig and the couple have some pretty exciting news! As well as this there’s some more crow chat, a business end experience and an early Christmas tree QFTP. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 141. That’s a crow | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770111/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770111/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week’s podcast things get personal! Chris and Rosie discuss sofas, sex, infidelity, and an inappropriate toenail arrangement. All of this plus a cracking ‘Would you rather…’. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 140. NOT a Halloween special | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770112/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770112/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s almost Halloween but Chris has got no time for ghosts or people that have seen them. Rosie&amp;rsquo;s on the fence. There&amp;rsquo;s bladder (and bum) based beef and one listener has a Big Mac confession. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 139. Baby name betrayal | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770113/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris and Rosie had a date night and they&amp;rsquo;re very hungover. Rosie&amp;rsquo;s got some parenting dilemmas. There&amp;rsquo;s door bell beef and some baby name betrayal. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 138. Party at the drive thru | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770114/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770114/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Chris and Rosie discuss Rosie’s shortened swimming career, Chris’s forgetfulness and what may or may not have happened in The Minority Report. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 137. Oh Crumbs | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770115/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rosie &amp;amp; Chris are back in your ears! The pair have a spanking new episode including a Celebrity Question, there’s a Rosie’s Mystery, some wonderful QFTP’s, long awaited beefs and a call from Rosie’s manager… it’s all happening! Enjoy x Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 136. Elephant Dolphin | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770116/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris &amp;amp; Rosie go way back in to the archives and share some more QFTP’s that never made the cut and they do not disappoint! There’s some classic nail grossness, a strange discussion about fire safety and an interruption from a maintenance man. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 135. Turbo time | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770117/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770117/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Chris and Rosie dig out some old questions that never made the podcast. There&amp;rsquo;s a 12 inch garlic bread, turbo wees and some unfortunate translation. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 134. Bon bons in the knicker drawer | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770118/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770118/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast Chris and Rosie share a new record that they have broken and why it’s one of their proudest moments! There’s the weekly beefs, and QFTP’s which involve nosey neighbours, a dead hamster and a tomato soup secret! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 133. The Iron Curtain | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770119/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770119/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been a tricky few days thanks to a temperamental curtain but the Ramsey’s are here to discuss their week, their beefs and your dirty laundry! There’s some mistaken identity, a cotton wool disappearance and some pregnancy advice, kind of. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 132. Fish Guy | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770120/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770120/</guid><description>Podcast Description There is something fishy about this week’s episode and it’s not just the pets. The beefs involve siphoning and strictly and the QFTP’s cover embarrassing Dads, milky mash and Cruise Ship antics! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 131. A thumbnail of wine | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770121/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rosie and Chris return and it’s STILL the summer holidays! When will they end?? The pair share their beefs over a little more than a thumbnail of wine and answer some questions from the smas and das which cover sex amnesia and swapping pants with your mum, enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 130. To whom it may concern | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770122/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770122/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Chris and Rosie record while the kids are in bed and it&amp;rsquo;s a plonk cast. They chat Yorkshire puddings, analogies and there&amp;rsquo;s a live show warm-up buzz in the air. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 129. Rosie Harissa | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770123/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris and Rosie are in the studio and there&amp;rsquo;s been technical problems, again. They chat pets, suspicious texting and there&amp;rsquo;s a new &amp;lsquo;our house&amp;rsquo; feature. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 128. Draw the minion! | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770124/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770124/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week’s podcast the Ramsey’s have some holiday kids club flash backs! Robin corrects Rosie’s spelling and Chris has some residual beef from sun stroke. Rosie puts her foot down over napkins and there is a live appearance from Sandra who helps out with some pronunciation. All of this plus some stinking QFTP’s. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Ep 127. Not a holiday | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770125/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770125/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Ramsey&amp;rsquo;s have been on holiday and Chris and Rosie are even more exhausted now. There&amp;rsquo;s sunstroke beef and Chris wants a swimwear poll. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 126 Good Grief | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770126/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rosie&amp;rsquo;s been to the dentist and Chris can finally breathe a sigh of relief. There&amp;rsquo;s laundry and chewing gum based beef and trips down holiday memory lane. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 125. Return of the toenails | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770127/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris is in the dog house after some technical problems but that doesn't stop the pair delivering another cracking episode for all the smas and das! This week they discuss cereal, manual labour and getting ready for a night out. The beefs are fresh and minty and the QFTP's cover a horrible nail chewing habit and some dirty sheets. All of this plus a surprise call from Rosie's brother.</description></item><item><title>Ep 124. The Midwife Always Knocks Twice | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770128/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770128/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Chris &amp;amp; Rosie are getting in to Euro 2020 and Wimbledon – Chris knows the off side rule and attempts to explain the rules on Tennis. There is some minesweeping chat, a story from a midwife and an ethical dilemma. All of this plus some cracking beef, enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 123. Case closed | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770129/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770129/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week the pair get topical, they return to the toothbrush saga and get opinionated over star signs. There is a stinky beef and some fabulous QFTP&amp;rsquo;s&amp;hellip; enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 122. Hack Guy | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770130/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770130/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week’s podcast Robin has a new name for Chris which isn’t going down well and Rosie is feeling on the tired side. The pair discuss Love Island, crisp facts and why Rosie wouldn’t do the Masked Singer. As well as this, paramedic Jess returns and Robin makes a cameo, enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 121. One ring to rule them all | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770131/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770131/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast Rosie has had some bad news and is improvising with a new instrument, Chris helped push a car up a hill and they both bring some bed time beefs. QFTP&amp;rsquo;s involve food minesweeping, medical students and an unexpected situation involving a fireman, batman and a damsel in distress. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 120. Low hanging fruit | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770132/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770132/</guid><description>Podcast Description The time has come for Rosie to take the Crisp quiz! SMA’s can play along to… Chris has had a comment on his breath from Robin, Rosie gets annoyed at Chris’s reaction after watching a crime drama and the QFTP’s involve some pretty disgusting sieving, a modern day love story and some naughty holiday snaps. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Ep 119. Like father, like son | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770133/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rosie&amp;rsquo;s got a new job, and Chris has got a new haircut. They talk unsuspecting occurrences, specialist subjects and there&amp;rsquo;s going out beef. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 118. What a man wants | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770134/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rosie&amp;rsquo;s in a good mood and it&amp;rsquo;s getting on Chris&amp;rsquo;s nerves. They talk coffee in bed, back scratching and it seems like Instagram is taking a side, Chris&amp;rsquo;s side. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 117. Festering Bowl of Bolognese | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770135/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris and Rosie are arguing and they&amp;rsquo;re sorry. They talk syncing, catching lambs and queuing at Pizza Hut. Plus there&amp;rsquo;s chicken tikka masala flavoured beef. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 116. Instructed by tumblers | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770136/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770136/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week there is an update on Sandra’s stash and Rosie’s lamp problem continues. The pair discuss some novelty glasses and the pros and cons of shopping as a family. QFTP’s involve some tough blisters, a poorly judged wedding prank and an attempt at food poisoning. Plus Rosie shares a childhood memory of a trip to a bread factory. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.</description></item><item><title>Ep 115. Sidebored | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770137/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770137/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week both Chris and Rosie come with some new features for the show. Expect unusual wishes and animal facts! Rosie has a parenting beef whilst Chris&amp;rsquo;s are more interior based. QFTP&amp;rsquo;s involve a trip to the doctors, an unfortunate puppy name and some mistaken identity. See you all at the bottle bank! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Ep 114. A lady from the 90's | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770138/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770138/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Chris &amp;amp; Rosie have some exciting SMA news! They discuss that thing called fashion, second hand clothing and Robin’s trampolining incident. The beefs are eggy and QFTP’s involve bins, a PDA that goes wrong and an unusual use of a plastic bag… environmentally friendly though. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 113. How deep do you sleep? | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770139/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770139/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Rosie revives Rosie&amp;rsquo;s Mysteries and it does not disappoint. The pair discuss their schedules which includes waiting in for a dishwasher and some chilly pub visits. Beefs cover some nosey behaviour and a long awaited haircut. As ever the QFTP&amp;rsquo;s are brilliant - there is coffin advice, an unfortunate nosebleed situation and a virtual reality headset. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 112 Coal-Slaw | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770140/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770140/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s probably the best day of Chris&amp;rsquo;s life, things are open! Meanwhile Rosie clears up coleslaw and recalls a cooking nightmare. They chat talents and come up with a segment for the live show. Plus Rosie has a new song. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 111. Total (lack of) Recall | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770141/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770141/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s ba*tard cold so Rosie&amp;rsquo;s recording in her dressing gown. Belinda Beef is back with her best greeting yet and Rosie inadvertently makes a mystery out of a movie. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 110. 110 take 2 | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770142/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770142/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s not been an easy week of podcasting for Chris &amp;amp; Rosie&amp;hellip; somewhere in the universe there are deleted audio files never to be found! Not to worry though as the pair recorded the show again! Here on take two of episode 110 the couple discuss jiving, medical samples, curry after effects and excuses for calling in sick. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>Ep 109. Flannel Heavy | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770143/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris and Rosie bring you the first podcast from their new home! The pair share removal men stories, some beef that gets Chris in to trouble and an unlikely photoshopped Dad for Robin and Rafe. There is a fair bit of flannel chat, discussion over grown ups getting pocket money and an unusual Funeral tradition. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>EP 108. Carpet Squares | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770144/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770144/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Chris &amp;amp; Rosie discuss bad haircuts, Mothering Sunday and Valentines. They are joined by Barry Beef and they share the grievances from the week. QFTP&amp;rsquo;s include a breastfeeding mix up, couscous and some kinky clapping. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 107. Bucking Mad | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770145/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770145/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Chris and Rosie discuss grey hairs, lockdown babies and the SMA tour. There is a Rosie&amp;rsquo;s mystery that involves some swollen genitalia, the beefs get crispy (literally) and a listener gets in touch to share an unusual use of a sock. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 106. Pay as you go go go go go | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770146/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770146/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s not long until the kids are back at school and Chris and Rosie&amp;rsquo;s are in high spirits. They discuss the SMA tour, the return of Bike Guy and how they would feel if Louis Theroux took over their podcast. There&amp;rsquo;s a brilliant Rosie&amp;rsquo;s Mystery and some jaw dropping QFTP&amp;rsquo;s. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 105. Coffin Confessors | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770147/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770147/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Rosie revives Rosie&amp;rsquo;s Mysteries with a special canine edition! Chris has been walking much to Rosie&amp;rsquo;s despair and the beefs get tense! There&amp;rsquo;s some spag bowl discussion, a supermarket romance and a funeral tradition that get the guys thinking. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 104. Flock of Lasagne | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770148/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770148/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Chris shares why he think&amp;rsquo;s his wardrobe is effecting his mood and Rosie reveals why she made a certain purchase in the week. They discuss Rosie&amp;rsquo;s Jaw and Robin&amp;rsquo;s latest choice of TV Show. There&amp;rsquo;s some fresh beef and QFTP&amp;rsquo;s that involve a kilt, lasagne and some Sambuca. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Ep 103. Bones | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770149/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770149/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast Rosie welcomes you to Sunshine Land! There&amp;rsquo;s a ankle update from Chris, some phantom baby crying, strange German trolling news and an appearance from Belinda Beef! QFTP&amp;rsquo;s involve extravagant first dates and an office poll about mash, beans and jelly! Enjoy. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 102 Cremetisserie | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770150/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rosie and Chris are back! They have a new baby and a breastfeeding update. The beefs have been mounting and there are some injury based questions from the public. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 101. Maternity Leave #3 | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770151/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770151/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s the final week of the maternity leave episodes and Chris and Rosie bring you some of the questions that never made it the first time round. There&amp;rsquo;s some bird bath scandal, chicken minesweeping and a lucky burglar. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 100. Best of #1 | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770152/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770152/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast Chris &amp;amp; Rosie celebrate 100 episodes! They might be on maternity leave with a broken ankle but they have recorded a message to introduce the best of SMA so far. Expect age old beefs, some brilliant QFTP&amp;rsquo;s, a brief cameo courtesy of Rosie&amp;rsquo;s Nana and THAT story about the breastfeeding groom. Enjoy and a big thanks to all the smas &amp;amp; das! Become a member at https://plus.</description></item><item><title>Ep 99. Maternity Leave #2 | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770153/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770153/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week&amp;rsquo;s maternity leave edition of the podcast Chris &amp;amp; Rosie bring you some of the QFTP&amp;rsquo;s that didn&amp;rsquo;t make the first cut! They involve a a windy Dad, a shopping disaster and some jacket potato discussion. There&amp;rsquo;s also a cameo from a certain member of the Ramsey clan! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 98. Maternity Leave #1 | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770154/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770154/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on SMA you get to hear the stories and questions that didn&amp;rsquo;t make it the first time round! Chris &amp;amp; Rosie saved some brilliant (and filthy) bits for all the smas and das to enjoy while they take some time off. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 97. Docket or Not | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770155/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770155/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s 2021 and thank F for that! Chris and Rosie talk about YouTube sensation Ryan, crap Christmas presents and Rosie has a cemetery related mystery&amp;hellip;plus Chris has been holding back a question from the public you&amp;rsquo;ll probably wish you&amp;rsquo;d never heard. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 96. Christmas Bonus Special | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770156/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770156/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s Christmas day! And Rosie and Chris have got some not going out at Christmas advice, spoon based beef and a few festive questions from the public. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 95. Turkey leg-over | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770157/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770157/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s the week before Christmas and the Ramsey&amp;rsquo;s are getting festive! They both confess their envy over a Christmas ornament and worry about what has now become the Christmas covid &amp;lsquo;bauble&amp;rsquo;. There are some festive beefs (and non festive ones!) and some wonderful Christmas themed QFTP&amp;hellip; anyone seen that scooter? Merry Christmas everyone! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 94. Gorgey Hun | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770158/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770158/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week the Ramsey&amp;rsquo;s discuss thrupples, nostalgic trips to the football, beverages in the shower and a frisky farmer. All of this plus Rosie&amp;rsquo;s Mysteries, weekly beefs and the return of Belinda! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 93. Living with Meatloaf | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770159/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770159/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Rosie reveals what Robin thinks of his parents, there&amp;rsquo;s some bath based beef and some festive singing. QFTP&amp;rsquo;s involve a phantom farter and a strange pregnancy craving. All of this plus the couple are joined by TV Presenter, Steph McGovern, for a quick chat! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 92. Narrow Church | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770160/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770160/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Chris is revealed as a listener&amp;rsquo;s guilty crush but there are some questions surrounding his character, the couple celebrate no longer peeing in a bucket and they discuss their Sunday Brunch experience. Barry Beef makes a return and QFTP&amp;rsquo;s involves gin miniatures and bad dates! Enjoy. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 91. See this finger, see this thumb | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770161/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770161/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast the Ramsey’s catch you up on their week – twin tilers, an electric boot problem and Rosie gets her words mixed up. There’s a fruity Rosie’s mystery and some beefs that might involve an expensive testing habit for Chris. Q’s from the p’s range from a stinky old pillow to a strange wedding night tradition. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Ep 90. Bed Kegs | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770162/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770162/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tensions are running high in the Ramsey household this week, so much so, there is some organic early beefs! Rosie and Chris discuss Outlander, sharing dreams and Nana Bridget. There&amp;rsquo;s a Rosie&amp;rsquo;s Mystery plus some brilliant QFTP&amp;hellip;. communal underwear anyone? Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 89. Where you bin my love? | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770163/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770163/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s a busy week for the sma&amp;rsquo;s and da&amp;rsquo;s - Rosie has a new song to share and Chris (with some help from the PM) has a lockdown quiz for all to play along. The couple discuss Jacket potatoes v&amp;rsquo;s Toasties, how to beat an egg and male personal hygiene. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 88. Mr Saturday Night | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770164/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770164/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Chris and Rosie talk about second hand bath water, have Mr Saturday Night related beef and some fact checking phone calls from Rosie&amp;rsquo;s family. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 87 Heels and shoulders | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770165/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 06:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770165/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Ramsey&amp;rsquo;s are back for another cracking episode - this week Rosie is getting in festive with some Halloween and Christmas plans. There&amp;rsquo;s some beef, a mystery which Chris does pretty well with and some great QFTP&amp;rsquo;s. Yoghurt anyone? Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 86. The today after tomorrow | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770166/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770166/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast the pair discuss socially distanced chat up lines, almost love on the tube and a knicker thief. Rosie delivers another great mystery involving airport security and the eef&amp;rsquo;s lead to a potential unexpected fashion statement. All this plus is there a new Superhero on the horizon? Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 85. Mark of Zorro | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770167/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770167/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week things get a little sexy with some fruity QFTP&amp;rsquo;s. The beef&amp;rsquo;s are as animated as ever with Rosie&amp;rsquo;s being particularly straight to the point! There is some covid romance chat, some dogging discussion and a would you rather that involves breaking wind. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 84. Top Sheet | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770168/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rosie and Chris are recording from their office this week. It's strictly business and also some Gaviscon flavoured beef, chicken burger mysteries and an assortment of questions from the public.&amp;nbsp;
Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 83. Give me an A | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770169/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770169/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast Chris shares his lockdown woes and Rosie shares some of his snoring! The mysteries have a little addition and the beef's double up. There are some brilliant QFTP's... including one that raises a medical question. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 82. Minty Fresh | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770170/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770170/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Chris surprises Rosie with a new feature! The pair discuss who gets what in a break up, baby showers v&amp;rsquo;s wetting the babies head, some ear lobe sucking and a minty fresh experience that went wrong. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 81. Spite Salmon | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770171/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770171/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Ramsey&amp;rsquo;s have reason to celebrate this week after becoming bestsellers and it&amp;rsquo;s got Rosie pretty emotional! On the podcast the couple discuss little white lies, stranger danger, trigger warnings and orchestrated arguments. All of this plus a question from Phil Ellis and the brilliant Rosie&amp;rsquo;s Mysteries. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 80. Auntie Pat | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770172/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770172/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast Chris and Rosie celebrate the release of their book and Barry Beef gets in touch with some kind words for the couple&amp;hellip; Rosie&amp;rsquo;s Mysteries returns and there is an update on Chris&amp;rsquo; ear wax! As well as this enjoy some brilliant QFTP&amp;rsquo;s including an incredibly awkward date and a great wedding story. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770173/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770173/</guid><description>Podcast Description To celebrate the release of Sh**ged Married Annoyed the Book here is bonus podcast ep with a couple of clips from the audiobook, enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 79. Around the World | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770174/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770174/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s almost back to school time and Rosie is feeling unprepared - will Robin be using the lost property PE kit? Also this week, Chris is missing his drinking partner and is determined to get Rosie out of the motorhome. As well as this the term &amp;lsquo;Gilf&amp;rsquo; is used on the podcast for the first time and there is some eggy discussion plus perhaps the most awful wedding story ever.</description></item><item><title>Ep 78. Magnety | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770175/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770175/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week the couple discuss Robin&amp;rsquo;s latest behaviour, Chris&amp;rsquo; week in London and an unfortunate bike accident. Rosie&amp;rsquo;s Mysteries returns alongside some familiar beef and some bizarre QFTP&amp;rsquo;s. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 77. Eat Your Words | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770176/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770176/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Chris and Rosie are recording from a hotel. They reflect on their motorhome holiday and Rosie solves more mysteries. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 76. Sweet sixteen unicorn | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770177/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770177/</guid><description>Podcast Description No only has it been motorhome week in the Ramsey household but it was also Chris&amp;rsquo; Birthday and there was an unusual choice of cake. There are vehicle based beefs and another instalment of Rosie&amp;rsquo;s Mysteries - all of this plus some great QFTP&amp;rsquo;s. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 75. A breath of fresh air | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770178/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770178/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast Chris and Rosie discuss hot baths, zoom dates, Guinea Pigs and revenge. It&amp;rsquo;s also the week that sees the debut of Rosie&amp;rsquo;s new feature&amp;hellip; enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 74. Queen Bee in The Side Garden | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770179/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770179/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Chris and Rosie discuss their new flying neighbours. Rosie has a mystery&amp;hellip;which is promptly solved and they hear about what not to do after you&amp;rsquo;ve been to Nandos. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 73. 36 hours later | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770180/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Another big week in the Ramsey household! Not only did they win a British Podcast Award (thanks smas &amp;amp; das) but they also announced a new addition to the family and perhaps a motorhome too! This week the pair discuss an odd date involving taxidermy, a drunk Dad doing DIY and they answer a big question that involves a trip to the bathroom and a million pounds. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.</description></item><item><title>Ep 72. Guest in the nest | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770181/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770181/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s been quite the week for the Ramsey&amp;rsquo;s. So much so there is double beef! Rosie explains some Real House Wives lingo and Chris reveals why he is not Bike Guy. There are some tales of childhood punishments and a strange choice of sleeping arrangements. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 71. Dull as dishwater | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770182/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770182/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Rosie and Chris have their weekly catch up and of course The Beefs! They reveal Robin&amp;rsquo;s new term for Rosie and Chris explains why he&amp;rsquo;s getting through so many Birthday Cakes in lockdown. There&amp;rsquo;s skiving off school confessions, a militant Grandmother and a question about toilet seats. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 70. Seventy several | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770183/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770183/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast there is a log update, Chris&amp;rsquo;s new coffee invention and the rules of the SMA drinking game are revealed! QFTP&amp;rsquo;s include a clapping complaint, an unusual Doctors appointment and a DNA dilemma. Also this week, friend of the show Carl Hutchinson gets in touch with a question for the couple. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Ep 69. Meal for Two | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770184/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770184/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week, it&amp;rsquo;s meal for two time! Chris and Rosie bring their beef to the table and discuss their week which involves Chris potentially buying enough logs to build a cabin. QFTP&amp;rsquo;s vary from a pizza slice being hidden in a questionable place to a story about a giant Ant that ends in tears. All of this plus a brilliant question from Scott &amp;amp; Jemma Bennett Become a member at https://plus.</description></item><item><title>Ep 68. Dental dam | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770185/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770185/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast Chris has chosen the questions and there is some absolute corkers, including some safe sex advice, an awkward text scenario and and update on a potential covid romance. As well as this, Rosie shares her annoyance with Birthdays and they both share the moment they nearly got a pet. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Ep 67. Streets of Heferlon | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770186/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770186/</guid><description>Podcast Description The beefs get real on this week&amp;rsquo;s podcast when Rosie takes it to a whole new level! The pair discuss the six in a garden dilemma and they share the joy of Robin starting to do chores. As always the QFTP&amp;rsquo;s go from the weird to the disgusting - this week they include a Pizza rating system, a smelly face and questionably, charitable ex boyfriend. Become a member at https://plus.</description></item><item><title>Ep 66. Fortune cookies | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770187/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770187/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week&amp;rsquo;s podcast Rosie&amp;rsquo;s love of cushions is escalating and Chris is having none of it. There is some discussion over the pronunciation of nougat, a potential lockdown love story and some strange one night stand behaviour. All of this plus a story about a car sale that takes a very strange turn. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Ep 65. Love Birds | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770188/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770188/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s episode 65 of the podcast and Chris is officially a &amp;lsquo;bike guy&amp;rsquo; but Rosie has some rules about this escalating hobby. The pair discuss breastfeeding, piercings, bad wedding presents and ghosts. There is some brilliant utensil based beef and angry Sharon from the pub makes an appearance to discuss her new club. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 64. Bath Buddy | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770189/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770189/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Rosie&amp;rsquo;s beef backfires and Chris gets annoyed at plants! They compare PE Classes and Rosie shares the details of her school trip to Holy Island.There are some great QFTP&amp;rsquo;s - involving bathing, eating yogurt without a spoon and drunken nights in a playsuit. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 63. The Twits | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770190/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770190/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week we find out who made an unlikely appearance in The Ramsey&amp;rsquo;s wedding photos and why Chris is staying relatively calm during a pandemic. There&amp;rsquo;s a drink based beef and an announcement from Barry. Some great QFTP&amp;rsquo;s and the first ever Shagged Married Annoyed guests! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 62. Yarden | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770191/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770191/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week&amp;rsquo;s podcast Rosie reveals what she likes to do at train stations and Chris has some ideas for the next series of Strictly. The beef&amp;rsquo;s get juicy and there are some very impressive Lamb impressions (why not?!). They discuss horror movies, ice eating and what to do when you find a sex toy in your new home (and it&amp;rsquo;s not yours). Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.</description></item><item><title>Ep 61. My lover | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770192/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770192/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast The Ramsey&amp;rsquo;s talk about their main motivation behind exercise and they settle on a new way of introducing each other. Chris gets a taste of his own medicine and Rosie gets annoyed at how good her husband is looking. There&amp;rsquo;s some smelly Q from the&amp;rsquo;s P&amp;rsquo;s and some great childhood fibs! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Ep 60. Zoom Pole | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770193/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770193/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast Chris shares his new hobby, Rosie gets annoyed by Chris&amp;rsquo; weight loss and the pair go down memory lane with some kids TV. The Foot Stool guy re-surfaces, there is some questionable Easter egg based behaviour plus some more Tiger Trapping tales. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 59. Tiger trap | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770194/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770194/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast Chris and Rosie settle a disagreement. Rosie reveals her past as a Bingo caller and shares a story about a phone in talent competition. There is some strange behaviour at Brighton beach, a postie in trouble and some questionable hand washing techniques. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 58. Fondling by the reservoir | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770195/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770195/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast the Ramsey&amp;rsquo;s have felt the full effect of the clocks changing&amp;hellip; as if things weren&amp;rsquo;t weird enough! Rosie has hit rock bottom with some questionable parenting and Chris offers sympathy to the millionaires in their mansions during social distancing. There&amp;rsquo;s some great Q&amp;rsquo;s from the P&amp;rsquo;s and the return of Becky Beef AND a celebrity question! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Ep 57. The Sniff test | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770196/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770196/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast The Ramsey&amp;rsquo;s talk about their self isolation woes, there&amp;rsquo;s some juicy beef and some fantastic q&amp;rsquo;s from the p&amp;rsquo;s. Enjoy, stay inside and wash your hands! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 56. The Depositor | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770197/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 07:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770197/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s strange times across the globe and this week Chris and Rosie bring you an extended version of the podcast. Not only do they discuss their feelings around the current situation (including good deeds that didn&amp;rsquo;t go to plan)but they deliver beef with a spin and they answer your questions and read your (filthy) stories. It will bring a whole new meaning to the word &amp;lsquo;deposit&amp;rsquo;. Enjoy and stay safe!</description></item><item><title>Ep 55. Elastic Burdens | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770198/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 07:00:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770198/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s been quite the week for Chris &amp;amp; Rosie and there is some great post awards chat. Chris had his parenting judged and the couple are figuring out what will go in the Wembley Show - Spoons anyone? There are some brilliant questions from the public - how do you feel about other peoples carpets? And a medical professional gets in touch. All of this plus the return of Barry Beef!</description></item><item><title>Ep 54. Pointing the Finger | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770199/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 07:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770199/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week&amp;rsquo;s podcast we here about Rosie&amp;rsquo;s night out, and there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of finger chat plus a new (returning?) character. There&amp;rsquo;s some technology themed beef, a request to settle an argument over a broken plate and a story about some lost chewing gum - where could it have gone? Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 53. Auntie Panky | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770200/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 07:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770200/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s been a busy week in the Ramsey household - Rosie has another new job and Robyn has Chicken Pox. However, the couple find time to share some beefs, answer questions from the public and discuss the pros and cons of role play. Enjoy! You can buy tickets for the Shagged Married Annoyed tour here: shaggedmarriedannoyed.com You can pre order the Shagged Married Annoyed book here: https://www.amazon.co.uk/ged-Married-Annoyed-Chris-Ramsey/dp/0241447127 Become a member at https://plus.</description></item><item><title>Ep 52. One in Thirty | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770201/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 07:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770201/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Chris and Rosie have been enlightened with some very on brand statistics&amp;hellip;Barry&amp;rsquo;s back and they get anecdotes from a real life member of the public and a doctor. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 51. Sip Swallow Chug, Chug, Chug | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770202/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 07:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770202/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Chris and Rosie have had a plumbing disaster, and Chris was a total legend-ish about it. There&amp;rsquo;s whistle wake up beef, restaurant food disasters and disgusting behaviour on a train. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 50. Billy’s Egg Trick | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770203/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 07:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770203/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fifty episodes in and the Ramsey&amp;rsquo;s are still delivering the beef! There&amp;rsquo;s some book chat and another of Barry&amp;rsquo;s family members gets in touch. Question&amp;rsquo;s from the public involve hedgehogs, placentas and frozen meals. Enjoy all of this and more, including the return of &amp;lsquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about S**t&amp;rsquo;. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 49. Brace yourself | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770204/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 07:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770204/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 49 and there&amp;rsquo;s a new Beef family member in town! As well as bringing you some exciting news The Ramsey&amp;rsquo;s get nostalgic about childhood illness envy, they reveal their worst 3 course meals, they share the next Chapter from Jesse AND there is a celebrity question. Brace yourself! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 48. Drip Drip Drop. | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770205/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 06:41:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770205/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tensions are running high on this week&amp;rsquo;s episode! As always there&amp;rsquo;s a weekly beef (with Barry getting more air time than ever) and some brilliant questions and stories from the public. This week these cover birth stories to tap water chat and dentistry to a sex themed urban myth. Enjoy. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 47. Express yourself | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770206/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 07:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770206/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Rosie and Chris give an update on the breastfeeding groom, tackle some important shopping trolley etiquette, discuss parent porn stars and they hear back from Friend of the show - Jess the paramedic. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 46. Wide Winifred | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770207/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 07:00:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770207/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s 2020 and Chris and Rosie return with yet another brilliant episode of Sh**ged Married Annoyed! There&amp;rsquo;s some great beef, an unlikely story involving a glow stick, a pretty rank pooh story (natch) and a general post Christmas catch up. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 45. Sweaty Veg: Christmas Special | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770208/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 07:00:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770208/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s the Christmas Special! And Rosie has Lapland beef and some topless memories. There&amp;rsquo;s also some festive (sort of) questions from the public. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 44. Bad breath boyfriend | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770209/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 07:00:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770209/</guid><description>Podcast Description Things are getting festive in the Ramsey Household, including the beef! There&amp;rsquo;s some questionable oral hygiene stories, a cat survival tale that will have you on the edge of your seat and some impressive rapping from Chris&amp;hellip;and Rosie. As well as all of this, there&amp;rsquo;s a celebrity question from comedy sister act Flo &amp;amp; Joan! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Ep 43. Raging semi | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770210/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 07:01:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770210/</guid><description>Podcast Description The semi finals! Who&amp;rsquo;d have thought it? Chris and Rosie return to discuss all things Strictly plus there&amp;rsquo;s a celeb question from Kelvin Fletcher. As well as this there are the weekly beefs, more than enough pooh based chat and some relationship advice. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 42. Don't hate, hydrate. | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770211/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 07:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770211/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Rosie introduces Barry Beef and Chris expresses his bin and recycling issues. As well as this they discuss Strictly, make a return to Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about S**t and have a brilliant celeb question from friend of the podcast Carl Hutchinson. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 41. Batman lives next door | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770212/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 07:00:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770212/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Rosie introduces a new feature as well as still delivering on the weekly beefs! There are some wonderful stories about going commando and getting caught out, sending risque pics and there&amp;rsquo;s a follow up explanation of the word &amp;lsquo;bucking&amp;rsquo;. All of this and a celeb question from Professional Dancer Neil Jones. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Ep 40. Cheese table | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770213/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 07:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770213/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s episode 40 and Chris is off to Blackpool! As well as talking all things Strictly, Rosie and Chris discuss Sandra&amp;rsquo;s latest stash and Rosie&amp;rsquo;s recent trip to London. There are some brilliant stories and questions from the public, topics range from an unfortunate cheese incident to a trip to A&amp;amp;E on a third date. And of course there is a celeb question - this week it&amp;rsquo;s from Strictly alumni Mike Bushell.</description></item><item><title>Ep 39. The Zodiac DJ | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770214/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 07:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770214/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s episode 39 of Sh**ged Married Annoyed and the Ramsey&amp;rsquo;s are back with some brilliant beef and some stories that cover being jilted at the alter, the Zodiac DJ, a bare chested massage and a wheelie bin. Plus it&amp;rsquo;s a podcast first for Rosie&amp;rsquo;s Mum Sandra who makes a cameo appearance! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 38. Buttery Beef | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770215/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 07:00:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770215/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week&amp;rsquo;s podcast Chris and Rosie discuss surviving Halloween week on Strictly and how Chris&amp;rsquo;s bottom has got bigger #glutesfordays There is some exquisite beef that gets Rosie raging and some brilliant questions from the public. As well as all of this the fabulous and fierce Michelle Visage sends in this week&amp;rsquo;s celebrity question. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Ep 37. The Urine Episode | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770216/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 06:00:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770216/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s definitely episode 37! And Chris meets a superstar while Rosie is having laptop bag issues. They discuss shopkeepers, kissing on the lips and receive the most disgusting email yet&amp;hellip; Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 36. Final Warning | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770217/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 06:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770217/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Chris and Rosie have shared massage beef. They talk favourite fridge pickings, Chris comes up with a new invention and they receive possibly the best email yet&amp;hellip; Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 35. Bit of the moon | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770218/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 06:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770218/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris and Rosie have been inundated with hostel stories so strap in for some hilarious/disturbing tales! Also this week there is some bluetooth beef, proposal nostalgia, a revelation that involves Yorkshire Pudding mix and a great question from the brilliant Sian Gibson. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 34. Coughcast | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770219/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 06:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770219/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast Rosie and Chris discuss school detention, Fireman Sam&amp;rsquo;s only Italian resident, that annoying workmate and much more! Plus Rosie has a cough that is getting on Chris&amp;rsquo;s nerves, big style. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 33. Popcast | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770220/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 06:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770220/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast Chris and Rosie discuss week one on Strictly, the train to London with Sandra the Womble, popping spots, noisy randy neighbours and there is a fishy question from Chris&amp;rsquo;s brilliant dance partner Karen Hauer. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 32. Butt Rings | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770221/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 06:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770221/</guid><description>Podcast Description There is some Lasagne based beef this week and Rosie is not happy! As well as discussing which way they stand in a shower the pair discuss second hand sex toys, falling asleep in front of the telly and they explain what a &amp;lsquo;pudding&amp;rsquo; is. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 31. Sugar Lips | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770222/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 06:00:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770222/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Chris and Rosie talk about their North Run experience (no running) they have some bed time beef and they answer some brilliant questions from the public. As well as this there are some truth bombs about what they do when Robyn&amp;rsquo;s not at home and Jamie Laing sends in a great question/fact! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Ep 30. Swamp rings | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770223/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2019 06:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770223/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast Rosie shares what she did for her Year Six project, Chris reveals what a bad loser he is, there&amp;rsquo;s some car themed beef and some dubious emails from listeners! Plus Chris tries his hand at giving Rosie a new nickname. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 29. Use your face more! | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770224/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 06:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770224/</guid><description>Podcast Description Strictly is getting closer and this week Chris and Rosie discuss Chris&amp;rsquo;s dancing face and what happened when Rosie gave Chris some dancing tips! There&amp;rsquo;s some Birthday Beef and we hear from a body double plus a brilliant celeb question! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 28. Oops! | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770225/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 06:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770225/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast Chris and Rosie discuss what constitutes a picnic, why it&amp;rsquo;s okay to have the heating on in August, driving instructor tales and advice on getting over an ex. As well as all of this there is not one but six brilliant questions from pop star twins Jedward. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 27. Found a good a chew | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770226/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 06:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770226/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Ramsey’s are back. The beefs reveal some questionable behaviour, there’s some strictly chat, a story involving a four finger Kit Kat, love bite tales and not one but three questions from YouTube super star Zoella. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 26. Out of Office #2 | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770227/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 06:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770227/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week the Ramsey&amp;rsquo;s are on their holidays so here are some bonus questions from the public! They include hotel etiquette, same dress dramas and some financial advice. Enjoy! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 25 Twinkle Toes | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770228/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 06:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770228/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Chris and Rosie both have some exciting news! They&amp;rsquo;re getting on well but there&amp;rsquo;s still some beef. They discuss natural(ish) alarm clocks, bread VS potatoes and going to gigs alone and have a question from local celeb Joe McEldry. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 24. Viennetta Vinny | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770229/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 06:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770229/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Chris is getting very comfortable with the opening of the podcast, a bit too comfortable for Rosie. They have alarm clock and Maltesers based beef and discuss toothpaste dispensing and teabag etiquette plus have a couple of questions from Rick Edwards. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 23. Did you hear about the Crab Girl? | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770230/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2019 06:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770230/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast the beef gets serious! Rosie and Chris discuss first cars, inherited traits and a disturbing urban myth. There is also a brilliant question from the fabulous Roisin Conaty Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 22. Push the button | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770231/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 06:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770231/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast double dipping returns, Rosie brings some serious beef and there&amp;rsquo;s a surprising personal grooming question. And as an additional treat, Chris has a little test for Rosie. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 21. Double dip with me all day long | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770232/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 05:50:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770232/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week the Ramsey’s discuss an interesting trip to an outdoor pool, the joy of ear wax, cheese grating techniques and Rosie’s trouble with phrases. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 20. Worrying Crush | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770233/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 06:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770233/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Ramsey’s are back from their Holidays and have some brilliant beef to share. They also answer questions about naked neighbours, dressing etiquette and a tooth pick alternative. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 19. Out of Office Reply | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770234/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 05:59:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770234/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rosie and Chris are on their holidays so on this week&amp;rsquo;s podcast they share some questions from the public that didn&amp;rsquo;t make it in the first time round. They discuss how often they change their sheets, plucking in public and pineapple on pizza. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 18. Fetch the bang pillow! | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770235/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 06:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770235/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Chris and Rosie discuss loud yawners, towel sharing and living together, separately. Rosie also recalls her eventful journey home from The Spice Girls – brace yourselves! Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 17. The square root of sex | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770236/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 06:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770236/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the podcast this week Chris and Rosie discuss nudist beaches, an unusual ‘would you rather’ and farting after sex. As well as all of this there’s their weekly beef and a celeb question from Comedian Lee Ridley. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 16. Fanny by the gaslight | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770237/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 06:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770237/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Rosie and Chris record the podcast next to the bare carcass of a chicken (good effort Rosie). They discuss tag team lie ins, embarrassing kid stories, lazy DIY and give some advice to couples going on holiday together. Or not. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 15. Our safe word is... | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770238/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 06:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770238/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast Rosie and Chris discuss safe words, what they wear in bed and things they believed as a kid. Plus, Rosie reveals her new song and there’s a celebrity question from the original Guv’nor – Al Murray. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 14. A pre-marriage thing? | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770239/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 06:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770239/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s podcast Chris and Rosie cover a variety of topics including swear words, women drivers (!) and how they feel about using each other’s phones. As well as this there is some weekly beef and a celebrity question from Podcast royalty Giovanna Fletcher. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 13. Bed time stand off | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770240/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 06:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770240/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast Chris and Rosie discuss embarrassing parental behaviour, who would win in a fight and dubious Instagram behaviour. They also hear from comedian Daniel Sloss who wants to know if either have conceded an argument when they actually think they’re right Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 12. Caravan of love | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770241/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 06:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770241/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week’s podcast Chris and Rosie discuss caravans, crisp packet colours and lying about sexual partners. They have a great question from Radio Royalty Sara Cox plus they answer the age old question – Ant OR Dec? Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 11. Floss before you flirt | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770242/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 06:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770242/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of Sh**ged Married Annoyed, Rosie and Chris are dealing with the Easter Egg aftermath. They discuss Game of Thrones (no spoilers) snoring, weeing in the shower and hoover obsessions. They also receive a question from none other than TV’s Vicky McClure AKA DI Kate Fleming. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 10. Who let the cats in? | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770243/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 06:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770243/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Rosie and Chris drink wine again! They discuss their biggest beef with the general public, sleeping on the sofa, the worst house party Chris ever went to and an incident in the bathroom which led to the best thing Rosie has ever done. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 9. Wine and a FAB time | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770244/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 05:55:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770244/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Rosie and Chris recorded the podcast accompanied by some wine! They discuss airport etiquette, putting on dirty clothes after a shower, their worst argument and Rosie gives some advice involving Skittles and shares a hidden talent. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 8. Diplomatic Immunity | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770245/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 06:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770245/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Sh**ged Married Annoyed, Chris &amp;amp; Rosie discuss arguing tactics, eating in bed, parenting styles and the woes of recycling. They also hear from a listener who wants to thank them for invigorating his sex life, who knew? Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 7. Shredded Beef | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770246/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 06:50:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770246/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris and Rosie bring you this episode of Sh**ged Married Annoyed from a studio in London. They chat about the stages of being away from your kids, the great crisp debate and family peeing (is this a thing?). They also answer your questions which this week cover sex injuries, praise for chores and celebrity crushes. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Ep 6. Let’s see shall we | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770247/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 07:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770247/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s episode of Sh**ged Married Annoyed Chris and Rosie discuss friends with benefits, romance at work, who’s the best in a crisis and which out of the two of them would Vicky Pattison liked to take out on the lash. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 5. Widowed by a Seagull | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770248/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 07:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770248/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s episode of Sh**ged Married Annoyed Chris has a near miss with a seagull and Rosie has some correspondence from The National Lottery. As well as all of this there’s questions about staying friends with exes, who apologises first and whether Chris could live with Rosie’s alter ego - Rosie Mamsey&amp;hellip; he definitely couldn’t, she wouldn’t have him. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Ep 4. Don't touch my bum, I'm a celebrity Mum | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770249/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 07:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770249/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Sh**ged Married Annoyed, Chris &amp;amp; Rosie discuss Celeb Mum of the Year, people that wipe bogies on toilet walls and if it’s okay to have sex whilst listening to a podcast&amp;hellip; it isn’t, it’s weird. Also Celebrity Chef Simon Rimmer gets in touch with a food based question for the couple. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Ep3. Episode three, take two. | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770250/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 07:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770250/</guid><description>Podcast Description As well as answering your questions on this week’s episode of Sh**ged Married Annoyed, Chris explains the rules he’s made since meeting Rosie’s family, Rosie outs Chris for his weird Tennis Snoring (and has evidence!), the pair discuss farting in front of your partner and of course there is a celebrity question – this week from the brilliant comedian – Kathryn Ryan. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.</description></item><item><title>Ep 2. Hungry eyes and a first date surprise | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770251/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 07:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770251/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week&amp;rsquo;s episode of Sh**ged Married Annoyed, Chris and Rosie have a recap on the foursome (not theirs!), they discuss going hungry on a date, they reminisce (kind of) about when they first moved in together and they answer Comedian Jason Manford&amp;rsquo;s questions. Also on this episode, Rosie is given the task of coming up with a northern based sex pun – not as easy as it sounds!</description></item><item><title>Ep 1. Three’s a crowd, four’s a chore | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770252/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 06:22:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770252/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the first episode of Sh**ged Married Annoyed, Rosie and Chris discuss their weekly beef, answer some risqué questions from Instagram and they hear from Ed Sheeran who needs an answer to an ongoing domestic debate. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trailer | Sh**ged Married Annoyed</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9011770253/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 12:01:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9011770253/</guid><description>Podcast Description The only way Rosie and Chris Ramsey can have a conversation without being interrupted by a toddler or ending up staring at their phones is by doing a podcast. They’ll be chatting all about life, relationships, arguments, annoyances, parenting, growing up and everything in between. Each week they will answer questions from the public and a secret celebrity. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/sma. https://plus.acast.com/s/sma.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item></channel></rss>