<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Crime Junkie on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/crime-junkie/</link><description>Recent content in Crime Junkie on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/crime-junkie/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>BWBRSA: Sextortion | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600353/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600353/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two harrowing stories – those of Asia Anderson and Walker Montgomery – illustrate how the rising digital threat of sextortion can impact anyone and forever change lives.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EXPERT ON: Safety from Online Sex Abuse | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600352/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600352/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join Brit and the founder of Safety from Online Sex Abuse (SOSA), Roo Powell, and learn about the incredible work SOSA is doing, how to stay safe online, and how any Crime Junkie parents can best support their children against the monsters of the internet.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Fiona Yu | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600351/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600351/</guid><description>Podcast Description An ASU student comes home one afternoon in 1997 to find her roommate, Fiona Yu, clinging to life in their shared apartment. She had been sexually assaulted, beaten, and left for dead. Though DNA evidence was left at the scene, the case goes cold. When other attacks of young women in the area are reported and their cases closed, there is hope that a connection will shed light on Fiona’s.</description></item><item><title>CONSPIRACY: Phillip Island Part 2 | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600350/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600350/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 23-year-old Beth Barnard is found murdered in her home, investigators immediately suspect a woman named Vivienne Cameron, whose husband had been having an affair with Beth. But the more investigators – and the wider public – dig into the mystery, the less the puzzle pieces seem to fit together.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CONSPIRACY: Phillip Island Part 1 | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600349/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600349/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 23-year-old Beth Barnard is found murdered in her home, investigators immediately suspect a woman named Vivienne Cameron, whose husband had been having an affair with Beth. But the more investigators – and the wider public – dig into the mystery, the less the puzzle pieces seem to fit together.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: J.B. Beasley &amp; Tracie Hawlett | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600348/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600348/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two 17-year-old girls set off one summer night in 1999 for a high school field party, excited to mark the end of summer with friends. But when they never make it to the party…or back home…the search is on.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Bruce Blackwood | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600346/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600346/</guid><description>Podcast Description The sudden disappearance of the manager at an Off-Track Betting parlor has his family, friends, and the police convinced he&amp;rsquo;s met with foul play at the hands of someone he knows.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>NEW LIMITED SERIES: Dark Arenas | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600345/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600345/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever thought about whose job it is to track international fugitives, hunt child abductors, conduct espionage, or pull human remains from concealed mass graves? Everyday thousands of good and decent people work in these Dark Arenas. They’ve chosen professions that grapple with the grotesque, deal with the deviant, and dodge the dangerous.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Reed Jeppson | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Reed Jeppson, a Salt Lake City teen, went outside to feed his dogs one Sunday afternoon in 1964 – and vanished, with the dogs, into thin air. Decades later, his heartbroken family still has so many unanswered questions.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Patricia Newsom | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600002/</guid><description>Podcast Description After nearly 50 years as East Haven, Connecticut’s Jane Doe, police have finally identified the murder victim found behind Bradlees Department Store as 18-year-old Patricia Newsom. Now, they need your help to catch her killer – or killers.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: Molly Young | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600003/</guid><description>Podcast Description On March 24th, 2012, Molly Young rushed to her on-again, off-again boyfriend Richie Minton&amp;rsquo;s aid, only to be found dead hours later in his Carbondale, Illinois apartment with a gunshot wound to the head. Did she take her own life, or was she the victim of foul play? With lingering doubts about the investigation&amp;rsquo;s integrity, the search for answers continues.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Rachel Good | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600004/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a young mother vanishes from her small town, alarm bells sound immediately. Local police are on the case, but just a few days into the investigation, the woman’s family discovers that she had been having a secret affair with a married police officer. When that officer turns out to be the lead investigator on the case, speculation runs rampant. Her family is sure she was murdered by this officer, and the motive seems clear.</description></item><item><title>Crime Junkies Help Solve a Case | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600005/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600005/</guid><description>Podcast Description In May 2021, Crime Junkie covered the 1981 murder of Father Patrick Ryan and the subsequent conviction of James Reyos. Now almost 40 years since James&amp;rsquo; arrest, officials discovered that there was untested evidence that has been sitting idle&amp;hellip;which proved James was innocent and was only uncovered because two Crime Junkies listening to our episode decided to make a little noise.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>UPDATE: James Reyos Exonerated | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600347/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600347/</guid><description>Podcast Description In May 2021, Crime Junkie covered the 1981 murder of Father Patrick Ryan and the subsequent conviction of James Reyos. Now almost 40 years since James&amp;rsquo; arrest, officials discovered that there was untested evidence that has been sitting idle&amp;hellip;which proved James was innocent and was only uncovered because two Crime Junkies listening to our episode decided to make a little noise.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH: Jade Winston | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600006/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 18-year-old Jade Winston is found with a fatal gunshot wound to the head in her Carrier Mills, Illinois, apartment in August 2007, the entire community is stunned, and investigators are split on whether she was murdered or if she took her own life. As rumors fly, a Coroner&amp;rsquo;s Jury rules Jade&amp;rsquo;s death a homicide. But 16 years later, the case is on the shelf, and her family is still desperate to know what happened…and praying that someone will give it the attention it deserves.</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Deanna Cook | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600007/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 32-year-old Deanna Cook is found murdered in her home, her family automatically suspects her ex-husband. But despite a swift arrest, the investigation into her homicide reveals appalling gaps in the Dallas 911 system and the people who failed Deanna when she needed them most.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Pherbia “Faye” Tinsley | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600008/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Pherbia Tinsley is found shot to death inside her car miles from her apartment in Central Virginia, authorities work fast to try and find her killer. Detectives uncover a handful of wild secrets in the lives of those around Pherbia which only deepen the mystery. Suspects are developed but the questions: who wanted Pherbia dead? and why? still plagues cold case investigators.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: Morgan Patten | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600009/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600009/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Morgan Patten is killed in a mysterious auto crash while visiting her fiancé in North Carolina, police are quick to call it a tragic accident. But her loved ones believe she was the victim of foul play, and they won’t rest until they learn the truth.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Jodi Huisentruit | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600010/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a local news anchor vanishes in the pre-dawn hours, the entire community is struck by the irony. The person who typically broke stories in their small town was now the focus of the biggest missing persons case in the Midwest. Leads and suspects are plentiful, but somehow, almost three decades have passed without a shred of evidence pointing to anyone in particular.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>PRECEDENT: Daniel M’Naghten | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600011/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600011/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1843 Daniel M’naghten gunned down another man in broad daylight. But when he was taken to trial things got complicated. His defense argued that he shouldn’t be held fully responsible because he wasn’t in his right mind. However, the courts didn’t know what to do with that because there was no precedent for this kind of thing. So his defense team got to work putting in place a defense strategy that is still used, almost in the exact same way, almost 200 years later.</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: Clarence Roberts | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600012/</guid><description>Podcast Description When the body of a man is found in the burned remains of the Roberts home, the family assumes it’s 52-year-old Clarence. But the question surrounding his identity remains for years… until another fire 10 years later leaves everyone with more questions than answers.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>UPDATE: Alissa Turney Trial | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600013/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600013/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you’ve been following Alissa Turney’s case, you’ll know that her stepfather, Michael Turney, has been acquitted of her murder which has left us all with too many questions. What does all this mean? What exactly happened in court? And what’s next? Well Alissa’s biggest advocate, Sarah Turney, is here to give us the answers.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Donyelle Johnson | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600014/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a young woman goes missing under mysterious circumstances, questions swirl around a local businessman. But throughout the next 15 years, authorities figure out he may be involved in much more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Shannon Siders | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600015/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a young woman vanishes, police think she left willingly. That changes when her body is discovered months later and it’s clear she was brutally murdered. Small town secrets keep this case a mystery for decades…. Until a cold case team is finally able to get people talking.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: Adrienne Salinas | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600016/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a promising young woman fails to show up for a Father’s Day celebration in 2013, her dad knows immediately that something is very wrong. And as investigators work to unravel the chaotic timeline of the night she went missing, they find no lack of viable persons of interest. But when her case goes ice cold, they’re forced to ask if they’ve been overlooking a monster in their midst.</description></item><item><title>CAPTURED: Gilgo Beach Killer | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600017/</guid><description>Podcast Description The update episode you all have been waiting for! On July 13th, 2023, Suffolk County ended the search for their Gilgo Murder suspect and charged 59-year-old, Rex Heuermann, for the murders of Amber Costello, Melissa Barthelemy, and Megan Waterman.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>UPDATE: Alicia Navarro | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600018/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600018/</guid><description>Podcast Description On July 26th, 2021, we covered the case of MISSING: Alicia Navarro. On July 26th, 2023, exactly two years after the release of our episode, 18-year-old Alicia Navarro showed up at a small police station in Montana and stated she was the person who vanished almost four years ago from Glendale, Arizona.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Allison and Marie-Josée Benitez | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600019/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a beautiful young woman and her mother go missing, all eyes turn to the strange behavior of her father. And when he crumbles under the scrutiny, a lifetime of secrets make their way to the surface.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Pamela Butler and Marta Rodriguez | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600020/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a successful career woman goes missing in Washington, D.C., her family immediately knows something is wrong. And when the investigation’s winding path eventually leads detectives right back to the place they started, her family’s long fight for justice produces a stunning result.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Maribel Ramos | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600021/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 36-year-old Maribel Ramos doesn’t show up to her weekly softball game, her friends and family immediately know something is wrong. And that sense of dread only increases when they go to her house, only to discover there’s no trace of her—despite her car still being in the garage. As investigators dig into the case, the signs quickly begin to point to one of the people closest to Maribel.</description></item><item><title>SERIAL KILLER: The Honolulu Strangler | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600022/</guid><description>Podcast Description When young women start disappearing from the streets of Honolulu only to soon be found brutally murdered, investigators at first dismiss any connection between the cases. But as the disappearances continue and the similarities pile up, they’re forced to confront a brutal truth&amp;hellip;there’s a serial killer in paradise.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: Shawn O’Brien | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600023/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Shawn O’Brien is found unconscious in his Cranston, RI, apartment and dies days later in the hospital, the unusual circumstances spark suspicions of foul play. But the investigation quickly stalls out, leaving a grieving family searching for answers on their own.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Denise Pflum | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600024/</guid><description>Podcast Description On a Friday afternoon in 1986, 18-year-old Denise Pflum leaves her home in Connersville, Indiana, to go searching for a purse she had left at a party the night before. When she doesn’t return home, it’s just the beginning of a nightmare that will haunt her parents for over thirty years.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>INFAMOUS: The Todt Family | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600025/</guid><description>Podcast Description When police and federal agents descended on the home of the Todt family, they never expected to discover the gruesome scene waiting for them inside. While investigators had been able to piece together bits and pieces of what may have happened, questions still remained about who instigated everything&amp;hellip; and why.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>PRECEDENT: Amber Hagerman | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600026/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600026/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Amber Hagerman was abducted in 1996 there was a witness who saw a man and a distinctive car near where she was taken. But there was no way to get this information out to the mass public in time and to this day the mystery of what happened to Amber still remains. But her story changed the way the country handles child abductions and a precedent to issue an Amber Alert in situations like hers, was made.</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Joey Lynn Offutt | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600027/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600027/</guid><description>Podcast Description When firefighters responded to 33-year-old Joey Lynn Offutt’s burning house in Sykesville, Pennsylvania, on July 12th, 2007, they were shocked to discover the remains of her infant son, Alexis Brolin III. Joey was nowhere to be found and at the time, investigators didn’t know if she was a victim of the crime &amp;ndash; or the perpetrator. But her family is convinced she was set up and their only hope is that someone will come forward with the information they’ve been desperately seeking for 15 years.</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Sasha Samsudean | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600028/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600028/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a friend is MIA after a night out, loved ones worry that she didn’t make it home safely. When police do a wellness check, they see that she did make it to her apartment… but surprisingly, she was far from safe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Brian Wehrle | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600029/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brian Wehrle vanished without a trace during a trip to his hometown of Carrollton, Georgia. Everyone suspects foul play, but no one knows what could have happened to him. And nearly 14 years after his disappearance, his family is hoping someone out there has the information they need to bring Brian home.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Bruce Cucchiara | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600030/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600030/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 57-year-old Bruce Cucchiara was gunned down in the parking lot of a New Orleans East apartment complex in 2012 his murder devastated his family and stumped law enforcement. For more than a year CounterClock&amp;rsquo;s Delia D&amp;rsquo;Ambra has investigated the case and unraveled a web of bizarre information and circumstances about his life and those who benefitted from his death.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: Nanette Krentel | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600031/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600031/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a fire destroys the Krentel home, family and friends are devastated to learn that one member, Nanette, didn’t make it out. But despite her death clearly being a homicide, her death remains unsolved.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Ashley Loring HeavyRunner | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600032/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600032/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 20-year-old Ashley Loring HeavyRunner goes missing on the Blackfeet Reservation in Montana, her older sister Kimberly is forced to pick up the slack of a system that’s designed to fail those it’s supposed to protect. Her investigation leads her to three people who may know what happened to her sister… but none will talk.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Mengqi Ji | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600033/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600033/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a young mother is reported missing, investigators quickly realize she was probably murdered. Their prime suspect is her husband, but a slew of suspicious statements and circumstantial evidence isn’t enough to put him behind bars&amp;hellip; until a lucky discovery gives them everything they need.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: Elizabeth Santos | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600034/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Elizabeth Santos’ unexpected and tragic death in 2020 left behind a million questions. Some believe it was the result of a mental health crisis, but many of her loved ones think she’s a victim of foul play, and they’ve been pushing for answers.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CAPTURED: Michael Townson | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600035/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600035/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a young mother is found brutally beaten to death in 2007, investigators are able to quickly apprehend her killer. But as the years go by, he decides to open up and reveal he has a darker past than anyone could’ve ever imagined.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Oakley Carlson | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600036/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Oakley Carlson was only 4 years old when she went missing in 2021. Investigators launched a desperate search to bring her home, but with each new piece of evidence, they learned that home may not have been the safest place for her. And systems put in place to protect her may have been the very thing that put her in the hands of the people responsible for her disappearance.</description></item><item><title>PRECEDENT: Adam Walsh | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600037/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600037/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1981 a young boy named Adam was abducted by a stranger from a shopping plaza. It would take almost three decades to bring closure to his family but in that time Adam’s legacy would forever change the way America views and handles missing children cases.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: QC Chadwick | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600038/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600038/</guid><description>Podcast Description When mother-of-three QC Chadwick and her husband, Peter, don’t pick their kids up and the bus stop, their friends and neighbors immediately know something’s wrong. But, they never could have guessed the horrors that had already occurred behind closed doors… and the lengths a man would go to in order to avoid capture.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Phoenix Coldon | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600039/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600039/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 23-year-old Phoenix Coldon walks out the front door of her family home, her parents never could have guessed that she wouldn’t come back. The search for her only turned up more questions, and over 10 years later, many of those questions still remain.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Darlene Hulse | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600040/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Darlene Hulse was forcibly taken from her home in Argos, Indiana on August 17, 1984. Her two oldest daughters witnessed the attack but they didn’t recognize the man who took their mother.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Julie Kibuishi and Sam Herr | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600041/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600041/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Julie Kibuishi’s body is discovered in Sam Herr’s apartment, investigators immediately launch a manhunt to track Sam down. But things take an unexpected turn when a new suspect places himself front and center, and confesses to a crime so callous, it’s as if it’s a movie.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>WANTED: Justice for Sasikala and Anish Narra | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600042/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Strangeland Season 2: Murder in Maple Shade is available right now wherever you listen to podcasts.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>INFAMOUS: The Vernon-Tolland Three | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600043/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600043/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the late 1960s and early 1970s, multiple young women and girls go missing in the Vernon-Tolland area of Connecticut. For years, investigators have wondered if these seemingly unrelated cases might share too strong a connection to be ignored. Three, in particular —Janice Pockett, Lisa White, and Debbie Spickler—bear striking similarities to each other, and have become known as the Vernon-Tolland Three.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Tracy Kirkpatrick | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600044/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600044/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 17-year-old Tracy Kirkpatrick is found murdered in March 1989, investigators struggle to find any evidence pointing to who killed her. Despite numerous efforts to dig up leads and strong tips through the investigation, the case has remained a mystery for nearly 40 years.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CONSPIRACY: Theresa Allore | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600045/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600045/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Theresa Allore vanishes from her college campus in Quebec, Canada, in 1978, local police dismiss her as runaway and force her family to start their own investigation that would span across 45 years. Over the decades, they piece together evidence and uncover an array of conspiracies from a potential serial killer on the prowl to the possibility of corrupt law enforcement.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: David Josiah Lawson | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600046/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Josiah Lawson headed off to college in Arcata, California with big dreams…only to be stabbed to death at a party off-campus. But a case that seemed straightforward when it began proves to be anything but…and years later, his mom is still fighting for justice.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Christina Calayca | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600047/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600047/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Christina Calayca disappeared on a camping trip in Ontario, Canada, in 2007, investigators expected to find her in a few short hours. But despite numerous search efforts, no sign of her was ever found. And 16 years later, her family is still searching for answers.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Sharmini Anandavel | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600048/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600048/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 15-year-old Sharmini Anandavel doesn’t come home from her first day at a new job, her family is immediately suspicious of one of their neighbors. But despite an overwhelming amount of circumstantial evidence, her death remains unsolved… at least, in the eyes of the law.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: The Family in Anaqua Springs | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600049/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600049/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Nichol Olsen and her two daughters are found shot in the home they shared with her boyfriend, a theory quickly emerges that lays the blame on Nichol. But to those who knew her, that’s not an option, and points to someone else as the culprit. Over three years later, the question still remains: what happened in that house on January 9th, 2019?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Aaron Taylor | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600050/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Aaron Taylor was 36 and experiencing homelessness when he was lit on fire on Christmas Day in 2007. Police think they know who’s responsible… but a lack of physical evidence…coupled with reluctant witnesses…has kept this case open for years. But multiple people know what happened…and investigators are hoping they’ll come forward.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Natanalie "Naty" Perez | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600051/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Natanalie Perez was chasing her dream of being a singer when she fell victim to a violent sex-trafficking ring in Florida and disappeared in June of 2012. More than a decade later, her family and investigators from the Anti-Predator Project are still trying to find her…or find out what happened to her.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>PRECEDENT: Ernesto Miranda | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600052/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600052/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1963 Ernesto Miranda was arrested for kidnapping, rape and armed robbery. Ultimately, he gave police a confession but only because he didn’t know he had the option not to talk to them… or to get an attorney. Miranda’s path through the justice system set a precedent for informing those arrested of their rights. And now the Miranda Warning is something so engrained in us Crime Junkies we could probably recite it on our sleep.</description></item><item><title>Everyone Needs a True Crime Friend | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600053/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600053/</guid><description>Podcast Description There are Crime Junkies far and wide and SURPRISE! Conan O’Brien is in fact a Crime Junkie. On this special bonus episode, Ashley sits down with Conan to deep dive into what it is about true crime that has got them absolutely hooked. From the first case that caught each of their attention to the one that keeps them up at night, Ashley and Conan share it all!</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Phylicia Simone Barnes Part 2 | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600054/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600054/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 16-year-old Phylicia Simone Barnes is found dead in a river 40 miles from where she was staying, her family suspects one man is responsible. But bringing him to justice is far more difficult than anyone could have expected.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Phylicia Simone Barnes Part 1 | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600055/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600055/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 16-year-old Phylicia Simone Barnes goes missing while visiting her half-sister in Baltimore, the whole community comes together to search. But what started as a missing persons investigation that consumed the city of Baltimore quickly turns into something far more sinister.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>5 Years of Crime Junkie! | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600056/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600056/</guid><description>Podcast Description For our 5-year celebration episode, we take a look back at the impact Crime Junkie has made. From funding DNA testing to solving crimes, nothing would have been possible without the support of everyone who has tuned in every week for the last 5 years!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CONSPIRACY: Jonathan Luna | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600057/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600057/</guid><description>Podcast Description When federal prosecutor Jonathan Luna was found face-down in a creek with multiple stab wounds, homicide seemed like the obvious answer. Over time, though, public officials started to pose a different theory: that he took his own life. But for those who knew Jonathan, that wasn’t an option – and the more they learned about the circumstances surrounding his death, the more they started to wonder if it was being covered up by those in charge.</description></item><item><title>SURVIVED: Jaycee Dugard | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600058/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600058/</guid><description>Podcast Description 11-year-old Jaycee Dugard was abducted as she was walking to school in June of 1991. No one would see her again for 18 years, until two campus police officers did what parole and police officers couldn’t. But her story isn’t just one of survival – it’s one of strength, resiliency, and life after tragedy.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Anthonette Cayedito | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600059/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600059/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a 9-year-old girl vanishes from her home overnight, investigators must try and overcome a lack of evidence and follow a number of shocking, but ultimately dead-end tips that have them convinced she is still out there somewhere more than 3 decades later.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: Nadia Malik | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600060/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nadia Malik was trying to break free of an abusive relationship when she disappeared only to be found dead in a car. And while her family and many others are sure that one person is responsible for her death, the mysterious circumstances have made finding justice elusive.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Heather Teague | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600061/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600061/</guid><description>Podcast Description A young woman is abducted in the middle of the day, and despite seeming like an open and shut case, her family is still searching for answers almost 30 years later.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: The Short Family | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600062/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600062/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Michael and Mary Short are found murdered in their Virginia home in August of 2002, the question on everyone’s minds is: where is their nine-year-old daughter Jennifer? But as weeks go by with no solid leads, authorities grow more and more concerned that they won’t find Jennifer alive. And those worries only intensify when a homeowner across state lines finds something horrifying in his front yard.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Arianna Fitts | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600063/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600063/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Nicole Fitts is found murdered in a park in San Francisco, both her family and law enforcement have the same two questions: who killed her, and where is her 2-year-old daughter, Arianna? The investigation into Arianna’s disappearance leads them right to the people who were supposed to be watching her&amp;hellip; but they quickly realize that this case won’t be easy solve.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>WANTED: Justice for Hassani Campbell and Tianna Kirchner | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600064/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Five-year-old Hassani Campbell disappears without a trace, leaving behind a community desperate for answers. No one knew four-year-old Tianna Kirchner was missing for four years, until a chilling phone call shocks law enforcement and the public. Though not connected in life, one thing is clear: they both deserve justice.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CAPTURED: Killer on the High Bridge | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600065/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 19:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, October 31, 2022, the Indiana State Police, in conjunction with the Carroll County Sheriff’s Office, United States Marshals Service, and the Carroll County Prosecutors Office, held a press conference where they made the announcement thousands of people have been waiting to hear: an arrest had been made for the murders of Abby Williams and Libby German.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Celina Mays | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600066/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Celina Mays was 12 years old when she vanished from her bedroom in the middle of the night back in 1996. Her disappearance helped peel back the curtain on a small controversial church where an environment of shame, isolation and fear allowed sexual abuse to flourish.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SERIAL KILLER: Mack Ray Edwards | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600067/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600067/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 8-year-old Stella Nolan went missing in 1953, no one could have known that she was the first in a long list of children that would disappear throughout the 50s and 60s in Los Angeles, California. But despite child after child vanishing, it would take an unexpected twist of fate for anyone to even know there was a monster living in their midst.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Kreneice Jones &amp; LaMoine Allen | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600068/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Toddlers Kreneice Jones and LaMoine Allen disappear from a small town in Mississippi during a family gathering on Mother’s Day in 1992 under bizarre circumstances. The two children aren’t related – in fact, they barely know each other – and to this day, no one can make sense of what happened to them.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CONSPIRACY: Boys on the Track | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600069/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600069/</guid><description>Podcast Description When two boys are found deceased on the train tracks in Bryant, Arkansas, their deaths are considered a tragic and unexpected accident. But as their parents begin looking for answers, they uncover deep-rooted corruption and a scheme to cover up their deaths that everyone from the police to the prosecutor seems to be in on.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Owachige Osceola | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600070/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Recently divorced and living on her own in a new city, 27-year-old Owachige Osceola’s life was in a season of transition before she was killed in the bedroom of her Norman, Oklahoma apartment in September 2013. While the medical examiner who performed her autopsy concluded her cause and manner of death were “undetermined,” a detective who remains on the case today insists a killer has been allowed to walk free for nearly a decade.</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Yeardley Love | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600071/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600071/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 22-year-old Yeardley Love is found murdered in her apartment just a few weeks before graduating college, her friends all point police to one man: George Huguely, her ex-boyfriend. It doesn’t take long for investigators to uncover a disturbing history of domestic abuse, but despite multiple people knowing just how violent George could get, no one spoke up to get the help Yeardley needed.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Hang Lee | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600072/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600072/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 17-year-old Hang Lee leaves for a job interview and never comes home, police are quick to dismiss her as a troubled runaway. But when they finally take a deeper look into her case, they discover that the last man she was seen with has a violent criminal history, and no explanation for what happened to her.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CAPTURED: Timothy Coggins Killers | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600073/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600073/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1983, a young Black man named Timothy Coggins is found brutally murdered in Spalding County, Georgia. But just as promising leads are uncovered, the case is inexplicably closed. And it remains that way for more than 30 years, until a new investigator comes across the file and realizes just how solvable this murder could be.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Shakara Carter | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600074/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600074/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Shakara Carter is found strangled to death on a dead-end road in Grand Rapids, Michigan, she’s days away from testifying against a serial rapist. But she’s also one of about two dozen sex workers killed in the area over the years…and unlike some of those victims, Shakara’s killer is elusive.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Update from Brit | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600075/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 13:18:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Transcript</description></item><item><title>PRECEDENT: John Brady | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600076/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600076/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1958 John Brady, along with an accomplice, was accused of murdering his friend, William Brooks. John maintained that he had not taken part in the murder, that he was only part of a plan to rob the man. However, his accomplice turned on him and he was eventually found guilty. Though there was something the prosecution was holding back that would completely change the way a jury would view the case.</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Mekayla Bali | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600077/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600077/</guid><description>Podcast Description 16-year-old Mekayla Bali vanished from a bus depot in her hometown of Yorkton, Saskatchewan in 2016, leaving no trace and no clues as to where she might be now - or why.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Jenny Lin Part 2 | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600078/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600078/</guid><description>Podcast Description After days of searching for 14-year-old Jenny Lin’s killer, detectives received some promising tips that left everyone hopeful they’d solve one of the most disturbing murders Alameda County had ever seen.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Jenny Lin Part 1 | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600079/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600079/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1994, the brutal murder of a 14-year-old inside her parents&amp;rsquo; safe suburban house left a community shaken to its core, because not only had a bright and talented life been suddenly snuffed out, but police struggled to find a motive. And the more clues they uncovered, the more investigators realized the nightmare they were dealing with: Jenny Lin’s murder was more than a crime of opportunity —it had been carefully planned.</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: Davina Buff Jones | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600080/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600080/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Officer Davina Buff Jones is found dead in the middle of her shift on Bald Head Island, those in power are quick to rule her death a suicide. But the more her family learns about the circumstances surrounding her death, the more certain they are that someone got away with murder.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>BONUS: Possible Bell Victims | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600081/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600081/</guid><description>Podcast Description After Larry Gene Bell is arrested, investigators dive into his past and uncover three unsolved cases that are eerily like the two he’s convicted of. In this bonus episode, we cover the stories of the three women who detectives believe were killed by Bell.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>ALL GOOD PEOPLE HERE…IS HERE!! | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600082/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600082/</guid><description>Podcast Description The day has FINALLY arrived, Crime Junkies!! Ashley Flowers&amp;rsquo; debut novel ALL GOOD PEOPLE HERE is officially available NOW!If you haven’t already, go get your hands on a copy! You can find ALL GOOD PEOPLE HERE wherever books, ebooks, or audiobooks are sold or at AshleyFlowers.com/book
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Shari Smith and Debra Helmick | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600083/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600083/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 17-year-old Shari Smith is abducted from her driveway in broad daylight, it seems like her family’s nightmare can’t get any worse. But when her abductor starts calling them relentlessly, investigators hope that his recklessness will lead to his downfall&amp;hellip; that is, until a second girl goes missing in an eerily similar manner.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: The Millbrook Twins | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600084/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600084/</guid><description>Podcast Description When twin sisters Jeannette and Dannette Millbrook go missing in Augusta, Georgia in 1990, police are quick to write them off as runaways…even though the signs point to something much more sinister.
And if not for a family that refused to give up… and a podcast that shed light on some of the injustices they’ve faced…we probably wouldn’t know anything about them. Because even though this is one of the only open cases of missing twins in the country…it took decades for them to get the national spotlight.</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Kathy Page | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600085/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600085/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a young woman is found dead in a crashed car, the first thought is a tragic accident. But after investigating the scene, investigators can clearly see this is a homicide. After interviewing friends and family, all signs point to her estranged husband&amp;hellip; but thirty years later, he is still a free man.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Susan Robin Bender | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600086/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Susan Robin Bender got into a van in 1986 and was never seen again. Police believe the teenage girl met with foul play and have renewed the search for answers, decades after her mysterious disappearance&amp;hellip;but her mom thinks she knows who’s responsible.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SERIAL KILLER: Khalil Wheeler-Weaver | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600087/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600087/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a New Jersey family is rocked by the disappearance of one of their own, they set up a trap to catch the man they believe to be responsible. But once that man is behind bars, police discover that the full extent of his crimes goes beyond what they expected.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Ruby J. Doss | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600088/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600088/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1986, a young woman named Ruby Doss is found strangled to death in the East Sprague area of Spokane, Washington. For decades, similarities between Ruby’s death and a string of other murders in the area send investigators chasing false leads. It seems like justice for Ruby is a lost cause, until a completely unrelated crime in another state blows the case wide open.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Jamie Fraley | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600089/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Everything was going great for Jamie Fraley when she vanished in April of 2008, after telling a friend she was getting a ride to the hospital. Police quickly zero in on a suspect, but a bizarre development throws the investigation off course…and years later, her family still has more questions than answers.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Shawn Edwards Part 2 | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600090/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600090/</guid><description>Podcast Description After years of rumors, gossip and dead end leads, the investigation into 14-year-old Shawn Edwards’ murder heats up – but even a shocking confession can’t close this cold case.
Anyone with information about the homicide should call Middletown Police at 845-343-3151.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Shawn Edwards Part 1 | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600091/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600091/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 14-year-old Shawn Edwards is stabbed and beaten to death outside of a high school in Middletown, NY, the whole community is shocked. Why would anyone want to hurt – let alone murder – this friendly, popular kid? As the investigation unfolds, police try to separate fact from fiction, only to come up emptyhanded. It seems like everyone’s a suspect…but no one has a motive.
Anyone with information about the homicide should call Middletown Police at 845-343-3151.</description></item><item><title>Ashley Flowers Wrote a Book! | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600092/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get ready Crime Junkies because Ashley Flowers’ debut novel All Good People Here will officially be released on August 16th! You can read the first 2 chapters on AshleyFlowers.com/book AND preorder your copy NOW!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Dawnita Wilkerson | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600093/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600093/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Dawnita Wilkerson stops answering her phone one Sunday in June of 2020, her loved ones know something is wrong – especially because she’s been telling everyone that her ex-boyfriend and one of his relatives have been threatening her. Two years after her disappearance, police and her family are still hoping someone out there will come forward with information they need to solve the case.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Joseph Kinville III | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600094/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600094/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 16-year-old Joseph Kinville III is brutally stabbed to death in a field in his neighborhood in Arcadia, Florida, law enforcement is stumped from the start and his mother is devastated. The mystery only deepens when the teen&amp;rsquo;s estranged father is murdered a few weeks later, hundreds of miles away in Michigan. The identity of Joseph&amp;rsquo;s murderer has remained unknown since his murder in 1999, but evidence from his crime scene may still hold the answers law enforcement needs.</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: Pravin Varughese | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600095/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600095/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 19-year-old Southern Illinois University student Pravin Varughese dies unexpectedly, police quickly rule his death a tragic accident and close the case. But for many, the facts just don’t quite add up. His mother’s years-long battle for justice is marked with soaring highs and dizzying lows – but even with so much progress, there are still unanswered questions.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: Casey MacPherson-Pomeroy and Caleb Guillory | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600096/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Casey MacPherson-Pomeroy and Caleb Guillory had plans to ring in the new year on the beautiful Caribbean island of Anguilla. But before the proverbial ball could drop, they were both dead. The four people with them that night haven’t spoken publicly about the incident since &amp;ndash; and until they do, the mystery of what happened to Casey and Caleb will remain on the island.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Dulce Maria Alavez | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600097/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600097/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 5-year-old Dulce Maria Alavez vanishes from a playground in New Jersey, the whole community pitches in to help search for her. But thousands of leads later - and nearly three years after her mysterious disappearance – law enforcement still isn’t sure where she is…or who took her.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>DESAPARECIDA: Dulce Maria Alavez | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600098/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cuando Dulce María Alavez, de 5 años, se desaparece de un parque infantil en Nueva Jersey, toda la comunidad colabora para ayudar a buscarla. Pero despues de miles de pistas, y casi tres años después de su misteriosa desaparición, la policía aún no está segura dónde está&amp;hellip; o quién se la llevó.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SERIAL KILLER: The Freeway Phantom | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600099/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600099/</guid><description>Podcast Description When six young girls are found murdered, their similarities link them all to one killer. With no witnesses and no leads, investigators are still asking who is The Freeway Phantom over forty years later.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: John Welles | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600100/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 21:04:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Investigative journalist, Delia D&amp;rsquo;Ambra, is back with a fourth season of CounterClock. She jumps right into investigating a teenager&amp;rsquo;s mysterious death from 2003 in rural South Florida only to find that nothing is as it seems. Twists and turns are around every corner, and finding the truth of what really happened to 17-year-old John Welles proves to be Delia&amp;rsquo;s most dangerous and difficult journey yet.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>PRECEDENT: Polly Klaas | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600101/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Polly Klaas was taken from her own home in the middle of the night back in 1993. But had the legal system worked like it was supposed to, the man who took her never should have been walking free that night to enter her home. Her case went on to spark an outcry in the country for harsher punishment on repeat offenders. But when her case set the precedent for the three-strikes rule there was backlash no one anticipated.</description></item><item><title>Important Message | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600102/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600102/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you&amp;rsquo;d like to leave words of encouragement &amp;amp; well wishes for Brit, we&amp;rsquo;ve posted a virtual card on our social media accounts as a place to do so. Please feel free to share longer messages, stories, and images, by emailing them to us at crimejunkie@audiochuck.com
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Michelle Eason Part 2 | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600103/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600103/</guid><description>Podcast Description When the bodies of eight missing sex workers are found in the home of a serial killer in Poughkeepsie, New York, one woman is noticeably absent: Michelle Eason. Decades after closing the case against Kendall Francois, police are still looking for Michelle - and they think there’s a good chance someone else may be responsible for her disappearance.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Michelle Eason Part 1 | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600104/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600104/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Michelle Eason is reported missing, she’s the fifth sex worker in one year to vanish from Poughkeepsie, New York. As police work to get to the bottom of all the disappearances, there’s no shortage of suspects.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>INFAMOUS: Circleville Letters | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600105/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600105/</guid><description>Podcast Description An anonymous letter-writer antagonized residents of Circleville, Ohio for years, singling out the school superintendent, Gordon Massie, and a local bus driver, Mary Gillispie, as the focus of much of the vitriol. When Mary finds a booby trap with a loaded gun in 1983, the gun is traced to her brother-in-law Paul Freshour – but the letters would continue long after Paul went to prison for attempted murder.</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Karen Gregory | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600106/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Karen Gregory dies a violent death in the hallway of her own home, on a quiet residential street in Gulfport, Florida. After a two-year search for justice, police find out that their killer was right in front of them all along.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: Erica Alonso | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600107/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600107/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Erica Alonso disappears on Valentine’s Day after a night out with her ex-boyfriend, a months-long search turns up clue after clue before her body is found in the middle of nowhere. The case looks like a murder until some surprising evidence is found – and investigators come to a conclusion that, to this day, leaves many questions unanswered and has her family demanding more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Marqueise Coleman | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600108/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marqueise Coleman had his whole life ahead of him when he was shot to death in a trailer in North Carolina – all because he was in the wrong place at the wrong time. Police say this horrific crime can be solved if someone just speaks up, and his family and friends won’t rest until he gets justice.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>UPDATE: Flathead County Doe | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600109/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600109/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is an update to the August 2020 episode &amp;ldquo;UNIDENTIFIED: Flathead County Doe.&amp;rdquo; In the year and a half since the release of that episode, more people submitted their DNA to genealogical databases, and in February 2022 Flathead County Doe was identified as Steven Gooch.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>INFAMOUS: Juan Rivera | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600110/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600110/</guid><description>Podcast Description the summer of 1992, the brutal rape and murder of 11-year-old Holly Staker shakes the community of Waukegan, IL to its core. When Juan Rivera confesses to the crime, it seems like Holly’s family and members of the public might be able to breathe a sigh of relief. But that’s only the beginning of a case that would haunt the Illinois justice system for years.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Erica Gene Shultz | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600111/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600111/</guid><description>Podcast Description From the moment her sister Erica’s phone went to voice mail, Emily Corbin knew something was wrong. But thanks to all those true crime shows – and countless episodes of Crime Junkie – she also knew exactly what she had to do to find her. Her tenacity not only led police to Erica, but helped solve her murder and two others &amp;ndash; and took the worst kind of serial predator off the streets.</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Emma Walker and Mya Peña | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600112/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emma Walker had what looked to the world like a picture-perfect high school relationship — until her football player boyfriend revealed the ugly truth. Mya Pena looked past the red flags and saw a guy in need of unconditional love. And when she couldn’t give that to him, he decided she wouldn’t be giving it to anyone else either.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: JoAnn Matouk Romain Part 2 | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600113/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600113/</guid><description>Podcast Description The January 2010 death of JoAnn Matouk Romain gets even more mysterious when her family learns of two other cases connected to hers. One, which seems to not even be real, and another that is all too real and shares some eerie similarities.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: JoAnn Matouk Romain Part 1 | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600114/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600114/</guid><description>Podcast Description In January 2010 JoAnn Matouk Romain runs a quick errand to get gas followed by attending a 15-minute prayer service, then she walks into the freezing lake across the street to take her own life. Or at least that&amp;rsquo;s what police say. But from the very moment they notify the family about her case they know something isn&amp;rsquo;t right. And the deeper they look they learn that nothing is what it seems.</description></item><item><title>PRECEDENT: Megan Kanka | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600115/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600115/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Megan Kanka went missing in 1994 her case exposed one of the holes in the sex offender registry. Yes, people were registered but that was only known to government officials, not to those living among potential predators. Had her parents known who was living right down the street from them Megan’s story might have ended differently. Instead, it set a precedent for community reporting.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>PRECEDENT: Jacob Wetterling | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600116/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600116/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Jacob Wetterling went missing in 1989 one of the first thoughts police had, was to track down all the local violent sex offenders in the area to see if they could be potential suspects. But this was easier said than done because back then there was no centralized database for this sort of thing. Jacob’s case went unsolved for decades and his mom always wondered if her son fell through the cracks of a system without enough regulation.</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Linda Smith | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600117/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Audiochuck’s newest weekly show, The Deck, is hosted by Ashley Flowers and takes true-crime listeners through a deck of playing cards that is unlike any other.
For years, state prison systems and local law enforcement agencies across the U.S. have replaced the face cards of queens, kings and aces in traditional playing card decks with images of missing and murdered people. Investigators have passed these modified decks out in jails and prisons hoping that they will make their way into the hands of someone with answers.</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Georgia Leah Moses | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600118/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600118/</guid><description>Podcast Description A 12-year-old girl slips through the cracks…and exposes them in every system that should have protected her. Now her sister is fighting for justice, hoping to find out who murdered her sister nearly 25 years ago.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SURVIVED: Chrystul Kizer and Cyntoia Brown | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600119/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600119/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 17-year-old Chrystul Kizer is arrested for first-degree murder in Milwaukee, the investigation uncovers a connection between her and her victim that can’t be ignored. And it mirrors an eerily similar story &amp;ndash; that of Cyntoia Brown &amp;ndash; that played out over a 15-year span in Tennessee.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Diane Francis | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600120/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 08:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600120/</guid><description>Podcast Description A woman goes missing, leaving behind little evidence to help figure out when, how, where or why she disappeared. But her determined daughter has spent years piecing together every clue she can find.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Lauren Dumolo | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600121/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600121/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Lauren Dumolo disappeared, she left behind a ton of questions, a mystery that keeps unfolding and a family desperately searching for answers.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: Patricia Viola | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600122/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Just before Valentine’s Day in 2001 a New Jersey housewife goes missing. For almost a decade her case remains unsolved until a bizarre connection is made to a clue that washed ashore years before.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Mary Lynn Witherspoon | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600123/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600123/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Mary Lynn Witherspoon doesn’t show up to work at the South Carolina school where she taught, her friends and family immediately know something must be wrong. And they immediately suspect the involvement of a person who had been stalking and harassing Mary Lynn for more than twenty years. There’s just one problem: that person is supposed to be in jail.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Damien Nettles | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600124/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600124/</guid><description>Podcast Description A 16-year-old vanishes from England’s Isle of Wight. And the quest for answers leads us deeper and deeper into an underbelly most didn’t even know existed on the island.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: Sherese Walker Bingham Part 2 | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600125/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 08:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600125/</guid><description>Podcast Description The investigation into Sherese Walker Bingham’s death points police in one direction: toward her husband, Eugene Bingham Jr. But all of their evidence isn’t enough to make a murder charge stick.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: Sherese Walker Bingham Part 1 | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600126/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600126/</guid><description>Podcast Description A woman takes her dogs for their nightly walk and is shot and killed with her own gun in a downtown Indianapolis state park. Is it a tragic accident or cold-blooded murder?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Candace Rough Surface | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600127/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600127/</guid><description>Podcast Description When young mother goes missing from the reservation border town of Mobridge, South Dakota, investigators struggle to find any leads in the case. A chance discovery along the muddy banks of the Missouri River answers one question. But it’ll take 15 years and a whole lot of chance to finally unravel the mystery of what happened – and why – on one fateful night in 1980.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Kierra Coles and Keeshae Jacobs | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600128/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two women. Two cities. Two years apart. Both of them – vanished without a trace. Both are mysteries that need to be solved.
If you have information on the disappearance of Kierra Coles please contact the Chicago Police Special Victim’s Unit at 312-747-8274. And if you have any information on the disappearance of Keeshae Jacobs please contact Crime Stoppers at 804-780-1000 or text I-TIP to 274637 to submit tips anonymously.</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Janet Abaroa | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600129/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600129/</guid><description>Podcast Description After 25-year-old Janet Abaroa is discovered brutally murdered in her North Carolina home, her family suspects her husband’s involvement. But a lack of direct evidence means the case goes cold for years, leaving Janet’s family without closure and potentially putting another woman in danger.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: Ellen Greenberg | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600130/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ellen Rae Greenberg had everything going for her when she was found dead in the apartment she shares with her fiancé. Police are quick to say she died by suicide – despite the 20 stab wounds she sustained. But her heartbroken parents are sure she was murdered and their search for answers has raised serious questions about the investigation.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>NEW SHOW: STRANGELAND | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076602671/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076602671/</guid><description>Podcast Description Audiochuck&amp;rsquo;s new true crime podcast Strangeland is available to binge right now wherever you get your podcasts! Or visit the website strangelandpodcast.com
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Enrique Roman Martinez | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600131/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600131/</guid><description>Podcast Description A young soldier vanishes during a camping trip. His partial remains wash up on the beach 10 days later.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CAPTURED: Allan Showery | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600132/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600132/</guid><description>Podcast Description This year’s Halloween’s special is the story of a woman whose tragic murder almost went unsolved… until a tip came in from the last person police expected.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Young Men From Their Cars | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600133/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600133/</guid><description>Podcast Description A strange phenomenon keeps occurring where young men go missing from their cars and then seem to vanish into thin air. It happened in 2008 to Brandon Swanson, 2020 To Jason Landry, and 2021 to Daniel Robinson. It seems impossible that they could walk away from their vehicles, sometimes even leaving their clothes behind and never be seen again. Their families need your help to find their loved ones!</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Meredith Kercher | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600134/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600134/</guid><description>Podcast Description A 21yo British woman is less than a month into a foreign exchange in Perugia, Italy when she is brutally murdered in her apartment. Everyone’s world is turned upside-down. And for the woman who found herself in the center of the storm &amp;ndash; and on trial for murder &amp;ndash; it has stayed that way ever since. My question is: Why, all these years later &amp;ndash; long after the courts have spoken &amp;ndash; are we still talking about Amanda Knox?</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Billy Stafford | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600135/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600135/</guid><description>Podcast Description A violent marriage ends in a bloody murder. Police solve the case &amp;ndash; but it’s the victim who ends up on trial in a case that thrust the issue of domestic violence into the public conversation and made it impossible for law enforcement to ignore.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: The Hendricks Family | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600136/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600136/</guid><description>Podcast Description For years, David Hendricks was the walking embodiment of the true crime trope &amp;ldquo;The Husband Did It.&amp;rdquo; After his family was brutally murdered in their Illinois home back in 1983, police were quick to zero in on him as their main suspect despite the lack of evidence and mostly because&amp;hellip; nothing else made any sense. Decades later some still believe in his guilt but knowing what we know now can you still be so sure?</description></item><item><title>CAPTURED: Denver Hammer Killer | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600137/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600137/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the 1980s the Denver area was terrorized by a hammer-wielding mad man. But as fast as the attacks started, they suddenly stopped. Leaving the area to wonder if the mad man was dead or had moved on to another place. Once answers came, decades later the public would learn that the truth was much more concerning.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: Joyce Chiang | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600138/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600138/</guid><description>Podcast Description One woman’s promising career in Washington, D.C. is cut short when she mysteriously vanishes one night on her way home from work.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Gabby Petito | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600139/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 18:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Summary: Gabby Petito is missing after a cross-country trip with her fiancée. He returned home alone with her van and since has refused to speak with her family or police. The Family’s approved GoFundMe page can be found here: https://www.gofundme.com/f/help-us-find-gabby NOTE: Be aware of other pages as they may be scams. Like Gabby, Lauren “El” Cho went missing this summer as well after her friends say she walked out towards the mountains and was never seen again.</description></item><item><title>INFAMOUS: Armored Truck Heists | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600140/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 14:14:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Robbing an armored truck is one of the most difficult and dangerous crimes someone can commit. These illegal acts take patience, precision and planning&amp;hellip;skills most run-of-the mill robbers don’t possess. If a suspect is successful, the payoff can be millions of dollars all at once, which is why throughout the decades some men and women have tried to execute the perfect plan to net one of these mobile money pots.</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Debra Jackson (Orange Socks Doe) | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600141/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600141/</guid><description>Podcast Description For decades after she was mysteriously murdered and left on the side of a busy interstate, she was known only as Orange Socks Doe. But after years of investigations, law enforcement learns that her case may be even more complicated than they first thought.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Ryan Shtuka | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600142/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600142/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a young man vanishes in a small resort town, the question is: does someone know something, or does no one know anything?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CAPTURED: Rocky Mountain Killer | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600143/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two notorious murder cases stay ice cold for decades, until a mysterious clue helps bring a killer to justice.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Mary Badaracco | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600144/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600144/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a 38-year-old woman leaves her home - and a violent marriage - without saying goodbye, her two adult daughters suspect her husband. By the time police take interest in the file and begin investigating, years have passed and the case is cold. If you have any information regarding the disappearance and possible homicide of Mary Badaracco please contact the Connecticut State Police Western District Major Crime Squad at #800-376-1554 or email WDIST.</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Lisa Au | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600145/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600145/</guid><description>Podcast Description A young woman’s shocking murder forces residents to question the very people who are supposed to keep them safe.
If you have any information about the murder of Lisa Au, please call the Honolulu Police Department at 808-529-3111, or you can go online and submit your tips anonymously at www.honolulucrimestoppers.org.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SERIAL KILLER: The Cleveland Strangler | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600146/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Police in Cleveland enter a home in Mount Pleasant to arrest a man on sexual assault charges. But they don’t find their suspect. And what they do find sends an already struggling community into chaos.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Alicia Navarro | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600147/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600147/</guid><description>Podcast Description A teenage girl finds community online, but her family believes she also found something much more sinister. If you have any information about the disappearance of Alicia Navarro, please call the Glendale Police Department at (623) 930-3000. You can go to www.AntiPredatorProject.org to make a tax-deductible donation or you can buy something from their clothing line at www.getapparel.org with all of the profits going directly to the organization.</description></item><item><title>DESAPARECIDA: Alicia Navarro | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600148/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Una joven encuentra una comunidad en línea, pero su familia cree que ella se encontró con algo más siniestro. Si usted tiene información sobre la desaparición de Alicia Navarro, por favor llame al Departamento de la Policía de Glendale al (623) 930-3000. Si desea hacer una donación deducible de impuestos, puede visitar la página de www.AntiPredatorProject.org. O también, puede comprar mercancía en www.GetApparel.org. Todas las ganancias irán directamente a la organización.</description></item><item><title>INFAMOUS: Tommy Zeigler | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600149/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tommy Zeigler was sentenced to death for the murders of his wife, her parents, and a customer at his Winter Garden, Florida furniture store in 1976. He’s still on death row today - 45 years later. But did he do it? And could DNA evidence exonerate him?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SEASON OF JUSTICE!!! | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600150/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Audiochuck’s founder and CEO, Ashley Flowers, has founded a new non-profit called Season of Justice. Season of Justice (SOJ) is dedicated to providing funding to law enforcement agencies and families to help solve cold cases. SOJ provides grants to law enforcement for advanced DNA analysis solutions, such as forensic genealogy and next-generation sequencing. The organization also awards grants to families to support awareness campaigns, search teams and other initiatives that can assist in pushing their cold cases forward.</description></item><item><title>WANTED: The Keddie Cabin Killer | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600151/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600151/</guid><description>Podcast Description A family’s brutal murder rocks a tiny California town and leaves behind too many unanswered questions.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: Kaysera Stops Pretty Places | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600152/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600152/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 18-year-old Kaysera Stops Pretty Places disappears after a night with friends in Hardin, Montana, her family and friends hold their breath waiting for answers. As the months pass, the story that starts to emerge is one so inconceivable, it will have you wondering: what exactly is going on in Big Horn County?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SERIAL KILLER: Bruce McArthur | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600153/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600153/</guid><description>Podcast Description For years, the LGBTQ+ community in Toronto, Canada worried there was a serial killer targeting men in the city’s Church and Wellesley neighborhood. Police disagreed and downplayed their concerns &amp;ndash; and all the while, more men vanished into thin air. But the truth, when it was finally revealed, showed just how complicated a relationship still exists between Toronto Police and the LGBTQ+ community.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CAPTURED: Jennifer Pan | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600154/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600154/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Pan Family seemed to have it all until a shocking home invasion upended their lives in the most vicious way imaginable.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Branson Perry | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600155/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600155/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2001, a young man vanished without a trace and more than 20 years later the only thing law enforcement is sure of is that someone in Skidmore, Missouri knows something. If you have any information about the disappearance of Branson Perry, please contact the Community United Effort Center 24-hour tip line at 910-232-1687, the Nodaway County Sheriff’s Office at 660-582-7451, or the Missouri State Highway Patrol Hotline at 1-800-525-5555.</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Mollie Olgin | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600156/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two teenage girls in love are forced to endure an unimaginable trauma that rocks their south Texas town.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>INFAMOUS: The Signal Mountain Murders | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600157/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600157/</guid><description>Podcast Description A summer joyride turns deadly when three men are viciously gunned down in the hills of southern Tennessee.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Father Patrick Ryan | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600158/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600158/</guid><description>Podcast Description A Catholic priest is found savagely beaten to death in an Odessa, TX motel room in 1981. A man confessed to the crime &amp;ndash; but instead of closing the case, people are still left wondering: Was justice served in the murder of Father Patrick Ryan?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>INFAMOUS: The Setagaya Family Murders | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600159/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600159/</guid><description>Podcast Description A Tokyo family is slaughtered in their home, leaving behind a brutal and baffling mystery.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Rosie Tapia | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600160/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600160/</guid><description>Podcast Description A little girl vanishes from her bedroom in the middle of the night only to be found brutally murdered, forcing her community to recognize that the worst really IS possible.
If you have any information about the murder of Rosie Tapia, please call the Salt Lake City police department at 801-799-3455.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Diane Louise Augat | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600161/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600161/</guid><description>Podcast Description A woman leaves her sister’s home one April day in 1998 and never returns. But she doesn’t vanish into thin air, because over the next several years, there are sightings, phone calls, even physical signs that she might be out there somewhere. If you have any information about Diane Augat’s disappearance, contact Crime Stoppers of Tampa Bay at 1-800-873-TIPS.
May is Mental Health Month. Please take care of yours.</description></item><item><title>INFAMOUS: Prom Night Murders | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600162/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600162/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1989 the small town of Lakeville, Indiana was rocked by the massacre of a pastor and his family. The pastor&amp;rsquo;s only surviving son was ultimately convicted of this infamous crime but there is more to this twisted story than has ever been told before. On April 29th, 2021 (the 32nd anniversary of the crime) the audiochuck original podcast CounterClock will be releasing 20 episodes on this case to binge!</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Sierah Joughin | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600163/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600163/</guid><description>Podcast Description A beautiful young woman&amp;rsquo;s brutal murder at the height of Midwestern summer shatters her community&amp;rsquo;s sense of safety forever and exposes a monster hiding right there in plain sight. Please join us in supporting www.justiceforsierah.org
Transcript</description></item><item><title>INFAMOUS: #ChallengeAccepted | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600164/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600164/</guid><description>Podcast Description When two women are violently murdered five years apart and half a world away, advocates look for a way to call attention to the serious and growing issue of femicide in Turkey. The campaign takes off &amp;ndash; but while it gains momentum, it loses its original meaning. This is the real story behind the viral #ChallengeAccepted campaign that flooded your Insta feed in the summer of 2020.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Peggy Reome | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600165/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600165/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a mother of three walks out her front door and into the New York morning, she leaves a trail of heartbreak, suspicion, and unanswered questions in her wake. It takes almost 15 years for investigators to finally untangle the truth about her disappearance –and the unimaginable reason behind it all. For resources on child sexual abuse, including what to look for and how to file a report, visit www.</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Esther Hollis | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600166/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600166/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Esther Hollis goes missing after a conversation with her husband, her best friend and sister try to get justice in what they believe is a no body homicide.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>NEW SHOW: O.C. Swingers | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076602708/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076602708/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re dropping in your feed again today to share some exciting news! Audiochuck has teamed up with well-known journalist and podcaster Justine Harman for audiochuck’s newest 10-part series, O.C. Swingers! When Newport Beach Orthopedic surgeon Dr. Grant Robicheaux and his fresh-faced girlfriend are accused of drugging and raping many women, the attractive young couple claims the prosecution simply has a problem with their party lifestyle. But you can’t spell “lifestyle” without “lies”.</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Donnah Winger | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600167/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600167/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1995 a new mother is killed after being attacked by a man who&amp;rsquo;d been harassing her. Or at least, that&amp;rsquo;s what everyone believed. But years later investigators learn there might be much more to the story.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Heather Bogle | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600168/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600168/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a woman is murdered in a small Rust Belt town, the quest to find her killer gets turned upside down.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>UNIDENTIFIED: St. Louis Doe // Beth Doe | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600169/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two different people have one terrible thing in common: they were both brutally murdered but despite evidence left at the scene no one has been able to identify them in decades, leaving many still wondering who they are and what really happened to them.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SURVIVED: Elizabeth Smart | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600170/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Elizabeth Smart was abducted at knifepoint in the middle of the night from her bedroom in Salt Lake City, Utah, in 2002. She was 14 years old. For more than 9 months, she was held captive by a predator – one who kept her hidden in plain sight. To learn more about the programs and services Elizabeth mentioned please visit https://www.elizabethsmartfoundation.org
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: The Lundys Part 2 | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600171/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600171/</guid><description>Podcast Description After Mark Lundy was convicted of viciously slaying his wife and daughter, another story started to emerge, leading many people in New Zealand to wonder…was the wrong man behind bars?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: The Lundys Part 1 | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600172/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600172/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a woman and her young daughter are found brutally murdered in their home, the investigation leads to the person who was supposed to have loved them more than anyone else in the world.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>BWBRSA: Operation Fireball 2.0 | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600173/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600173/</guid><description>Podcast Description BWBRSA: Operation Fireball was one of our most popular episodes ever! And it&amp;rsquo;s more terrifying than we even knew because after our episode many women from all over the country wrote in and said they experienced the exact same thing! With the help of Delia D&amp;rsquo;Ambra we tracked down the bartender and witness from our original story and spoke to a number of other survivors along with an agent from the FBI to figure out what&amp;rsquo;s really going on!</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: Holly Bartlett | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600174/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600174/</guid><description>Podcast Description On a cold day in March 2010, workers discovered a woman lying unconscious under the MacKay Bridge in Halifax, Nova Scotia, Canada - barely breathing and clinging to life. It was 31-year-old Holly Bartlett. Police say she walked almost a quarter of a mile from the front door of her condo building, where she crawled through a hole in a barbed wire fence, climbed a 20ft concrete cable abutment, and fell to the frozen ground below.</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Jaliek Rainwalker | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600175/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600175/</guid><description>Podcast Description A child&amp;rsquo;s mysterious disappearance sparks tough questions about his adoptive family and the system that placed him there. If you know anything about the disappearance of Jaliek Rainwalker, please contact the Cambridge-Greenwich police at 518-677-3044.
For more information on how you can support the nonprofit Child Advocates, check out their website www.childadvocates.net
Transcript</description></item><item><title>NEW SHOW: Dark Arenas | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076602718/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076602718/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever thought about whose job it is to track international fugitives, hunt child abductors, conduct espionage, or pull human remains from concealed mass graves? Every day thousands of good and decent people work in these Dark Arenas. They’ve chosen professions that grapple with the grotesque, deal with the deviant, and dodge the dangerous. In audiochuck’s newest original series, Dark Arenas, you will hear first-hand accounts of what it&amp;rsquo;s like to investigate the darkest crimes and most violent criminals in society.</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Harvey and Jeannette Crewe | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600176/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600176/</guid><description>Podcast Description A shockingly brutal crime rocks a rural New Zealand community, but the fallout has bigger consequences than anyone could ever have imagined.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>UPDATE: Sumter County Does - IDENTIFIED!!! | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600177/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600177/</guid><description>Podcast Description As of 2pm ET on January 21, 2021 The Sumter County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office has identified the Sumter County Does as 25-year-old Pamela Buckley of Colorado Springs, CO and 30-year-old James Freund of Lancaster, PA. To continue to support the DNA Doe project go here: https://dnadoeproject.org/
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CAPTURED: Bay Area Predator | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600178/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600178/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Michaela Garecht was abducted in 1988, no one was prepared for the heartbreaking investigation to drag on for over 30 years. But just when the case seems to be ice-cold forever, police make a stunning announcement.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Jeramy Burt | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600179/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Late one night in 2007, Jeramy Burt left his home to meet up with a friend but never made it. His disappearance opened up a mystery made even more complicated by love triangles, secret recordings, an arrest, and a connection to another missing local man years before.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>INFAMOUS: Las Cruces Bowling Alley Massacre | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600180/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600180/</guid><description>Podcast Description A normal Saturday morning at the bowling alley takes a shocking and brutal twist that shakes a New Mexico town all the way to its very foundations.
If you know anything about the Las Cruces Bowling Alley Massacre, you can report tips to Crime Stoppers anonymously by calling 1-800-222-8477 or by visiting their website at www.nmcrimestoppers.org.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Gina Hall | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600181/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600181/</guid><description>Podcast Description A young college student never comes home after a night of dancing. All the evidence suggests she&amp;rsquo;s been murdered, but if her body is never found, can her killer ever be brought to justice?
To get some fun stuff with our new logo check out our website here!
We’ll be taking some time off next week for the Holidays! Our next regular episode will be Monday, January 4th. See you in the New Year!</description></item><item><title>AUDIO EXTRA: Bizarre Crime History | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600182/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600182/</guid><description>Podcast Description Crime Junkie OFFICIALLY turns 3 today, and we decided to give ourselves and YOU a little birthday gift&amp;hellip;we’re still the same pod, but with a NEW LOOK! And to celebrate we are giving you a very different kind of bonus episode! Join us as we take a look back at some of the most bizarre moments in criminal justice history - Crime Junkie style! In addition to a new logo, we have a few goodies to share with you here!</description></item><item><title>STALKED: Dorothy Jane Scott // Cynthia Jane Anderson | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600183/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600183/</guid><description>Podcast Description Even though they&amp;rsquo;re strangers who&amp;rsquo;ve never met, two women suffer through similar patterns of fear and intimidation, praying for help that doesn&amp;rsquo;t come until it&amp;rsquo;s too late.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Girly Chew Hossencofft | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600184/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600184/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a young mother fails to show up at her scheduled shift at the bank, her friends and colleagues are immediately suspicious. The investigation into her disappearance uncovers a truth so twisted, it’s almost impossible to believe &amp;ndash; and shows us all how tangled people can become in the web of a con-man’s lies.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>BWBRSA: Operation Fireball | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600185/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600185/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;re dropping in your feed on an unusual day of the week to tell you an unusual Crime Junkie story. Thanks to the podcast Something Was Wrong, Ashley stumbled across a story that shook her to her core. She&amp;rsquo;s convinced that a bigger operation is going on undetected and she needs you to listen and write in to help solve this mystery! This story is also a good reminder to always be weird, be rude, watch out for one another, AND STAY ALIVE!</description></item><item><title>INFAMOUS: Manhole Murders | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600186/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600186/</guid><description>Podcast Description The investigation into one man reported missing from South Bend, Indiana, uncovers four dead bodies and many uncomfortable truths, and shines a light into one of the darkest corners of America.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Madeleine McCann | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600187/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600187/</guid><description>Podcast Description Madeleine McCann was just three years old in 2007 when she disappeared from her family’s room during a resort vacation in Portugal. The whole world watched with bated breath for the last 13 years while authorities searched, chased leads and named potential suspects. Most assumed we’d never know the truth about what happened to Madeleine. But you know what they say about assumptions…
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Leigh Occhi | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600188/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600188/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1992, a teenage girl disappears from her home during Hurricane Andrew, leaving behind only a few gruesome clues and kicking off a search for answers that hits closer to home than anyone could ever have expected.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CONSPIRACY: Fort Hood | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600189/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600189/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a 20-year-old soldier goes missing from one of the largest military bases in the country, her tight-knit family is determined to find her and bring her home. But the investigation into her disappearance uncovers more than anyone bargained for - secrets, lies, and a system that failed to protect the people within it. And it has left everyone asking: what is going on at Fort Hood, Texas?</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Tamika Huston | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600190/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600190/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Tamika Huston goes missing and leaves everything behind, her family is sure from the very start that something terrible has happened, because she never would have left without her dog. It will take dedicated police work and vital clues for them to learn the truth.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: Michelle O’Connell | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600191/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600191/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a young mom is killed by her boyfriend&amp;rsquo;s service weapon, local law enforcement treat her death as a terrible tragedy and rule it a suicide. But her family believes the truth is much more sinister.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>INFAMOUS: The “Lonely Hearts” Killers | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600192/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600192/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the late 1940&amp;rsquo;s, women who thought they&amp;rsquo;d found true love were being conned out of their life savings by a man and his sister who would go to brutal lengths to keep their scheme going.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Faith Hedgepeth | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600193/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600193/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 19-year-old college student Faith Hedgepeth is horrifically slain in her apartment after a night out clubbing, the local police are shockingly tight-lipped&amp;hellip;until information starts flooding out and raising so many new questions.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Shaquita Bennett // Tara Costigan | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600194/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600194/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, for Domestic Violence Awareness Month, we&amp;rsquo;re bringing you the stories of two women whose lives were stolen by their abusive ex-partners.
We are supporting two organizations. The Network, which is a Chicago based advocacy group who has provided training and services to people in the same area where Shaquita lived.
We also are supporting the Center for Survivor Agency and Justice in their missions to foster change at all levels and empower communities to better meet the needs of survivors everywhere.</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Tara Calico | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600195/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600195/</guid><description>Podcast Description A bright young college student vanishes while out on a bike ride, leaving behind a mystery that&amp;rsquo;s endured for over 30 years.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SERIAL KILLER: The Butcher Baker of Alaska | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600196/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600196/</guid><description>Podcast Description Robert Hansen owned and operated a successful bakery in Anchorage, Alaska in the 1970s and 80s, selling donuts and danishes to everyone in town. He was a well-known and well-respected member of the business community, living in a nice home in the suburbs with his wife and two children. In his spare time, he liked to fly his plane to the remote area around the Knik River and hunt for wolves and caribou and other large game.</description></item><item><title>MISSING: DeOrr Kunz Jr. | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600197/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600197/</guid><description>Podcast Description An idyllic family camping trip in the Idaho forests turns into a nightmare when 2-year-old DeOrr Kunz Jr. vanishes without a trace.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Stacey Stanton | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600198/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600198/</guid><description>Podcast Description After three decades of rumors, secrets and one man’s conviction&amp;hellip;the question remains, who really killed Stacey Stanton? Be sure to tune into CounterClock Season 2 starting September 10th on Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts. And check out the website to the show counterclockpodcast.com
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Pamela Milam // Vickie Lynn Harrell | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600199/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600199/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1972, two young women with their whole lives ahead of them vanish from public places, leaving behind only a tiny handful of clues.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Bradley Sisters | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600200/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600200/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a pair of young sisters vanished from their home in Chicago, they left behind a mystery that has haunted their family for almost two decades.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SERIAL KILLER: Ed Kemper | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600201/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600201/</guid><description>Podcast Description When female college students started turning up dead in Santa Cruz in 1972, local police had no leads and no reason to suspect their friend Ed might be behind the grisly killings.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>UNIDENTIFIED: Flathead County Doe | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600202/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600202/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Flathead County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office and the DNA Doe Project are so close to identifying a man who’s been a doe for almost 17 years, but they need your help get this case across the finish line. Could you be related to the Flathead County Doe?
Based on his DNA, the DNA Doe Project believes that his family lineage could be linked to one of 11 family names in one of 3 different counties.</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Martha Moxley | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600203/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600203/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 15-year-old Martha Moxley was brutally murdered in 1975, no one could have imagined that the search for her killer might lead right to the doorstep of American royalty.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>INFAMOUS: Bathtub Killer | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600204/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600204/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1996 there was one apartment complex in Texas that was home to two brutal killings, just months apart. It would take police years and several more innocent victims before they captured their killer.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: Phoebe Handsjuk | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600205/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600205/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a young woman falls 12 floors down a garbage chute to her death only questions remain. Was it suicide? Was it an accident? Or could something more sinister happened to Phoebe Handsjuk?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Rico Harris | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600206/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600206/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2014 Rico Harris left Los Angeles to drive north for a new life in Seattle, only to vanish somewhere along the way.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CONSPIRACY: The Smiley Face Killer | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600207/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600207/</guid><description>Podcast Description For over 20 years young college-aged men have been going missing, only to turn up dead in local waterways. Police think these cases are tragic accidents, but a small group of investigators have long believed there’s something else at work…something much more sinister that all leads back to one huge question. Are the Smiley Face Killers real?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: Rey Rivera | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600208/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600208/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2006 Rey Rivera was found dead at the Belvedere Hotel in Baltimore. Did he die by suicide, or was something more sinister at play?
Following the release of this episode, representatives of Porter Stansberry contacted Crime Junkie to inform us of information regarding Rey Rivera’s case that had not yet been made public, and we want to alert our listeners to that information for the sake of being exhaustive.</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: Tamla Horsford // Joseph Smedley | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600209/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600209/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the last few years two people died under very mysterious circumstances. Though their cases aren&amp;rsquo;t connected they were each quickly ruled an accident or suicide. But if you take a closer look, there might be much more to their stories and their families need your help to find the truth about what really happened. Sources for this episode cannot be listed here due to character limitations. For a full list of sources, please visit: https://crimejunkiepodcast.</description></item><item><title>WANTED: Monsters of Ohio Part 2 | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600210/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600210/</guid><description>Podcast Description After Asenath Dukat, 11 more young girls in Ohio were kidnapped and murdered. Many under eerily similar circumstances. Is this the work of one or two predators or are there many monsters still on the prowl in Ohio?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>WANTED: Monsters of Ohio Part 1 | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600211/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600211/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the 1980s something strange was going on in Ohio. Almost a dozen young girls were kidnapped and murdered, many of the killers still unknown to this day. And it all started in June of 1980 with the case of Asenath Dukat.
All ad-sales profits from this episode are being donated to the NAACP To learn more check out these podcasts:
1619 (New York Times)
About Race
Code Switch (NPR)</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Matthew, Daniel, &amp; Islan | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600212/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600212/</guid><description>Podcast Description This very special episode for Pride Month tells the stories of three people joined together not just by the desire to live peaceful happy lives as their authentic selves, but also because they faced a similar indignity in how our legal system allowed injustice in their cases.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Margaret Ellen Fox | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600213/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600213/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2017 the FBI released a chilling recorded phone call that may be the only clue as to what happened to Margaret Ellen Fox back in 1974.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: The Yuba County Five | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600214/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600214/</guid><description>Podcast Description In February 1978, five young men headed from their home in Yuba County, California to catch a college basketball game – and never came home.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Danielle Imbo &amp; Richard Petrone | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600215/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600215/</guid><description>Podcast Description In February 2005 Danielle Imbo and Richard Petrone had been broken up for a number of weeks. But on February 19th the two met up spontaneously for a couple drinks and then were never seen again.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: Mitrice Richardson | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600216/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600216/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mitrice Richardson disappeared after being released from an LA County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s station, leaving behind questions about mental health, police bias, and much more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Diana Alvarez | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600217/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600217/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2016 a young girl went missing from her home in the middle of the night. It would take four excruciatingly long years before her family would get solid answers about what happened to her.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>INFAMOUS: The Dexter Killer | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600218/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600218/</guid><description>Podcast Description In October 2008, Johnny Altinger headed out to meet up for the first time with Jen, a woman he’d met on a popular online dating site. They had plans to meet at her place for a casual hook-up, and Johnny diligently followed the driving directions she’d emailed him earlier that day. But when he walked through the door of her detached garage in Edmonton, Alberta, it wasn’t love he found but something much more sinister.</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Najah // Angie | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600219/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600219/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two Indianapolis women have been murdered. Though the cases aren&amp;rsquo;t connected they both have eerie parallels and both remain unsolved. Are you the person out there who can help IMPD and Avon Police solve these murders?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>INFAMOUS: Lipstick Killer | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600220/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600220/</guid><description>Podcast Description A young Chicago girl&amp;rsquo;s brutal murder in 1946 led police to a dangerous criminal with more blood on his hands than anyone could have imagined. However, decades later those who re-examine the facts wonder if they got the wrong man.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Barry and Honey Sherman | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600221/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600221/</guid><description>Podcast Description In December 2017, a realtor touring the mansion of billionaires Barry and Honey Sherman made a gruesome discovery: the bodies of 75-year-old Barry and 70-year-old Honey semi-seated and hanging from the railing around their pool deck. Police believe the deaths were targeted, and many feel the motive was money. Who killed Barry and Honey Sherman? And why?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CAPTURED: The Monster of Miramichi | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600222/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600222/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1989, Allan Legere was serving a life sentence for the murder of an elderly shopkeeper in a rural part of New Brunswick, Canada. Until he escaped. For seven months, he evaded capture, living in the woods around the Miramichi river, only coming out at night to steal food, rob houses, and murder the community’s most vulnerable citizens. More than 30 years later, people still remember the fear and panic that gripped a community, caused by one man - the Monster of the Miramichi.</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Missy Bevers | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600223/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600223/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Texas fitness instructor Missy Bevers was murdered in 2016, police and the public seized on an unusual clue that could lead them to her killer.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CAPTURED: A Secret Stalker | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600224/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 22:39:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600224/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1992 Lisa Ziegert felt like someone was watching her at a gift shop where she worked. People would tell her no one was there; it was just in her head. But when she goes missing from that very same gift shop, everyone begins to wonder if Lisa had been right.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Jessica Heeringa | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600225/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600225/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jessica Heeringa was a young mom in her mid-20’s who was trying to provide for her family. She was smart, loving, a hard worker… and then, in 2013, she vanished from her job at a local gas station.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Relisha Rudd // Unique Harris | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600226/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600226/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we bring you two mysterious disappearances. Why did it take 18 days for people to notice 8-year-old Relisha Rudd was missing? And how did 24-year-old Unique Harris vanish from her apartment without the glasses that were critical to helping her see? Please join us in supporting blackandmissinginc.com
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Breanna Moore | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600227/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600227/</guid><description>Podcast Description Breanna Moore was a young woman on the very cusp of the rest of her life when dating violence turned to murder and stole her entire future away from her.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SERIAL KILLER: Rodney Alcala | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600228/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600228/</guid><description>Podcast Description He was charming enough to win an episode of The Dating Game back in the 70&amp;rsquo;s and that charm is what allowed Rodney Alcala to slip through police&amp;rsquo;s fingers time and time again. Though his reign of terror lasted only a few years, he may be one of the most prolific serial killers of our time and police still need your help to identify some of his victims.</description></item><item><title>WANTED: Massachusetts Murderer | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600229/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600229/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is there a predator in Massachusetts who targeted two girls with an eerie connection?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: The Beaumont Children | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600230/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600230/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane, Arnna, and Grant Beaumont left their home in Adelaide to go swimming at the beach on Australia Day 1966 and were never seen again. Their disappearance changed Australian life forever.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CONSPIRACY: Ray Gricar | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600231/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600231/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2005, a day of playing hooky for Ray Gricar turned into an enduring mystery for his friends and family and left the world to wonder if there is a bigger conspiracy at play.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Denise Johnson | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600232/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600232/</guid><description>Podcast Description After more than two decades of rumors and secrets, the question still remains, who killed Denise Johnson? You can listen on any podcast app for free or visit www.counterclockpodcast.com
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Brittanee Drexel | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600233/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600233/</guid><description>Podcast Description High school junior Brittanee Drexel just wanted to get away for Spring Break and have a good time with her friends in Myrtle Beach. Her mysterious disappearance would frustrate law enforcement and haunt her family for years to come. For more information on human trafficking, visit https://polarisproject.org/
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Lindsay Buziak | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600234/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600234/</guid><description>Podcast Description 24-year-old Lindsay Buziak was an up-and-coming real estate agent in beautiful Victoria, BC, when she was found stabbed to death in the upstairs bedroom of a house she was showing to prospective clients. Nearly 12 years later, Lindsay’s family and friends &amp;ndash; and local police &amp;ndash; are still trying to find out who killed Lindsay and why. Saanich police tip-line: tips@saanichpolice.ca or 1-888-980-1919 Crimestoppers (anonymous): 1-800-222-TIPS // 1-800-222-8477</description></item><item><title>WANTED: A Christmas Killer | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600235/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600235/</guid><description>Podcast Description 5 days before Christmas in 1984, 12-year-old Jonelle Matthews went missing from her Colorado home and she wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be discovered for over three decades. In the course of the investigation one man&amp;rsquo;s bizarre actions have put him front and center on police&amp;rsquo;s radar and they call him a person of interest in this Christmas killing.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SERIAL KILLER: Highway of Tears | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600236/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600236/</guid><description>Podcast Description Loren Donn Leslie was only 15 years old when police discovered her remains on a lonely logging road off Highway 16 in British Columbia. Since the late 1960s, women and girls have gone missing from the communities that surround Highway 16, or been found murdered along the desolate 450-mile stretch of road known as the Highway of Tears.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Jody LeCornu | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600237/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600237/</guid><description>Podcast Description In March of 1996 a young woman was shot under very bizarre circumstances. 23 years later her case remains unsolved, but her twin sister is still fighting for justice.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SERIAL KILLER: Dellen Millard | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600238/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600238/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dellen Millard was the 27-year-old millionaire heir to a Canadian aviation company when he murdered a perfect stranger during a test-drive. What unfolded in the months that followed would leave Canada &amp;ndash; and the world &amp;ndash; in disbelief.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Brian Shaffer | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600239/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600239/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brian Shaffer was supposed to be enjoying a night out with friends on April 1, 2006. Instead, he vanished. 13 years later, the mystery of what happened that night still endures.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>RED BALL: The Burger Chef Murders | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600240/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600240/</guid><description>Podcast Description Listen to episode 2, 3, and 4 RIGHT NOW by Searching Red Ball on your favorite podcast directory!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: Kyle Antonacci | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600241/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600241/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Navy sailor Kyle Antonacci was found dead in his barracks in 2010, investigators quickly ruled it a suicide. However, discrepancies pop up right away and his family is left with one critical question: did Kyle really die by suicide, or was it something more sinister?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>INFAMOUS: D.C. Sniper | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600242/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600242/</guid><description>Podcast Description For three weeks in October 2002, the nation&amp;rsquo;s capital region was paralyzed with fear as a series of deadly sniper attacks killed innocent people across Washington D.C., Maryland, and Virginia. This week, we partnered with the FBI to bring you this episode and to commemorate the 100th anniversary of the first African-American agent joining the Bureau. Together with a very special guest from the FBI, we delve into the case of the notorious DC Sniper.</description></item><item><title>INFAMOUS: The Preppy Murder | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600243/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600243/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Jennifer Levin is found murdered in Central Park in 1986, and one of her private school friends is arrested for the crime, it catalyzes bitter debates about sex, privilege, legal ethics, parental responsibility, socioeconomics, victim’s rights, and so much more, because before there was the OJ Simpson trial, there was the Preppy Murder.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Annamarie Cochrane Rintala | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600244/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600244/</guid><description>Podcast Description Just like love knows no gender, neither does jealousy, dysfunction or murder. In honor of domestic violence awareness month we are partnering with The Network/La Red to bring awareness to issues of domestic violence within the LGBTQ community.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SERIAL KILLER: Robert William Pickton | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600245/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600245/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week&amp;rsquo;s episode, we talk more about the man responsible for making Canadian women disappear for years and what horrors were found on his pig farm.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Women of Vancouver’s downtown Eastside | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600246/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600246/</guid><description>Podcast Description For two decades, women living in a ten-block stretch of Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada, were disappearing without a trace. This week’s episode is part one of a two-part series. It’s a story of tragedy and triumph – and of one man who terrorized the downtown Eastside for almost two decades.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Lauren Spierer | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600247/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600247/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the early morning hours of June 3, 2011, Lauren Spierer went out and celebrated the end of a semester by partying with friends. It should have been like so many weekends before. But on this morning Lauren would leave the company of her friends and walk off alone in the direction of her apartment, never to be seen again.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Yingying Zhang | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600248/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600248/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Chinese graduate student Yingying Zhang agreed to spend a year in America, she did so by looking forward to the opportunities it would present for her future. However, in June of 2017, 26-year-old Yingying would go missing while on her way to an appointment. Over the next several weeks, a dark saga would begin to play out as police began figuring out what had happened to her&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>INFAMOUS: Darlie Routier (Part 2) | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600249/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600249/</guid><description>Podcast Description After Darlie was sentenced to death for the murder of her two boys her defense team immediately started the appeals process. There was a lot of information they felt the public didn&amp;rsquo;t get to hear and evidence that could prove an innocent woman is sitting on death row for a crime she did not commit.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>INFAMOUS: Darlie Routier (Part 1) | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600250/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600250/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1996 a small Texas community was rocked by the tragic slaying of two young boys. The police and prosecution had their sights set on one person as the perpetrator: The boy&amp;rsquo;s mother. And they would work tirelessly to make sure she paid the price.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Adam Walsh (Preview) | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600251/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600251/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1981 a young boy named Adam was abducted by a stranger from a shopping plaza. It would take almost three decades to bring closure to his family but in that time Adam’s legacy would forever change the way America views and handles missing children cases.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Russell and Shirley Dermond | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600252/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600252/</guid><description>Podcast Description In May of 2014, a married couple went to check in on their elderly neighbors, who lived alongside the scenic Lake Oconee. Inside the older couple&amp;rsquo;s house, they would find one of the most gruesome crime scenes of all-time, which kicked off a terrifying mystery that remains unanswered today&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SERIAL KILLER: The Hillside Strangler | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600253/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600253/</guid><description>Podcast Description Between October of 1977 and February of 1978, a serial killer terrorized women in Southern California. Originally preying upon sex workers in Los Angeles, this offender began to target young women irregardless of race or background, before simply vanishing for good. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t until a year later that police were able to link a separate crime to this spree, and from there, began to track down the culprit&amp;hellip; or, in this case, culprits&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Kimberly McAndrew | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600254/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600254/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, August 12, 2019, marks the 30th anniversary of Kimberly McAndrew&amp;rsquo;s disappearance. Over the years investigators have tried using old fashioned police work as well as psychics to solve the case but so many years later no one has found Kimberly. If we have any listeners in Nova Scotia who know anything about Kimberly’s disappearance, you can contact the Rewards for Major Unsolved Crimes Program at 1-888-710-9090. Or Crime Stoppers at 1-800-222-TIPS</description></item><item><title>CAPTURED: Lloyd Lee Welch | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600255/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600255/</guid><description>Podcast Description During spring break of 1975, Sheila &amp;amp; Kate Lyon went missing from a shopping center near their home and for almost 40 years no one knew what happened to them. Over the years horrible men would come into focus as suspects. Men who took the lives of 10-year-old Amanda Ray, 5-year-old Neely Smith, and 15-year-old Kathy Beatty. But it wasn&amp;rsquo;t until a cold case investigator came across a single old report from 1975 (a report that had been there all along) that the case would finally be solved and Mr.</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Kara, Kelsey, &amp; Jessica | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600256/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600256/</guid><description>Podcast Description Three cases over ten years. Each one bringing a killer a little closer to justice. EDIT TO THE EPISODE: please note Kylr Yust was not Jessica Runions boyfriend. Just a friend.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SERIAL KILLER: Charlie Brandt | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600257/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600257/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2004 a seemingly normal man commits an unthinkable crime. Police and friends are left to wonder what caused this man to just snap but his older sister holds the key and reveals a dark family secret that would completely change the investigation.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Brandy Hall | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600258/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600258/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2006 Brandy Hall vanished after leaving her post at the volunteer fire station early. It would take many years, 3 clues found in three different bodies of water and a lost tip, before anyone would have an idea of what might have happened to her that night.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>INFAMOUS: Alice Crimmins | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600259/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600259/</guid><description>Podcast Description Long before Casey Anthony, there was another mother America loved to hate&amp;hellip; Alice Crimmins. When her children went missing from their room one summer night, the police and the press were quick to point the finger at the &amp;ldquo;sex-crazed&amp;rdquo; mother. At the start of the women&amp;rsquo;s lib movement, Alice stood for everything that threatened the status quo of how a wife and mother should behave. But over 50 years later we can re-examine the case and her multiple trials to see if there really was a case against Alice or if she was the victim of a witch hunt.</description></item><item><title>UNIDENTIFIED: Sumter County Does | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600260/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600260/</guid><description>Podcast Description In August of 1976, the bodies of a young man and woman were found in rural Sumter County, South Carolina. Police would infer a lot from their belongings and the state of their bodies, but more than four decades later, their identities - as well as the identity of their killer - remain a mystery&amp;hellip; BUT the Crime Junkies have a chance to change that.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Reyna Marroquin // Michelle Schroader | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600261/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600261/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we have two stories of women who were murdered and laid to rest, Reyna and Michelle. It would take decades before Reyna would be able to rest in peace and Michelle and her family are still waiting for their day.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CONSPIRACY: North Fox Island &amp; The Oakland County Child Killer Part 2 | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600262/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600262/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part 2 we discuss more suspects in the Oakland County Child Killings and how some or all of them might be connected to North Fox Island.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CONSPIRACY: North Fox Island &amp; The Oakland County Child Killer Part 1 | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600263/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600263/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the 1970s the affluent neighborhoods around Detroit, Michigan were terrorized by a child killer but were the four murders connected to a bigger conspiracy across the state and possible across the nation?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Patti Adkins | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600264/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600264/</guid><description>Podcast Description Patti Adkins had been having a secret relationship with a man from her work. When she went missing in July of 2001, troubling details emerge about their affair and the days leading up to her disappearance.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: The Eastburn Family | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600265/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600265/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1985 Katie Eastburn and two of her daughters were brutally murdered while her husband was away. It would take over 20 years and three trials before their killer would be brought to justice.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SERIAL KILLER: Israel Keyes | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600266/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600266/</guid><description>Podcast Description Israel Keyes is the most terrifying name you have probably never heard of. Officials believe he hunted and killed people all across the US and abroad from as early as 1997 - 2012.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Suzanne Lyall | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600267/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600267/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1998 a 19 year old college student boarded a bus from her job at the mall to go back to her campus dorm room. She was seen getting off the bus around 9:45 at night but was likely abducted somewhere between her bus stop and her dorm. Many theories and suspects have emerged over the years but her location still remains a mystery to this day.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>UPDATE: Killer on the High Bridge | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600268/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600268/</guid><description>Podcast Description On April 22, 2019, the Indiana State Police released new information in the unsolved murder case of Abby &amp;amp; Libby in Delphi, Indiana. Here are the updates you absolutely NEED TO KNOW!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: Kendrick Johnson | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600269/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600269/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2013 a 17-year-old boy&amp;rsquo;s body was found rolled up in a high school gym mat. Local law enforcement was quick to rule it an accident and move on but the family is sure this is a case of murder being covered up.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Timmothy Pitzen | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600270/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600270/</guid><description>Podcast Description On April 3, 2019 someone claiming Timmothy Pitzen approached a stranger in KY and told them he had escaped abductors. The news went wild with this information as the public waited for DNA results to come in. We learned that the man was not Timmothy but it reignited one of the most mysterious disappearance cases in IL history. On this episode of Crime Junkie, we will tell you about the day Timmothy left school with his mom in 2011 and the strange circumstances surrounding their whereabouts after.</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Jerry Michael Williams | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600271/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600271/</guid><description>Podcast Description One day before his anniversary Jerry Michael Williams went for a duck hunting trip on Lake Seminole but never returned home. For years people were convinced he had been eaten by alligators but the truth was much more sinister.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Rachel Cooke | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600272/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600272/</guid><description>Podcast Description 17 years ago, college student Rachel Cooke was visiting her family home in Texas for her winter break. She went out for an early morning run on her regular route but never return. No sign of Rachel has been found in all these years but there was a break in 2017 that could hold all the clues to what happened to her.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Kacie Woody | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600273/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600273/</guid><description>Podcast Description Like many young kids, Kacie Woody had an active online life in 2002 but the ‘friends’ she was meeting online turned out not to be friends at all. Kacie’s story is a cautionary tale that her dad and best friend still champion for, to warn against the dangers of the internet.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Kirsten Hatfield | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600274/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600274/</guid><description>Podcast Description It took decades and DNA science to catch a predator who was able to snatch a girl, Kirsten Hatfield, from her own room in the dead of night.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>UPDATE: April Tinsley &amp; The Monster in Ft. Wayne | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600275/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600275/</guid><description>Podcast Description Captain Kevin Smith of the Indiana State Police granted us an interview to discuss the arrest of April Tinsley&amp;rsquo;s killer who was apprehended in July of 2018 using new genealogy methods. He tells us what it was like finally catching John Miller after 30 years, how they decided to use this method to find him and what this new technology means for the future of law enforcement.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Amy Lynn Bradley | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600276/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600276/</guid><description>Podcast Description In March of 1998 Amy Lynn Bradley and her family set off on what was to be the trip of a lifetime, a full week-long cruise around the Caribbean. But little did they know their dream vacation would turn into a nightmare when Amy goes missing from their stateroom in the early morning hours of March 24, 1998. Over 20 years have passed and clues of her fate are few and far between but there have been credible sightings to suggest that Amy is alive and being held captive.</description></item><item><title>UPDATE: Angela Mischelle Lawless (Interview with Josh Kezer) | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600277/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600277/</guid><description>Podcast Description UPDATE: Josh Kezer, the man who was wrongfully convicted of Angela&amp;rsquo;s murder and then later declared actually innocent, reached out to us to discuss the case. If you are familiar with the case details you can skip to 52:20 just to hear his interview.
In November 1992, Mischelle Lawless was found by passersby deceased in her car with the headlights on and vehicle still running. Police have spent decades trying to piece together what happened to Mischelle that night.</description></item><item><title>MYSTERIOUS DEATH OF: Lynn Messer | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600278/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600278/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2014, Lynn Messer went missing from her 260-acre farm in the middle of the night. When her remains are found on the farm two years later, despite a thorough search, her family and investigators are left wondering if this was a terrible accident or foul play.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CAPTURED: Dr. No | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600279/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 00:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600279/</guid><description>Podcast Description We just found out the man we know as Dr. No has been captured. His name is Samuel Legg III and Brit and Ashley tell you everything we know in the early days of his arrest.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Sneha Philip | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600280/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600280/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sneha Philip was last seen shopping just a couple blocks away from the World Trade Centers on September 11, 2001. She never returned home that night or after the attacks leaving many to speculate whether she died as a result of the terrorist attacks or if she saw the tragedy as an opportunity to walk away from her life and start over.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>WANTED: Austin Yogurt Shop Killer | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600281/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600281/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the early 90&amp;rsquo;s, Austin, TX was turned upside down when four young girls were sexually assaulted, murdered, then set on fire inside an ICBY store. Four men were accused of the crime, but there have always been questions around their guilt. Those questions have only been amplified in recent years as new DNA technology as revealed an unknown perpetrator&amp;rsquo;s DNA at the scene.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Robert Wone | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600282/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600282/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is probably the strangest case of murder we have ever covered here on Crime Junkie. It&amp;rsquo;s the story of Robert Wone who, while staying in a friend&amp;rsquo;s DC guest room, was brutally attacked. But with a staged crime scene, a timeline that doesn&amp;rsquo;t add up, and three people keeping secrets we may never get to the bottom of what happened in the Swann Street house on August 2, 2006.</description></item><item><title>SERIAL KILLER: Dr. No | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600283/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600283/</guid><description>Podcast Description During the 80&amp;rsquo;s and 90&amp;rsquo;s, a serial killer was operating out of Ohio, killing sex workers and leaving their bodies along interstates. Could their killer be a truck driver who called himself Dr. No? And could his crimes extend beyond the Ohio state lines?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>WANTED: Bradford Bishop // Yaser Said | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600284/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600284/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, we have two stories for you of men who are wanted for killing their families. Our first story is about a man named Bradford Bishop, a man who, after not receiving a promotion at work, went home, and methodically killed his entire family. Officials believe he then fled the country and has been living out his days in Europe. Our second story is about a man named Yaser Said who is still on the FBI&amp;rsquo;s 10 most wanted list for murdering his two daughters in the back of his cab.</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Asha Degree | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600285/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600285/</guid><description>Podcast Description In February of 2000, a 9-year-old girl named Asha Degree packed her book bag and tucked it away, waiting for the right time to sneak out of her North Carolina home. To this day, no one knows why she left, or why she was walking along Highway 18 alone around 4 in the morning. And the case would only get more confusing as her belongings start to pop up along that same highway, spaced out over 26 miles, and 18 months.</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: The Watts Family | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600286/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600286/</guid><description>Podcast Description The most recent family annihilator case in the U.S. was incredibly heartbreaking and had every American checking their TVs and smartphones regularly for updates. In this week&amp;rsquo;s episode, we give you our take on the case of Chris Watts who murdered his wife Shanann and their two young daughters, 4-year-old Bella and 3-year old Celeste.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Colleen Orsborn | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600287/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600287/</guid><description>Podcast Description In March of 1984, 15-year-old Colleen Orsborn skips school for a day on the beach but never returns home. Her case was connected to the infamous serial killer, Christopher Wilder, and it took 27 years for her family to find out that Colleen had been located just weeks after she went missing and was near them all along.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SERIAL KILLER: On The Colonial Parkway (Part 2) | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600288/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600288/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part two, we tell you about the murders of Cassandra Lee Hailey, Richard Keith Call, Annamaria Phelps, and Daniel Lauer. Could all four of the murders be connected? Or could there be four killers roaming free?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SERIAL KILLER: On The Colonial Parkway (Part 1) | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600289/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600289/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1986, park rangers near Virginia&amp;rsquo;s Colonial Parkway get notified of a possible traffic accident. When rangers arrive, they are confronted with a violent scene. The deaths of Cathleen Thomas and Rebecca Dowski. Though it is brutal and seemingly unprovoked, the public doesn&amp;rsquo;t start getting truly concerned until two more young people, Robin Edwards and David Knobling, are murdered just off the Parkway.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>UPDATE: Alissa Turney | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600290/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600290/</guid><description>Podcast Description An interview with Alissa&amp;rsquo;s half-sister, Sarah, reveals she no longer thinks her sister ran away. She thinks Alissa was the victim of foul play and she alleges that the perpetrator may be her own father.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Alissa Turney | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600291/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600291/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2001 Mike Turney reported to Phoenix, Arizona police that his 17-year-old step-daughter, Alissa, had run away to California. But 7 years later, a serial killer comes forward with a story that would launch an investigation into her disappearance and make her family fear that Alissa had been a victim of foul play.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Oklahoma Girl Scouts | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600292/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600292/</guid><description>Podcast Description One of Oklahoma&amp;rsquo;s darkest stories. Three young girl scouts are brutally murdered while away at their first night of camp. A Native American man is pinned for the crime but decades later much of the public still wonder if the real culprit eluded capture.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Zachary Bernhardt | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600293/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600293/</guid><description>Podcast Description In September of 2000, Zachary Bernhardt went missing from his mother&amp;rsquo;s bed while she was out for a brief walk. Is his mother hiding something or could Zach have been the victim of a local predator?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: The Camm Family | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600294/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600294/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2000, David Camm, a former Indiana State Trooper, came home from playing basketball to find his entire family had been murdered in their garage. It was only days before he would be charged with the crime and it would take three trials and thirteen years to get close to the truth.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>INFAMOUS: Lizzie Borden | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600295/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600295/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lizzie Borden took an ax Gave her mother 40 whacks When she saw what she had done She gave her father 41 But did she really? In this episode, we tell the story of Lizzie Borden and the other suspects in the case who you&amp;rsquo;ve probably never heard of.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CONSPIRACY: Women in the U.S. Military | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600296/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600296/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2010, statistics came out that 120 female U.S. soldiers stationed in Iraq had died. Half of those deaths were reported to be non-combat related. 30 those non-combat related deaths were ruled suicides, but there is evidence to suggest many of them may have actually been murders. In this episode, we dive into the case of LaVena Johnson and other women of the U.S. military who died very suspicious deaths during Operation Iraqi Freedom.</description></item><item><title>EXPERT ON: Domestic Violence | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600297/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600297/</guid><description>Podcast Description In our last episode, we talked about Susan Powell who was a victim of domestic violence. Many of her friends talked about Josh&amp;rsquo;s strange behavior and the recalled things that should have been warning signs. Today we talk to an expert on the topic, Ashley Bendiksen. She will tell us her story of survival, what signs to watch out for and how to safely leave a toxic relationship. Ashley Bendiksen is an acclaimed survivor speaker and award-winning activist, speaking and training nationally on the topics of domestic violence, teen dating violence, sexual assault, and bystander intervention.</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: The Powell Family | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600298/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600298/</guid><description>Podcast Description During a blizzard on December 6, 2009 Josh Powell Claims to have taken his two young sons, ages 2 and 4, camping. When he returned home he finds friends and family frantically searching for them. They&amp;rsquo;re all relieved when he and the boys arrive safely. But where is Susan? Josh becomes a prime suspect in her disappearance but when the system fails to prove a case against him and protect his kids he turns on them and kills them in an unimaginably brutal fashion.</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Angela Savage | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600299/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600299/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sometime after dropping off her young daughter at the school bus, Angela Savage and her 6-month-old son were abducted. Angela&amp;rsquo;s body would eventually be found on a dirt path near her home, having been assaulted, tied up and left with no shoes. Despite being a small community the case goes cold for almost 30 years until a strange incident connects Angela&amp;rsquo;s murder to the death of another young girl and police are able to solve the case.</description></item><item><title>SERIAL KILLER: Bible John | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600300/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600300/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the late 1960s, three women were murdered after attending the same nightclub. But aside from their location, all three women had something very specific in common. Was this thing they had in common the reason they were killed or was their killer, a man now known as Bible John, after them because they were frequenting a nightclub known for hookups and infidelity? It is now decades later and police are still looking for a red-haired man last seen with all three women.</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Danielle "Gabby" Akers | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600301/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600301/</guid><description>Podcast Description In April of 2016, Danielle &amp;ldquo;Gabby&amp;rdquo; Akers&amp;rsquo;s body was found in a creek bed 60 miles from her home. She had no clothes or personal belongings with her and it&amp;rsquo;s still unknown how she got so far from home without a vehicle. The family believes that someone murdered Gabby, but the investigation has stalled and no major media outlets are covering the case. The family is looking for some kind of closure and we hope someone listening to this episode may know something about what happened to Gabby.</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: The Coleman Family | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600302/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 08:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600302/</guid><description>Podcast Description When the head of security for a cutting edge televangelist starts getting threatening emails, no one seems too concerned. But as those threats escalate and eventually come to fruition, law enforcement isn&amp;rsquo;t convinced that everything is as it appears.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Chandra Levy | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600303/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 08:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600303/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a political intern goes missing, all eyes turn towards her hometown congressman. But when that lead dries up, and other women are being attacked, who is really to blame?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>WANTED: Answers from a Deputy | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600304/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600304/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Terrance Williams goes missing, most law enforcement officers consider him a low-priority; He wanted, or needed, to disappear. But when his last known location is with Deputy Steven Calkins, suspicions are raised as to whether or not this is a random disappearance, or a plotted out crime.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Leah Roberts | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600305/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 08:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600305/</guid><description>Podcast Description After friends and family can&amp;rsquo;t get ahold of her for days in a row, they decide that college student Leah Roberts is missing. Two weeks later, her car is found, and her loved ones are ready to have answers&amp;hellip; But will they get the answers they crave?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SERIAL KILLER: Todd Kohlhepp | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600306/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 11:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600306/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our Fan Club supporters will be happy to note that today, we are covering the multiple murders committed by Todd Kohlhepp. This man lured literally countless people to his property, only to systematically torture and murder them. To find out more about one of his possible victims, check out our bonus episode about the disappearance of Tammy Kingery in our fan club.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>IF I GO MISSING: Tanya Rider | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600307/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 07:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600307/</guid><description>Podcast Description When hard-working Tanya Rider misses two shifts and is late for a third, her husband knows something is wrong. But can he convince the local sheriff&amp;rsquo;s department to take her disappearance seriously? ALSO IN THIS EPISODE: What is an &amp;ldquo;If I Go Missing&amp;rdquo; folder and why do I need one?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Barbara Nantais &amp; Claire Hough | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600308/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 07:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600308/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the dreamy summers of southern California, two murders happen within yards of each other, but a decade apart. Questions echo throughout these cases. Are they connected? Can DNA help solve these cases? Or does it just muddle the facts even more?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>WHITE COLLAR: The Dalkon Shield | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600309/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600309/</guid><description>Podcast Description With the permission from the team over at Swindled Podcast, we are covering one of their best True Crime stories. It’s a story of lies&amp;hellip;. cover-ups&amp;hellip; and murder. But murder that was done out in the open while a company actually profited from women’s deaths. In today’s episode, we are discussing the Dalkon Shield, an IUD that killed at least twenty women, hurt hundreds of thousands, and is still being used overseas today Huge thanks to Swindled Podcast for their research into this episode.</description></item><item><title>CAPTURED: Monster in Fort Wayne | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600310/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 18:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600310/</guid><description>Podcast Description On July 15, 2018 police finally made an arrest in the 30-year unsolved murder of April Marie Tinsley. In this breaking clip, Ashley calls Brit to tell her the news.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Angela Mischelle Lawless | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600311/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600311/</guid><description>Podcast Description In November 1992, Mischelle Lawless was found by passersbys deceased in her car with the headlights on and the vehicle still running. Police have spent decades trying to piece together what happened to Mischelle that night. Who would she have pulled over for? Where was she headed? And even though a man served 16 years for her murder the current sheriff is convinced they still have not captured Mischelle&amp;rsquo;s killer and it could all be tied back to the man&amp;hellip; or men&amp;hellip; who initially found her car.</description></item><item><title>CONSPIRACY: The Women of Juarez | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600312/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600312/</guid><description>Podcast Description Since 1993, women in Juarez, Mexico have been dying violent deaths. Is this the work of one killer or multiple? Also, why did the state police work so hard to convince the public that it was the work of a man who was incarcerated, while many of the murders were still being committed?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SERIAL KILLER: The Claremont Killer | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600313/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600313/</guid><description>Podcast Description Since 1996, people in Claremont had been looking over their shoulders when they go out for a night on the town. Over the span of a few years, three girls were taken from the same place in nearly identical fashions. Many years later, those crimes would be connected to other attacks dating back to 1988. And somehow, in 2016, a man was arrested for these crimes&amp;hellip; But we still don&amp;rsquo;t know exactly how police got his name.</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Sage Smith | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600314/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600314/</guid><description>Podcast Description On November 20, 2012, Sage Smith left her home at 5:30 for a date. She was seen alone at 6:30 talking to someone on the phone and then possibly sighted one more time at 7:00 at a cafe, again alone. Her father and friends were advocates and attempted to investigate her disappearance on their own, but ended up in the same place where the police ended up. At a dead end.</description></item><item><title>UPDATE: Katelin Akens | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600315/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 06:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600315/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this update episode, Ashley gets the chance to talk to Lisa, Katelin&amp;rsquo;s mom, about Katelin&amp;rsquo;s case, and like, you all asked&amp;hellip; What about Katelin&amp;rsquo;s step-father?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Sylvia Likens | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600316/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600316/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sylvia was a happy, beautiful 16-year-old when her parents left her and her sister in the care of Gertrude Baniszewski while they went on the road for work. But, within a few short months, Sylvia was beaten, humiliated, and ultimately left to die from neglect and severe abuse, inflicted by not only Gertrude, but the Baniszewski children, and neighborhood kids as well.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SERIAL KILLER: The Green River Killer | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600317/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600317/</guid><description>Podcast Description Through the &amp;rsquo;80s &amp;amp; &amp;rsquo;90s, women in the state of Washington were turning up dead. First, along the Green River, then in other clusters throughout the state and even into Portland, Oregon. Not only had these women been murdered but their killer would re-visit their corpses and sexually assault them multiple times until their corpses were fully decomposed and consumed by maggots. A man named Gary Ridgeway had been pointed out by a number of witnesses as being the Green River Killer but police were unable to make an arrest until DNA connected him to four crime scenes in 2001 – two decades and at least 49 victims later.</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Misty Copsey | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600318/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600318/</guid><description>Podcast Description In September of 1992, a young teenager named Misty Copsey went missing after visiting the local fair in Puyallup, Washington with her best friend. Almost 26 years have passed and all we have are a handful of suspicious suspects and a pair of jeans found at a site that could be linked to a serial killer. Plus, a rogue private citizen, whose efforts to try to solve the case have become an obsession, that might actually be distracting from the real investigation.</description></item><item><title>CAPTURED: Ashley Freeman and Lauria Bible's Killer | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600319/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 13:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600319/</guid><description>Podcast Description In April of 2018, we were all talking about the capture of the Gold State Killer but did you know another long-time cold case was solved that same week? On December 29, 1999, best friends Lauria Bible and Ashley Freeman were having a sleepover at Ashley&amp;rsquo;s house. Sometime in the early morning hours of December 30th, Ashley&amp;rsquo;s parents were murdered and their home set on fire. The two girls were never seen again.</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Amber Tuccaro // Henry McCabe | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600320/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600320/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we tell you not one but two stories that have been underreported despite the terrifying audio capture shortly before each of their deaths.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Bethany Decker | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600321/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 03:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600321/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2011, Bethany Decker&amp;rsquo;s life was far from easy. As a young wife and mother with a husband overseas in the military, things were strained. When her husband comes back for a short leave, Bethany shares some shocking news and then disappears, never to be seen again.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CAPTURED: The Golden State Killer | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600322/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 12:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600322/</guid><description>Podcast Description On April 25th, 2018, a decades-long search for the man believed to be the Visalia Ransacker, the East Area Rapist, the Original Night Stalker, and the Golden State Killer was identified and apprehended by authorities. We spoke with Criminology Podcast&amp;rsquo;s Mike Morford, who took us through some of the most notable factors of the crimes and arrest, and what this means for cold cases everywhere.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Kenia Monge | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600323/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 03:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600323/</guid><description>Podcast Description 19-year-old Kenia Monge went missing in downtown Denver on April 1, 2011. When Kenia&amp;rsquo;s stepdad finds an eerie text message from a stranger on her phone, it leads him and police right to her killer. However, without Kenia&amp;rsquo;s body and no clue where she might be the only thing they could do was wait for the man to strike again.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SERIAL KILLER: L.I.S.K. | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600324/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 03:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600324/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a young escort goes missing after an outcall on Long Island in 2010, no one bothers to search for her. No one except a single detective and his dog who while looking, stumble upon the burial ground of a serial killer&amp;hellip; or&amp;hellip; killers? What unfolds is one of America&amp;rsquo;s greatest unsolved mysteries.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>ADNAN: What Serial Didn't Tell You | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600325/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 03:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600325/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hundreds of millions of people tuned into Serial season one back in 2014. Sarah Koenig told us all about the story of 18-year-old high school senior Hae Min Lee who disappeared on January 13th, 1999. Hae&amp;rsquo;s body was later found in Leakin Park, and not too long after the discovery of her body, police zeroed in on their prime suspect: Adnan Syed. Sarah took us all through 12 episodes of &amp;ldquo;Did he or didn&amp;rsquo;t he?</description></item><item><title>UPDATE: Monster in Fort Wayne, Indiana | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600326/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 07:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600326/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this bonus episode, we get the opportunity to talk with April Tinsley’s mom, Janet, about the investigation into her daughter’s murder and the torment April&amp;rsquo;s killer has put her family, and the city of Fort Wayne through. Be sure to listen to episode 18, WANTED: Monster in Fort Wayne, Indiana, before you listen to this update episode. Source: Interview with Janet Tinsley conducted by Ashley Flowers
Transcript</description></item><item><title>WANTED: Monster in Fort Wayne, Indiana | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600327/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 03:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600327/</guid><description>Podcast Description Thirty years ago this week, a little girl in Fort Wayne, Indiana, was abducted, sexually assaulted, murdered and now, forgotten by everyone. It is one of the most horrific crimes we&amp;rsquo;ve ever researched, and yet when we ask people if they know about April Tinsley, we only get blank stares. This man, who police believed was local, not only committed the crime, but taunted police and the community for 16 years after.</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Kiplyn Davis | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600328/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 00:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600328/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1995, one of our listeners from Kentucky was high school pen pals with a girl named Kiplyn Davis from Spanish Fork, Utah, when one day the Spanish Fork Police called looking for answers. Kiplyn had gone missing. Kiplyn&amp;rsquo;s story takes over 16 years to unfold and even though a few young men have been accused of and pled guilty to murder, no one has ever found Kiplyn or her remains.</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: The Longo Family | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600329/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 00:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600329/</guid><description>Podcast Description What makes a seemingly normal family man snap, murder his entire family, and assume a new identity in Mexico? Christian Longo was a husband, and father of three kids, who moved his family to Oregon to escape legal and money trouble he had accrued back in Michigan. But the new start didn&amp;rsquo;t take away the pressure of supporting a family on a part-time, minimum wage income. One December day, Christian&amp;rsquo;s family is found in the most horrific ways and Christian is nowhere to be found.</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Katelin Akens | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600330/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 00:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600330/</guid><description>Podcast Description In December of 2015, Katelin was to board a plane from VA to AZ. She texted her mom that she made it to the airport and her phone was dying, so she would text later. But Katelin never made it on that flight and she has never been seen since. The investigation into her disappearance will make you question everything about Katelin&amp;rsquo;s last day and by the end, you won&amp;rsquo;t know who&amp;rsquo;s account can be trusted.</description></item><item><title>SERIAL KILLER: Herb Baumeister | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600331/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 00:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600331/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the late &amp;rsquo;90s, Indianapolis was rocked when it was found out that a local businessman was murdering gay men and burying them on his 15-acre estate called Fox Hollow Farms.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>UPDATE: Niqui McCown | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600332/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 01:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600332/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this bonus episode we get the opportunity to talk with Niqui McCown’s daughter, Payton, and get all our left over questions from episode one answered!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CONSPIRACY: Bardstown, Kentucky | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600333/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 00:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600333/</guid><description>Podcast Description A 35-year-old woman named Crystal Rogers went missing from Bardstown, KY back in 2015. Her car was found on the side of a busy parkway with a flat tire, keys, wallet, and phone still inside. Just 16 months later, while searching for answers, Crystal&amp;rsquo;s father is murdered in cold blood. Now, people are wondering if these two crimes are connected to a bigger conspiracy that started with the murder of a police officer in 2013.</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Tent Girl | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600334/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 00:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600334/</guid><description>Podcast Description On May 17, 1968, a woman was found in the woods, murdered and wrapped in tent fabric. For over 30 years she remained unidentified in a Kentucky grave with a donated headstone that bore the name &amp;ldquo;Tent Girl&amp;rdquo;. But &amp;rsquo;90s internet and a superhero named Todd come together to give this girl a name and give her family the answers they waited so many decades for.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>WANTED: Killer on the High Bridge | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600335/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 00:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600335/</guid><description>Podcast Description On February 13th, 2017, Abby Williams and Libby German went for a hike near the Monon High Bridge, in Delphi, Indiana. After Libby posted a Snapchat photo of Abby at 2:07 pm, the girls were never seen alive again. Searchers found their bodies near a creek parallel to the bridge less than 24 hours later on Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day. The investigation that has since ensued has left an entire nation searching for the Killer on the High Bridge.</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Amy Weidner | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600336/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 00:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600336/</guid><description>Podcast Description A teenage mother stays home from school one day with her daughter because she isn&amp;rsquo;t feeling well. Just a few hours after her family leaves the house she is brutally attacked. Surely it had to be someone she knew. Did they know she would be home that day? It is a case that goes cold for nearly two decades before someone unexpected comes in and cracks the case wide open.</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Bryce Laspisa | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600337/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 00:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600337/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bryce Laspisa started acting strange on August 27, 2013. Just a couple of days into his sophomore year, friends started to become concerned about his unusual behavior. He planned a trip home to visit his parents and what should have been a 7-hour journey turns into 30-hours of mystery that leave police and Bryce&amp;rsquo;s family baffled when on August 30th at 5:30 am Bryce&amp;rsquo;s vehicle is found overturned with no sign of Bryce.</description></item><item><title>SERIAL KILLER: Shawn Grate | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600338/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 00:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600338/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shawn Grate is currently awaiting trial in Ohio for two counts of murder but his admitted body count is much more. From 2005 - 2016 he terrorized vulnerable women of Ohio but police had no idea. Shawn Grate murdered women police didn&amp;rsquo;t even consider missing and it wasn&amp;rsquo;t until one day in September when an unthinkable call to 911 changed everything.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Karina Holmer | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600339/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 00:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600339/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1996, Boston saw one of the most brutal, and now notorious, murders of their city. Over 20 years later, not many people outside of Boston know the name of the Swedish nanny who was brutally murdered, dismembered and thrown away with the garbage on an early August morning. Karina had secrets and shortly before her death she wrote a letter to her friend in Sweden and shared something that would forever haunt those who learn about this case.</description></item><item><title>WANTED: Robert Fisher | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600340/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 00:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600340/</guid><description>Podcast Description Robert William Fisher is an American fugitive wanted for the murder of his wife and two children. Their home in Scottsdale, Arizona was blown up on April 10, 2001, in an attempt to cover up the crimes. However, no one has seen or heard from Robert since before his family was murdered. Was he the one who killed them? Or could he be a victim too?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>SERIAL KILLER: The West Mesa Serial Killer | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600341/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600341/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy New Year! For our first episode of 2018, we outline the still-unsolved murders of the West Mesa Serial Killer **FYI: We&amp;rsquo;ve marked this episode as explicit because there are a couple of f-bombs. Sorry! We&amp;rsquo;ll do better next time, I promise!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Laci Peterson - Part Two | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600342/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2017 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600342/</guid><description>Podcast Description The story everyone thinks they know&amp;hellip; but do you really? In part two, we discuss the continued focus on Scott as a suspect in the disappearance and murder of his wife, Laci.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MURDERED: Laci Peterson | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600343/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600343/</guid><description>Podcast Description The story everyone thinks they know&amp;hellip; but do you really? In part one we cover Laci’s disappearance and the suspicion that fell on her husband Scott Peterson.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MISSING: Niqui McCown | Crime Junkie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7076600344/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7076600344/</guid><description>Podcast Description The story of an Indiana woman who disappears from a laundry mat only weeks before her wedding.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>