<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Do You F*cking Mind? on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/do-you-fcking-mind/</link><description>Recent content in Do You F*cking Mind? on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 13:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/do-you-fcking-mind/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>270. Self inconsistency, self conflict and finding your authentic self | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830268/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830268/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you live a life that’s true to your authentic self? In this episode I’m exploring the concept of the authentic self, what it means to be happy and how you can tap into it more effectively. I’m also jumping into the idea of self inconsistency and self conflict. Together these concepts will help you understand more about what it is that makes you happy, and how to live that life more authentically.</description></item><item><title>269. Imposter Syndrome and The Psychology of Your 20s with Jemma Sbeg | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830001/</guid><description>Podcast Description My beautiful beans I’m joined by the amazing Jemma Sbeg, host of the podcast The Psychology of Your 20s. We’re talking all about quarter-life-crises, imposter syndrome, finding friends, and figuring your shit out.
LINKS:
Listen to The Psychology of Your 20s via https://linktr.ee/thepsychologyofyour20s
Follow @jemmasbeg on IG
Check out @thatpsychologypodcast on IG
Follow @dyfmpodcast on IG Follow @alexispredez on IG Join the DYFM Facebook Group https://bit.ly/dyfm-group .
Follow @listnrentertainment on IG CREDITS</description></item><item><title>268. A chat with The Weekend Briefing allll about DYFM | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830002/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830002/</guid><description>Podcast Description A different kind of episode today! We're jumping into an interview I did with Antoinette Lattouff from The Weekend Briefing - where I make a pretty big announcement about something coming in 2024!! LINKS:
Listen to The Briefing podcast https://spoti.fi/3R9E8C1 .
Follow @thebriefingpodcast on IG Follow @dyfmpodcast on IG Follow @alexispredez on IG Join the DYFM Facebook Group https://bit.ly/dyfm-group .
Follow @listnrentertainment on IG CREDITS
Host: Alexis Fernandez Executive Producer &amp;amp; Editor: Elise Cooper</description></item><item><title>267. 8 Steps to Overcome Burnout | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830003/</guid><description>Podcast Description What actually IS burnout and how can you get through it/over it. I’m going to take you through my 8 steps to overcome it and how to differentiate stress from burnout.
BRAIN FACT:
The impact of alcohol on sleep and it’s interaction with your neurochemistry when sleeping. LISTENER QUESTION:
A bean gets in touch with what sounds like a very unhealthy relationship, asking for my advice on whether they should stay together or go their separate ways.</description></item><item><title>266. Rebuilding yourself after divorce and heartbreak with Renee Chagoury | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830004/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830004/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do you rebuild your identity after a divorce? How do you find yourself after breakup with children? Renee Chagoury is one of my oldest mates, a single mum of two girls, a schoolteacher and the founder of Sole Sisters Run Club. Her journey of rebuilding herself after a breakup instils hope that there is something else out there that you can do from the inside out that will make you a better person.</description></item><item><title>265. How to make the rest of the year the BEST of the year | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830005/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do you make the best of the rest of the year? Today’s episode is all about how to feel like you have milked the last few weeks of out of life. There is so much that you can do in this final month of to really make the most of it.
Brain Fact: The story of the woman who had a worm in her brain! The 4 ways you can get a parasite living inside you (skip ahead to around 11 minutes if you’re squeamish)</description></item><item><title>264. Are you getting used to a life you don't want? | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830006/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830006/</guid><description>Podcast Description This ep is a juicy one. I’m talking about getting comfortable because it’s easy, rather than challenging and pushing yourself toward a life you actually want.
We’re talking about the signs you’re slipping into a pattern, living up to someone else’s ideals instead of your own, not knowing what you want, feeling lost and frustrated, and how to start to turn it all around.
Listener Question:
I’ve struggled to set boundaries my whole life and people often walk all over me.</description></item><item><title>263. Dealing with the pressure of having it all figured out by 30 | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why does turning 30 come with so much pressure to have your shit together? I’m going to explore WHY we feel like we need to have our life sorted by 30, and how to get out of that comparison loop and just live your life no matter your age or stage.
Listener Question:
I'm from England but have established a life in Australia. My long distance boyfriend has put it to me that I should come back to England to start our lives together and I don't know what to do.</description></item><item><title>262. How to rewrite your reputation | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830008/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Let's talk reputation my beans: what it is, how you get one and MOST importantly how you can change your reputation if you've got a baaad one.
Brain Fact: The Ceiling Effect in pharmacology .
Listener Question:
Me and an ex bestie had a falling out a few years ago but I still have to interact with them in group settings. It’s hard but I do it cause I don’t wanna miss out on group things with mates.</description></item><item><title>261. Get A Grip with Abbie Chatfield: Trolling, Learning and Being a Better Friend | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830009/</guid><description>Podcast Description I'm joined by the QUEEN of podcasting and social media and being hot and clever – Abbie Chatfield.
I really wanted to dive into a chat all about being trolled on social media, navigating friendships, and how to talk to someone whose beliefs are SO different to your own.
LINKS:
Listen to It’s A Lot with Abbie Chatfield https://linktr.ee/itsalotpod .
Follow @itsalotpod on Instagram https://bit.ly/itsalot-instagram .
Listen to Abbie’s podcast episode with her mum about the little cockroach https://bit.</description></item><item><title>260. How to stop a grudge from ruining your relationships | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830010/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830010/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you're holding grudges in a relationship, if you're keeping score for when someone let you down, I want you to STOP. Here's how to stop grudges getting in the way of forming long lasting, meaningful relationships. BRAIN FACT:
Nerve Growth Factor (NGF): A type of protein that places a key role in growth, development, and the maintenance of nerve cells in the nervous system.
EXTRA READING
Nerve Growth Factor Explained from Science Direct https://bit.</description></item><item><title>259. 6 ways to boost your self-worth | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Like Ru Paul said - If you can't love yourself how in the hell you gonna love somebody else can I get an AMEN up in here?!
In this episode I’m refreshing my tips for boosting your self-worth to live the bad ass life you deserve.
BRAIN FACT:
RBD: REM sleep disordered: characterised by the absence of normal muscle atonia during REM sleep
EXTRA READING
REM Behaviour Disorder explainer from Stanford Medicine: Health Care - https://shc.</description></item><item><title>258. Turning Desperation into Attraction: How to get what you REALLY want | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830012/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 13:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830012/</guid><description>Podcast Description My beautiful BEANS this episode we're diving into how to turn your desperation into true attraction; we're talking in romantic relationships, your career, your friendships.
BRAIN FACT:
How does local anaesthetic work? Did you know that cocaine was one of the first local anaesthetics discovered and used!
EXTRA READING
Read 'Basic pharmacology of local anaesthetics' from BJA Education https://bit.ly/3SqoRPA .
Watch this explainer on how local anaesthetic works from Armando Hasudangan on YouTube https://bit.</description></item><item><title>257. The neuroscience of ketamine and it's effects on depression | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why is Ketamine being used to treat depression and anhedonia? In this science-y episode I'm going through the neuroscience of Ketamine and the brain, the chemical makeup of the drug, and why it's being used in many trials to treat people with treatment resistant depression and anhedonia.
BRAIN FACT:
ECT therapy – what is It, how does it work, what type of mental disorders is it used as a treatment for.</description></item><item><title>256. Fave Ep: You're setting the bar TOO low | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830014/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you know if you are setting the bar too low for yourself, your relationships and your career / abilities? In this episode, I cover what happens when you do that, and why it is important to turn that around so you can start expecting and receiving more out of life.
Brain Fact: Explaining Urbach-Wiethe disease. of people who don't experience the physiological aspects of the fear response.</description></item><item><title>255. 10 Years of Friendship with Steph Claire Smith and Laura Henshaw | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830015/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adult friendships can be harrrrrd – and being in business with a mate is even harder. In this episode I’m joined by two friends who seem to have it figured out! Steph Claire Smith and Laura Henshaw, founders of KIC – the wellbeing and lifestyle community that’s an app and a podcast (kinda like us!). They talk all about the friendship, their relationships with their bodies, and how they got to where they are today.</description></item><item><title>Mini Ep: A note from Alexis | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830016/</guid><description>Podcast Description I’m on holidays beans! For some listening to fill your ears check out some of your favourite episodes below;
'Why discipline is the ticket to the life you want'
'Chase change, don’t let change chase you'
'10 things I learnt in my 20s'
'10 ways to show up for yourself'
'Motivation, Purpose and Body Image'
'Self love – finding your worth' LINKS
Send your Listener question to info@dyfmpod.com Join DYFM + https://bit.</description></item><item><title>253. Missed Opportunities: Becoming OK with the shots you didn't take | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830017/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830017/</guid><description>Podcast Description You can spend your whole life thinking about a bad decision that you mad . or the opportunity you didn’t take, or mistakes you made. In fact most people do! It can be crippling, so I want to take you through the ways you can live a life without regret, and reclaim contentment in your decisions.
PET LOVE: Watch 'Lupin' on Netflix https://bit.ly/lupin-trailer .
SBS Podcasts ‘Learn a Language’ https://bit.</description></item><item><title>252. Self Awareness: You can't change what you won't acknowledge | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830018/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why do we struggle to be aware of ourselves? It’s hard to turn the lense on yourself, particularly during the bad shit. I’m going to take you through how to practice self awareness and level up your life (and how to stop being the kind of person to throw blame instead of apologise).
Pet Love: Listen to The Dream Podcast https://bit.ly/thedream-podcast .
Brain Fact: Exploring Corpus Callosum https://bit.ly/corpus-callosum .</description></item><item><title>251. Your Break-Up Questions Answered | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830019/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830019/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week I'm diving DEEP into your questions beans – and there's a breakup theme coming through!
These are the topics/listener questions I’m covering;
How to commit to breaking up with someone who doesn't take you seriously when you try to break up with them
Feeling regret over ending a relationship once an ex has a new partner
Going through a difficult break up
An unhealthy sister-in-law relationship
LINKS</description></item><item><title>250. The science of overthinking and how to overcome it | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Overthinking? Me? Never (lol absolutely yes). I’m going to take you through what’s happening in your brain when you’re overthinking. Plus I’ll give you some steps for how to overcome it and get out of that overthinking spiral.
Listener Question: I’ve repeatedly been excluded from group gatherings of my boyfriend’s friends. Is this normal? And how do I figure out if I’m being left out on purpose or if it’s just a misunderstanding.</description></item><item><title>249. Understanding sunk cost fallacy &amp; why it's screwing you | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830021/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830021/</guid><description>Podcast Description The phrase Sunk Cost Fallacy is going to help you stop wasting your time on shit that doesn’t work. In this episode I’m explaining this concept where you keep putting money and time and effort into something that isn’t working, but you don’t want to quite cause of all the effort you’ve already put in.
Brain Fact: Cyclooxegenase and reducing pain and inflamation in the body Listener Question: I have been cheating on my wife for 7 years, and the woman I was cheating with recently broke up with me.</description></item><item><title>248. You're doing closure wrong: Here's how to move on | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hello my beautiful beans! In this episode I’m gunna talk you through how to get closure in your life; primarily about romantic relationships but you could also apply a lot of this to friendships or even losing a job or opportunity.
Brain Fact: Borderline Personality Disorder
Listener Question: My ex has said they want to keep the door open on our relationship now that we've broken up. What should I do?</description></item><item><title>247. Narcissistic parents and in-laws: How to spot them and deal with them | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830023/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830023/</guid><description>Podcast Description What makes someone a narcissist? What's the difference between a covert and overt narcissist? and how, oh HOW, do you handle a relationship with a narcissist - particularly narcissistic parents and in-laws; This is what I'm diving into in this episode. Then I get into a listener question about whether or not to move cities to be with a partner when being mid-way through tertiary study. Specifically how to tell if you actually want to move for yourself and not just because your partner is somewhere you aren't.</description></item><item><title>246. Dealing with pathological &amp; compulsive liars | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830024/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lying is normal, but lying pathologically is NOT. I got a listener question specifically around dealing with a liar so I'll jump off with that and then get into the episode of today.
Brain fact: Photobleaching your rods (what happens when you suddenly go into a bright light)
Read about Rhodopsin https://www.britannica.com/science/rhodopsin See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>245. Histrionic personality disorder, weird MIL vibes, co-dependent relationship advice, moving on from a cheater: Answering Your Questions | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830025/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830025/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the episode of today I'm explaining HPD or Histrionic Personality Disorder. And I answer 5 of your questions covering a difficult mother in law relationship, a sister who betrayed trust, assessing a relationship as co-dependent and how to readjust, struggling to move on from an ex-fiance who cheated - when you have a kid together, and finally is it worth telling your friend you're crushing on them when they have a partner.</description></item><item><title>244. How to keep a promise to yourself | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830026/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode is all about how to make a commitment to yourself and stick to it, and why you're setting yourself up to fail (and it's not necessarily your fault).
Brain Fact: Troxler's Fading https://bit.ly/troxlersfading-dyfm .
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>243. Limit the amount of people that owe you and liberate yourself | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830027/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode I talk about why you should limit the amount of people that owe you. Why feeling that someone owes you something can be very detrimental for your happiness, self love and productivity and what you can do to stop feeling this way TODAY. Brain Fact : Lateral Inhibition (AAANNNDDD a fun optical illusion for you to try) See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>242. The illusion of endless options on dating apps and why it can be so harmful | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830028/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Let's talk about dating apps. I asked you guys what you thought about them, the good and the bad. I pulled all this information together to had a chat about where dating apps fall short and why to not get too invested in them and how to not feel so hurt by them when things don't go well for you. I also go over your best and worst dating app situations and some of them are seriously F*****D!</description></item><item><title>241. Leaving someone is not giving up on them | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830029/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830029/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this ep I go over the difference between problems that are 'joint' and 'individual' in a relationship. How to let go of the guilt of leaving a relationship and how to feel more empowered to make the right decision around leaving or staying in a relationship. Brain Fact : Rejection Sensitive Dysphoria See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>240. Why discipline is your ticket to the life you want | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830030/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Okay time to talk about all things discipline! Why you need it, why it will make your life so much better and more fulfilling and why it will increase your self love and improve your relationship with yourself exponentially! Brain Fact : Joy Milne, the woman who can smell Parkinson's
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>239. Green flags to look for in your day | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830031/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830031/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode goes over a bunch of green flags to lean into to improve your overall happiness, productivity, relationships and peace of mind. Brain Fact : Hangovers on the brain See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>238. You do not have to be the bigger person. Your peace of mind comes first | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830032/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830032/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today's ep I go over what it means to be the bigger person, when it is good and when it is not helpful to your own peace of mind or mental health. Sometimes being the bigger person may mean keeping the wrong people in your life just to 'save face' and this could mean your boundaries keep getting crossed and you struggle to see growth in your healing journey.</description></item><item><title>237. How to overcome retroactive jealousy and overthinking in a relationship (E) | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830033/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 20:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830033/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode I cover how to deal with feelings of retroactive jealousy and overthinking in a relationship, and how overcoming these feelings will improve the quality of your relationship not only with your partner but with yourself. When you master this, you will feel more confident within yourself and happier in your skin.
(Encore episode) See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>236. Determine your own value and never look for it in other places again | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830034/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 20:00:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830034/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode I break down the difference between perceived value and actual value. How to stop letting other people determine your value and how to use the idea of value exchange and the principal of effort + sacrifice to turn everything around and start determining your own value.
Brain Fact : Zahavian signal
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>235. Chase change, don’t let change chase you | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830035/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 20:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830035/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s episode I talk about my favorite statement and one I try and live by all the time. How to become someone who is adaptable and resilient to change and loss and how to gain so much more along the way. I will talk about how to become someone who takes control of the changes in their life, instead of leading a life where you are only reactive to the things that happen to you and end up feeling powerless to external situations.</description></item><item><title>234. The difference between drive and self-control and how to have both | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830036/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 20:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830036/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s episode I break down what drive is compared to self control, how to know where your strengths are and where you weaknesses are and then I give you tools to help create a balance between the two.
Brain Fact: Changing your surroundings to improve your focus
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>233. Boundaries vs Controlling behaviour AND how to set healthy boundaries to improve your self love | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830037/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 20:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830037/</guid><description>Podcast Description There is so much to talk about on today's episode!
I have two main categories.
How to know the difference between a boundary and a controlling behaviour (and how to know if it is being done to you)
How to be able to set boundaries while keeping your walls down and in turn, helping you increase your self love + confidence
Brain Fact: Reverse Psychology
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>232. Feeling like you have plateaued? Try this to level up! | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830038/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 20:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hello! Today's episode is all about how to change things up and feel back on track and kicking goals when you are feeling a bit flat or like everything has plateaued in your life and doesn't excite you like it used to. I give you some tips and ways to approach things differently.
Brain Fact : Noise induced hearing loss
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>231. Dealing with anxious and stressful thoughts in 5 steps | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830039/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 20:00:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830039/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode I take you through a five step process to help you get your anxious or spiralling thoughts under control, so your emotions don't end up controlling you and your day.
Brain Fact : Carbon monoxide poisoning
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>230. How to get over the fear of your partner cheating on you or falling for someone else | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830040/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 20:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830040/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode dives deep into dealing with fearful emotions around if your partner is ever going to fall for someone else, or cheat on you or flirt with someone else. I will go into how to process these thoughts, and what to think about when this happens to make it feel less threatening. And then of course I talk about your own relationship with yourself and how that impacts these feelings of fear.</description></item><item><title>229. Why self esteem and purpose are linked and 4 ways to maximize it | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830041/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 20:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830041/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode I go over 4 ways to understand how tapping into your purpose and understanding what that is can completely transform your self esteem and significantly improve your relationship with yourself.
Brain Fact : The Reflex Arc
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>228. Life advice to get you through the week | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830042/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 20:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830042/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode I dive into all kinds of scenarios and give you advice from toxic parents, unbearable heartbreak, how to not be so anxiously avoidant when in the dating scene and MORE. Thank you for all the listener questions sent in!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>227. 5 ways to feel more empowered DAILY | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830043/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 20:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today I talk all about self empowerment and how to take control of situations NOW to feel like you have more of a say in your future.
I give 5 simple things to do each day to start to feel more empowered.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>226. Its not about what you can do, its what you will do. 6 steps to DO that thing | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830044/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 20:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830044/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode I go over 6 steps to help you go from thinking you 'COULD' do something to actually doing it. There is so much already at your disposal and for one reason or another you just are not maximising your abilities. This ep aims to change that for you. Brain Fact : Munchausen Syndrome / by proxy See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>225. Do these 7 things NOW to increase your self-confidence | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830045/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 03:14:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830045/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is an encore episode of ep 147. One of my all time most useful episodes. Every week I touch on the importance of your relationship with your self and how to improve it, and this episode encompasses so much of what I touch on in most episodes.
Also, it has one of my all time favourite brain facts.
Brain Fact : Water intoxication
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>224. You are more than enough. How to feel it (6 tips) | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830046/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 20:00:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830046/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this ep I talk about when you feel down on yourself, and feel like something is lacking or that you are 'not enough'. when this happens you start to feel more self critical in all areas in your life not just the one area that caused you to feel this way, and this can then affect your own relationship with yourself.
I go over 6 points to start feeling like you are enough, and you can start to action these today.</description></item><item><title>223. Breaking down the low dopamine morning trend, and what you should do instead | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830047/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 20:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830047/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this ep, I am going to break down what I like about the low dopamine morning trend (all over Tiktok and blogs) and what I disagree with, and what the science says instead. I then give suggestions of what you can take from this trend and what you should do instead of some things that are suggested.
Brain Fact : Barbiturates
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>222. How to chose your friends wisely | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830048/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 20:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830048/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is all about knowing how to chose your inner circle friends and how to chose those that you like having around but are not going to be closest to you. I will go over warning signs of unhealthy friendship behaviours and healthy signs of a good friendship, and lastly, I will talk about the friendship you have with yourself.
Brain Fact : Anti-epileptic Drugs
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>221. How to forgive yourself when others won't | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830049/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 20:00:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830049/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode I talk all about self forgiveness when someone wont forgive you. What to do when you have apologised and are not forgiven, how to move past that, how to be kind to yourself and truly get to a point of forgiveness to yourself.
I also cover how to forgive yourself for how you have treated yourself in the past.
Brain Fact : Vertigo (Vestibular System)</description></item><item><title>220. Who is getting the best of you? A lesson in self love | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830050/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:33:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830050/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode I go how you can be giving the best of you to YOURSELF and ways to do that as often you end up getting the leftovers of what you have to offer. This episode also helps you improve those relationships that are most important to you.
Brain Fact : Neurofibrillary tangles
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>219. 4 tools to get you to know what you want. | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830051/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 20:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830051/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode covers 4 key ways to help you know what you want in all areas of life, and goes into why we struggle so much with knowing what we want in the first place.
Brain Fact: Epidural and Spinal anaesthetic
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>218. 5 ways to feel empowered and never feel like a victim again | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830052/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 20:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830052/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode I go over 5 ways to learn how to become more empowered with your life circumstances and situations so you feel more in control with where you are headed instead of feeling like a victim to your circumstances.
Brain Fact : Amyloid Plaques
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>217. 4 ways to stop feeling disappointed, and to feel more in control | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830053/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 20:00:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830053/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode we look at 4 things you can implement to feel less disappointed and to feel like you are more in control of your life.
Brain Fact: CJD and Mad Cows disease (Bovine Spongiform Encephalopathy)
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>216. 10 things I learnt in my 20s | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830054/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 20:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lets go over the 10 things I learnt in my 20s. (there may need to be a part 2 to this one)
Brain fact : Morning light and its positive effects on mood disorders and ADHD
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>215. Do this every day for 30 days and see what happens for you (encore) | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830055/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 20:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830055/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is one of my most shared episode of all time.
In this ep I give 4 simple things to do every single day. If you can stick to it for 30 days, you will notice some great changes in your life!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>214. How to tell the difference between gut instinct and anxiety | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830056/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 20:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830056/</guid><description>Podcast Description How to follow your instinct better!
This episode helps you pull apart the feelings of anxiety vs the feelings of a gut instinct telling you not to do something or to go for something. If you normally suffer from anxiety this will hopefully help you feel less fearful in making big decisions.
Brain fact: Ozempic - diabetes drug (now commonly used for weightloss)
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>213. Green flags to look for in a partner (encore) | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830057/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 20:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830057/</guid><description>Podcast Description One of my favourite episodes ever. Talking all about the good things to look out for in a partner. This is also great for you to look at your own behaviour and see how many green flags you are brining into your relationships.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>212. Navigating friendship conflicts and poor communication styles with a partner | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830058/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 20:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830058/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode I answer a bunch of GREAT listener stories and give my advice on what to do if you are being pushed out of a friendship group for no good reason, if your partner doesn't communicate with you for days or even weeks after a fight and SOOOO much more.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>211. How to become more assertive in every area (encore) | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830059/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 20:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today is an encore episode of one of my all time favourite topics. Assertiveness.
I will give you a whole bunch of tips on how to increase your assertiveness no matter who you are speaking to!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>210. Know yourself better so people don't take advantage of you | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830060/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 20:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lets talk about all the ways that people take advantage of you (intentional and intentional ways) and how to know yourself better so you can respond to these moments, so you don't feel stuck or caught up in what someone else is saying or doing.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>209. They were out of your life and now they want back in. What do you do? | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830061/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 20:00:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today I talk about how to navigate a situation where either you ended a relationship with someone or they ended it with you and now they want back in.
How do you know if you want them back? or how do you keep them out? do you owe them anything? all this and MORE
Brain Fact: EPO - blood doping
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>208. Why knowing your limitations will unleash your potential | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830062/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 20:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lets talk about our limitations.
There are ones you cannot change, and others that are temporary where you can do something about it.
In this episode I talk about the importance of being able to identify where your limitations are to be able to help you move forward and progress in certain areas of your life, and how this can help you and not hinder you.
Brain Fact : Serotonin Syndrome</description></item><item><title>207. How to have a difficult conversation with anyone | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830063/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 20:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830063/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode I go over a whole bunch of tools to take with you when entering a difficult conversation. It doesn't matter if you are breaking up, asking for a pay rise, talking to your parents about a sensitive topic, ANYTHING. This will help you feel more comfortable and confident approaching these kinds of conversations.
Brain Fact: Monoamines and MAOIs as a treatment for depression
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>206. The Ick. Is it instinct? Do I run or do I stay? | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830064/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 20:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lets talk about the ICK!
What is it, how to know if it is an alarm bell for a red flag or just something small you can move past.
I also go over a WHOLE bunch of 'Icks' send through to me by you beans. HILARIOUS.
Brain Fact: Why smells trigger such strong memories.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>205. How to stop having FOMO (and deal with people who have it) | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830065/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 20:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830065/</guid><description>Podcast Description FOMO! What is it? why does it consume you so much?
This episode will go over why you feel this way, even when you don't want to go out, and how to start getting over FOMO.
It also goes into dealing with people who have it, and how to navigate those conversations.
Brain Fact - L-Theanine
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>204. How to slow down ageing and combat oxidative stress | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830066/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 19:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830066/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is more science focused than my other ones. On this episode I cover what oxidative stress is, how it affects your body and the ageing process, what free radicals are, and what antioxidants are. I go over interventions to improve your health span and overall health with behaviours and what to eat / exclude. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>203. Watch your life transform when you start to challenge yourself | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830067/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 19:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830067/</guid><description>Podcast Description www.dyfmpod.com
On this episode I go over the difference between voluntary and involuntary discomfort. Why challenges will transform you physically, psychologically and neurologically and how you can harness this. I give you 4 steps to work through to help you change your perspective on daily discomfort.
Brain fact - Aphantasia
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>202. Pep Talk - Declutter the mind | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830068/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 19:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pep Talk - Declutter the mind See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>201. Pep Talk - What is not meant for you will be met with resistance | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830069/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 19:00:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pep Talk - What is not meant for you will be met with resistance See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>200. Your pain and discomfort is the ticket to the life you want (encore) | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830070/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 19:00:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830070/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is an encore episode of one of my most shared episodes.
I decided to re-release this one as lately I have received many questions from my listeners that I think are covered in detail in this episode, and I feel can provide many answers. No matter if you are going through pain, or have gone through a painful time in the past, there is something in this episode for everyone.</description></item><item><title>199. Finding your Purpose after a breakup | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830071/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 19:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lets talk about why you feel like you have no purpose after a break up and WHAT you can do about it, and how finding your purpose will transform how you feel about yourself and your life ahead of you.
Brain Fact: Neuropeptide Y and its links to weight gain and reduced anxiety.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>198. Pep Talk - What can I begin to heal today? | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830072/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 19:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pep Talk - What can I begin to heal today? See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>197. Pep Talk - Stop resisting. Face that thing and get it done | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830073/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 19:00:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stop resisting. Face that thing and get it done
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>196. Time to cut your losses and become more ruthless | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830074/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 19:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830074/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today's episode I go through 9 ways to help you learn to cut your losses in order to be happier, have more self respect and to achieve growth in all areas.
Brain Fact: Fetal Alcohol Syndrome (FAS)
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>195. 10 ways to show up for yourself | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830075/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 19:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome!
On this episode I give you ten ways that you can show up for yourself to feel happier (and to not feel guilty). I also go into what is NOT showing up for yourself, but may be disguised as self love.
Brain Fact - Cranial Nerves and Bell's Palsy
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>194. Pep Talk - Becoming at ease with the outcome | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830076/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 19:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pep Talk - Becoming at ease with the outcome See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>193. Pep Talk - Get out of your own way today | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830077/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 19:00:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pep Talk - Get out of your own way today
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>192. The difference between negative self talk and constructive criticism | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830078/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 19:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830078/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today's ep I am covering the importance of giving yourself constructive criticism.
I cover what proper positive feedback looks like and what negative self talk looks like, how to know the difference between the two and how to pull yourself up on your sh*t in a constructive way that aids your growth and self love.
Brain / Science Fact: Hormonal contraceptive pills
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>191. The importance of showing up for other people | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830079/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 19:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830079/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode I go over the importance of showing up for other people, what will change in your life when you start to do this more consistently, and ways that you can show up for others (your partner, friends, family and even strangers).
Science fact: Why some magnesiums act as a laxative
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>190. 7 ways to achieve balance to become a happier person | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830080/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 19:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830080/</guid><description>Podcast Description The podcast is finally back and this is the first episode back since October last year.
This episode is based around a lot of my recent and old lessons that I have learnt. 7 ways that you can achieve better balance. Sometimes one bad thing happens to us, and it ends up consuming our entire life, affecting our health, our relationships and our performance in what we do. This episode will help you put things into perspective and teach you how to lean in to other areas of your life during hard times so you can find moments of happiness even when you feel you are struggling.</description></item><item><title>189. Are you blocking the right people from entering your life? | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830081/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 22:09:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today I will get you looking into your own behaviours to see if you are welcoming the right people or pushing them out of your life.
Often we carry unhealthy traits from past relationships into our future (romantic or friendship) and it determines the quality of our future relationships. I also cover how know if you confuse exciting but toxic behaviour as being loved.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>188. Let go of the idea it could have been different | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830082/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 22:08:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Let’s talk about how to t stop keeping our focus in the past, and the importance of shifting your awareness and thoughts to the present and future so you can expand your opportunities and experiences.
Brain Fact: Hemispatial Neglect
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>187. Self Employment and Money Mindset with Lizzie | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830083/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 22:07:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830083/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s episode I have the super talented Lizzie.
Lizzie is a successful freelance copy and content writer who has started her own successful business (not before many testing times in her 20s).
We talk about how to make the steps to branch out on your own, how to gain a better money mindset and how to feel ready to go out and turn your side passion in to a money generating job.</description></item><item><title>186. Toxic psychos and red flags - Encore | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830084/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 22:06:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830084/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is an encore episode of one of my all time most shared episodes.
This is a guide to understand if you are dating someone who is a walking red flag (or a good way to see if you possess any of these traits). Feel free to send it to anyone who you think may display these behaviors!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>185. Why inner peace is the real success and how to achieve it | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830085/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 22:05:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830085/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode goes through 8 key points in helping you to get closer to feeling calmer and happier within yourself, and to determine if you are doing what you are doing for the right reasons.
Brain fact: alcohol related blackouts
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>184. How vulnerability will transform your relationship with yourself | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830086/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 22:04:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830086/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode, I will go over the importance of vulnerability and how that will not only save you time, improve all your relationships, but also how learning to be more vulnerable will do wonder for your self love and self respect. Do not miss this one!
Science fact: Epigenetics
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>183. How to bounce back stronger after emotional defeat | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830087/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 22:03:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830087/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode delves into what you can do when you feel defeated (after the breakdown of a relationship, losing hope for something, losing an opportunity or job, or being blindsided).
I go into a whole bunch of things you can do to turn this situation into something beneficial to help you grow beyond what you thought possible.
Brain / Science fact: Cyanide poisoning
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>182. How to be less defensive, and dealing with defensive people | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830088/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 22:02:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830088/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode will breakdown why people become defensive, different defensive behaviors and what they look like, and how you can deal with people (in particular partners) who get easily offended and become defensive all the time.
Science fact: Epi pen
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>181. Change what you think about trust | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830089/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 22:01:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830089/</guid><description>Podcast Description So much about what we thing of trust is warped. Often, we think that in order to trust someone, we need proof that they won’t hurt us or that they really are doing the right thing. But that is not the definition of trust.
This episode will cover how a strong relationship with yourself will make it easier for you to trust others, and how to mend a relationship where you are trying to rebuild trust.</description></item><item><title>180. If you want lasting change, do these 5 things | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830090/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 22:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830090/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode I break down 5 tips on how you can better structure your goals and stick to them.
Brain fact: Narcolepsy
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>179. What to do when it feels like NOTHING is going your way | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830091/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:59:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830091/</guid><description>Podcast Description When you are feeling hopeless and when nothing is going your way, there are actually SO many things that can be done. This episode will cover how to find what you have power over, and what to do when you are feeling this way to turn it around.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>177. Take control over your emotions | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830092/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:57:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s focus will be on:
learning to not let things bother you so much
learning how to return back to a calm state as soon as possible
I will go over 10 points to help you take control over your emotions and deal with external situations and stimuli in the healthiest way possible.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>176. How to stop devaluing yourself | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830093/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:56:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830093/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode I go over 4 things to focus on to help you stop devaluing yourself and how to know when to step away from a situation.
Brain fact: meningitis
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>175. 7 ways to stop feeling inadequate | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830094/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:55:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you suffer from feelings of inadequacy?
Do you feel that you are falling short, or not enough or that you are not who you think you ‘should’ be? Or not living up to someone else’s expectations of you?
This episode will cover this and give you 7 steps to helo you deal with these feelings and let them go.
Brain fact: Circadian Rhythm
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>174. Pep talk - Do your future self a favour | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830095/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:54:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pep talk 7
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>173. Its your turn to be the asshole | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830096/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:53:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830096/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode will teach you how to worry less when someone things you are an asshole, and how to learn to walk away from a situation when someone has a bad opinion of you. I cover the benefit of learning to be the asshole in some situations (and why that is a good thing for both parties involved).
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>172. Coersive control - how to identify it | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830097/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:52:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830097/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode I go over 10 different forms of coercive control and what to look out for.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>171. Pep Talk - Cut the dead weight | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830098/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:51:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pep talk 6
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>170. Co existing with people that you don't agree with | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830099/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:50:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830099/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode will help you have better conversations with and a healthier approach to people that you don’t agree with.
You will learn to feel more comfortable debating topics where you differ in opinion without feeling hurt or attacked. I will go over 4 key questions to ask yourself when you are dealing with someone that you disagree with, to help you navigate your way through these conversations.</description></item><item><title>169. Pep talk - I live for this feeling | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830100/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:49:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pep talk 5
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>168. 10 things you should know about yourself | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830101/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:48:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830101/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode will help you get to know yourself a bit more and get you asking important questions and the WHY behind them, so you know what areas in your life you want to give more attention to, to increase your self love.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>167. Pep talk - You never regret taking action | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830102/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:47:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pep talk 4
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>166. 5 ways to stop being manipulated | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830103/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:46:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today i go over my 5 key ways to avoid being manipulated. This applies to friends, family and most importantly, romantic relationships.
Brain fact: folic acid and neural tube defects
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>165. Pep talk - Stop waiting for someone to decide if they want you | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830104/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:45:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pep talk 3.
Stop waiting for someone to decide if they want you in your life. You make the call.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>164. Are ultimatums toxic or necessary? | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830105/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:44:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are ultimatums toxic or necessary?
Let’s talk ultimatums. When are they healthy and when are they toxic? Can you give an ultimatum and not be controlling?
I answer all your questions on this podcast episode and give you a whole lot to think about if and when you want to give an ultimatum.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>163. Self love - being alone vs being lonely | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830106/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:43:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830106/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode I break down the important differences between being lonely vs being alone and I highlight the importance of learning to love being alone.
No matter if you are in a relationship or single, if you live alone or not. You will see that when you learn to enjoy your own company the quality of all your other relationships will improve.
Brain fact: Alexia
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>162. You decide the quality of your interactions | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830107/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:42:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pep talk number 2
You decide the quality of your interactions. Take the power back and stop giving others the power to control your emotional state throughout the day.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>161. Pep talk - Rest in order to grow | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830108/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:41:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to the pep talks for the month of August.
These are two 5-10 minute episodes per week where I can be with you when you start your day and give you a pep talk and a topic to focus on each episode for that day / week / or longer.
Hope you enjoy!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>160. Playing the DYFM card game and getting deep with bestie Liv | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830109/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:40:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830109/</guid><description>Podcast Description To celebrate the re-release of the DYFM card game, I decided to sit down with my bestie Liv and pull out some card game questions on each other. We ask all questions about our relationship and our own personal lives.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>159. Self Love and finding your worth (encore) | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830110/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:39:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830110/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is all about finding your self worth and how that translates across to self love, and how they go hand in hand.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>158. Teach People how to treat you (encore) | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830111/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:38:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830111/</guid><description>Podcast Description This encore episode delves into how you have to teach people how to treat you.
If you don’t, then they will treat you according to their standards, and not yours. This is one of my all time favorite episodes so I have brought it back!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>157. Tyrone answers all your questions about our relationship | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830112/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:37:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830112/</guid><description>Podcast Description The time has arrived!
I never thought this would happen but Tyrone has finally agreed to be a guest on the podcast. And what better topic than to get him answering all your questions. We had so much fun recording this one.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>156. This is why you struggle with acceptance | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830113/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:36:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830113/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is all about why we struggle with acceptance. What it means for us and why it is detrimental. I offer ideas of what you can do to accept things faster, and why that can positively affect your life, your relationships and your experiences moving forward.
Science fact: enzymes and lactose intolerances
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>155. Stress and the effects on the brain, and how to reverse it (Encore) | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830114/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:35:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830114/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is an encore episode of Stress and the effects on the brain.
I delve into how neurochemicals can affect the physical structure of the brain, and how that then changes your behaviour, mood, productivity, sleep and overall health. AND I explain ways that you can turn that around no matter how hard you think it may be to change.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>154. 11 fascinating myths about the brain | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830115/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:34:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Finally! A whole episode of brain facts / brain myths. I am in my element
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>153. Create excuses or create change. You decide | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830116/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:33:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830116/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode I go into why we make excuses, why it is detrimental for us and I give 9 tips to help you become more accountable so you stop making excuses and start taking action instead.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>152. The neuroscience of visualisation to get what you want | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830117/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:32:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830117/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode will go over 7 points as to why visualization can help you achieve what you want, and I give 4 tips on how to start visualizing no matter if you have never tried it before.
Science fact: Acne medication - Isotretinoin
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>151. Your Breakup Manual - 9 | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830118/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:31:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830118/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is another one to add to the bank of my heart break hacks! I have 9 steps to focus on to help you start to mend and move on.
Brain fact - Alice in wonderland syndrome
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>150. Its never too late. How to stop that narrative | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830119/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:30:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830119/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode will be your motivator to do that thing you have always wanted to do, or change what you want to change, no matter your age or your levels of expertise on something. It’s all about how you approach it. It is never too late.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>149. 6 Steps to controlling your anger | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830120/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:29:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830120/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode goes over 6 actionable straps to intercept and curb your anger. It also covers how to interact with people who are angry or lashing out at you.
Brain fact - Pre workout DMAA and why it got banned
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>148. This is why you need to stop explaining yourself | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830121/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:28:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830121/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode goes into why over-explaining yourself can actually stop you from taking action, make you doubt yourself, and make you become easily swayed by what other people think you should do with your life. This episode will explain what you should be doing instead.
Brain fact - rat lungworm disease
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>147. Do these 7 things to increase your self confidence | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830122/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:27:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830122/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode I break down what self confidence is, and give 7 things you can do to start to increase your confidence levels.
Brain fact - water intoxication
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>146. How to tap into your levels of awareness to improve at anything | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830123/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:26:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830123/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode will go into the four stages of competency and how your awareness of self is crucial to become competent at anything you do, in particular how to treat yourself and how you perceive yourself and your abilities.
Once you gain awareness, you can take control and make a change. But you cannot change what you do not acknowledge.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>145. This is why people keep letting you down, and what to do about it. | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830124/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:25:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Let’s talk about why you keep getting let down, and the tangible things you can do to change that. So much is in your control, don’t be stuck feeling powerless in situations involving others.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>144. Stop searching in others what is already within you | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830125/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:24:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830125/</guid><description>Podcast Description So much of your time and emotional energy is spent searching and looking for what you already have within you. You just have to learn to identify and harness the amazing power that already exist. This episode will cover 5 key categories where you may be searching for things in other people. And remember, identifying is the first step!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>143. Why independence will increase self love | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830126/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:23:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830126/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode breaks down the difference between independence and being guarded and having your walls up. I explain how true independence includes vulnerability and accepting support. I explain why that is, and I give you a few ideas for how you can increase your independence regardless of what kind of relationship you have in your life.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>142. Are you setting the bar too low? | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830127/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:22:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you know if you are setting the bar too low for yourself, your relationships and your career / abilities? In this episode, I cover what happens when you do that, and why it is important to turn that around so you can start expecting and receiving more out of life.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>141. Do this for 30 days, and see what happens for you | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830128/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:21:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today I give you 4 things to do every day for 30 days. These things alone may not seem like much but when done every day for 30 days it can completely transform your life. I mean it. Do it alone, or with a friend or your partner.
Brain fact (pharmacology) - Heroin mechanism of action
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>140. Be gone insecurities! Cut the dead weight | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830129/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:20:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830129/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode dives into insecurities. Where they stem from, why we feel the way we feel, how they manifest, and most importantly, what you can do about it.
Brain fact - Brain freezes and headaches.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>139. Cut the ties to your old self (you dont need it) | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830130/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:19:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830130/</guid><description>Podcast Description So often what holds us back from making change in our lives is our attachment to our old self.
Why are we so attached?
Why do we struggle to let go?
What can we do to start changing that?
All of this is covered in the episode
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>138. You have the power to transform your life through thought - Tayla Clement | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830131/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:18:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830131/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode with Tayla Clement is one of the most powerful episodes you will listen to. Learn how Tayla transformed her life, from not wanting to live, being in a world of emotional pain, to a successful thriving woman in just a few years. I absolutely loved this interview and no matter where you are in life, no matter your age, you will learn some great lessons from Tayla.</description></item><item><title>137. Your pain and discomfort is your ticket to the life you want | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830132/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830132/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode will teach you to stop avoiding pain and discomfort and instead, use it to fuel your growth. I explain how by doing that, you will experience more happiness and joy than by avoiding what we fear the most.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>136. Understanding brain waves to increase productivity and focus | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830133/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:16:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830133/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode I go over the 5 different brain waves and explain what states they get us into, what we get when we have optimal time at these frequencies and when we have too much or too little. I give you guys 6 tools to maximize your potential and why your brain will respond so well when you implement them. Good times!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>135. Are you in a possessive relationship? Here are some hints... | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830134/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:15:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830134/</guid><description>Podcast Description How to look out for red flag indicators of possessive behaviour. It may even be YOU. I go into why we do it, what we think it means to us, some examples of possessive behaviour and how to address them.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>134. Breakup hacks and juicy stories (for friendships and partners) | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830135/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:14:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830135/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s episode I respond to listener questions and give advice on friendship breakups, getting over situationships, break ups, love bombing and MORE.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>133. Powerlessness - how to turn that sh*t around | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830136/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:13:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830136/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode will cover how we condition ourselves to feel powerless, and how that affects our lives and what you can do to stop feeling this way.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>132. Top 7 Tips to increase your self Belief | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830137/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:12:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830137/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode I give 7 tips on how to increase your self beleif that you can do every single day.
Brain fact - the role of glucose in the brain
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>131. Maximise your potential and have no regrets | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830138/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:11:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830138/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode gives you tips on how to maximize your potential even if you don’t know what you want to do with your life, what your purpose or passion is.
Brain fact - how aspirin can cause tinnitus
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>130. 10 ways of dealing with conflict after a fight (and how to repair) | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830139/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:10:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830139/</guid><description>Podcast Description I asked and YOU answered. What are the main issues when you are glue with your partner. I took the top 10 most common answered and address them here on the podcast.
For my long time listeners, I also tell you guys the story of my engagement and how Tyrone proposed. CUTEEEE
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>129. Confidence to change jobs and take that leap of faith | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830140/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830140/</guid><description>Podcast Description I have made this episode in conjunction with SEEK to give you the best tips on how to gain the confidence to leave your job and go for the new career you have always wanted. Take that leap!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>128. Your identity after having children, and what happens in the BRAIN - Interview with Lorena | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830141/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:08:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today I talk all about baby brain, identity after giving birth and becoming a parent and what happens with your sense of self, and keeping up with pressure from yourself and external pressures ALL with my cousin Lorena, who has just launched her own podcast too!
Brain Fact - What is actually happening when you experience ‘Baby Brain’
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>127. Why am I still SO heartbroken? 6 Heartbreak Hacks | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830142/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:07:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830142/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode goes into 6 ideas / hacks for you to try to help get over those heartbreaks that feel never ending. I also go into what happens in the brain when we are in love, vs when we are going through heartbreak.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>126. Loss aversion and why that makes us lose more | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830143/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:06:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830143/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode explains what loss aversion is, how it impacts your decisions around risk and major life changes and how it impacts your view on failure and success. If you can understand loss aversion you will learn to cut your losses, lose less and take more strategic risks.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>125. Learn how to read people in dating (Situationships) | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830144/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:05:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830144/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode I give exact pointers to look for to know if you are in a dead end situationship or if it is going to evolve into a relationship. I talk about what to do if you are in one, and how to navigate your way out of it or explore it further. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>124. Ambition - What is it and how to increase it. | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830145/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:04:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Let’s talk about ambition.
Are you born with it? How do you learn it? On this episode I give 4 ways in which you can increase your ambition.
Brain Fact - Can you live with half a brain?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>123. Imposter syndrome be GONE!! | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830146/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:03:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Imposter syndrome! What is it? Where does it stem from? And a HEAP of tips to put into practice to overcome it.
Brain fact - Lithium
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>122. Self Love - Working on your Self Efficacy | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830147/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:02:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830147/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is self efficacy? How does it affect our self love? Where do you get it from and how you improve it.
Brain fact - The cerebellum
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>121. Happiness - How to create lasting change | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830148/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:01:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830148/</guid><description>Podcast Description How to create lasting happiness! In this episode I talk about what hedonic adaptation is and how that plays a role in our happiness, and what you can truely do to raise your baseline level of happiness. Brain Fact - Stereoblindness
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>120. Ask yourself these 8 things every morning | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830149/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830149/</guid><description>Podcast Description I have a task for you! I want you to ask yourself these 8 things each morning to help you stay on your track, grounded and most importantly, above all, to increase your overall happiness. Brain fact today - Synesthesia See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>119. The mindset of a Serial Killer | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830150/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:59:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830150/</guid><description>Podcast Description It is here the 'Mindset of a ..." series and today we are kicking off with my personal fave, Mindset of serial killers! What makes them become serial killers? Why do they do it?? Are they born this way or does something cause this?
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>118. Walking away when people think the worst of you | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830151/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:58:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830151/</guid><description>Podcast Description This podcast will go over how to tackle walking away from someone when they think the worst of you. How do you deal with unresolved drama, and letting it go for the sake of your own mental health. This is mainly in romantic relationships but can be applied to friendships as well. Brain fact today - Capgras Syndrome See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>117. Should I stay or should I leave? 7 questions to ask yourself | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830152/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:57:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830152/</guid><description>Podcast Description This ep will give you 7 questions to ask yourself to know if it is time to leave your relationship or if there is work that can be done to save it. (your partner can do it too!) Brain fact today : I talk all about the neurotransmitter and endocannabanoid Anandamide See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>116. Introverts and extroverts - Which one are you, and what does it mean? | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830153/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:56:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830153/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lets talk about the difference between introverts, extroverts (and ambiverts!) and what you can do to be happier, feel more recharged and productive no matter where you are on the continuum. Brain fact for today - Difference between amphetamines and methamphetamines - talking about the mechanism of action on the brain. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>115. How to become more self assured | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830154/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:55:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830154/</guid><description>Podcast Description This ep is all about gaining more self assurance. That feeling of being comfortable in your own skin, knowing who you are, feeling grounded and sure of it, no matter what is going on externally. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>114. How to get out of your own way | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830155/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:54:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today I go over my top 5 points for getting out of your own way. This will help you get closer to where you want to be, be more in a flow state, and feel less resistance in your life. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>113. The four communication styles | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830156/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:53:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Announcement on this ep about where my Mindset Hacks modules will be accessible from as of next week!! This episode breaks down the 4 communications styles - Aggressive, passive, passive aggressive and assertive. I go over how to identify them and what changes you can make to improve your communication with your partner / friends / family.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>112. How to become more assertive in all areas | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830157/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:52:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830157/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode goes into how to become more assertive. I talk about what assertiveness is and is not, and give exact tips on improving your assertiveness in all areas of your life. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>111. Should we get rid of girl code? | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830158/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:51:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830158/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is Girl Code outdated? Toxic? Does it serve a purpose? This episode breaks down different ways of looking at girl code, and what I think we should be doing instead. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>110. Body image, self image and self love with the Bodzilla (aka April) | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830159/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:50:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today I get to interview my friend and amazing body activist and podcaster April Helene-Horton, aka The Bodzilla. We go into topics of body confidence, dealing with unsolicited comments, self love and body image. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>109. Retroactive jealousy and overthinking | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830160/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:49:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830160/</guid><description>Podcast Description This ep is all about retroactive jealousy and overthinking. What is it? Why does it happen? and what you can do to change these thoughts. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>108. How habits can transform your life | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830161/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830161/</guid><description>Podcast Description Let's talk about habits and why the brain is so good at them and how you can use this to your advantage. Habits will help you save time, reduce stress, perfect a skill, get shit done, improve mood and relationships and overall satisfaction with your life. Who doesn't want that! See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>107. Constructing strong goals for the new year (or anytime) | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830162/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:47:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830162/</guid><description>Podcast Description A bit late, but here it is! First ep of 2022, all about how to structure your goals and give yourself the best chance at making these changes stick. Its possible and its exciting! (although this episode is even MORE effective if you listened to episode 106, and put that into practise!) See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>106. Leave the past in the past and end the year with a bang | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830163/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:46:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830163/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is all about closing the chapter for the end of the year and identifying what you DON'T want to take with you into the new year. I have 5 exercises for you to work through and it will be the perfect prep for next episode which will be all about setting yourself up for a great year. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>105. Cognitive enhancers / Nootropic brain foods with professor Andrew Scholey | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830164/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:45:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830164/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode I interview Neuroscientist Professor Andrew Scholey, who has published hundreds of articles on the neurocognitive effects of natural foods. There is so much great information in this episode about what you can be doing (and eating) to improve your brain health, focus and attention. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>104. How to kill procrastination and take action | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830165/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:44:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830165/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode goes into the DEPTHS of why we procrastinate, what happens when we do, and ACTIONABLE tasks to put into practice to curb your procrastinating. Also a cool science fact on DIM! See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>103. Why toxic positivity won’t make you happy, but what will instead | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830166/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:43:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830166/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode breaks down what toxic positivity is, where it stems from and why it won't make you happy. It explains what you can be doing instead to work on your happiness and self love.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>102. Is breadcrumbing happening to you? | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830167/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:42:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830167/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode explains what breadcrumbing is, and how it is a form of emotional manipulation. I go over ways to identify it, and why people do it in the first place.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>101. Ten things you and your partner should know about eachother | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830168/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:41:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Let’s go over the ten things that you SHOULD know about your partner. (And if you don’t, well now you have this list so you can tell your ask each other).
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>100. Take that leap of faith! (Where it all began) | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830169/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:40:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830169/</guid><description>Podcast Description its our 100th episode! Today i go back to the original episode of ‘Taking a leap of faith’ and I add another 7 points on how to take a leap of faith. I go into the journey of the last 100 episodes and what has happened and how this podcast and bean community has grown. Thank you for joining for the last 100 episodes! Can’t wait for the next 100!</description></item><item><title>99. Dealing with family drama and conflict | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830170/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:39:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Advice on family conflict and drama! I got sent a whole bunch of listener questions and stories around how to navigate problems with family relationships (in laws, siblings, parents etc).
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>98. A pep talk for when things don’t go well for you | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830171/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:38:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830171/</guid><description>Podcast Description Todays episode is a bit of a guide to navigate times where things are not going well. How to separate your sense of self from what is happening, how to approach it and how to move forward from it with purpose. Oh and of course a bit of pharmacology chat for the brain fact at the start!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>97. Overcoming fear of failure, judgement, abandonment and being alone | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830172/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:37:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830172/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode covers why we fear being alone or abandoned or not ever finding someone. It also covers the fear of being judged or letting people down. Some fears are good and others can be paralyzing and it is important to identify them and know how to counter these thoughts so you can enjoy your life.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>96. Moving cities, changing careers and taking the leap - with my spirit animal Karli | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830173/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:36:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830173/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today I interview Karli, one of my best friends and my housemate when I lived in LA. This episode covers moving from Australia to LA, changing careers, struggling before making it, and then (obviously) general banter. Enjoy!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>95. How we form memories, false memories and ways to improve your memory | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830174/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:35:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830174/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is all about the different kinds of memory. Working memory, long term memory, how memories are formed, stored and retrieved. What false memories are and how they come about and how to improve your own memory consolidation and retrieval.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>94. How to stop self sabotaging | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830175/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:34:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830175/</guid><description>Podcast Description Self sabotage can creep up in so many ways and cock block you from having hte relationship, job or experience that you want to have. This episode will help you identify when you are doing it, and explain why it is that you do it so you can start making different choices.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>93. Green flags to look out for in a partner | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830176/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:33:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830176/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today I go over 15 green flags to look for (and to take on board yourself). These traits are all golden and should be a stable in a healthy relationship. I also go over things that people think may be green flags but are actually the opposite.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>92. Self love - The different versions of you | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830177/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:32:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830177/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s episode I go over ways to release some of the pressure you may be putting on yourself by tapping into different facets of your personality, and understanding what you truly want or need at any given time.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>91. Love bombing - How to identify it and how to run for the hills | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830178/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:31:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830178/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is love bombing? This episode goes into how to identify all the traits of a love bomber, why it is a narcissistic trait and how to move on from it, get over a love bomber or leave this kind of relationship.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>90. Body image, relationship with food and self - with Arabella Hampshire | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830179/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:30:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today I have Arabella Hampshire on the podcast. She is not only a health and life coach but she focuses on the relationship with self to begin to heal toxic relationships with food and self image. She is a book of wisdom so sit back and hear her amazing words, everyone can learn something from her.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>89. Find the strength to leave (relationship, job, group) | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830180/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:29:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today I will give you 11 points to consider to help you feel you have the strength and resources to leave a situation that is not serving you. It could be a job, a relationship, an organization, a group of friends, anything. I also go into how to not let guild make you stay in a situation.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>88. The incredible benefits of sauna on brain performance and health | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830181/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830181/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is all about the benefits of sauna on the brain and body. It covers what neurotransmitters are increased, how it reduces stress, depression and anxiety, improves focus and reduces chances of neurodegeneration. There is just so much info packed in here and so much to learn!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>87. A guide to self love - where to find it | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830182/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:27:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830182/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode will go over 11 ways to increase your self love that you can put into action today. How to feel more comfortable in your own skin to start living a life that you are happy with.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>86. Co-dependency and self love | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830183/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:26:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830183/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode I break down what co-dependency actually is, how to identify it, what the warning signs are and how it ties in with self love.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>85. How to stop catastrophising and calm your anxious mind | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830184/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:25:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830184/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, I will explain one of the common cognitive distortions - catastrophising. What it I is, what happens when we do it, WHY we do it and of course some actionable tools to put into practice to start re-training your thought patterns.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>84. A letter to my ex - with Jordin | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830185/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:24:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830185/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today I interview my beautiful friend Jordin Fleming. We dive deep into overcoming setbacks, being confident in your own skin, and finding validation within yourself. Lots of banter, fun and deep discussions here.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>83. Am I the red flag? Am I the drama? | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830186/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:22:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830186/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode will talk about red flags from YOUR perspective, and give you actionable tools to improve how you react or respond to things in relationships to strengthen your bond with family, friends, partners or relatives in a healthy way.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>82. Find your point of no return to take massive action | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830187/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:22:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830187/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode covers the reasons why you are holding yourself back from making change, from taking a leap of faith and what you can be doing to start heading in the direction of where you want to go, to start taking bold action and raising your standard for your own life. It goes into the psychology of ‘luck’ and irreversible decisions and why they are beneficial. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>81. Breakup and Heartbreak Hacks to move on | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830188/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:21:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830188/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, I cover a huge amount of scenarios that you may be faced with when dealing with heartbreak, and how to gain the tools to help you move on faster and for good. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>80. Dopamine - Addiction, Motivation, Reward and how to stop feeling flat | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830189/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:20:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830189/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s episode I go into a deep dive into the neurotransmitter dopamine. How it is involved in reward seeking behaviour, and addiction. I explain the difference between chemical and behavioural addictions. I then talk about the role it plays in focus and motivation and talk about natural ways to increase your levels of dopamine or what to do if you are constantly feeling flat or unmotivated.
See omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>79. Banter with Katie Williams. Goals, accountability and life balance | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830190/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:19:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830190/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode I have Katie Williams on the pod. We talk all things career, getting shit done, drive, goals and having balance in life. I swear this girl and I share so much in common and it was so good to finally get her on. I think you guys will LOVE it and her.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>78. Let’s get personal. A bit about my life | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830191/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:18:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830191/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is quite different to all my other ones. I answer your questions about my own personal life, ups and downs, adventures, love life, overcoming challenges and growing up. Thanks for tuning in beans! (No brain hacks in this ep today)
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>77. How to stop c*ck blocking yourself from doing things | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830192/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:17:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830192/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today I go into all the reasons why you may be hesitating or procrastinating, and then I go into ways of approaching thoughts or situations differently, so you can start taking action, and stop unintentionally blocking yourself to reaching your full potential.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>76. Self Love - Empowerment | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830193/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:16:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830193/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode I dive into more self love, and how you can empower yourself to take more control with your life and your choices. I break down 4 specific hacks and I talk about how to stop putting your happiness in the hands of others.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>75. Decision Fatigue, Cogntivie Ease and Tackling Procrastination | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830194/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:15:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830194/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode explains what decision fatigue is, how we have a quota of decisions we can make in a day before we start to struggle, how it affects our impulse control and our tendency to procrastinate. It covers the importance of making habits in your life, and explains what cognitive ease is and how to become a better analytical thinker.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>74. Letting go of unrealistic expectations to improve your relationship | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830195/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:14:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830195/</guid><description>Podcast Description So often, our unrealistic expectations of our partner get in the way of creating a great connection. This episode helps you identify these unrealistic expectation you may have, or that your partner may have, and I will show you how letting go of them actually brings you closer, and makes you feel more comfortable within the relationship.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>73. Starting a business and trusting the process with the boys from the Funny Business Podcast | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830196/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:13:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830196/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today I am interviewing Rob and Lach from the Funny Business Podcast. We discuss starting a podcast, taking that leap, networking, general banter and I put them on the spot and ask them some questions from the DYFM game.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>72. How to say no (in any situation, to anyone) | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830197/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:12:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830197/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode goes through my top tips on how to say no. No matter who you are dealing with. How to not feel guilty or intimidated, or how to not feel like your arm is being twisted. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>71. Vaccines and the biology of COVID-19 - with genomics expert Tim Mercer | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830198/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:11:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830198/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s episode, I interview Tim Mercer, a genomics and synthetic biology expert who also works on developing mRNA vaccines. We answer all the listener questions about different vaccines, the biology of COVID-19, the future of the virus and so much more!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>70. Science of sleep, and its effects on weight gain, mood disorders and memory | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830199/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:10:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830199/</guid><description>Podcast Description The long awaited SLEEP episode.
This episode covers a LOT about sleep. The effects of lack of sleep, blue light, and how your circadian rhythm works. I talk about health, weight gain, mood disorders, memory deficits, and how they are all linked to poor sleep quality and ways you can mend this.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>69. Forgiveness and what to do when you struggle to forgive | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830200/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:09:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830200/</guid><description>Podcast Description How to forgive, and wrap your head around forgiveness. This is for people who have apologized but even more so for those who have never sought to appologise or repair the problem. This episode will get you in a place of power and give you much more peace around situations where someone has wronged you.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>68. Science deep dive - Serotonin, Tryptophan, and ways you can treat depression | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830201/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:08:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830201/</guid><description>Podcast Description Science Deep Dive - My first one yet. This episode will cover how tryptophan can be converted to serotonin or instead, a neurotoxin. What you can do to lower levels of toxicity which can cause depression and neurological disorders, and how to increase other neurotrophic factors within the brain and body for a more neuro-protective effect.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>67. Dealing with unsolicited comments Pt 2. | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830202/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830202/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are back for more. Part 2 of even more unsolicited comments. In this episode I answer specific comments received by my listeners and give you advice on how to deal with people who are always dishing out these comments.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>66. Top 4 discipline hacks and more brain science | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830203/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830203/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today I delve into my top 4 discipline hacks that are actionable and will get you results, and I delve into the effects of magnesium in the brains and what happens when you are deficient.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>65. Imagine if the only person you had to impress was yourself | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830204/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830204/</guid><description>Podcast Description lets look at when trying to impress other people can be detrimental. And what happens, and what starts to occur in your life when you focus on impressing yourself first.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>64. Advice with Alexis - Listener stories | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830205/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830205/</guid><description>Podcast Description Listener stories are back! All things relationship, friendship, work, family fights and MORE!!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>63. What else are you doing with your time? | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830206/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830206/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you feeling stagnant? Do you feel that you always give up on something you want, and don’t know how to overcome procrastinating? What to do when you want more out of life, but feel the steps to get there are too overwhelming. This episode covers it all and more.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>62. Friendship conflicts and how to come back from it | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830207/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830207/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is all about friendship conflicts, what happens when we get disappointed or feel left out or abandoned and how to change that pattern, and also what you can do about it is to eliminate suffering.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>61. Win or learn - how to create more success for yourself | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830208/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830208/</guid><description>Podcast Description When you change the way you perceive set backs, you overcome them faster, you change how you respond, and you create more opportunities for yourself in the future. This episode breaks down actionable steps to tackle setbacks in your life in the most productive way possible.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>60. Feeling stagnant? (Lockdown edition) | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830209/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830209/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode will give you some tools to tackle lockdown (and feeling stagnant or just boredom in general). These are easy to put into practice but will CHANGE YOUR LIFE. Hope you enjoy!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>59. Confidence - Identifying your truth | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830210/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830210/</guid><description>Podcast Description Confidence and how to increase it. It’s more simple than you think, but you need to be consistent.
Science fact - what is mRNA and how mRNA vaccines work
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>58. How to argue better - Understanding confirmation bias | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830211/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830211/</guid><description>Podcast Description Confirmation bias. What is it? Do we all have it? How to reduce it or make it work in our favor. This episode aims to give you ways of strengthening your relationships by learning how to argue, seeking to understand and learn how to read people better, all by understanding confirmation bias.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>57. Shit happens (literally) and toxic relationships - with my cousin Giselle | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830212/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830212/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode you guys finally get to meet my cousin Giselle. We talk about the aftermath of a toxic relationship and how to get back to your original self. And other great anecdotal stories that will make you feel better about hitting rock bottom.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>56. Commitment Phobia - what can you do? | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830213/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830213/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode covers what commitment phobia is, why it happens, how to identify it and what to do if you are on the receiving end of the relationship or if you are the one with the commitment barriers.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>55. Overcoming challenges with Lucy and Nikki | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830214/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830214/</guid><description>Podcast Description I’ve finally gotten Lucy and NIkki on the podcast. We talk about overcoming challenges, answer hypothetical questions and general banter.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>54. Advice with Alexis - listener stories | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830215/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830215/</guid><description>Podcast Description Finally! The second round of listener stories. In the his episode I give advice on all things friendship, work, relationships and more. Hope you guys enjoy and there will be more to come.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>53. How to expand in life - soft action vs bold action | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830216/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830216/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode will cover how to differentiate between soft action and bold action. How to implement both kinds and how that can make or break you getting to the next step or goal in your life.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>52. How to set boundaries so you can live your truth | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830217/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830217/</guid><description>Podcast Description This topic is a highly requested one. The Elise covers why you should set boundaries, what happens when you do, nad how to set them with family, friends, at work and even with yourself.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>51. Expanding your self brand nad network - with Ryan aka DJ Harpoon | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830218/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830218/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we have Ryan on the podcast! He is a DJ, music producer, go getter and just a great time. Sit back and enjoy us tell some stories and answer the listener questions.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>50. Stress on the brain and how to reverse the effects | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830219/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830219/</guid><description>Podcast Description The stress episode is here. This one is full of science facts, brain anatomy and some cool shit about epigenetics and how our behaviours can influence our genes. This will hopefully get you thinking about your brain health and how to optimize it.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>49. Assumptions and friendship advice with liv | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830220/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830220/</guid><description>Podcast Description She is back and this time we are answering all your questions around navigating friendships, and also addressing some great assumptions about us. You know us, just general banter as usual.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>48. Lets break down attachment theory / styles | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830221/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830221/</guid><description>Podcast Description See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>47. Quitting the 9-5 and backing yourself with Ash | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830222/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830222/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode I interview my good friend and boxing trainer Ash (from Hit Like A Girl). We talk about how to take that leap, quit your job, and back yourself. She is a total legend, super down to earth and gives great advice on how to find and follow your purpose.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>46. Teach people how to treat you | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830223/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830223/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is for everyone! It covers specific scenarios in your life where you can command more respect instead of demanding it. It is for friendships, romantic relationships, work relationships and everyting in between. I will also give specific expanse of scenarios and what you can do or say in these situations.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>45. Improve your attention. Explaining ADHD and how to improve your general attention span | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830224/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830224/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode will give a brief overview on what ADHD is, to give you insight into if if you have always self diagnosed yourself with it. It will then be focused on general lack of attention and focus and give six hacks into how you can turn this around for yourself. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>44. How to deal with ghosting | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830225/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830225/</guid><description>Podcast Description The much requested episode on ghosting is here. I talk about different kinds of ghosting, how to identify it and the warning signs, why it hurts so much and what to do about it. I also answer a bunch of listener questions around ghosting.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>42. Dealing with closure, unrequited love and being cheated on (pt.2) | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830226/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830226/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is part 2 of episode 41. But it dives into how to get over a parter who cheated on you and how to deal with that kind of deception, closure and also how to move on from someoen who as never loved you back, and never will. There is A LOT of tough love here. It may be hard to hear bit it will help you.</description></item><item><title>41. Getting over your ex pt. 1 | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830227/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830227/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is one episode that I have had so many requests for that I have had to break it down over two episodes to cover as many aspects of this topic as possible.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>40. Self love - Finding your worth | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830228/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:39:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830228/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode covers the building blocks you need for self love. Having self worth and self respect and specific ways of how you can get these.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>39. Gaslighting - WTF is it and how to know if it is happening to you | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830229/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:38:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830229/</guid><description>Podcast Description Finall! The episode I’ve been talking about for so long. This one will cover gaslighting, what it means, the main traits, how to know if you ar being gaslit and what to do about it.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>38. Top 10 things to let go of to live the best life | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830230/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:37:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830230/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode will break down my top 10 things you must let go of in order to live a great life. Each tip is followed by a hack on how you can implement change in your life.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>37. Self image and social media use | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830231/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:36:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830231/</guid><description>Podcast Description This podcast goes into why we are so compelled to use social media apps, why it controls us, how it affects the brain and what to do about it. It also covers all the issues that arise with self and body image and how you can chane how you feel about it.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>36. Dealing with unsolicited comments | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830232/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:35:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830232/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here it is! The episode everyone has been asking for. Specific ways to deal with unsolicited comments about ANYTHING.
we all get them, and often we don’t know how to respond, or don’t respond. But no matter if someone has a comment to say about your body, skin, lifestyle, sexuality, job, being single, style, this podcast has it covered. Bit of swearing as per usual so be prepared for that too.</description></item><item><title>35. Stop making excuses for other people’s behaviour | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830233/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:34:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830233/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode will break down why we make excuses for why others treat us badly. What happens when we do that and what you can do to change this.
This can be applied to relationships, friendships, family and work colleagues.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>34. How to nail your New Years resolutions | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830234/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:33:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830234/</guid><description>Podcast Description New Years resolutions! This episode will talk about the mindset behind proper goal setting and resolutions. If you have struggled in the past with this, pay close attention becasue this episode will teach you how to re-write what you think you know about sticking to a goal and making it happen.
Mince Bowl Recipe
Fry up bacon, onion, garlic. Then add zuccini, mushroom, capsicum, olives, mince meat or brown rice ‘ lentils.</description></item><item><title>33. 2020 wrap up with Liv | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830235/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:32:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830235/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wrapping up the most hectic year of 2020 with my bestie Livc and answering all your questions too.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>32. How to know if someone is into you | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830236/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:31:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830236/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get ready for some hard truths as we take a look at the behaviours you want to be aware of when you are dating someone, have a crush on or are causally seeing someone. Do their actions mean they like you or are they just not that into you?
And of course some brain facts in here too!
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>31. Mindset around eating and training | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830237/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:30:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830237/</guid><description>Podcast Description Im answering all your questions this week about eating and exercise and a balanced diet. Lets goooooo
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>30. The limit of your self worth lies in how you let others treat you | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830238/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:29:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830238/</guid><description>Podcast Description You can’t have self love if you don’t first have self respect and self worth. This podcast episode will explain how by raising your standards with what you will accept from others, you improve your own relationship with yourself.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>29. Dating, coming out and career success with Luke Antony | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830239/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:28:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830239/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to my most MA rated episode yet! Luke (my gorgeous friend) covers some great dating disaster stories, amazing career journey as a singer and how his mindset has changed to make him a stronger person and performer.
Check out Luke’s music:
@lukeantonyp
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>28. Anxiety. What’s going on in the brain? | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830240/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:27:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830240/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode gives an insight into the main anxiety disorders, and then goes into dealing with feelings of anxiety. I go into what is going on in the brain, and ways of treating and dealing with anxiety.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>27. Love Languages and Banter with Liv | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830241/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:26:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830241/</guid><description>Podcast Description You asked and we delivered. LOVE LANGUAGES. This is a not so serious, banter filled insight into our opinion on love languages. We also had the opportunity to answer a bunch of your questions about it.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>26. Coming back from failure and defeat | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830242/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:25:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830242/</guid><description>Podcast Description Re-think waht failure is! This podcast will break down how you perceive failure and get you looking at what you can and cannot control.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>25. What it Takes - With Stefanie aka My Sister | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830243/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:24:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830243/</guid><description>Podcast Description My SISTER is on the POD to talk all things goal setting, motivation, drive and doing what it takes to get you where you want to be. From competing at an elite level across 4 different sports (now currently on the Australian bobsleigh team) and being a firefighter. This episode is amazing for anyone looking for mindset hacks to help them with motivation.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>24. Early Warning Signs and Red Flags | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830244/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:23:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830244/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode goes into how to identify early warning signs when you are starting to date someone or starting a new friendship or work relationship. How to identify these behaviours as red (or pink) flags and what do do about it.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>23. Putting Yourself Out There. What Will People Think? | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830245/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:22:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830245/</guid><description>Podcast Description Putting yourself out ther after a set back or criticism can be daunting as farrrk. This episode gives you some tips on how you can tackle this feeling and take that leap.
As usual, this podcast has swearing and lots of tough love, so this podcast ep may not be your cup of tea.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>22. Dating, Friendship Advice and Banter with Liv | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830246/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:21:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830246/</guid><description>Podcast Description You’ve seen her all over my instagram, you have asked and we have delivered.
My first ever guest on the podcast and who better than my bestie Olivia, here to discuss all things about adult friendships, dating, dud lemons and being an overal vibe LOL.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>21. Dealing With Cooked Duds That Are Stuck in Your Life | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830247/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:20:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830247/</guid><description>Podcast Description Part 2 of dealing with toxic people and narcissists. This episode deals with the people you can’t just eliminate from your life due to external circumstances. How too manage your expectations and protect yourself around these lemons.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>20. Narcissists - Cutting the Dead Weight | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830248/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:19:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830248/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is part 1 of 2 covering the topic of dealing with a narcissist. In this episode, I uncover how to spot one and what the red flags are. I also cover how to deal with marcissists who you are truing to get out of your life. Part 2 will cover how to deal with narcissists that are stuck in your life.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>19. What You Focus on Expands | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830249/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:18:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830249/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is the way you speak about your life shaping your circumstances? This episode will talk about your own confirmation bias and what you choose to see and focus on and how that shapes your reality.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>18. Check Yourself Before You Wreck Yourself | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830250/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:17:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830250/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode dives deep into accountability. What does it mean to be accountable? How do you hold yourself and others accountable to better your relationships and get sh*t done? See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>17. Finding Your Purpose pt 1. | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830251/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:16:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830251/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode will explain what your purpose could be and it may not be what you think.
You may spend years trying to find out what it is and always fall short or be disappointed but it may be right in front of you and it doesn’t have to do with your job (although it may!).
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>16. Is Your Need For Certainty Controlling Your Life? | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830252/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:15:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830252/</guid><description>Podcast Description Does the thought of losing your job / partner / home make you live safe and conservative? Do you life to protect those things close to you? What would you do if these things did fall apart? This episode will explain how your need for certainty can control your life and what you can do to be more in the moment. (As usual, this episode comes with some hard truths so if you want to be nurtured then this episode is not the one today).</description></item><item><title>15. Slaying Single | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830253/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:14:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830253/</guid><description>Podcast Description No matter if you are loving being single, searching for your partner or heartbroken, this podcast will share some real truths about your mindset and how to navigate single life like a boss.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>14. Motivation to Get Sh*t Done | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830254/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:13:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830254/</guid><description>Podcast Description Drive, motivation, all the good stuff. This ep will get you challenging what beleifs you hold around what you can do, and why. It’s a whole dose of tough love, so dont say you were not warned.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>13. Comparison Will Kill You | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830255/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:12:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830255/</guid><description>Podcast Description Coverin all kinds of comparisons. From friends, to standards, to people you don’t know. How to overcome thins feeling of pitting yourself against other people, even those who are closest to you.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>12. Overcoming Guilt | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830256/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:11:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830256/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode covers the difference between rational and irrational guilt, learned guilt and manifested guilt. I aim to give you the kick to start living for your own set of rules and not others’.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>11. Moving the Eff on | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830257/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:10:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830257/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tools and hacks on how to move on from lovers, broken friendships, life experiences and much, much more. Time for some MORE tough love as we get real with why we feel attached to these things.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>10. Fear vs Love | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830258/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:09:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830258/</guid><description>Podcast Description How to stop fear being the driving force in your life. Learn to become more accountable, take action, and move forward with the things that matter while learning to release judgement and comparison.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>9. Straight Up Self Love | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830259/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:08:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830259/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode delves into my six main reasons for why we have a bad relationship with ourselves and goes into hacks on how to overcome them.
Warning - there are some truth bombs in here.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>8. Birthday Resolutions | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830260/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830260/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today is my birthday, so I want to invite you into my yearly ritual of resetting myself for the year to come with the best mindset possible.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>7. Toxic Psychos and Red Flags | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830261/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:06:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830261/</guid><description>Podcast Description My list of red flags to look out for, to know if you are dating a toxic psycho.
I go into why people get stuck in a toxic relationship, the science behind it and how to step away.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>6. Motivation, Purpose and Body Image | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830262/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:05:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830262/</guid><description>Podcast Description You spoke and I listened.
Topics that my beans (listeners) wanted covered. WARNING - I seem to swear a lot, it appears.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>5. Listener Stories pt. 1 | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830263/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 19:04:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830263/</guid><description>Podcast Description Some seriously relatable and crazy stories.
Topics ranging from relationships, toxic people and navigating breakups. Tune in to hear all the advice.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>4. How I keep fit, eat and stay motivated | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830264/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 06:30:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830264/</guid><description>Podcast Description Answering all your questions around fitness, nutrition, mindset, how i stay motivated and on task. Tune in to get the low down on my day to day life and what I did to my hair as a child. See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>3. Overcoming Jealousy | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830265/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 06:15:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830265/</guid><description>Podcast Description How to tackle the green eyed monster that is jealousy. Whether it be relationship jealousy, comparing yourself to your friends or feeling like you are in competition with your peers, this episode covers it all.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>2. Heartbreak Hacks | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830266/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 06:14:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830266/</guid><description>Podcast Description A blunt but practical way to navigate your way out of the shitstorm that is being dumped.
Real and useful hacks to get you back on track to being the best version of yourself.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>1. Taking a Leap of Faith | Do You F*cking Mind?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5712830267/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 10:34:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5712830267/</guid><description>Podcast Description The first episode of DYFM! No matter if you want to move cities, change careers or start a business, this episode talks about how to navigate through all the shit to get to where you want to be… and taking that leap of faith.
(originally published 16th March 2020) Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>