<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Trial: Brianna Ghey on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-trial-brianna-ghey/</link><description>Recent content in The Trial: Brianna Ghey on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 16:53:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-trial-brianna-ghey/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Boy Y Gives His Evidence | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990001/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 16:53:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990001/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s episode we’ll explain that Boy Y gave his evidence to the court by typing his answers because he is unable to speak.
How he told the jury that Girl X was ‘giddy’ before they met Brianna on the day she died.
And how he said he wanted to explain to police that Girl X had used his hunting knife to kill Brianna but instead lied because he was ‘scared’ officers would ‘tell him off.</description></item><item><title>It's All Fantasy | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 19:48:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990002/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s episode we will hear what Girl X says happened when Brianna was killed.
We’ll hear Girl X admit that the idea of stabbing Brianna was fun.
And that she lied to Police and sent a message to Brianna, after she knew she was dead, as a cover.
The Trial takes listeners behind the headlines and into the courtrooms of some of the biggest criminal cases in the world.</description></item><item><title>The joke that went too far | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990003/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we’ll hear that Boy Y thought Girl X’s alleged plan to kill Brianna was a joke - but&amp;nbsp;that it went too far. We’ll also explain what the Police found when they searched their bedrooms. And how notes allegedly written by Girl X outlined the characteristics of serial killers. Both deny the murder.
The Trial takes listeners behind the headlines and into the courtrooms of some of the biggest criminal cases in the world.</description></item><item><title>Cover Story | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 16:05:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we’ll hear about the moment the two teenagers were arrested on suspicion of Brianna’s murder.&amp;nbsp; We’ll also hear that Girl X denied being involved in the alleged attack on Brianna and that she whatsapp’d Boy Y to “make sure the story adds up. And we’ll explain that Boy Y told police he saw Girl X stab Brianna in the back. Both defendants deny murder.
The Trial takes listeners behind the headlines and into the courtrooms of some of the biggest criminal cases in the world.</description></item><item><title>"I've just seen murderers" | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990005/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 15:37:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we'll hear evidence that Girl X allegedly had a 'hit list' of five children she wanted to kill.
We'll hear how messages exchanged between the two teenagers accused of Brianna's murder show Boy Y was reluctant to do it on a school night because he wanted to revise.
And we'll hear of the harrowing testimony from the dog walker who found Brianna's body shortly after the attack.</description></item><item><title>Blaming Each Other | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990006/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 19:27:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990006/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Liz examine the final part of the prosecution opening of their case as it was presented to the court.
They reveal how the jury has been told that the two teenagers accused of her murder had allegedly planned to kill her two weeks earlier but that Brianna had failed to show up.
The court has also heard how a handwritten 'murder plan' and clothing stained in Brianna's blood were discovered at their homes following their arrest.</description></item><item><title>The Alleged Murder Plot | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 21:05:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990007/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Liz examine the opening of the prosecution case as it was presented to the court.
They reveal how the jury heard that Brianna was stabbed 28 times before she died.
And how the two teenagers accused of Brianna’s murder&amp;nbsp;were preoccupied with violence and torture and&amp;nbsp;allegedly plotted to kill up to five different people in the days before her death.
The Trial...takes listeners behind the headlines and into the courtrooms of some of the biggest trials in the world.</description></item><item><title>Introducing The Trial: Brianna Ghey | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990008/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 17:36:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990008/</guid><description>Podcast Description "The Trial..." takes listeners behind the headlines and into the courtroom of some of the biggest trials in the world.
Our first series "The Trial of Lucy Letby" was a worldwide hit, with over 13million downloads, while season 2 focused on the murder of Ashling Murphy, a 23 year old teacher from Ireland.
It’s third season covers the trial of the killing of Brianna Ghey, a 16 year old transgender girl from Warrington, England.</description></item><item><title>Ashling Murphy: "She was everything to us" | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990009/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 18:03:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990009/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Caroline and Nicola bring you the emotional victim impact statements of Ashling Murphy&amp;rsquo;s partner, sister, and mother. These statements were read in court to Jozef Puska as he was sentenced to life in prison for her murder.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ashling Murphy: The Sentencing | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990010/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today&amp;rsquo;s episode, Caroline and Nicola look ahead to tomorrow&amp;rsquo;s sentencing hearing for Jozef Puska who was found guilty of Ashling Murphy&amp;rsquo;s murder last Thursday. They speak to Defence Barrister Eimear Delargy, who sheds some light on how sentencing in Ireland works and what we can expect tomorrow.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ashling Murphy: A Turning Point | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990011/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 17:01:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990011/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Nicola chat to Mary McDermott from Safe Ireland about what needs to be done now, in the wake of the conviction of Jozef Puska for Ashling’s murder, to enable more women to feel safe - not just walking the streets, but in their homes too.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ashling Murphy: The Killer | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990012/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 19:47:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990012/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Nicola explain more about Jozef Puska’s defence, and how he argued crucial CCTV evidence in the case should be thrown out because it breached his right to privacy.&amp;nbsp;We’ll also hear from Forensic Psychologist Dr. Ciara Stanton about his possible motivation for the attack on Ashling.
Follow The Trial: Ashing Murphy @TheTrialPodcast
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ashling Murphy: Her Name is Ashling | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 21:43:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, the jury, after just hours of deliberation, found Jozef Puska guilty of the murder of Ashling Murphy. In this episode, Caroline and Nicola talk about Ashling, what her death means, what this verdict means and what kind of a light this trial has shone on the legal system.
Follow The Trial: Ashling Murphy on Twitter @TheTrialPodcast
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ashling Murphy: A Stark Choice | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 18:49:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990014/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Nicola discuss Justice Tony Hunt’s charge to the Jury before he sent them out to begin deliberating their verdict at 15.34 today. In a five hour address to the nine man, three women panel, he broke down the evidence into five parts, confession, DNA, eye witnesses, lies and inferences. As part of this, he read a transcript of Jenna Stack’s evidence recounting how she saw Puska crouched over Ashling in a ditch by the Grand Canal.</description></item><item><title>Ashling Murphy: Who Killed Ashling? | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 19:33:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990015/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Nicola go over the closing speeches from the Prosecution and from the Defence.
Follow The Trial: Ashling Murphy on Twitter @TheTrialPodcast
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ashling Murphy: Jozef Puska takes the stand | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 19:52:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990016/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Nicola discuss the evidence of Jozef Puska who took the stand in his own defence on Thursday. His cross examination by Anne Marie Lawlor concluded on Friday afternoon when she accused him of concocting a pack of lies for the jury, a charge which Puska denied.
Follow The Trial: Ashling Murphy on Twitter @TheTrialPodcast
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ashling Murphy: The Medical Evidence | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 19:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990017/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode we hear about expert medical evidence which says that Jozef Puska was not under the influence of any drugs when he made his alleged confession on 14 January, two days after Ashling was killed. Emeritus Professor Michael Ryan of University College Dublin also pointed out that the abdominal surgery which&amp;nbsp; Puska underwent on the previous day was not ‘major surgery’ but was a keyhole diagnostic procedure.</description></item><item><title>Ashling Murphy: The Confession | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990018/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 18:08:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990018/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Caroline and Nicola go over what the court heard from witnesses that say Josef Puzka allegedly admitted from his hospital bed to killing Ashling Murphy.
Follow The Trial: Ashling Murphy @TheTrialPodcast
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ashling Murphy: The Fitbit | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 16:56:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990019/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Caroline and Nicola bring you the evidence the court heard about data on Ashling’s fitbit recorded the moment she was allegedly attacked. We also hear about a woman who told the court that Josef Puzka followed her to the canal minutes before he allegedly attacked and killed Ashling Murphy.
Follow The Trial: Ashling Murphy on Twitter @TheTrialPodcast
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Ashling Murphy: The Eye Witness | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990020/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 19:50:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990020/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this second episode of The Trial, Ashling Murphy,&amp;nbsp; Caroline and Nicola discuss the testimony of Jenna Stack who came across Jozef Puska and Ashling Murphy in the ditch at Grand Canal way, Tullamore minutes before she died. They also recap a harrowing week for the Murphy family which included hearing post mortem evidence that Ashling’s voice box was cut during an attack which saw her receive 11 stab wounds which ultimately caused her death.</description></item><item><title>Ashling Murphy: "I'm the murderer" | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 18:17:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990021/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this first episode of The Trial, Ashling Murphy,&amp;nbsp; Caroline and Nicola discuss the opening statement of prosecuting counsel Anne Marie Lawlor who outlined the State’s case against Jozef Puska, and how two days after her death, he confessed, telling detectives “I’m the murderer”.
The jury was also told there was just a 1 in 14,000 chance that DNA found under the fingernails of Ashling didn’t belong to Puska and that extensive CCTV evidence taken on the day of the murder saw him trailing two other women on his bicycle.</description></item><item><title>Introducing The Trial: Ashling Murphy | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 15:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990022/</guid><description>Podcast Description From the team that brought you The Trial of Lucy Letby, this is The Trial: Ashling Murphy.
Ashling Murphy was a 23yr old primary school teacher who was killed whilst jogging near Tullamore, County Offaly, Ireland.
Her death stunned the nation.
Jozef Puška stands trial in Dublin Central Criminal Court, accused of her murder.
Listen to the evidence and hear the details behind the headlines every Tuesday &amp;amp; Friday, from October 17th.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Over to you… | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 16:15:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990023/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Caroline and Liz sign off for the time being. So they’re handing over to you and will try to answer some of the questions you’ve been asking throughout the trial. Many of these questions couldn't be addressed earlier due to legal restrictions, and they still can’t answer everything, but they’ll shed some light on some of the things you’ve wanted to know.&amp;nbsp;
They also bring up an update from the steps of Manchester Crown Court about a development in the trial against Lucy Letby.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: The expert witness | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 15:41:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990024/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Liz chat to eminent barrister Mary Prior KC, who explains just how defendants appeal their convictions following the announcement that Lucy Letby plans to contest the jury’s verdicts in her case.
We also have an exclusive interview with the prosecution’s main expert witness Dr Dewi Evans, who tells us why he fears Lucy Letby may have killed or harmed more babies in her care.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: The court watchers | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 15:54:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990025/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Liz bring together people from the public gallery who followed this trial for a chat about how this case has affected them.
And we’ll share some of last night’s candlelit vigil for the babies at Chester Cathedral.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Another Judge | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990026/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 08:57:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990026/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Liz chat to expert legal commentator, Joshua Rozenberg KC, who explains just why Lady Justice Thirlwall is the perfect judge to chair the public inquiry into Lucy Letby’s crimes, and Tamlin Bolton, a senior lawyer with Switalskis Solicitors, who is representing several of the victims’ families.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: The Whistleblower | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990027/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 16:52:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990027/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Caroline and Liz speak to Dr. Fiona MacRae, an&amp;nbsp;anaesthetist&amp;nbsp;at the Countess of Chester Hospital for over 25 years including the time that Lucy Letby was on the neonatal unit. Dr.&amp;nbsp;MacRae&amp;nbsp;gives us a unique insight into the hospital culture that, she says, could have facilitated an environment that allowed Lucy Letby to get away with murder for as long as she did.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Another Victim? | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990028/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 15:33:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990028/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode the parents of a premature baby boy cared for by Lucy Letby tell Liz of their fear that he may have been harmed by her. They also recall she said he was her “favourite” and more than once she removed the tubes helping him to breath to take pictures of him.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: The Twins | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990029/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990029/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Caroline and Liz hear from the parents of twin boys, Baby L and Baby M. While today they are happy healthy seven year olds, the parents will always be haunted by the fact that Lucy Letby very nearly killed their babies.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Toxic Culture | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990030/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 16:43:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990030/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Liz speak to Dr John Gibbs, one of the consultants who repeatedly tried to blow the whistle on Lucy Letby. He speaks of his regret that hospital managers didn’t listen or go to police sooner.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Violation of Trust | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990031/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 15:21:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lucy Letby abused the trust not only of the babies and their parents, but also of her nursing colleagues. In this episode Caroline and Liz chat to the deputy senior investigating officer, DCI Nicola Evans, about how she was able to manipulate everyone around her to get away with murder for so long.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Questioning a Killer | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990032/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 15:46:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Until she entered the witness box back at the start of May, there were few who really knew what Lucy Letby was like. But one person knew better than most. Detective Sergeant Danielle Stonier spent over 20 hours interviewing Lucy Letby when she was arrested. In this exclusive interview with the detective, Caroline and Liz ask what it was like to question one of the worst murderers in modern times.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Catching the Killer | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990033/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 14:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lucy Letby was killing in plain sight. But during the trial we heard little about how she was caught. Caroline and Liz sit down with Detective Superintendent Paul Hughes to talk to him about how this case landed on his desk.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: The Sentence | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990034/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 20:34:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990034/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Liz bring you details of what happened in court when Lucy Letby was handed a whole life order.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Vanilla Killer | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990035/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Caroline and Liz explore who exactly is Lucy Letby? And examine how this ordinary ‘girl next door’ went on to become the worst serial child killer in modern times.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: The Verdict | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990036/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 17:14:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today nurse Lucy Letby has been found guilty of murdering and attempting to murder babies in her care. Caroline and Liz go over the verdicts and give you all the details from the steps of Manchester Crown Court.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Crisis, Comedy and Court Reporting | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990037/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 15:11:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990037/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, while we all wait for the jury verdict, Caroline and Liz speak with Tristan Kirk, the courts correspondent for the Evening Standard&amp;nbsp;in London.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: More of our best guests | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990038/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 11:08:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990038/</guid><description>Podcast Description As we continue to wait for the jury to reach their verdicts, Caroline and Liz have pulled together more of the most memorable moments from their guest interviews.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Some of our best guests | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990039/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 13:35:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990039/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, while we all wait for the jury verdict, Caroline and Liz have put together some of the most memorable moments of their guest interviews.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Open Justice | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990040/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 11:40:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990040/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, while we all wait for the jury verdict, Caroline and Liz speak with Mike Dodd, a former reporter and long-time legal advisor for the Press Association. "If the public don't know what's going on in the courts, they've got no idea whether justice is actually being administered or whether the system is working."&amp;nbsp;
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Waiting and watching | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990041/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 11:39:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990041/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, while we all wait for the jury verdict, Caroline and Liz speak with Polly Rippon – a former court reporter with 20 years' experience. In this interview, we hear why judges are eager to see more reporters in their courtrooms.&amp;nbsp;
Polly has told her court reporting students, “You might be in court and feel almost as if you’re intruding a bit into someone’s life. But actually you have to think of the greater good that you’re doing: you’re telling members of the public what's happening in court, that the courts are functioning properly, that the police are doing their job.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: The jury retires | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990042/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 14:53:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990042/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Liz explain that the jury has now been sent out to consider their verdicts.&amp;nbsp;They were asked to begin their deliberations after listening to the judge sum up the case for more than four days.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: 'The presumption of guilt' | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990043/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 13:32:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990043/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Liz outline the closing speech of Lucy Letby’s barrister, Ben Myers, KC. He tells the jury that the prosecution case is based on a presumption of guilt and not innocence. And he claims she is wrongly being blamed for mistakes in care at the hospital.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter&amp;nbsp;@LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: ‘No innocent coincidences’ | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990044/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 11:19:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990044/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Liz continue to explain what prosecutor Nick Johnson KC said in his closing speech. He tells the jury Lucy Letby underwent training on the dangers of air embolus just days before she allegedly started harming babies and that the timings of some of the alleged attacks were strikingly similar.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: The beginning of the end | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990045/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 14:33:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990045/</guid><description>Podcast Description All the evidence has now been presented to the jury in the trial of Lucy Letby. In this episode, Caroline and Liz explain what prosecutor Nick Johnson KC said in his closing statement and how he is pulling together what he calls the ‘patterns' or ‘similarities’ in the alleged attacks.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: The end of the evidence | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 13:57:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990046/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Liz outline the conclusion of the defence case and the end of the evidence. They also explain the judge’s directions to the jury and how they should decide whether Lucy Letby is guilty or innocent of the charges she faces.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: ‘A very calculating woman’ | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990047/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 17:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990047/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Liz explain what Lucy Letby said at the conclusion of her cross-examination. They discuss the prosecution claims that she was out on the razzle, drinking with colleagues in the months before her arrest. And how it’s alleged that she’s a calculated murderer who killed babies for attention and sympathy.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: ‘Homicidal activities’ | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990048/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 15:37:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990048/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Liz explain what Lucy Letby said when questioned by the prosecution about Babies K to Q. They discuss how she accepts that two of her alleged victims were poisoned with insulin - just not by her. And how the prosecution say she was plotting to kill all three of the triplets.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Dr. A | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990049/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 17:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990049/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this bonus episode Caroline and Liz take a closer look at what Lucy Letby says about her relationship with Dr A. They examine how it’s alleged she attacked and murdered babies on the neo-natal unit - to get his attention because she had a ‘crush’ on him.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Dancing the dance | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990050/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 13:00:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990050/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Liz explain what Lucy Letby said when questioned by the prosecution about three of the alleged victims in the case - Baby I, Baby J and Baby K. They discuss how she was accused of getting a “thrill” out of watching the grieving parents of Baby I bathe their daughter after she died and how she allegedly took the opportunity to try to kill when staff were busy with an emergency.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: False trails | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990051/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 15:54:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990051/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Liz explain what Lucy Letby said when questioned by the prosecution about four of the alleged victims in the case - Baby E, Baby G, Baby H and Baby I. They discuss how she denies ‘cooking’ or faking medical notes to cover her tracks and attacking babies soon after their parents reluctantly left their cotsides.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: The Gang of Four | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990052/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990052/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Liz explain what happened in court when the prosecution began questioning Lucy Letby for the first time. They discuss how she believes a ‘gang of four’ hospital consultants were out to get her, and blame her for the sudden collapses and deaths of babies to cover up for failures in their care.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: I’ve only ever done my best.’ | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990053/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 19:30:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990053/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Liz explain what Lucy Letby had to say about the specific allegations relating to babies G to Q. They discuss how she disputed the evidence given by doctors and nurses on the unit and reveal what she said when asked directly if she’d attacked babies in her care.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter&amp;nbsp;@LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Aussie Court Rules | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990054/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 12:45:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last week was unusual because the court didn’t sit at all due to the Bank Holiday and juror sickness. Today Lucy Letby resumes her evidence from the witness box and we’re hoping to bring you a bonus episode on this later in the week.
In the meantime, we hope you enjoy this interview with Australian Associated Press Reporter Karen Sweeney. Caroline&amp;nbsp;and Liz chat to Karen, who has been following the podcast from the beginning, about her career and court reporting in Australia.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: The Denials | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990055/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 16:49:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990055/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Liz explain what Lucy Letby had to say on the second day of her defence case. We examine the specific allegations relating to the first six babies in the trial - babies A to F - and how she said it was ‘awful’ being accused of murdering children in her care.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Lucy Letby Pleads Her Innocence | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990056/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 17:41:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990056/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this bonus episode, Caroline and Liz outline the start of Lucy Letby’s defence and explain what she said about why she is innocent of the charges against her. We’ll hear how she was traumatised and left with PTSD by her arrest and how she insisted she never did anything to hurt the babies in her care.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: The Prosecution Closes | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990057/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 16:02:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990057/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Liz focus on the final days of the prosecution case against Lucy Letby.
We’ll hear more from the interviews she gave to police after her arrest and how she was so depressed after being moved off the neo-natal unit that she contemplated suicide.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Arrested | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990058/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 15:19:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990058/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Liz explain how police found a diary, a selection of handwritten notes and hundreds of medical handover sheets during searches of Lucy Letby’s home. We also reveal what she told police when questioned and how she wept when photographs of her bedroom were shown in court.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Off the ward | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990059/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 15:11:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990059/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Liz outline how Lucy Letby was telephoned at short notice by her manager and asked not to work her night shift following the collapse of the 17th baby in the case, Baby Q. In a series of text messages to colleagues she said the call had ‘messed with her head’ and prompted her to have a ‘meltdown’ because she was worried she was ‘in trouble.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Baby Q: “I was worried about what was happening on our unit.” | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990060/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 13:45:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990060/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Caroline and Kim Pilling, standing in for Liz, go over what the court heard about the final baby in this case, Baby Q. He was a baby boy who was considered to be stable, until one morning when he collapsed just after Lucy Letby had left the nursery he was in. The prosecution allege that the clear fluid Baby Q had vomited before his collapse was water or saline which had been forced down his nasogastric tube by Lucy Letby.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Unnatural Causes? | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990061/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 13:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990061/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Caroline is joined by Kim Pilling from the Press Association. He’s been at Manchester Crown Court every day covering the trail and is standing in for Liz while she’s away.
The court has heard from an expert pathologist who told the jury that six of the babies in the case did not die from natural causes.&amp;nbsp;He told the court one of the babies had “huge” bruising to his liver, the like of which he might expect to see in children involved in road traffic accidents, accidents with bicycles and non-accidental assaults.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: The Triplets, Part 2: Baby P, “He’s not leaving here alive, is he?” she asked a doctor... | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990062/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 16:53:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990062/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Liz examine what the prosecution say happened to Baby P, the second of two identical triplets allegedly murdered by Lucy Letby at the end of June 2016.
The nurse is accused of killing him 23 hours after his brother, by injecting air into his feeding tube and tummy.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: The Tipping Point | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990063/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 15:28:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990063/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Liz examine what the jury have heard about attempts made by a senior doctor to have Lucy Letby removed from the neo-natal unit after the death of two triplets. The nurse is accused of killing the brothers by injecting air into their tummies and bloodstreams on successive shifts after she returned from a holiday to Ibiza.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: The Triplets, Part One: Baby O, “Everything seemed to be going well for the triplets." | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990064/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 16:51:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990064/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and&amp;nbsp;Liz examine what the prosecution say happened to&amp;nbsp;Baby O,&amp;nbsp;the first of two&amp;nbsp;identical triplets allegedly murdered by Lucy Letby at the end&amp;nbsp;of June 2016. The nurse is accused of killing&amp;nbsp;the brothers by injecting air into their tummies and&amp;nbsp;bloodstreams on successive&amp;nbsp;shifts after she returned from a holiday to Ibiza.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Baby N: “Lucy Letby said to my partner, ‘I hope he’s alright,’ and gave her a hug.” | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990065/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 16:44:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990065/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Liz examine what the prosecution say happened to Baby N, a premature baby boy admitted to the Countess of Chester Hospital with the blood-clotting condition haemophilia.
Lucy Letby is accused of attempting to murder him by thrusting a piece of medical tubing or equipment down his throat, causing him to bleed and collapse.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: The Defendant: “I certainly don’t fancy him… just a nice guy.” | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990066/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 19:10:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990066/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this bonus&amp;nbsp;episode&amp;nbsp;Caroline and Liz take an in depth look at what the jury have heard&amp;nbsp;about the nurse at the centre of the trial.
They examine text messages between Lucy Letby and her colleagues which show she had a ‘flirty’ friendship with a doctor on the unit and look at what they reveal about&amp;nbsp;her&amp;nbsp;private life.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Baby K: “It didn’t really make sense to me why the tube became dislodged.” | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990067/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 16:53:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990067/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Liz examine what the prosecution say happened to Baby K, an extremely premature baby girl who Lucy Letby is accused of attempting to murder by tampering with her breathing tube.
We’ll hear evidence from TV doctor, Dr Ravi Jayaram, who said he suspected he interrupted Lucy Letby attacking Baby K. And that after she was transferred to a more specialised unit, she sadly died because of problems associated with her ‘extreme prematurity.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: An Association: "We didn’t want to believe it.” | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990068/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 14:48:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990068/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this bonus episode, Caroline and Liz discuss the change in focus the court took this week, as the&amp;nbsp;jury heard more about how doctors were getting worried about a possible link between the babies who&amp;nbsp;had been collapsing in the neonatal unit. It’s&amp;nbsp;the&amp;nbsp;first time the court has heard that there were some&amp;nbsp;people who had started ‘to think the unthinkable”.
Follow The Trial of Lucy Letby on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Baby M: “I was praying to my God to help him.” | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990069/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 16:40:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990069/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Liz examine what the prosecution say happened to Baby M, a twin boy Lucy Letby is accused of attempting to murder by injecting with air.
Jurors have heard how doctors first became suspicious about Lucy Letby 10 months before baby M’s collapse and how a medical log of the drugs he was given during attempts to save his life was later found under Lucy Letby’s bed when police searched her home after her arrest.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Baby L “He had been given insulin he should not have been given.” | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990070/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 17:03:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990070/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Liz examine what the prosecution say happened to Baby L, a&amp;nbsp;twin boy Lucy Letby is accused of poisoning with insulin.
We also hear about how the nurse celebrated winning £135 on the Grand National shortly&amp;nbsp;after the attack allegedly took place and how there was drama in court when she broke&amp;nbsp;down in tears after a doctor she worked with gave evidence for the first time.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Baby J Part 2 “All the investigations could not explain why she had the seizures.” | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990071/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 16:49:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990071/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Liz and Caroline explain the rest of the evidence the jury have heard about&amp;nbsp;Baby J, ‘a nice little baby’ who Lucy Letby is accused of attempting to murder in November&amp;nbsp;2015 by smothering.&amp;nbsp;
Jurors have been told her parents had been preparing to take her home when she&amp;nbsp;suddenly collapsed and suffered two seizures at the end of a night shift. The court heard&amp;nbsp;there was no ‘obvious’ medical cause for her brain being starved by oxygen and&amp;nbsp;it’s the&amp;nbsp;prosecution case that Lucy Letby must have been responsible.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Baby J: “She was extremely well and coming home.” | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990072/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 17:03:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990072/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Liz and Caroline explain the evidence the jury have heard in relation to a&amp;nbsp;premature baby girl, Baby J, who Lucy Letby is accused of attempting to murder by&amp;nbsp;smothering in November 2015.
Baby J was born 8 weeks early and underwent surgery for a perforated bowel in the first few days after her birth. Jurors heard she was recovering well and her mother and father were preparing to take her home.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Baby I: “Our daughter could go from perfectly fine to nearly dying in seconds." | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990073/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 16:35:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990073/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Liz and Caroline explain the evidence the jury have heard in relation to a very premature baby girl, Baby I, who Lucy Letby allegedly attacked three times, before murdering her on the fourth attempt.
Jurors heard from a doctor who said she saw Lucy Letby crying on the neo-natal unit and saying:&amp;nbsp;‘It’s always me when it happens, my babies…”&amp;nbsp;The court was also shown a sympathy card Lucy Letby wrote to the parents of Baby I after she died.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Baby H, Part 2 "Whilst at Chester, her monitor regularly set off alarms. This didn’t happen at Arrowe Park.” | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990074/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 17:03:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990074/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Liz and Caroline finish explaining the evidence the jury heard in relation to Baby H, a premature baby girl who Lucy Letby is accused of trying to murder twice on consecutive night shifts. Baby H was a poorly baby who was on and off a ventilator while at the Countess of Chester Hospital. But within two days at Arrowe Park Hospital, she dramatically improved. Prosecutors say Lucy Letby was sabotaging her care while she was at the Countess.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Baby H, Part 1 - "They were not able to explain why she had suffered a cardiac collapse." | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990075/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 17:39:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990075/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Caroline and Liz examine what happened to Baby H, a baby girl, who Lucy Letby allegedly tried&amp;nbsp;to kill twice in 24 hours. In the early hours of September 26, 2015, Baby H collapsed and didn’t have a&amp;nbsp;heartbeat for twenty-two minutes while staff battled to save her life. Jurors were told the doctors were so&amp;nbsp;worried that they urged her parents to have her baptised in case she didn’t make it.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: "Let’s not ignore the importance of open justice” | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990076/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 16:24:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990076/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Liz and Caroline had hoped to bring you details of evidence heard by the jury during their first week back. But, unexpectedly the case was delayed and unable to go ahead because of health and family issues relating to two members of the jury.
We’re hoping they will be back to normal next week.&amp;nbsp;In the meantime, we have two excellent interviews this week: Part 2 of the interview with media law expert Mark Hanna, and another with the legendary boss of news agency Cavendish Press, Jon Harris, AKA Mr Justice Harris.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Interview with media law expert Mark Hanna. | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990077/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990077/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Trial of Lucy Letby is back after the Christmas break with an interview with&amp;nbsp;Mark Hanna, one of the&amp;nbsp;editors of McNae’s Essential Law for Journalists - the book considered to be the ‘bible’ of media law for reporters. Liz and Caroline chat to Mark about the legal tightrope they are treading to bring listeners the podcast – one of the first to cover an ongoing&amp;nbsp;legal case – each week.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Baby G, Part 2: “She wasn’t moving.” | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990078/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 16:45:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990078/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Caroline and Liz explain how Lucy Letby allegedly tried to kill Baby G, the most premature baby in the case, on two more occasions.
We hear how she is said to have attacked the tiny infant on a day shift, within the space of five hours, on her original due date, leaving her with irreversible brain damage.
We also hear part two of the chat with former chief crown prosecutor, Nazir Afzal, where he describes the importance of trials being open to the public and how trust in the justice system would benefit from live streaming trials.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Baby G, Part 1 “Just a little tiny thing” | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990079/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 18:11:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990079/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Caroline and Liz examine what happened to Baby G, the most premature baby in this case, who Lucy Letby allegedly tried to kill three times in a fortnight.
We also chat to former chief crown prosecutor, Nazir Afzal, about the difficulties faced by&amp;nbsp;lawyers preparing and running such a long and complicated trial, and why advances in&amp;nbsp;technology have revolutionised courtrooms.
Follow us on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Baby F, Part 2 ‘His heart rate was high and his sugar was low, something wasn't right.’ | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990080/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990080/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Liz explain what the prosecution experts say happened to Baby F, a premature twin boy who Lucy Letby allegedly tried to poison with insulin.
We hear how two bags of feed were allegedly contaminated by Lucy Letby and how all of the nurses on duty during the night shift were called to court - and each denied putting insulin into baby F’s feed.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Baby F, Part ‘He was given insulin that was never prescribed.’ | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990081/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 16:59:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990081/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Liz examine what happened to Baby F, a premature twin boy who Lucy Letby allegedly tried to kill with insulin. We hear how his blood sugar suddenly crashed soon after the nurse allegedly&amp;nbsp;poisoned his intravenous feed and how, after she finished her shift, she went salsa dancing with a colleague. We also chat to freelance broadcaster, Matt O’Donoghue, about the skill of condensing a day’s worth of evidence&amp;nbsp;into just a few minutes for television or radio.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Baby E 'I trusted her completely…' | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990082/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990082/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Liz examine what happened to Baby E, a premature twin boy who Lucy Letby allegedly attacked with a plastic medical tube or wire before she murdered him. We hear from his mother, who the prosecution say, interrupted the nurse while she was attacking her son, and about more text messages Lucy Letby exchanged with colleagues after his death. We also chat to former Old Bailey court reporter and media law expert Tim Crook, professor of journalism at London's Goldsmiths University, about why court reporting is still important in the modern era.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Bonus Episode - Interview with a Courtroom Artist | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990083/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 09:23:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990083/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this bonus episode of the Trial of Lucy Letby, Liz and Caroline speak to Julia Quenzler, a&amp;nbsp;courtroom artist at the Lucy Letby trial. Over her 30 year career she has sketched defendants, barristers and court scenes of some of the most high profile cases in modern&amp;nbsp;history. It is a fascinating listen that you won’t want to miss.
Follow us on Twitter @LucyLetbyTrial
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Baby D: ‘It never crossed my mind she was in danger of dying.’ | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990084/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990084/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Caroline and Liz examine the case of Baby D, a baby girl born full term, who was admitted to the neo-natal unit with an infection because of a hospital mistake. We hear testimony from her devastated parents who say they saw Lucy Letby ‘hovering’ around their daughter’s cot hours before she died. We also have a fascinating interview with a court artist, who has drawn defendants and court scenes of some of the world's most significant criminal trials over her 30-year career.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Baby C: ‘The smallest baby I had ever seen’ | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990085/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990085/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Liz and Caroline review what the jury heard about the death of baby C, described by one nurse as the smallest baby she had ever seen. It is alleged that Lucy Letby was close to the infant’s cot and injected him with air causing his collapse, while her defence say she was not responsible and the hospital was not equipped to deal with a baby of his size.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Baby A | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990086/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990086/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Liz and Caroline continue their examination of the trial, which is focusing on each baby in turn. They look into what the prosecution say happened to Baby A – the first alleged victim. A premature twin boy, he died 24 hours after his birth in June 2015. We’ll also hear about a significant rash found on some of the alleged victims and hear text messages Lucy Letby sent to colleagues after Baby A’s death.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Baby B | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990087/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990087/</guid><description>Podcast Description In&amp;nbsp;our continuation of the Trial of Lucy Letby,&amp;nbsp;Liz and Caroline focus on the case of Baby B, the twin of Baby A.&amp;nbsp;She was allegedly attacked 27 hours after her brother, but survived. We’ll hear testimony from nurses and doctors who successfully resuscitated Baby B when she collapsed. Liz and Caroline also chat to experienced journalist Kim Pilling, who works for the Press Association and has one of just a handful of media seats in the actual courtroom.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: A scrawled post-it note | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990088/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 15:32:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990088/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Caroline and Liz begin outside the crown court where Liz goes over the opening statements of both the prosecution and the defence. The prosecution accuse Lucy Letby of being ‘a poisoner’ and ‘constant malevolent presence’ on the unit, while the defence say the case against her is based entirely on coincidence and assumption, describing her as a hard working nurse who only tried to help the babies in her care.</description></item><item><title>Lucy Letby: Nurse on trial | The Trial: Brianna Ghey</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8486990089/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 14:42:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8486990089/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this first episode of The Trial of Lucy Letby, Caroline and Liz go over the background of the case that has grabbed the attention of people all over the world. We’ll find out how the jury has heard that staff at the Countess of Chester Hospital grew suspicious of the nurse back in 2015 after an unexplained rise in deaths and serious collapses of babies in the neonatal unit.</description></item></channel></rss>