<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Up Front with Simon Jordan on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/up-front-with-simon-jordan/</link><description>Recent content in Up Front with Simon Jordan on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 05:45:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/up-front-with-simon-jordan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Chris Eubank Snr | "I’ve always backed Conor Benn, I think he beats them all" | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 05:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530001/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, we are joined by 2-weight world champion Chris Eubank Snr, a boxing legend whose journey from South London to the ring via New York is etched in boxing folklore. Eubank was known for his eccentricity and unique blend of charisma and showmanship which made him a standout figure in the world of boxing and beyond.
During the 1990s, Eubank engaged in two legendary clashes with Nigel Benn that brought Britain to a standstill.</description></item><item><title>Ricky Hatton | “I’d rather be loved in my hometown than rich like Floyd Mayweather Jr" | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 05:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530002/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week's episode, we sit down with one of the most beloved British boxers of all time - Ricky ‘The Hitman’ Hatton.
Hatton's journey from a council estate in Hattersley to becoming a two-weight world boxing champion is the stuff of legend. His epic showdowns with boxing giants Floyd Mayweather Jr. and Manny Pacquiao saw thousands follow him to Las Vegas, leaving a mark on boxing history. But it was his memorable IBF light-welterweight title victory against Kostya Tszyu in Manchester back in 2005 that remains the pinnacle of his career, a night etched in the hearts of an entire nation.</description></item><item><title>Michael Owen | “You don't have to be THAT GOOD to be a Premier League player anymore” | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 05:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530003/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s episode we are joined by one of only four Englishmen to win the Ballon d’Or. Michael Owen was a phenom who burst onto the scene with THAT goal against Argentina in the 1998 World Cup.
He went on to score over 150 goals for Liverpool before becoming a ‘Galactico’ at Real Madrid. He returned to England in 2005, joining Newcastle United but his injuries had started to take their toll.</description></item><item><title>Derek Chisora | "See this is why Tyson Fury doesn't like you!" | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 05:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530004/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week's episode, we sit down with a true force of nature in the world of boxing - Derek Chisora.
From his meteoric rise as a British heavyweight contender, capturing the public's attention with his raw power and fearless attitude, to facing off against some of the sport's biggest names, Chisora has showcased his warrior spirit time and again. His battles against the likes of Vitali Klitschko, Dillian Whyte, and Oleksandr Usyk have earned him a spot in boxing history.</description></item><item><title>Rick Parry EFL Chair | “Attendance in League 2 is within the top 10 leagues in Europe” | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 05:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530005/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week's episode Simon sits down with EFL Chair Rick Parry, a visionary in English football. As the top-flight's chief executive, he brokered the largest TV rights deal in history at the time, £700million, and the division prospered. He was also Liverpool's chief executive for 12 years, presiding over that iconic Champions league triumph in Istanbul.
Now, in his current role as the chairman of the English Football League, Parry continues to play a pivotal role in shaping the landscape of English football.</description></item><item><title>Ruud Gullit | “It’s difficult for Ten Hag... Man United are stuck in the nineties” | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 05:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Simon is joined by a Dutch footballing icon from the ‘total football’ era. One of only 38 men to have lifted the Ballon d'Or, Ruud Gullit joins the show to discuss his illustrious career, from rejecting Ajax as a young boy all the way through to his infamous spell as manager of Newcastle United.
One of the greatest players to ever grace a football pitch, Ruud won multiple European cups during his time at AC Milan whilst also captaining the Netherlands to European Championship glory in 1988.</description></item><item><title>Eddie Jones | "Saying Australia could win the World Cup was CRAZY" | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 07:08:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eddie Jones is one of the most recognisable coaches on the international rugby stage. Having coached his native Australia, Japan and of course England, where he won multiple Six Nations titles and reached a World Cup final in 2019.
Known for his tough coaching methods, his controversial statements and his unwavering commitment to excellence, Eddie Jones is one of the game’s great characters.
He joined the show on Friday 27th October, two days before he announced his resignation from his position as Head Coach of Australia.</description></item><item><title>Stuart Broad | “I was staring at them singing SAME OLD AUSSIES ALWAYS CHEATING!” | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 05:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530008/</guid><description>Podcast Description A World Cup winner with four Ashes victories to his name, Stuart Broad is a modern cricketing icon who always stepped up when the lights were shining brightest.
After retiring at the end of this year’s electric Ashes series, Stuart joins the show to reflect on his illustrious career whilst providing insight on the current England cricketing revolution, spearheaded by Ben Stokes and Brendon McCullum
A winner, a wind-up merchant and a fierce competitor who has never been afraid to speak his mind, ‘Broady’ pulls no punches on this week’s episode of Up Front.</description></item><item><title>Adam Booth | “I’ve lost faith in boxing, it’s just TOO EASY to dope!” | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 05:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530009/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week's episode, we are joined by one of the UK's most respected boxing trainers - Adam Booth.
Famous for guiding David Haye to cruiserweight and heavyweight glory and overseeing Andy Lee's historic WBO middleweight title win, Adam joins Simon to discuss his history in boxing, his run-ins with some of the world's greatest, and the dark side of doping in the sport.
Subscribe for future episodes and head to http://www.</description></item><item><title>Carl Frampton | “The rise of YouTuber fights is a REAL concern for boxing” | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 05:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530010/</guid><description>Podcast Description For this episode Simon sits down with a boxer who lit up his sport, in divisions that don’t always get the attention they deserve. Rising from the streets of Tigers Bay, Belfast, Carl ‘The Jackal’ Frampton would go on to become a two weight world champion, brining a noisy and partisan crowd with him no matter the venue.
Carl joins the show to discuss his action packed career and his feud with the McGuigans whilst also giving his unique perspective on the current boxing landscape ahead of KSI and Tommy Fury’s showdown.</description></item><item><title>Billy Joe Saunders | 'Eubank Jr will NEVER be a World Champion. He can't box!' | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 05:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530011/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week’s show we have a boxer who was borne out of a community, where we are often told that fighting is in the blood. Billy Joe Saunders is a two weight world champion, whose only career defeat came two-and-a-half years ago at the hands of Saul ‘Canelo’ Alvarez, in front of the biggest live boxing audience in the USA since Ali vs Spinks.
Billy joins the show to announce his comeback, whilst giving us the inside scoop on a career that has featured success and controversy in equal measure.</description></item><item><title>Paolo Di Canio | "I turned down Sir Alex because I'm West Ham through and through" | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 05:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530012/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s episode we are joined by a Premier League icon, who was known for his beautiful goals, controversy, fall outs and a fiery Italian passion.
Paolo Di Canio started his career at his boyhood team Lazio before plying his trade at a selection of Italian football’s biggest clubs. He went on to achieve legendary status at West Ham United after cementing himself as one of the game’s most volatile yet entertaining talents during his spells at Celtic &amp;amp; Sheffield Wednesday.</description></item><item><title>Steve Bruce | “They ridiculed me, like Harry Maguire” | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 05:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530013/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s episode we are joined by a three time Premier League winner and a defensive stalwart who captained a Manchester United team that kickstarted Sir Alex Ferguson’s dominance in English football.
Steve Bruce has since managed over 1,000 games across a 24 year period, even managing for Simon Jordan at Crystal Palace. He joins the show to open up on the difficult moments within his career, whilst also giving his thoughts on the state of play at his former clubs Newcastle and Manchester United.</description></item><item><title>Lawrence Dallaglio | Borthwick arrived ‘shocked and surprised’ at England ‘mess’ | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530014/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 05:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530014/</guid><description>Podcast Description As England look to make their mark at the Rugby World Cup, on this episode Simon is joined by a member of the most successful English rugby side of all time. The 2003 World Cup winner and a leader who was inspired by tragedy.
Lawrence Dallaglio was a one club man, a Lion and an England great who was once described by Warren Gatland as ‘the best captain he had ever worked with’.</description></item><item><title>Stephen Hendry | "I was NOT happy when Ronnie tied MY record!" | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530015/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we are joined by a rarity, a sportsman who can genuinely be called the greatest of all time. With 7 world titles, 36 ranking titles and 777 century breaks, only Ronnie O’Sullivan can be compared to the great Stephen Hendry. And like Ronaldo and Messi the GOAT debate continues with Simon Jordan posing the questions.
A dominant force in the 1990s, Stephen took the world of snooker by storm, overseeing an era of dominance that had never seen before.</description></item><item><title>Up Front - The Best Bits | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Simon Jordan has chosen his favourite conversations from the podcast so far and tells you what it’s like behind the scenes on the pod. You’ll hear robust exchanges, raw honesty and insight from those competing at the top of a range of sports in this episode. You’ll also hear why Simon wanted to speak to particular guests and how he prepares for an interview with someone whose strident views on a particular subject need to be put under proper scrutiny.</description></item><item><title>Mike Dean | “I HATED VAR and was PETRIFIED of it” | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530017/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is Up Front with Simon Jordan. A show brought to you by William Hill that pulls no punches and tells it EXACTLY like it is.
Mike Dean is arguably the most recognisable Premier League referee there has ever been. The first to brandish 100 red cards, he is known for his eccentric approach, no look yellow cards, exaggerated step overs and banter with the players, there’s simply never been another match official like him.</description></item><item><title>Warren Gatland | “Sport has gone woke, you need mental toughness!” | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530018/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530018/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is Up Front with Simon Jordan. A show brought to you by William Hill that pulls no punches and tells it EXACTLY like it is.
This week we are joined by one of the most successful rugby coaches of the modern era. Warren Gatland has won multiple Six Nations Championships, coached the British &amp;amp; Irish Lions but his toughest challenge is just around the corner…
On the eve of the Rugby World Cup in France, Warren joins the show to discuss the current state of Welsh rugby whilst also giving an insight into what it takes to coach on the elite, international stage.</description></item><item><title>Frank Warren | “Fury vs Ngannou is a sham and you know it Frank!” | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530019/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is Up Front with Simon Jordan. A show brought to you by William Hill that pulls no punches and tells it EXACTLY like it is.
Frank Warren is a boxing promoter who has always blazed his own path. He broke ‘the boxing cartel’ and has worked with a number of this country’s most iconic fighters. Ricky Hatton, Joe Calzaghe, Chris Eubank and Tyson Fury to name just a few.</description></item><item><title>Troy Deeney | "Saudi Arabia... That’s something I'd be interested in!" | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530020/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is Up Front with Simon Jordan. A show brought to you by William Hill that pulls no punches and tells it EXACTLY like it is.
Troy Deeney is a goalscorer and a leader known for his forthright honesty, making him almost unique amongst footballers today.No player has ever followed the path that Troy took. From bricklayer to the Premier League. From prison to an FA Cup final. Troy joins the show to discuss his unique career whilst offering an exclusive insight into what’s next…</description></item><item><title>Sam Allardyce | “I’ll never recover from losing the England job" | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 05:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Synonymous with the Premier League, Sam Allardyce has been portrayed as a long ball specialist, branded a dinosaur and even renowned as a revolutionary. We simply cannot tell the story of modern British football without the man they call ‘Big Sam’. Fresh from his short term Leeds United experiment, Sam joins the show to discuss his time at Leeds whilst looking back at the key moments in his career.</description></item><item><title>Sir Ian Botham | "Cricket is NOT racist, misogynistic or elitist!" | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530022/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is Up Front with Simon Jordan. A show brought to you by William Hill that pulls no punches and tells it EXACTLY like it is.
Sir Ian Botham is one of the greatest all rounders in the history of cricket. A prodigious talent who created as many headlines off the pitch as he did on it. Ian joins the show to discuss his colourful career whilst giving the inside scoop on this year’s highly competitive Ashes test series.</description></item><item><title>Victoria Azarenka | “You were banned from Wimbledon, simply because of your passport…” | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530023/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we are joined by 2x Grand Slam champion and former world number one, Victoria Azarenka. Born in Belarus, during the final years of the Soviet Union, Victoria’s career in tennis started purely by chance. After moving to the USA as a teenager to pursue her dream she would go on to become the first Belarusian to capture a tennis Grand Slam, winning the Australian Open in 2012.</description></item><item><title>Barry McGuigan | “If you are caught DOPING, you should be BANNED for LIFE!” | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530024/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530024/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is Up Front with Simon Jordan. A new show brought to you by William Hill that pulls no punches and tells it EXACTLY like it is.
This week we are joined by the ‘Clones Cyclone,’ Barry McGuigan. An Olympian and a former world champion who helped to heal a desperately divided country, Barry joins the show to discuss his illustrious career both in and out of the ring.</description></item><item><title>David James | “I think Arsenal have taken away Ramsdale’s character” | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530025/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 06:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530025/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is Up Front with Simon Jordan. A new show brought to you by William Hill that pulls no punches and tells it EXACTLY like it is.
David James spent 25 years as an elite goalkeeper for the likes of Liverpool, Manchester City, Portsmouth and Aston Villa. Often criticised throughout his career he eventually went on to become England’s number one, winning 53 caps along the way.
Often portrayed in the media as an ‘atypical’ footballer.</description></item><item><title>Carl Froch | “Tyson Fury is using money as an excuse to avoid Usyk!” | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530026/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 06:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530026/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is Up Front with Simon Jordan. A new show brought to you by William Hill that pulls no punches and tells it EXACTLY like it is.
Carl Froch is one of the greatest boxers this country has ever produced. A 4 time world champion who never shied away from the biggest fights. Carl joins the show to discuss his illustrious career, his unique psychological makeup, whilst also giving his views on the troubled boxing landscape.</description></item><item><title>James Wade | “I was diagnosed with bipolar after knocking my house down!” | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 06:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530027/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is Up Front with Simon Jordan. A new show brought to you by William Hill that pulls no punches and tells it EXACTLY like it is.
James Wade is one of the most iconic names in the modern darts era. A supremely talented ‘leftie’, James burst onto the scene at the age of 24 when he became the youngest player to win a major PDC title. He has since gone on to win a total of 10 major titles but not without his fair share of controversy.</description></item><item><title>Matt Le Tissier | "After COVID, my family were worried about my mental health" | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530028/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530028/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is Up Front with Simon Jordan. A new show brought to you by William Hill that pulls no punches and tells it EXACTLY like it is. This week we are joined by a rarity in football, a one club man. Considered a maverick and nicknamed ‘Le God’ we welcome Matt Le Tissier to Up Front.
One of the greatest technical players the UK has ever produced Matt Le Tissier would go on to score 209 goals in an illustrious career at Southampton FC.</description></item><item><title>Tim Sherwood | "I find it difficult to blame Levy for Spurs' problems" | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530029/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530029/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is Up Front with Simon Jordan. A new show brought to you by William Hill that pulls no punches and tells it EXACTLY like it is. This week we are joined by one of only 15 captains to lift the Premier League trophy, Tim Sherwood. A core part of the successful Blackburn sides of the 90s, Tim went on to make over 600 appearances for a number of teams before being thrust into one of the biggest jobs in management after the dismissal of Andre Villas Boas at Tottenham Hotspur.</description></item><item><title>Johnny Nelson | "We would go to prisons and spar with murderers!" | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530030/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530030/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is Up Front with Simon Jordan. A new show brought to you by William Hill that pulls no punches and tells it EXACTLY like it is.
This week we are joined by Johnny Nelson, this country’s longest ever cruiserweight world champion who experienced years of self-doubt, ridicule and hardships before reaching the summit. Years of tutelage turned under the late, great Brendan Ingle took him from a scared kid in a man’s body to a British boxing great.</description></item><item><title>John Barnes | "Society would not accept a black Simon Jordan!" | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530031/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530031/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is Up Front with Simon Jordan. A new show brought to you by William Hill that pulls no punches and tells it EXACTLY like it is.
This week we are joined by John Barnes, a footballing icon of the 80s and 90s who remains one of the most electric players to ever grace these shores. Now an author and commentator on issues of race and class in modern Britain, John joins the show for an explosive interview that leaves no stone unturned.</description></item><item><title>Sir AP McCoy | “I broke my back and rode again 8 weeks later” | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530032/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530032/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is Up Front with Simon Jordan. A new show brought to you by William Hill that pulls no punches and tells it EXACTLY like it is.
The term ‘GOAT’ is thrown around in the media but this week we are joined by a man who is undoubtedly the greatest of all time in his chosen discipline, Sir AP McCoy.
The winner of 4,358 races, AP joins the show to diagnose the mindset of a serial winner.</description></item><item><title>Graeme Souness | “I wouldn’t have walked out on Match of the Day” | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530033/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530033/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is Up Front with Simon Jordan. A new show brought to you by William Hill that pulls no punches and tells it EXACTLY like it is. After recently announcing his departure from Sky Sports, footballing legend, friend and former sparring partner Graeme Souness joins the show to dissect the ever changing world of modern football. The captain of the great Liverpool side of the 80s, Graeme offers his unique insight on leadership, management and what it takes to stay at the very top of your profession.</description></item><item><title>Tony Bellew | “Don’t come on here and be a PR for Eddie Hearn &amp; AJ!” | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530034/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530034/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is Up Front with Simon Jordan. A new show brought to you by William Hill that pulls no punches and tells it EXACTLY like it is.
Our debut guest is a former world champion boxer who is known for his forthright views and his combustible nature. Tony Bellew goes Up Front with Simon Jordan as they debate Anthony Joshua’s place in the boxing world, the recent Conor Benn situation and the handling of it by Simon’s verbal sparring partner… Eddie Hearn.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to Up Front with Simon Jordan | Up Front with Simon Jordan</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7289530035/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 14:54:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7289530035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to Up Front with Simon Jordan, a new podcast from William Hill which sees the broadcaster and former Premier League club owner test the biggest names in sport.
Simon will ask the questions most interviewers shy away from and hold his guests opinions up to proper scrutiny. He will investigate how sporting challenge, achievement and experience have influenced athlete’s lives whilst imparting his own forthright views on a range of sports and topics.</description></item></channel></rss>