<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/zoe-science-nutrition/</link><description>Recent content in ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 12:06:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/zoe-science-nutrition/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why unhealthy carbs are making you sick, and what to do about it | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530102/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you realize how closely your diet affects your general health and well-being? Have you ever wondered how advertising affects what you eat? How much do you think your childhood diet is affecting your health in the long run?&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
In today’s episode, Jonathan is joined by Prof. Walter Willett to discuss the importance of carefully considering what you eat and making decisions that support your health.
Professor Walter Willett, from the Harvard T.</description></item><item><title>Could this diet solve your gut issues? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530101/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you know what FODMAPs are? Many of us aren’t aware of these cryptic carbohydrates hidden in everyday foods.
How can undigested FODMAPs cause bloating, gas, and other symptoms as they ferment in your gut?&amp;nbsp;
In today’s episode, Dr. Will Bulsiewicz, ZOE’S U.S. medical director and a board-certified gastroenterologist, teaches us about FODMAPs and how to tell if a low-FODMAP diet could be right for you.&amp;nbsp;
If you want to uncover the right foods for your body, head to zoe.</description></item><item><title>What is the low-FODMAP diet, and should you try it? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530100/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you know what FODMAPs are? Many of us aren’t aware of these cryptic carbohydrates hidden in everyday foods.
How can undigested FODMAPs cause bloating, gas, and other symptoms as they ferment in your gut?&amp;nbsp;
In today’s episode, Dr. Will Bulsiewicz, ZOE’S U.S. medical director and a board-certified gastroenterologist, teaches us about FODMAPs and how to tell if a low-FODMAP diet could be right for you.&amp;nbsp;
If you want to uncover the right foods for your body, head to zoe.</description></item><item><title>How body fat impacts health and aging | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530099/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530099/</guid><description>Podcast Description As we age, the distribution of our body fat changes, particularly around menopause.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Most people think of body fat as bad, but fat tissue plays a number of hugely important roles in our health.
In today’s episode of ZOE Science and Nutrition, Jonathan is joined by Dr. Sarah Berry and Prof. Deborah Clegg. Together, they debunk the myth that fat is bad, enlighten us about why body fat is distributed where it is, and explore the differences in fat distribution between men and women.</description></item><item><title>Exercise myths busted: Practical steps to sustain your health | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530098/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Admit it, exercise isn't everyone's favorite pastime. Of course, our ancestors weren't hitting the gym by choice — our evolution has wired us to stay active, and this natural activity actually slows down the aging process. The good news is that you can achieve the benefits without feeling like you're "exercising."
In today’s episode, Prof. Daniel Lieberman debunks exercise myths. He also teaches us how exercise impacts our health and how learning from our evolution can unlock the secrets of a longer life.</description></item><item><title>Does ZOE work? Here's what our latest trial results show | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530096/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530096/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’ve been working for the past 2 years on a randomized controlled trial of ZOE membership.&amp;nbsp;
Participants used personalized nutrition advice to try to improve their health — and the results are fascinating.&amp;nbsp;
In today’s episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition, Jonathan, Sarah, and Tim ask: How did ZOE hold up as part of this trial?
If you want to uncover the right foods for your body, head to zoe.</description></item><item><title>We risked it all! Does ZOE work? Here's what our latest trial results show | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530097/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530097/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’ve been working for the past 2 years on a randomized controlled trial of ZOE membership.&amp;nbsp;
Participants used personalized nutrition advice to try to improve their health — and the results are fascinating.&amp;nbsp;
In today’s episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition, Jonathan, Sarah, and Tim ask: How did ZOE hold up as part of this trial?
If you want to uncover the right foods for your body, head to zoe.</description></item><item><title>How to prevent heart disease, according to science | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530094/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Heart disease is among the top five causes of death globally, and it’s the first in the United States and United Kingdom. In the U.S., it causes 1 in 5 deaths.
But what is heart disease, exactly? Can we take steps to avoid it? Prof. Eric Rimm, of the Harvard T.H. Chan School of Public Health, is here to enlighten us.&amp;nbsp;
In today’s episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition, Jonathan and Eric explore what we can do to reduce our chances of getting heart disease.</description></item><item><title>The surprising truth about lectins | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530001/</guid><description>Podcast Description What are lectins, and are they dangerous? These “antinutrients” have come under attack and were recently the subject of a dietary fad fueled by a popular book. As always, there’s more to the story.
In today’s episode, Jonathan is joined by Dr. Will Bulsiewicz to dive deep into the world of lectins. They dissect questionable studies, debunk myths, and offer expert advice about how to approach foods containing these misunderstood compounds.</description></item><item><title>Aging and longevity reimagined: Is mindfulness the secret? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can the power of your thoughts help defy aging? Could your mind help improve your eyesight or even heal wounds faster?&amp;nbsp;
These ideas might seem far-fetched, but our guest, Harvard Professor Ellen Langer, has spent four decades uncovering the real science behind this.
In this episode, discover how to harness your mind-body connection to enhance your well-being.
Ellen Langer is an American professor of psychology at Harvard University. In 1981, she became the first woman ever to be tenured in psychology at Harvard.</description></item><item><title>Resistance training: How to stay strong as you age | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you feel like your muscles are shrinking or getting weaker? Many people gradually lose muscle mass as they get older. And this leads to an increased risk of falls, osteoporosis, and fractures.&amp;nbsp;
When it comes to your muscles, it’s a case of use them or lose them. But what is the most effective way to use our muscles and maintain strength? Ex-bodybuilder and professor of exercise science Brad Schoenfeld tells us how.</description></item><item><title>The surprising link between dementia and oral health | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530004/</guid><description>Podcast Description More than 50 systemic health conditions — including Alzheimer’s, diabetes, and heart disease — are associated with oral disease.&amp;nbsp;
The link between systemic and oral conditions is always microbial, inflammatory, or both. So, how can we look after our gums to improve our health?
In today’s episode, Jonathan and Prof. Alp Kantarci pose the question: How does the health of your oral cavity shape your general health?
Dr. Alp Kantarci is a professor, scientist, dentist, oral health researcher, periodontist, dental implant surgeon, and senior member of staff at the Forsyth Institute, an independent research institute that focuses on the connections between oral health and overall wellness.</description></item><item><title>Unlock longevity: Dr. Peter Attia's essential strategies | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Peter Attia doesn’t want a slow death. He doesn’t want his final years to be defined by poor mental and physical faculties that only worsen as the years roll by. But, by making changes to his lifestyle today, he’s taking control of his health tomorrow.
In today’s episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition, Jonathan and Peter ask: How can you maintain your health as you age?&amp;nbsp;
Download our FREE guide — Top 10 Tips to Live Healthier: https://zoe.</description></item><item><title>Cardio exercise: How much do you really need? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Not all of us want to go to the gym 5 times a week, but what if there was a way to do quick, short high intensity 20 second exercises and still reap benefits - or does that sound too good to be true?
Javier and Jonathan break this down as they look at recent studies and results, optimizing exercise routines to achieve the desired health benefits, taking into account factors like intensity, duration, and frequency as well as discussing the effect of working from home vs commuting to the office.</description></item><item><title>Gut microbiome testing: What can it reveal about your health? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Your gut microbiome, a bustling community of microorganisms, is a vital player in your overall health. It doesn’t just impact your digestive system —&amp;nbsp;it has a profound influence on your brain health and well-being.
However, the gut microbiome is a complex, long misunderstood realm, and figuring out how it affects daily life can leave even the most dedicated health enthusiasts scratching their heads.&amp;nbsp;
Here at ZOE, we’ve transformed our understanding of this bustling microbial world, where both “good” and “bad” gut bacteria reside.</description></item><item><title>The shocking damage ultra-processed foods cause to your brain | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530008/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s been a surge in our consumption of ultra-processed foods, especially in the United Kingdom and the United States, where these foods contribute about two-thirds of people’s caloric intake. Also a cause for concern is emerging evidence of ultra-processed foods’ detrimental effect on our brain health and overall well-being.
When most of our calories come from ultra-processed foods, the risk of chronic physical and mental health conditions escalates. Scientists are now uncovering the intricate mechanisms behind this relationship, particularly concerning the effects of these foods on our brains.</description></item><item><title>Food before exercise: What does science say? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get science-based nutrition advice straight to your inbox: https://bit.ly/3ExWxCG Most of us like to have breakfast before we exercise in the morning, but what happens if we don’t eat anything first? The issue goes beyond weight loss and exercise timing to involve blood sugar, insulin sensitivity, and other — perhaps unexpected — aspects of your health.
In today’s short episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition, Jonathan and Professor Javier Gonzalez ask: Should we exercise on an empty stomach?</description></item><item><title>Skin aging and acne: What you should do | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530010/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a listener to this show, you’ve probably heard of the gut microbiome. But did you know that your skin has its own microbiome?&amp;nbsp;
Recent evidence suggests that these microbiomes are vital for our skin health. So, what should we do? Which foods make an impact?&amp;nbsp;
And if we want our skin to look healthier, how about those collagen supplements that many of you have asked us about?&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>The great calorie deception: Are food labels misleading? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Millions of us are counting calories every day. But do we know if those numbers truly reflect the energy we get from eating?
It’s about time that we debunked the “one-size-fits-all” approach to calorie counting and unmasked the outdated methodologies that contribute to inaccuracies in food labeling.
In today’s episode, Jonathan and Dr. Sarah Berry ask: How exactly do we measure calories, and is calorie counting actually effective?</description></item><item><title>Antibiotics: The surprising truth about probiotics and what to do instead | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Antibiotics are one of the greatest discoveries of the 21st century. Since their inception, they’ve saved countless lives, but these miracle drugs come at a cost. In some cases, they can seriously affect your health or can even be life-threatening.
In today’s episode, Jonathan puts himself under the microscope. After an injury forced him to take antibiotics, he shows you the effect they had on his own gut bacteria.</description></item><item><title>Butter vs. margarine: What does science say? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Whether you’re frying, baking, or topping your toast, most of you will eat either butter or margarine at some point today. The fact that these spreads are such a staple means that we need to know their effects on our health. And It might surprise you to learn that this impact has changed quite dramatically over the past 20 years.
In today’s short episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition, Jonathan and Dr.</description></item><item><title>Healthy aging: The surprising power of your social life | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530014/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Unfortunately, many of us spend our later years in poor health. But is this avoidable? And can we actually increase our healthy years?
While aging is inevitable, there are steps we can take to minimize its effects on our health. And surprisingly, some of these steps have nothing to do with exercise or diet. Simply spending time with others can provide countless benefits to us as we age.</description></item><item><title>Chronic diarrhea? Here's what to do | Dr. Will Bulsiewicz | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530015/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’ve all had unpleasant toilet experiences in our time. It can be distressing to deal with and not something we like talking about.&amp;nbsp;
But when does normal diarrhea become chronic? And when do we need to seek medical care?&amp;nbsp;
In today’s episode, Jonathan and Dr Will ask what is chronic diarrhea and how can we rule out something more serious? Will also shares tricks of the trade to ease your symptoms and tells us how our amazing guts work to keep our whole body healthy.</description></item><item><title>The truth about organic food - according to science | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530016/</guid><description>Podcast Description What does "organic" food mean? And how do you know if something's organic?
Of course, foods tell you if they're organic in massive letters on the packaging. And they cost way more. But what makes a food organic? Is eating organic better for your health? And are the benefits worth the expense?
Luckily, Professor Tim Spector is here today with answers. Tim is one of the world's top 100 most cited scientists, a scientific co-founder of ZOE, and the author of the bestselling book Food for Life: The New Science of Eating Well.</description></item><item><title>What’s the best natural sugar substitute? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get science-based nutrition advice delivered straight to your inbox. https://bit.ly/46BPTYz&amp;nbsp;
Are you trying to eat less sugar? If you are, you might have tried a natural sugar alternative. Stevia, robinia honey, coconut sugar, agave… the list of these table sugar replacements seems to be growing day by day. But what even are these alternatives? Are they really natural? And do they offer us a healthier way of getting that sweet taste?</description></item><item><title>Is dairy good or bad for you? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530018/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Decades ago, there were reams of adverts instructing us to drink our milk so we don’t break our bones. But in the decades since, public opinion toward dairy is very different, and the scientific community has largely debunked these ideas.&amp;nbsp;
Many of the health-conscious among us choose to avoid it altogether. Our reasons range from a belief that dairy leads to inflammation, to acne, or even to an increased risk of heart attack due to high levels of saturated fat.</description></item><item><title>The truth about menopause supplements | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530019/</guid><description>Podcast Description More than half of women who go through menopause find its symptoms distressing. In fact, 10% leave their jobs because of the burden.
It’s no wonder that a huge selection of supplements claim to relieve menopause’s unpleasant effects. But do they actually work? Which products are backed by clinical evidence, and which are just “menowashing”?
In today’s short episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition, Jonathan and Dr. Sarah Berry ask: What’s the evidence behind menopause supplements?</description></item><item><title>How snacking impacts your health | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Evidence shows that all over the world, people are snacking more — with the United Kingdom and the United States leading the way in unhealthy snacking habits.&amp;nbsp;
But what exactly counts as a snack? And is all snacking unhealthy?
Snacking can be a confusing and controversial topic. There are various opinions and myths about what's good for you. Many people struggle to make healthy choices, while others may be unaware of the impact of snacking habits on their gut health and overall well-being.</description></item><item><title>How to stop diarrhea and what NOT to do | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530021/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’ve all wrestled with diarrhea at some point. It comes in many forms. And being able to read these differences can help us understand what’s going on inside us and how we should treat it.&amp;nbsp;
In today’s short episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition, Jonathan and Dr. Will ask: What are the health risks associated with diarrhea, and how can we treat it?&amp;nbsp;
Follow ZOE on Instagram.
If you want to uncover the right foods for your body, head to joinzoe.</description></item><item><title>The menstrual cycle decoded: Lifestyle tips to ease your symptoms, with Hazel Wallace | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530022/</guid><description>Podcast Description How much do you know about menstrual cycles? About half of us are more informed than the other half. The menstrual cycle has great significance, affecting various aspects of health. And more than 90% of people who get their periods experience premenstrual symptoms. However, misconceptions and limited understandings abound, leaving many people in the dark.
In today’s episode, we’re joined by Hazel Wallace. She’s a medical doctor, nutritionist, and author of The Female Factor.</description></item><item><title>Conquer IBS: 3 steps to healthier digestion | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Irritable bowel syndrome (IBS) is a lot more common than you might think. In fact, it affects 1 in 10 people globally. Yet there are still a lot of questions about why it occurs and how best to treat it.&amp;nbsp;
Could new research connecting gut health to mental health help us unravel its mysteries?
In today’s short episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition, Jonathan and Dr. Will ask: What exactly is IBS, and how does it connect to our brains?</description></item><item><title>Protein &amp; exercise: The secrets of healthy aging? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530024/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530024/</guid><description>Podcast Description As we age, our bodies undergo numerous changes, including a decline in muscle mass and cognitive function. For many of us, exercise and diet play crucial roles in maintaining our health and well-being.&amp;nbsp;
But how can the protein we eat affect our abilities to exercise and stay healthy as we age?
It can be difficult to separate fact from fiction when it comes to the effects of protein. How much do we need?</description></item><item><title>The surprising health impact of eating too fast | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530025/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530025/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’ve probably all been reprimanded for eating too fast at the dinner table or suffered the dreaded “itis” from eating way too much food at a family gathering. Our society and the systems we’ve developed to feed it have ballooned to such a point that they easily override our natural bodily systems that tell us when we’ve had enough to eat.&amp;nbsp;
When nearly&amp;nbsp;50% of the United States population&amp;nbsp;is projected to have obesity by 2030, can something as simple as changing the speed with which we eat really be an effective tool for weight loss and sustaining a healthy body?</description></item><item><title>HRT for menopause: is it safe? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530026/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Menopause is a time of significant hormonal changes which can lead to a range of symptoms that can severely impact quality of life for many women. So, a drug that promises to reduce these symptoms is incredibly welcome, but it has been steeped in controversy.
HRT (Hormone replacement therapy) has been widely debated, with conflicting information about its effectiveness, with some suggesting HRT is outright dangerous. In fact, a massive study twenty years ago linked it to an increased risk of breast cancer.</description></item><item><title>Omega-3 supplements: why you're (probably) wasting your money | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530027/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Omega 3s,” - we’ve all seen the name Omega 3s advertised on labels from nuts to seeds and even eggs! But are these fats healthy for us, or is this just another food myth?
In today’s short episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition, Jonathan and Sarah ask: Is fish oil and omega 3 intake essential or is this just another food myth?
Follow ZOE on Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/zoe/
Download our FREE guide — Top 10 Tips to Live Healthier: https://zoe.</description></item><item><title>How ultra-processed foods wreak havoc on your body | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530028/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ultra-processed foods have become ubiquitous in modern diets. Many of us eat them regularly without understanding their potential impacts on our health.&amp;nbsp;
From hidden additives to addictive properties, these highly processed foods can pose risks.&amp;nbsp;
Navigating the complex world of ultra-processing can be challenging, and many people struggle to understand what to avoid, how to break unhealthy habits, and make positive changes to their health.
In today’s episode, Jonathan is joined by a special guest, Dr.</description></item><item><title>Why eating nuts makes you healthier, according to science | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530029/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530029/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s short episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition, Jonathan and Sarah ask: If nuts are so full of fat, can they really be good for us?
There is no shortage of variety when it comes to the mighty (yet humble) nut and the ways we consume them. Dried, chopped, made into butter or roasted (over an open fire, anyone?) these little guys provide the nutrients our brains and bodies need in surprisingly high quantities.</description></item><item><title>Protein: are you getting enough? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530030/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 12:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Proteins, carbs, and fats …&amp;nbsp; most people understand what the last two are. Carbs are sugars, and fat is, well, fat. It's protein that’s so important to our diets, but so often misunderstood —&amp;nbsp;by the general public, that is.
Since the 1950s and 1960s, scientists have been measuring how protein affects our performance, how it supports and maintains the body’s structure, and how best to incorporate it into our diets.</description></item><item><title>Trans fats: how worried should you be? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530031/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trans fats have a bad reputation. But we now know a lot more about these fats than we did when the first horror stories about them emerged.&amp;nbsp;
So, based on the latest science, just how worried should we be?
Listen to today’s short episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition to find out.&amp;nbsp;
Follow ZOE on Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/zoe/
Download our FREE guide — Top 10 Tips to Live Healthier: https://zoe.</description></item><item><title>'Miracle' weight loss drug Ozempic is approved. But does it work? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530032/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530032/</guid><description>Podcast Description A miracle weight loss drug that’s approved in the US and the UK and has few side effects?
Ozempic is going viral on social media. Users are posting dramatic before and after pictures of their weight loss. An Ozempic trend is allegedly blossoming in Hollywood, and famous personalities like Elon Musk claim to have taken it.&amp;nbsp;
Many remain doubtful, dismissing the craze as just another internet scam preying on people’s insecurities.</description></item><item><title>Nightshade vegetables: hazard or health food? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530033/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nightshade vegetables —&amp;nbsp;even the name is ominous. Some people believe they exacerbate arthritis and can cause inflammation. So, should we avoid them?
In today’s short episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition, Jonathan and Will ask: What are nightshade vegetables, and how can they benefit our bodies?
Download our FREE guide — Top 10 Tips to Live Healthier: https://zoe.com/freeguide Studies referenced in the episode:
Potato glycoalkaloids and adverse effects in humans: an ascending dose study&amp;nbsp;Effect of red pepper on symptoms of irritable bowel syndrome: preliminary study&amp;nbsp;Treatment of arthritis with topical capsaicin: a double-blind trial&amp;nbsp;In defence of potatoes: How resistant starch from potatoes affects the gut microbiota&amp;nbsp;Health benefits of eating tomatoes emerge&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>Michael Mosley: 4 habits that changed his life | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530034/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530034/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you had to do just one thing to improve your health, what would it be?
Our busy lives mean it can be difficult to keep up healthy habits, and with so much conflicting advice out there it’s tricky to separate fact from fiction. In today’s episode, Jonathan is joined by medical doctor, journalist, and presenter Michael Mosley, who is alongside ZOE regular Tim Spector, to discuss Michael’s four key habits to improve our health.</description></item><item><title>Everything you've heard about lactose is wrong | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530035/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lactose is usually only discussed in the context of intolerance. This intolerance can make us feel bloated, gassy and uncomfortable. But from cow’s milk to yoghurt and even breast milk, lactose is everywhere! So, can it really be that bad for us?
In today’s short episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition, we’re joined by Dr Will B. to find out.&amp;nbsp;
Follow ZOE on Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/zoe/
Download our FREE guide — Top 10 Tips to Live Healthier: https://zoe.</description></item><item><title>Best of gut health - anniversary edition | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530036/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gut health is a topic we talk about a lot at ZOE. The gut doesn’t just fight disease, it boosts our mood, processes energy and so much more. Today’s bonus episode journeys through everything we’ve learnt about gut health so far. And what a myth-busting journey it is!
In this episode, Jonathan delves into the microbiome, highlighting the most useful tips from conversations with ZOE’s U.S. Medical Director and resident gut health expert, Will Bulsiewicz, and Tim Spector, one of top 100 most cited scientists and author Food for Life.</description></item><item><title>The future is here: AI and personalized healthcare with Eric Topol | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530037/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530037/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you were to ask Siri, Alexa, or ChatGPT for medical advice right now, that would be a terrible idea.&amp;nbsp;
But with recent developments in technology, this looks set to change. AI has become more intelligent, wearable devices - more accurate, and personalized medicine - increasingly mainstream.
But is any of this safe? Should we really trust machines with our health? And will any of this actually happen?</description></item><item><title>Eggs: are they good for me? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530038/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eggs are nutrient-dense and have a long shelf life. Compared with many other protein sources, they’re on the cheaper side. But they’re not as popular as they used to be. And a lot of this comes down to a debate about cholesterol.
In today’s short episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition, Jonathan and Sarah ask: What’s the truth about eggs?
Follow ZOE on Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/zoe/
Download our FREE guide — Top 10 Tips to Live Healthier: https://zoe.</description></item><item><title>How to maximize health in your later years | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530039/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why do some people remain fit and healthy in their later years while others become increasingly frail?&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Researchers from Kings College London have been following thousands of twins for 30 years in an effort to understand how each of us ages differently. And some of their findings will surprise you!
In today’s episode, Jonathan speaks to Claire Steves to better understand what all this means, shedding light on how aging works and what we can do about it:</description></item><item><title>The ultimate guide to constipation | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530040/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530040/</guid><description>Podcast Description The formal definition for constipation is ‘Having fewer than three bowel movements per week’. But, did you know that you can have a bowel movement every day and still be constipated? Recent data has shown that a quarter of people worldwide have at one point reported symptoms, suggesting that there is so much more to constipation than simply infrequent bowel movements.
In today’s short-ish episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition, Jonathan and Will attempt to dispel some misconceptions about constipation and empower you to have better bowel movements.</description></item><item><title>How to eat well on a budget | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530041/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530041/</guid><description>Podcast Description The cost of living has soared. Energy prices have doubled, and food costs have gone up enormously. As a result, the weekly shopping bill can be shocking.&amp;nbsp;
For some, this is merely an inconvenience. But many others face the awful choice between heating their home and maintaining their usual diet. The consequence is that many of us are throwing cheaper ingredients into our shopping baskets to save money.&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>Signs of an unhealthy gut | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530042/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our gut helps fight disease. It processes energy for us and boosts our mood. So, having a healthy gut is extremely important – but there’s still a lot we don’t know. Gut biome tests are a new, exciting technology, but are they the be-all and end-all for dietary decision-making? And are there simpler ways — and tastier ways, perhaps — to tell what’s happening inside our bodies?
In today’s short episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition, Jonathan and Dr.</description></item><item><title>How to improve blood sugar control with exercise | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530043/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Blood sugar is one of the rare nutrition topics where everyone agrees: We should avoid big peaks and dips and aim for a steady curve.&amp;nbsp;
Spikes cause inflammation, accelerate aging, and lead to type 2 diabetes. Crashes make us feel moody and tired, and crave foods we don’t need.&amp;nbsp;
We can control our blood sugar through what and how we eat. But something else affects our blood sugar — physical activity.</description></item><item><title>Foods to lower your cholesterol | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530044/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530044/</guid><description>Podcast Description More than half of us have high cholesterol —&amp;nbsp;and new research suggests that having even slightly raised levels in our 30s could significantly increase our chances of developing heart disease. Medication is a common fix, but it comes with side effects. So, today we’re looking at how much changing our diets can help.&amp;nbsp;
In this short (ish) episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition, Jonathan and Sarah ask: Can we lower our cholesterol by changing our diets?</description></item><item><title>Should we be worried about strep A? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530045/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 14:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530045/</guid><description>Podcast Description This year, cases of an invasive bacterial infection are rising earlier than usual in the US, the UK and other countries across Europe.&amp;nbsp;
The group A Streptococcus bacteria - commonly known as Strep A - usually only causes mild illness. However, things have become severe in some cases, with several children dying in recent weeks.
So, should we be worried? And what symptoms should we look out for to help us identify this illness in ourselves and our families?</description></item><item><title>How to make New Year’s resolutions stick | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530046/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to 2023! Whether you partied last night or went to bed early, we’re all in the same boat: a new year means thinking about new year’s resolutions.&amp;nbsp;
This tradition dates back 4000 years, so it’s certainly stood the test of time. But are new year’s resolutions a good idea? Or simply a get way to set yourself up to fail?&amp;nbsp;
Perhaps science has something to say about this.</description></item><item><title>The health benefits of eating together | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530047/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530047/</guid><description>Podcast Description You might think what you eat and when are the only factors that play into the health of your diet. But recent research has shown that who you eat with can also play a role. And it could even make your food taste better!
In today’s short episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition, Jonathan and Sarah ask: Can eating with other people really improve your food?&amp;nbsp;
Studies referenced in today’s episode:&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>Tim Spector’s journey from health crisis to healthy eating - a chapter from Food for Life | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530048/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530048/</guid><description>Podcast Description What should I have for dinner? A question you no doubt ask yourself daily. But I bet you don't spend too long coming up with an answer. ZOE's scientific co-founder, Tim Spector, has been trying to answer this question for a decade.
If you're a regular listener, you probably know him well. Five years ago, he published the best-selling book, The Diet Myth, and just last month, he released the follow-up, Food for Life, the New Science of Eating Well.</description></item><item><title>Should you worry about gluten? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530049/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530049/</guid><description>Podcast Description The last decade saw a rise in gluten-free diets. But the number of us with diagnosed gluten intolerance each year hasn’t changed. Eliminating gluten is the only treatment for those with celiac disease, but the rest of us could be doing more harm than good by embracing ultra-processed, gluten-free foods.&amp;nbsp;
In today’s short episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition, Jonathan and Will ask: Should you be worried about gluten?</description></item><item><title>The secrets of good sleep | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530050/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530050/</guid><description>Podcast Description We all know how good it feels to drift into deep sleep and wake up feeling refreshed.&amp;nbsp;
The positive effects of a good night’s sleep affect every aspect of our lives. We feel energetic, focused, and ready to take on the day’s challenges.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
But the long-term effects of bad sleep are less known. It turns out, they have a huge impact on our health and even how long we live.</description></item><item><title>Heartburn: why it happens and what you can do | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530051/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530051/</guid><description>Podcast Description The acid in your stomach is so powerful it can dissolve metal. Luckily, your stomach is fine-tuned to deal with its acidic fluid, but the rest of your body isn’t quite as hardy. So, if acid escapes from your stomach and reaches your esophagus, it can cause a painful sensation in the chest —&amp;nbsp;this is heartburn. It isn’t rare, with more than 1 billion people suffering from it globally.</description></item><item><title>The truth about vitamin supplements | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530052/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Good information about vitamins is hard to find. With over 70% of Americans and 40% of Brits using them, it's a hugely lucrative market, which means numerous voices in the media and online pusing a pro-vitamin agenda. All without the scientific evidence to support their claims.&amp;nbsp;
So do we need vitamins to lead a healthy life? Or could these supplements actually cause serious health complications?
In this episode, Jonathan speaks with Prof.</description></item><item><title>Menopause: Does diet play a part? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530053/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530053/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's a condition that affects half the population, but there are countless unanswered questions about menopause. The symptoms vary significantly from person to person, including sleep problems, hot flashes, weight gain, and an increased risk of heart disease.&amp;nbsp;
In one of the largest studies to date, ZOE researchers have uncovered a link between menopause and our diets —&amp;nbsp;and this could hold the key to reducing the severity of menopause symptoms.</description></item><item><title>How your gut affects your mental health | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530054/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530054/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a lab in Ireland, a group of scientists stand around a stainless steel table. One of them is holding a device, not unlike a small turkey baster. His free hand plunges into a box on the table and retrieves a mouse.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Using his device, he administers the brown solution within…rectally.&amp;nbsp;
This unfortunate soul has just received a fecal microbiota transplant. The donor was not another mouse but a human being.</description></item><item><title>Cooking oils: what to use and when | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530055/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530055/</guid><description>Podcast Description We use it to fry, roast, or dress a salad. Cooking oil is a kitchen staple. But it's hard to know which is healthiest for each scenario.
In today’s short episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition, Jonathan and Sarah ask: what cooking oils should you use and when?&amp;nbsp;
Follow ZOE on Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/zoe/
Download our FREE guide — Top 10 Tips to Live Healthier: https://zoe.com/freeguide Studies referenced in the episode:</description></item><item><title>Will fermented foods improve my gut health? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530056/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fermentation is a hot craze in fancy restaurants around the world. And fermented foods, like kombucha and kimchi, are even sold in corner stores.&amp;nbsp;
Listeners of this show will have heard that fermented foods might benefit our gut health. But these foods make us uneasy. The idea of letting food rot, then eating it goes against everything our parents taught us. So, is fermentation scary and dangerous?&amp;nbsp;
This episode will show you why it's not only safe but beneficial to eat fermented foods, and that fermenting foods is something you can try at home.</description></item><item><title>How fasting affects energy and mood - The Big IF Dailies | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530057/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever lost your temper because you were hungry? Feeling short-tempered when you’re overdue a bite to eat is an almost universal experience, with its own adjective - ‘hangry’. If missing just one meal turns you into a grump, you may think that fasting would turn you into the Incredible Hulk. However, new data suggests this might not be the case.&amp;nbsp;
In this daily episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition, Dr Sarah Berry joins Jonathan to answer the question: how does fasting affect your energy and mood?</description></item><item><title>3 meals a day VS little and often - The Big IF Dailies | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530058/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can you make it from lunch to dinner without a snack? Tradition tells us that three meals a day is the right way to eat, but times have changed, and many of us now choose to eat little and often. The debate continues as to which is better.&amp;nbsp;
Today, we discuss new data that could settle this once and for all.
In this daily episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition, Jonathan is joined by Dr Sarah Berry to answer the question: should we eat little and often or 3 meals a day?</description></item><item><title>Gut bacteria &amp; fasting: meet the night crew - The Big IF Dailies | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530059/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nowadays, food can be delivered to your door with just a few swipes of your smartphone. The result? Many of us eat more frequently, at any time of the day. And this may have some downsides. New research shows that for our gut bacteria to perform their helpful activities, we may have to embrace the dietary patterns of our ancestors.&amp;nbsp;
In today’s daily episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition, Jonathan is joined by Tim Spector to answer the question: How do gut bacteria repair your gut while fasting?</description></item><item><title>Does calorie counting work? - The Big IF Dailies | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530060/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Food package labels can be complex. With so much information, many of us set a beeline for the calorie number, but there’s more going on in food than just the amount of energy. How much value is there in counting calories, and should you continue? The latest science could make you reconsider.&amp;nbsp;
In today’s daily episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition, Jonathan is joined by Dr Sarah Berry to answer the question: Does calorie counting work?</description></item><item><title>Should you avoid late-night snacks? - The Big IF Dailies | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530061/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530061/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’ve all been there at least once, hovering by the fridge and looking for something to graze on just before bed. What you eat after dark can disrupt your sleep and digestion. Yet new evidence suggests that when we snack is less important than what we snack on, so suddenly that midnight snack may not be a guilty pleasure after all.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
In today’s daily episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition, Jonathan is joined by Dr Sarah Berry to answer the question: should you avoid late-night snacks?</description></item><item><title>What breaks a fast? - The Big IF Dailies | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530062/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fasting has been shown to improve our metabolism, slow disease and potentially increase our life span. While world religions have practiced fasting for millennia, the trend of fasting has soared in popularity in the last decade.&amp;nbsp;
Not all fasts are made equally and there are a lot of different rules to follow. Some purists argue that you’re only allowed water while fasting others believe there can be more flexibility during your period of abstinence.</description></item><item><title>5 foods I got wrong - Tim Spector | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530063/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Where were you in 2015? President Obama was in the White House, The UK was a member of the European Union, and you couldn’t escape Bruno Mars's global smash: Uptown Funk. More importantly, 2015 marked the release of Tim Spector’s first book: The Diet Myth.
If you think the world has felt different since 2015, wait until you hear about the advances in nutritional science. Since then, Tim has had a chance to rethink his position on dietary staples like bread, milk, ultra-processed foods and more.</description></item><item><title>What does science say about intermittent fasting? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530064/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530064/</guid><description>Podcast Description It seems like every day, someone new mentions intermittent fasting. But what is it, exactly?&amp;nbsp;
There are myriad options —&amp;nbsp;from the 5:2 diet, with two days of extreme calorie restriction each week, to the warrior diet, which involves eating only raw fruit during the day and a mammoth feast at night. Whatever the approach, intermittent fasting involves restricting the window of time when you eat.
Supporters evangelise the benefits, promising weight loss, disease prevention, and even life extension.</description></item><item><title>Fiber: Why it’s important and how to get more of it | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530065/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Diets rich in fiber are associated with good heart health and metabolic wellbeing. This type of diet can do wonders for our gut microbiome. With so many benefits, relatively low cost, and high availability, fiber should be a staple nutrient in our diets —&amp;nbsp;but most of us have a deficiency.
&amp;nbsp;
In today’s short episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition, Jonathan and Will ask: If fiber is so good for us, why are we not eating enough of it?</description></item><item><title>Heart health and aging: Do our blood vessels hold the secret to long life? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530066/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530066/</guid><description>Podcast Description 60,000 miles long. That’s the length of the tube system inside us that transports blood, oxygen, and nutrients to the cells in our body.&amp;nbsp;
If these tubes fail, the result can be fatal. In some cases, it’s a heart attack. In others, it’s a stroke, where the blood supply to the brain is disrupted, and brain cells are damaged or killed.&amp;nbsp;
Heart attacks and strokes are a major cause of death in developed countries - but we can take action to reduce the risks.</description></item><item><title>Gas &amp; Bloating: the causes &amp; how to stop it | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530067/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Most of us are familiar with the unpleasant feeling of being bloated. It can happen after eating specific foods or when you experience slower bowel movements. Sometimes, it can be a symptom of an underlying health condition.&amp;nbsp;
To take a closer look at issues related to gas and bloating, we’ve invited a special guest this week: superstar gastroenterologist and Zoe’s US Medical Director Will Bulsiewicz.
In today’s short episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition, Jonathan and Will ask: what are the main causes of gas bloating and how do we stop it?</description></item><item><title>How your food choices affect the planet | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530068/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our planet is overheating. Human society is creating too much carbon dioxide, stopping the sun’s warmth from escaping back into space. As earth gets hotter, its ice caps are melting, causing sea levels to rise, and submerging entire communities. Floods, droughts, and wildfires are already becoming much more common.
Some effects of climate change are now irreversible, but there is still hope, and adjusting what we eat might play a bigger part than you’d imagine.</description></item><item><title>High cholesterol foods: what really happens when you eat them? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530069/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cholesterol in our food has a bad reputation. Many of us think of it as something to try to cut it out of our diet completely.&amp;nbsp; Yet new research could redeem eggs and other cholesterol-rich foods.&amp;nbsp;
In today’s short episode of ZOE Science and Nutrition, Jonathan and Sarah ask: what happens when you eat high cholesterol foods?&amp;nbsp;
Follow ZOE on Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/zoe/
Download our FREE guide — Top 10 Tips to Live Healthier: https://zoe.</description></item><item><title>How to make your body clock work for you | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530070/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530070/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s world, we increasingly live our lives late into the night. Whether it's work obligations, socializing, or being glued to a screen, we ignore the sun's rise and fall.&amp;nbsp;
But most of us are unaware that a clock is ticking away inside us.&amp;nbsp;
It uses light to keep time and tells us when to sleep and eat. Should we listen? Or is this biological clock simply a relic from a past time?</description></item><item><title>Artificial sweeteners - worse than sugar? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530071/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Artificial sweeteners are everywhere. Not only in diet soft drinks but in many foods that you wouldn’t expect. You’ve probably eaten some today without realising.
Sweeteners have been around for over a hundred years yet remain the subject of much debate. It's hard to know how they stack up next to the alternatives.
In today’s short episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition, Jonathan and Sarah ask: are artificial sweeteners worse than sugar?</description></item><item><title>Can spices improve your health? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530072/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kanchan Koya grew up in a house filled with wonderful fragrances from the spices simmering on her grandmother’s stove. In India, it was a common belief that spices were more than just pleasant tastes. Ancient wisdom said they had medicinal properties, and it was common for household medicine cabinets to store dried spices, not pills.
Kanchan grew up to become a molecular biologist, studying in the US at Harvard Medical School.</description></item><item><title>How healthy are meat and dairy alternatives? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530073/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vegan diets are increasingly popular. As more of us reduce our animal product consumption, countless new meat and dairy alternatives appear on our supermarket shelves. Manufacturers market these products as healthy options (unsurprisingly), but perhaps we shouldn’t be so quick to trust them…&amp;nbsp;
In today’s short episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition, Jonathan and Sarah ask: are meat and dairy alternatives healthier than their animal-based counterparts?
Follow ZOE on Instagram: &amp;nbsp;https://www.</description></item><item><title>How food can improve your mood | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530074/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530074/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’ve all felt the effects of food on our mood, so it would stand to reason that dietary intervention for mental health would be well studied and a regularly deployed treatment.&amp;nbsp;
But this is far from reality, as historically, psychiatry was only concerned with what happened from the neck up.
In today’s episode, Jonathan is joined by Felice Jacka, Professor of Nutritional Psychiatry and Director of the Food &amp;amp; Mood Centre at Deakin University.</description></item><item><title>Can you reverse damage from a bad diet? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530075/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530075/</guid><description>Podcast Description A recent study claims that eating a hotdog reduces life expectancy by 38 minutes, and eating salmon could extend it by 70 minutes. At face value, this data implies you can eat your way to immortality. Taken with a pinch of salt, it suggests you can offset the harm from poor dietary choices. But does food really work this way?
In today’s short episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition, Jonathan and Sarah ask: can you reverse the effects of a bad diet?</description></item><item><title>How to control blood sugar spikes | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530076/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Biochemist Jessie Inchauspe heads into work one morning at a genetics lab in California. During the morning meeting, management offer staff the chance to self-test a new medical device. Jessie accepts.&amp;nbsp;
She couldn’t have known this device would take her on a journey of discovery to reshape her health and help countless others do the same.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
The device was a continuous blood sugar monitor, and it was this, combined with her academic background, and a remarkable willingness to use herself as a lab rat, that began a journey of discovery into how blood sugar affects our health.</description></item><item><title>Saturated fat: Monstrous or misunderstood? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530077/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530077/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you're confused about the health effects of fats, you are not alone. You've probably read the headlines - fats are killing us! Then found claims they’re actually healthy in the same publication the following week.
Saturated fats have been touted as the worst of all.&amp;nbsp;
While there’s ambiguity around other fat sources, saturated fats are universally demonized.
But are they really the super villain we've been led to believe?</description></item><item><title>This is what the Keto Diet does to your body... | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530078/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Keto has been promoted as a magic bullet for weight loss by its supporters and slammed as dangerous by its opponents. It's no surprise - completely removing almost all carbohydrates is not what most people consider ‘a balanced diet’.
With carbs off the table, Keto diets involve a dramatically increased fat intake. At the same time, drastically reducing carbs means starving our gut microbes of the fiber that feeds them.</description></item><item><title>Processed foods - convenient or catastrophic? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530079/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530079/</guid><description>Podcast Description The word ‘processed’ has become synonymous with being unhealthy. The mainstream media encourages us to detox from processed food or offers us ‘10 easy ways’ to stop eating it.&amp;nbsp;
But nearly everything we consume has undergone some type of processing.
In today’s short episode of ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition, Jonathan and Sarah ask: If most of what we eat is processed, can it really be that unhealthy for us?</description></item><item><title>Our ancestors’ diet: surprising discoveries from a 5000 year old iceman | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530080/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530080/</guid><description>Podcast Description A mummified man found in the mountains of Italy on a nutrition science podcast? Have we gone completely off track?&amp;nbsp;
We haven’t - we promise.&amp;nbsp;
This unfortunate soul could be the key that unlocks an entirely new understanding of human health.&amp;nbsp;
This mummy, discovered in an alpine snow drift by two hikers, gives us a remarkable glimpse into the surprising dietary choices of our ancestors.
In today’s episode, Jonathan discovers some secrets held by our ancestors by speaking to two outstanding guests:</description></item><item><title>Introducing: ZOE Shorts | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530081/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530081/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re excited for you to hear our NEW bitesize podcast: ZOE Shorts.
Some of you requested some short-form episodes, so we delivered!
In between the longer episodes, Jonathan teams up with world-leading nutrition researcher and podcast regular Dr Sarah Berry to tackle one hot topic from nutrition science in just 15 minutes.
From saturated fats to vitamins, time-restricted eating and much more, find out the history, the different sides of the argument and, of course, hear what the latest science says from ZOE Science and Nutrition.</description></item><item><title>Superfoods | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530082/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530082/</guid><description>Podcast Description From blueberries to salmon, kale to acai, it seems like anything and everything can be classed as a superfood these days.
Supposedly they can prevent cancer, reduce inflammation, and even help you live longer…
In today’s short episode of ZOE Science and Nutrition, Jonathan and Sarah look at the history of superfoods and ask: are some foods really more ‘super’ than others? Or is this just another marketing ploy?</description></item><item><title>Inflammation, aging and disease. What's food got to do with it? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530083/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530083/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a biological process that we need to stay alive. Yet too much of it leads to disease and a shorter life.&amp;nbsp;
Inflammation is the immune system’s response to an outside event it thinks is dangerous. This stimulus could be an injury, like falling off your bike or an infection by a virus or bacteria. But inflammation can also be triggered by our food in the hours after we eat.</description></item><item><title>Can bread be healthy? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530084/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 16:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530084/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s no exaggeration to say that bread shaped modern humanity - it was the cultivation of wheat for flour that transformed our ancestors from hunter-gatherers to city dwellers.&amp;nbsp;
Today, millions of us start the day with a slice of toast, and most lunches in the US and UK are wrapped in a slice of bread or a burger bun as a cheap, flexible, and delicious energy source.
But modern industrial processes designed to reduce the time and cost of baking mean today’s bread would be unrecognizable to our ancestors.</description></item><item><title>Is Coffee Healthy? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530085/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Coffee’s earliest consumption dates back millennia when the tribesmen of Ethiopia used its ground-up berries to help aid concentration during prayer.&amp;nbsp;
Arriving in Europe in the 17th century, Coffee quickly began to replace beer and wine as a favourite breakfast drink.&amp;nbsp;
In the 20th century, coffee was blamed for high blood pressure and heart attacks, and more recently linked to a rising epidemic of poor sleep.&amp;nbsp;
None of this has prevented coffee’s relentless rise.</description></item><item><title>Your Gut is Full of Bugs: Why This is Great News | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530086/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530086/</guid><description>Podcast Description You may have heard there are bugs in your gut. But do they matter?&amp;nbsp;
Today, the evidence shows the answer is a resounding yes. This ecosystem of tiny microbes living in our bodies is one of the most exciting areas in medical research, linked to everything from metabolic to mental health.
So while many of us have heard that gut health is essential, few of us understand why and what we should do to support our gut bacteria.</description></item><item><title>Fats and oils: What’s the real story? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530087/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we’re talking about fat, a delicious component of our food with a terrible reputation.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Fats have been broadly associated with weight gain and heart disease until recently.
A mountain of new scientific evidence suggests this is wrong and that it's not as simple as ‘all fat is bad’. Indeed, eating more healthy fat might actually reduce heart disease for many people.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
In today’s episode, Jonathan speaks to Dr Sarah Berry to learn about what science tells us today, whether it is possible to lose weight on a high-fat diet, what oils we should be cooking with, and the different types of fats.</description></item><item><title>Is exercise or nutrition more important for weight loss? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530088/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 07:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our transformation into coach potatoes happened in the blink of an eye. Only 100 years ago, most people relied on manual work to make their living.&amp;nbsp;
Today, things are different. Many of us live our lives in front of a screen. Online shopping and remote work mean some of us don’t need to leave the house at all. So how bad is this for us?&amp;nbsp;
The answer is now clear: Low levels of physical activity lead to an increased risk of disease and a lower quality of life in older age.</description></item><item><title>Menopause: How your body changes and what you can do | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530089/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 07:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530089/</guid><description>Podcast Description There's a condition that leads to an increased risk of heart disease, dementia, and early death that's been affecting people for as long as they've existed. The many symptoms can severely impact quality of life - ranging from headaches and memory problems to anxiety and weight gain.&amp;nbsp;
This condition affects more than half of the world's population, but unbelievably its rarely discussed and the scientific research that exists on it is limited.</description></item><item><title>Alcohol: Can it ever be healthy? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530090/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 07:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530090/</guid><description>Podcast Description For many of us, it's a ritual to help us wind down after a long day, an excuse to catch up with friends, or a lubricant to an awkward social situation. Alcohol can be delicious, but our relationship with it is often complicated.&amp;nbsp;
Good times with friends aren’t without sacrifice, and many of us feel the morning after impact of a few too many drinks. For an unfortunate minority, alcohol can lead to addiction and even death.</description></item><item><title>Is Dark Chocolate Good for Weight Loss? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530091/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 07:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530091/</guid><description>Podcast Description This plant has been used by human beings for thousands of years with samples found in 5000-year-old pottery discovered in the upper Amazon. The Mayans considered it a gift from the gods and used it in their sacred ceremonies, where it was believed to have mystical healing powers. For the Aztecs, it was worth more than gold and given to their victorious warriors.&amp;nbsp;
We are talking, of course, about chocolate.</description></item><item><title>Food Intolerances: What's the Story? | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530092/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 07:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530092/</guid><description>Podcast Description 1 in 5 people suffer from food intolerances, a figure that’s growing each year. As a result, people are eating increasingly restricted diets, removing dairy, gluten and many other foods from their plates. Unfortunately, they end up eating highly processed foods that damage their gut microbiome and lead to long-term health problems. Even with food restrictions, many people see limited improvements in their symptoms.
The whole topic of intolerance is full of pseudoscience, dubious blood tests, and miracle cures.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition | ZOE Science &amp; Nutrition</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6344530093/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6344530093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to the brand-new podcast from ZOE, the people behind the world's largest scale nutrition study.
ZOE Science &amp;amp; Nutrition is the podcast where the world’s top scientists explain the latest health, nutrition, and gut health research in terms we can all understand. So join us every other Thursday on this journey of scientific discovery!
Scientists featured in this trailer: Will Bulsiewicz &amp;amp; Tim Spector OBE. Follow ZOE on Instagram: https://www.</description></item></channel></rss>