<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>If You're Listening on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/if-youre-listening/</link><description>Recent content in If You're Listening on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 01:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/if-youre-listening/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Can Zelenskyy get the world to care about Ukraine again? | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ukraine's President Volodymyr Zelenskyy has a new problem. As well as fighting Russia, he also has to fight Israel and Hamas for the world's attention.
The shift in attention to Gaza has already meant Ukraine has lost crucial support.
The question is — can Zelenskyy get the world to care about Ukraine again? And if not, what will that mean for the war?
Subscribe to If You're Listening on the ABC Listen app.</description></item><item><title>What is China's "panda diplomacy"? | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080002/</guid><description>Podcast Description China's pandas are not just pandas. They're diplomats.
You're friendly to China? You get a panda. You criticise China? You get no pandas.
In recent years China has been hostile toward the West, with the most literal symbol of their displeasure being the withdrawal of their pandas from zoos around the world.
And yet, Chinese President Xi Jinping appears to be having a change of heart.
This may indicate something very important — a return to a more peaceful relationship with the West.</description></item><item><title>Can OpenAI save us from a robot apocalypse? | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080003/</guid><description>Podcast Description The world's most famous artificial intelligence company, OpenAI — the creator of ChatGPT — was set up to create a superintelligent AI, while at the same time safeguarding humanity from an omnipotent robot overlord which could enslave us all.
But last week the company fell into chaos. OpenAI fired its wunderkind CEO Sam Altman.
Just days later, under intense pressure, Sam Altman was put back in charge and the entire board was booted.</description></item><item><title>China's play to win the heart of the Pacific | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080004/</guid><description>Podcast Description China is using cash to try and shore up support in the Pacific.
In Honiara, the Solomon Islands capital, they just built most of the venues in the Pacific Games precinct.
And China is not alone. Like a geopolitical version of The Bachelor, China, Taiwan, Australia and the United States are all trying desperately to win Honiara's heart.
This tussle has caused panic in Taipei and Canberra, anger in Beijing and Washington, and actual violence in the Solomons.</description></item><item><title>How North Korea makes a fortune stealing crypto | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080005/</guid><description>Podcast Description As international sanctions have cut into North Korea's ability to import and export things, they've become desperate for cash.
They've been running crazy schemes to get it — smuggling, stealing, lying, cheating, swashbuckling — but that's nothing compared to what they make from stealing cryptocurrency.
In fact, most of their foreign currency now comes from stolen crypto.
So, can anything be done to stop the world's first nuclear-armed crypto bro, Kim Jong-un?</description></item><item><title>Can Israel rescue the hostages? | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080006/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Israeli hostages Hamas took back on October 7th still have not been rescued.
The 1976 Entebbe rescue mission is legendary and gave Israel a reputation — they get hostages back no matter what.
Now this reputation is putting enormous pressure on Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu to rescue the hostages again.
The question is — can he?
Subscribe to If You're Listening on the ABC Listen app.
Catch up on our series about the Israel-Gaza conflict on YouTube: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Who is Hezbollah, the group backing Hamas? | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080007/</guid><description>Podcast Description While Israel tries to defeat Hamas, they also have to worry about a much more dangerous paramilitary group on their northern border: Hezbollah.
The express purpose of Hezbollah, which formed 40 years ago, is also to eradicate Israel.
It would be a nightmare for Israel if Hezbollah swings in and backs Hamas up.
So where did Hezbollah form, why do they hate Israel, and what hand did Israel have in their creation?</description></item><item><title>How did Hamas catch Israel by surprise? | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080008/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Israeli Government has one of the most well-resourced intelligence communities in the world, specifically tasked with preventing attacks from Hamas.
So how did it fail to detect an operation that involved months of planning, meetings in multiple countries, and thousands of militants?
This is part two in our series on the Israel-Gaza conflict.
Subscribe to If You're Listening on the ABC Listen app.
Catch up on our series about the Israel-Gaza conflict on YouTube: https://www.</description></item><item><title>How a quadriplegic charity worker became the founder of Hamas | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last week, Hamas burst out of the Gaza Strip into southern Israel, killing at least 1,400 people, the vast majority of them Israeli civilians.
But Hamas' origins go back decades, to its founder Ahmed Yassin.
How did a disabled refugee from Gaza become one of the most influential men in Palestine?
And how did he take Hamas from obscurity to wresting control of the Gaza Strip?
Subscribe to If You're Listening on the ABC Listen app.</description></item><item><title>The ridiculous assassination plot that sent Haiti into chaos | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080010/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2021, a doctor from Florida met with a group of men to plan the overthrow of the Haitian President.
The plot triggered a series of events which led to the President's death, the almost total collapse of the government, and the rise of mob rule in Haiti.
So why is Kenya now being sent in to save the day?
Subscribe to If You're Listening on the ABC Listen app.</description></item><item><title>Should Elon Musk have stopped Ukraine attacking Russia? | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080011/</guid><description>Podcast Description In September last year, Elon Musk refused to let the Ukrainian military use his Starlink satellites to attack Russia.
Musk jumped on Twitter and posted “Starlink is meant for peaceful use only”. So how did we get into a situation where Elon Musk gets to personally decide whether a Ukrainian military operation succeeds or fails?
And was he justified in refusing to help? Subscribe to If You're Listening on the ABC Listen app.</description></item><item><title>The assassination that broke the bond between Canada and India | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hardeep Singh Nijjar was murdered in Vancouver in June.
Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau has just come out saying the Indian Government assassinated him.
India is, of course, denying it.
So who was Niijar? Why would anyone — much less the Indian Government — want to kill him?
And is there more to this story than meets the eye?
Subscribe to If You're Listening on the ABC Listen app.</description></item><item><title>Why Modi picked a fight over India's true name | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080013/</guid><description>Podcast Description When world leaders received their invitations to the 2023 G20 summit in New Delhi, everyone got a bit of a surprise. It referred to Narendra Modi as the Prime Minister of Bharat, not India.
The debate over the naming of India stretches back nearly 80 years, and tells an important story about the country's history.
And Modi's new push for a change in the constitution is just the latest in a series of political fights centred on race, religion and unity in India.</description></item><item><title>The race to build a petrol station on the moon | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080014/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080014/</guid><description>Podcast Description The US, Russia, China and India are all sending missions to the moon — and all to its totally unexplored south pole.
Why? Well, in order to make the next giant leap, we need to build a petrol station on the moon.
How a discovery made a century ago will allow us to use the moon as a stepping stone to explore the solar system.
Subscribe to If You're Listening on the ABC Listen app.</description></item><item><title>Is the century-long search for a weight loss drug over? | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080015/</guid><description>Podcast Description For a century society has bullied and shamed people into trying to lose weight, without much result.
Now, a seemingly accidental discovery by Danish pharmaceutical company Novo Nordisk may be the first weight loss drug that actually works.
People are hailing semaglutide, marketed under the names Ozempic or Wegovy, as a miracle weight loss drug — but it comes at a cost.
One clear winner is the Danish economy, as semaglutide has shot Novo Nordisk into the stratosphere as the most valuable company in all of Europe.</description></item><item><title>China cooked its population data. Now its economy is in crisis | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080016/</guid><description>Podcast Description China's economy is struggling. Similar things are happening across Asia but in China it's happening extremely fast.
And a big part of the reason why is the disastrous One Child Policy and years of dodgy population data.
How can you make plans for a country when you don't know how many people you have?
Now the population is going backward, the property sector is faltering, and China is in a world of trouble.</description></item><item><title>Why is Russia meddling in West Africa? | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080017/</guid><description>Podcast Description While everyone has their eyes on the war in Ukraine, West Africa is threatening to break out into war.
There's been a seemingly unstoppable wave of coups washing along the edge of the Sahara, gaining strength each time.
After the recent military coup in Niger, locals were seen chanting "down with France" and "long live Putin".
What are France and Russia doing in West Africa? And could they end up in a proxy war?</description></item><item><title>How microchip-maker TSMC became the world's most important company | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080018/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Microchips are in your car, your microwave — there might even be one in your kettle. They run everything.
And the best microchips are made by TSMC, the Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company.
TSMC chips have put Western tech companies and militaries streets ahead of China, and China is not happy about it.
TSMC is so important, that the world could go to war over it.
Find more If You're Listening on YouTube: https://www.</description></item><item><title>The decision that saved Australia from Argentina's 100 per cent inflation nightmare | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Inflation in Argentina is at 100 per cent. The government is printing money fast and locals are spending in US dollars because the peso is so unreliable. The economy is like a rollercoaster.
It might be tempting to think, "they're different over there", but here's the thing: they're kind of not. Argentina — one of the wealthiest countries in the world — was once uncomfortably similar to Australia. Until it totally lost control of its own economy.</description></item><item><title>How a bunch of boxes might land Trump in prison | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Donald Trump has been charged with trying and failing to delete CCTV evidence of farcical, and allegedly criminal behaviour.
It's just the latest charge in the case against the former president over his… interesting decision to take classified documents with him when he left the White House.
Could it land him in jail? We tell the story of how Trump got into this predicament, and his plan to get out of it.</description></item><item><title>How "General Armageddon" and a bromance almost brought down Vladimir Putin | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080021/</guid><description>Podcast Description A bromance is a powerful thing. Lennon and McCartney. Holmes and Watson. Gilbert and Sullivan. Han and Chewy. But occasionally a bromance can nearly get you killed.
A month ago the entire world watched transfixed as a former chef named Yevgeny Prigozhin marched with his private army on Moscow. At the core of this mutiny is a bromance between Prigozhin and a guy you've probably never heard of — General Sergei Surovikin.</description></item><item><title>INTRODUCING | If You're Listening | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080022/</guid><description>Podcast Description If You're Listening is back, and better than ever. Same espionage, same corruptions, same scandals, but more often.
Not only will we be in your feed every Thursday, we'll also cover a different story each week. And if you prefer to watch rather than listen, we're also making videos for iView and YouTube.
Episode one drops Thursday, 27th July.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S07 E6 - How will the war against Ukraine end? | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 01:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080023/</guid><description>Podcast Description After ten months of war, a few likely outcomes of the war in Ukraine are emerging.
A win for Vladimir Putin. A win for Volodymyr Zelenskyy. A bitter frozen conflict. Neither Putin or Zelenskyy will sign a peace agreement and admit defeat. But what if Putin’s regime ends?
Guests:
Dr Paul Dibb - Emeritus Professor of Strategic Studies at ANU; Former Director of the Australian Joint Intelligence OrganisationLieutenant General (retired) Ben Hodges - former commanding general of the US Army in EuropeDr Mykhailo Minakov - Philosopher; Editor in Chief of Focus Ukraine blog from the Kennan Institute at the Wilson CenterMichael Bociurkiw - Global Affairs Analyst and former spokesperson for the Organization for Security and Cooperation in EuropePhilip Short - Former BBC Moscow Correspondent; Author of Putin: His Life and TimesProfessor Daniel Treisman, University of California, Los Angeles, co-author “Spin Dictators: The Changing Face of Tyranny in the 21st Century”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S07 E5 - Has Putin finally pushed the Russian people too far? | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 01:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Protest is not allowed inside Russia.
There was little resistance from the Russian people to the invasion of Ukraine, and those who didn’t like it simply left. But Vladimir Putin has made a decree that has caused discord across Russia. Has he finally pushed his people too far?
Guests:
Zoya Sheftalovich - Contributing editor for POLITICODr Christina Ezrahi - Historian; author of Swans of the Kremlin and Dancing for StalinDenis Volkov - Director - Levada Centre, MoscowDr Yevgenia Albats - Chief Editor of The New TimesDr Mykhailo Minakov - Philosopher; Editor in Chief of Focus Ukraine blog from the Kennan Institute at the Wilson Center
Transcript</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S07 E4 - Undersea sabotage? The mysterious pipe blasts | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 01:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080025/</guid><description>Podcast Description On 26 September, a series of underwater explosions destroyed a cluster of natural gas pipelines on the bottom of the Baltic Sea.
The pipes were designed to deliver gas directly from Russia to Germany, and the explosions exacerbated the already dire energy crisis in Europe.
Everyone agrees it was sabotage, but nobody can agree on who did it. Today: the mystery of the Baltic Sea bubbles, and the story of how Germany’s plan for peace-through-capitalism blew up in their face.</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S07 E3 - Why it’s hard to fight when you don’t know why | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 01:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080026/</guid><description>Podcast Description What does war look like on the ground, for the soldiers who go off to fight? What’s it like to be sent into the muddy confusion of a battlefield, asked to lay down your life for your country?
In this episode: two soldiers. A Ukrainian in his 50s and a Russian in his 20s. One of them is still on the battlefield. The other fought for a week, and is now serving a 15 year prison sentence.</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA S07 E2 | Zelensky's big call: run away or stay to fight | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080027/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 01:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vladimir Putin's plan for a three day takeover of Ukraine relied on a quick strike to take out Volodymyr Zelenskyy - to kill him, to capture him, or to make him flee. Putin assumed that Zelenskyy was weak, but on the very first day of the invasion, two events showed that Putin was wrong, and led to the transformation of a man into a symbol of defiance against Russian tyranny.</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S07 E1 - How war weakened strongman Putin | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080028/</guid><description>Podcast Description For 20 years the Russian President Vladimir Putin was happy to lurk in the shadows, trying and occasionally succeeding to manipulate the rest of the world into doing what he wanted them to do.
But this year he chucked that out the window.
His invasion of Ukraine has turned global security and the global economy upside down. In this episode we ask, why did he do it?
Guests:</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | 07 INTRODUCING Russia, If You're Listening series seven | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080029/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 01:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080029/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the seventh season of If You're Listening, we tell the story of the Russian invasion of Ukraine. Will Putin fulfil his dream of expanding the Russian empire, or has he made the biggest mistake of his life? Episode 1 drops Wednesday November 9!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>AUSTRALIA | S06 E8 - The 49-year-old energy prophecy that is finally coming true | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080030/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Australia is now in a race to build enough renewable energy to replace our coal fired power stations before they close. We’re in this situation because of a series of ignored warnings and missed opportunities over the last five decades.
Now, experts are telling us that the transition to a decarbonised economy presents a big opportunity for Australia. The question is - can we grasp it?
Guests:
Dr Alan Finkel - Commonwealth government energy advisor and former Australian Chief Scientist</description></item><item><title>AUSTRALIA | S06 E7 - The countdown on coal fired power | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080031/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the last five years, politicians in Australia and around the world have regularly tried to blame renewable energy whenever something goes wrong with our electricity supply.
But lately whenever something catastrophic has happened to our energy supply, it’s been old technology at fault.
This is the story of a series of disasters that show how the system we’ve always relied on to deliver electricity is faltering.
Guests:Dr Alan Finkel - Commonwealth government energy advisor and former Australian Chief Scientist</description></item><item><title>AUSTRALIA | S06 E6 - Can we keep digging for energy? | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080032/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Australia has always found energy underground - digging up coal, gas and uranium. As climate change begins to change the way we get our power, our leaders regularly argue that we can keep on digging for power while also saving the planet. But do nuclear energy, carbon capture and storage, and gas fired power have a role to play in the future?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>AUSTRALIA | S06 E5 - What we missed while we were knifing PMs | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080033/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080033/</guid><description>Podcast Description For more than a decade, Australian politicians have discovered - the hard way - that climate policy is a dangerous game. But as the Federal Parliament tore itself apart, the rest of the world moved on, finding new ways to understand the effects of climate change, and deal with it. This is the story of how Australia fell behind the rest of the world, and why we might finally be ready to catch up.</description></item><item><title>AUSTRALIA | S06 E4 - The decade when climate change became a culture war | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080034/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080034/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1997, the debate over climate change in Australia was relatively civil. The question was not whether climate change was happening, but what should be done about it?
In the following decade, Australia’s mining industry polluted the debate with misinformation. This is the story of how Australia's understanding of this vital issue went backwards.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>AUSTRALIA | S06 E3 - How long will the world want our coal? | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080035/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Australia intends to keep exporting coal for as long as there are countries willing to buy it. Miners have grand dreams of establishing new coal regions in Queensland to supply coal to the power stations and steel mills of India.
But how much longer will India, and our other big coal customers, keep needing it?
Guests:
Neelima Jain, Wadhwani Chair in U.S.-India Policy Studies at the Centre for Strategic and International Studies</description></item><item><title>AUSTRALIA | S06 E2 - How we became addicted to coal | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080036/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Australia’s second-oldest city, Newcastle, was built around a single resource - coal.
Since then, Australia has come to rely on coal for its prosperity. Our industries grew around the cheap energy it provided, and our global trade balance relies on its export.
But now, that has to end. The question is - what will happen to Australia, and its coal communities - when it does?
Guests:
Professor John Maynard, Emeritus Professor, Indigenous Education and Research, University of Newcastle</description></item><item><title>AUSTRALIA | S06 E1 - The legacy of our first decisions on climate change | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080037/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080037/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1987, scientists gathered in Melbourne for a landmark conference where they discussed, for the first time, the effects climate change might have on Australia.
In the decade after that, two decisions were made by federal governments - one Liberal, and one Labor - which have shaped the climate debate in this country ever since. Australia, If You’re Listening will look at why Australia’s found it so hard to tackle climate change since then, and what that means for the future.</description></item><item><title>INTRODUCING Season Six | Australia, If You're Listening | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080038/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080038/</guid><description>Podcast Description The sixth season of If You’re Listening tells the story of Australia’s turbulent history with climate change, and what that means for the future.
As we approach a federal election where climate and energy is a key battleground, this 8 episode series will examine how Australia wasted decades fighting change, instead of capitalising on it.
Episode 1 launches on February 23.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CHINA | S05 06 - Are the 'drums of war' beating over Taiwan? | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080039/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080039/</guid><description>Podcast Description For months commentators and politicians in Australia have been talking about one of the most frightening topics imaginable — a war between the United States and China over the island of Taiwan.
It's the last frozen remnant of a hundred year old Civil War — two governments both claiming to be the legitimate rulers of China, separated by 100 miles of ocean.
In this episode, we explain the bizarre story which led to the current tension, and look at what might happen next.</description></item><item><title>CHINA | S05 05 - Chinese students: Commodity or opportunity? | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080040/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080040/</guid><description>Podcast Description When the COVID-19 pandemic caused the shutdown of travel from China, it shone a harsh light on the way Australia treats Chinese students who come here to study.
Some feel isolated and discriminated against, others feel they are being treated as "cash cows" by a university sector desperate for their fees.
Can we do better? And can we handle it when problems arise inside the bubble we have created around Chinese students?</description></item><item><title>CHINA | S05 04 - Huawei and the new technology cold war | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080041/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080041/</guid><description>Podcast Description From humble beginnings in a tiny town whose name means "deep drainage ditch", electrical engineer Ren Zhengfei grew his company Huawei into a global technology giant, delivering competitive telecommunications equipment at low prices.
But when Australia accused Huawei of being a security risk, a snowball began to roll which led to arrests, hostages being taken, and pure white hot fury in Beijing.
This is the story of how a decision made in the midst of a Prime Ministerial spill may lead to a new technology cold war.</description></item><item><title>CHINA | S05 03 - The iron chain between Australia and China | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080042/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080042/</guid><description>Podcast Description When China rolled out their trade sanctions regime against Australia to try and punish us for a litany of perceived insults, the trade of one commodity was conspicuously left untouched.
China's desperate need to stimulate economic growth through construction has left them with an insatiable appetite for Australian iron ore.
In this episode, we look at the incredible things they've built using our most valuable resource, and what might happen if they decide to stop buying it.</description></item><item><title>CHINA | S05 Bonus episode - The story behind Bob Hawke’s mysterious Tiananmen Cable | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080043/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080043/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1989, five days after tanks rolled into Tiananmen Square in Beijing and brutally ended weeks of protests, the then prime minister Bob Hawke gave a horrifying description of what Australia thought happened.
But where did the account come from? And what did it get wrong?
Over the past three months China, If You're Listening investigated the source of this description and found it was a previously undisclosed diplomatic cable from the Australian Embassy in Beijing, which subsequently had key details retracted.</description></item><item><title>CHINA | S05 02 - How Tiananmen is being repeated in Xinjiang | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080044/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080044/</guid><description>Podcast Description For decades Australia has taken the approach that when it comes to China; we can criticise their human rights record without risking our trading relationship.
We told China we disapproved of their crackdown on students at Tiananmen Square in 1989, but continued to sell them iron ore.
Xi Jinping has made it clear that the arrangement has now changed, as he simultaneously takes the lessons Beijing learned at Tiananmen, and applies them to a crackdown on Muslims in his country's far west.</description></item><item><title>CHINA | S05 01 - Xi Jinping: The 'Man of Destiny' | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080045/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080045/</guid><description>Podcast Description At first glance, Chinese President Xi Jinping's life story seems simple. His father was a high-ranking Chinese government official, and opened doors for his son, who rose even higher.
But his rise to become the most powerful Chinese leader since Chairman Mao Zedong seems far more unlikely when you find out what Mao's policies did to Xi's family during his childhood.
In this episode we tell the story of Xi's — from its terrifying beginning to mysterious end — and ask if he is the catalyst for the deterioration of relations between China and Australia.</description></item><item><title>INTRODUCING Season Five | China, If You’re Listening | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080046/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080046/</guid><description>Podcast Description A podcast about how the relationship between Australia and China came to the verge of collapse.
Not long ago, Chinese President Xi Jinping was regularly having warm, friendly chats with Australia's Prime Ministers.
Now, he won't even take our phone calls, trade is being blocked, and Australian politicians are talking about preparations for war.
Episode 1 coming on the 1st of June.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>AMERICA | S04 09 - How Coronavirus destroyed Trump's MAGA promise | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080047/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080047/</guid><description>Podcast Description When the coronavirus pandemic swept the globe, killing hundreds of thousands in its wake, President Donald Trump's new way of running the country suddenly left America exposed.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>AMERICA | S04 08 - How China fooled Donald Trump | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080048/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 04:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080048/</guid><description>Podcast Description For a decade Donald Trump railed against China. But once he was elected, Chinese President Xi Jinping quickly broke down Trump's defences.
In today's episode, how President Xi turned Trump's disdain for China into a beautiful friendship.
And created the perfect distraction from what China was really doing.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>AMERICA | S04 07 - How Donald Trump turned the Presidency into a business | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080049/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 04:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Just this month, the public finally got access to Donald Trump's tax returns.
They revealed that he pays little to no tax, because he makes very little money.
So what does a businessman do when he needs to revamp his image and make a little cash? Become the most famous person in the world.
How Donald Trump tried to make money off the Presidency.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>AMERICA | S04 06 - Trump's desperate measure to halt immigration | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080050/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 04:01:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Donald Trump ran for election on some promises - building a wall between the US and Mexico, and stopping the immigration of Muslims.
But instead of living up to his promise to stem the tide of immigrants, he resorted to truly shocking measures.
How did Donald Trump push America's immigration system to the limits of what is legal, and what is morally justifiable?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>AMERICA | S04 05 - How Trump widened racial divides for political gain | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080051/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 04:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080051/</guid><description>Podcast Description When George Floyd was killed by police, protestors took to the streets in worldwide support of the Black Lives Matter protests.
Donald Trump has a long history with speaking out on issues to do with race.
So how far did his law and order response go toward soothing America's centuries old racial divide.
When Donald Trump was elected, he promised to Make America Proud Again but did he just end up making it worse?</description></item><item><title>AMERICA | S04 04 - How Saudi Arabia found an ally in the White House | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080052/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080052/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a businessman and presidential candidate, Donald Trump was extremely harsh on Saudi Arabia.
So when Washington Post journalist Jamal Khashoggi was murdered inside a Saudi consulate, why did Donald Trump come to the Kingdom's defence?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>AMERICA | S04 03 - How close did Trump get to nuclear war? | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080053/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Within months of taking office, Donald Trump threatened North Korea with "fire and fury".
Soon afterwards, he would tear up a nuclear deal with Iran and bring the US to the brink of war.
And yet that war never came.
This is the story of how Donald Trump resisted temptation and kept the peace.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>AMERICA | S04 02 - The surprising story of how Donald Trump took on the NRA | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080054/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 01:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080054/</guid><description>Podcast Description The most powerful gun lobby group in the United States was brought to the edge of collapse.
And right at that moment, Donald Trump vowed to do something about mass shootings.
Could Donald Trump finally defeat the NRA, or when the moment came, did he flinch?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>AMERICA | S04 01 - What a hurricane taught Trump about being president | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080055/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hurricane Maria smashed through Puerto Rico in 2017, destroying everything in its wake.
What did the worst American natural disaster in decades teach Donald Trump about how to be president?
When Trump was inaugurated, he promised to Make America Safe Again... when the hurricane hit, did he live up to his promise?
This is America, If You’re Listening. A podcast about how President Donald Trump has left his mark on the United States, and the world.</description></item><item><title>INTRODUCING Season Four | America, If You're Listening | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080056/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080056/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 2020 US Presidential election is shaping up to be a historical moment. Voters are deciding if the America of the last four years is the one they want to live in in the future.
President Trump's has presided over the most turbulent four years in living memory. He's dealt with crises, changed policies, and fought for his political survival.
America, If You're Listening will look back at these astonishing four years, and shed new light on the incredible chaos of Donald Trump's first term as President.</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S03 09 - Putin's Trump card: the CrowdStrike conspiracy theory | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080057/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Russian intelligence agencies and Vladimir Putin have spent three years spreading a conspiracy theory that Ukraine was the one who meddled in the 2016 election.
The theory quickly reached Donald Trump, and he became obsessed with proving it.
He's now being impeached for his scheme to get Ukraine to investigate it.
While this scheme has blown up in Trump’s face, and allegedly harmed America and Ukraine’s national security, it has played out perfectly for Putin.</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S03 08 - How Russia's rotten gas got Trump into trouble | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080058/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080058/</guid><description>Podcast Description You might think Trump's impeachment inquiry started because of a dodgy phone call to the Ukrainian President.
But the origins are actually in the Ukrainian gas industry - which is deeply corrupt and reliant on Russia - just the way Putin likes it.
In 2014, Joe Biden flew to Ukraine to try and break their Russian gas addiction.
And started the dominoes falling which would eventually lead to Donald Trump's infamous request for a favour.</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S03 07 - Putin goes nuclear to retain his popularity | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080059/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Like all dictators, Vladimir Putin is terrified of being overthrown by his people.
Keeping his popularity high among average Russians is a priority for him, and from 2014 to 2018 he was king of the mountain.
To keep that going in 2018 he announced an exciting new nuclear-powered nuclear missile.
But that's where things started to go wrong.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S03 06 - The spies who suck at spying | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080060/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080060/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2006, Russian assassins killed a dissident in London. But they left a spectacular radioactive mess behind them and ended up in a Moscow hospital.
But this wasn't the worst example of spycraft in England over the last two decades.
One attack went so disastrously wrong it made the United Kingdom finally wake up to the threat of Putin's Kremlin.
The story of how espionage screwups can have global consequences.</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S03 05 - When the Father of Brexit met Mother Russia | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080061/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080061/</guid><description>Podcast Description From almost complete obscurity, Nigel Farage rode a wave of British anger to take his idea of leaving the European Union from a fringe fantasy to a mainstream cause.
But as Farage rose from community hall meetings to primetime TV debates, he found himself increasingly allied with Vladimir Putin.
This is the story of how Mr Brexit came to recognise Putin's power and how it could help his cause.</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S03 04 - Putin's obsession with crushing the mother of Germany | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080062/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080062/</guid><description>Podcast Description German leader Angela Merkel was the most powerful woman in the world.
Which is why Putin was determined to take her down.
His campaign started by playing on her famous fear of dogs... and ended with the biggest migrant crisis the world had seen.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S03 03 - How to spin a war | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080063/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080063/</guid><description>Podcast Description When is an invasion not an invasion? When Putin's propaganda machine is involved, sowing false narratives, confusion and fear. From Putin's motorcycle gang to his 'little green men' and his hip-hop loving head of misinformation, Russia tried everything to convince the West it wasn't invading Ukraine.
The propaganda push worked - sort of, and tells us a lot about the misinformation Russia has gone on to do in the West.</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S03 02 - From spymaster to president | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080064/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Russian President Vladimir Putin came to power declaring he would kill his terrorist enemies, even if they were in the toilet at the time.
His transition from spymaster to President came in the midst of apartment bombings, and brutal crackdowns on those he held responsible.
He learned that having an enemy to fight makes you a popular leader.
The turbulent first years of his Presidency tell us a lot about why he has picked a fight with the West.</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S03 01 - A cold, wet day in Salisbury | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080065/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080065/</guid><description>Podcast Description The residents of the sleepy English town of Salisbury woke up one morning to find their town in chaos. Russian agents had attempted to assassinate a traitor with a terrifying weapon, in a brazen chemical attack on British soil. But the attempted assassination of Sergei Skripal is only one step in a series of events which began five years ago and may help bring about Brexit, and the impeachment of a US President.</description></item><item><title>INTRODUCING Season Three | Putin vs The World | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080066/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080066/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Russian campaign to meddle in the 2016 US Election was only part of President Vladimir Putin's big plan.
Season 3 of Russia, If You're Listening looks at where the scheme to destroy western democracies began, the damage it's done, and where it might end.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S02 08 - The night at the wine rooms | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080067/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080067/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's the meeting at a fancy wine bar in London that sparked the Mueller investigation.
Some say it was a boozy, alcohol-fuelled drinking session where a clever spy tricked a Trump official into divulging information about Russia.
Others say it was a brief encounter where a Trump official naively blurted something to a senior diplomat.
So what is the truth?
For the first time, both people at the meeting - George Papadopoulos and Alexander Downer - reveal what really happened that night.</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S02 07 - Oleg Deripaska: The collusion connection? | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080068/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Robert Mueller has investigated the relationship between former Trump campaign manager Paul Manafort and Russian billionaire Oleg Deripaska.
Deripaska is an aluminium tycoon with close links to Russian President Vladimir Putin.
Manafort tried to funnel secret insider information about the Trump election strategy to him.
Was that information then used by Russia to influence the election?
The story behind the last remaining collusion question.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S02 06 - Don McGahn: Mueller's star witness | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080069/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lawyer Don McGahn was on the Trump train from the beginning.
But the dream job of White House Counsel quickly turned into a nightmare, as he slowly fell out of favour with the President.
Then one night McGahn was forced to make a choice of historic proportions: help Trump potentially commit a crime or resign.
McGahn has found himself the centre of attention, as his testimony to Robert Mueller implicates the President in possible obstruction of justice.</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S02 05 - Julian Assange: Russia's favourite publisher | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080070/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080070/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Julian Assange was arrested last week, the only camera to capture it was Russian broadcaster RT.
It's the latest event in a long relationship between the Wikileaks founder and the state-sponsored network.
Assange has denied working with Russian military hackers to influence the US election.
But what does Robert Mueller know about Assange’s links to Russia?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S02 04 - Sergey Kislyak: The radioactive ambassador | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080071/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Everyone who meets Russian Ambassador Sergey Kislyak ends up in deep trouble. But what if that was the point?
Robert Mueller seems to have found no evidence that the Trump campaign were willing participants in the criminal Russian effort to disrupt the 2016 election.
But what if the Trump campaign were unwitting targets of a spy operation, led from the Russian Embassy
Were they tricked into taking pointless but suspicious-looking meetings - which the media and FBI would discover and investigate?</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S02 03 - Rob Goldstone: 'I regret all of it' | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080072/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Affable Englishman Rob Goldstone was literally in the room for the infamous Trump Tower Meeting, and he was with Donald Trump the weekend of the mythical "pee tape".
But when you look at the rest of the characters involved in the Trump/Russia saga - Republican operatives, Trump family members and Russian spies - Rob Goldstone seems like the odd man out.
He puts a lot of his story down to accidents and misunderstandings, but is that all there is to it?</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S02 02 - Maria Butina: Russian in the NRA | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080073/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080073/</guid><description>Podcast Description An undercover Australian journalist from Al Jazeera spent three years inside the National Rifle Association of America. He wasn't the only one trying figure it out. Simultaneously, a Russian secret agent was trying to infiltrate the NRA.
She is now the only Russian secret agent behind bars for Russia's meddling in the election, and could hold the key to understanding Putin's plans.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S02 01 - Trump's best day ever | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080074/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080074/</guid><description>Podcast Description After 22 months Mueller's report has dropped. But it hasn't been made public - yet.
US Attorney General Bill Barr has the report in his hot hands - and according to him - Mueller found no evidence of collusion.
But who is Bill Barr? And can we trust his summary of Mueller's findings?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S01 17 - Robert Mueller: 'Trump's worst nightmare' | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080075/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080075/</guid><description>Podcast Description We end the season with the head of the investigation into Russian interference in the 2016 US presidential election - Robert Mueller.
He's been taking down key players, circling closer and closer to Donald Trump.
But can he finish before the President shuts him down?
This is our last deep dive into a key character in the Russia investigation for this season, but we'll keep you updated with Trumpdates every time an important development in the story breaks.</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S01 16 - Michael Cohen: The fixer with the hush money | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080076/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael Cohen is called Donald Trump's personal lawyer, but really he's a "fixer" - a man who solves problems for the boss.
It all came unstuck when investigators probed into hush money payments he made to a model and a porn star.
He pleaded guilty to eight criminal counts, and announced he was happy to tell the truth to anyone who asked for it.
So what information will he give up and should Trump be worried?</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S01 15 - Felix Sater: Criminal, informant, developer, spy | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080077/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix Sater's life is a mystery.
He went to jail for stabbing a guy in the face, he was involved with the Russian Mafia, and was an informant for the CIA.
He also helped Donald Trump build his property empire. So are there any secrets? And what does he know?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S01 14 - Trump's Business: Secrets and deals | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080078/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Donald Trump's business flourished with the 80s real estate boom and bled money when the recession hit.
These days no one really knows how much he really has.
Why the secrecy?
Today, the story of the Trump Organization, and when Russian money might have ended up in his pocket.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S01 13 - James Comey: Integrity at all costs | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080079/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former FBI director James Comey is both Donald Trump and Hillary Clinton's biggest nightmare.
He's the grandson of a cop with a dogged commitment to integrity, independence and note taking.
But could his integrity be what cost Hillary Clinton the election? And did it cause Donald Trump to commit a crime?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S01 12 - Michael Flynn: General for hire | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080080/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080080/</guid><description>Podcast Description General Michael Flynn was a high ranking defence official and a Democrat before he joined up with Donald Trump.
He's now accused of planning a kidnapping, acting illegally as an unregistered foreign agent, and found guilty of lying to the FBI.
Why was he allowed to stay in the White House when he was compromised by the Russian Government?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S01 11 - Jared Kushner: Trump's Crown Prince | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080081/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jared Kushner was in charge of getting his father-in-law Donald Trump elected president.
He was a young property developer with no political experience and crushing debts.
And he went from one family besieged by scandal, to another.
So who is this man prepared to defend first, his father, then his father-in-law?
Subscribe in Apple Podcasts or your favourite podcast app to find out how this story ends.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S01 10 - The Troll Factory: Lies, stolen secrets and chaos | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080082/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080082/</guid><description>Podcast Description An army of professional Russian trolls tried to change the outcome of the 2016 US election from a four storey building in St Petersburg.
Did the dirty trickster Roger Stone help them? And was the Troll Factory ultimately successful?
Language warning: This episode contains some swearing.
You can get in touch at russia@abc.net.au.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S01 09 - The Crime: Russia steps over the line | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080083/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hacking, leaking, and the spreading of chaos.
How Russian Government hackers timed a Democratic National Committee email leak with Hillary Clinton's biggest scandal.
This week, we find out how Russia stepped over the line and tried to influence the outcome of the 2016 US Presidential Election.
This is the ninth episode of Russia, If You're Listening.
Each week, host Matt Bevan brings the story of a character involved in the investigation.</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S01 08 - Donald Trump Jr: The President's son and the 'treasonous' meeting | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080084/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080084/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2016 Don Jr took an ill-fated meeting with a Russian lawyer in Trump Tower.
The meeting is a pivotal moment in the entire story of Trump and Russia and has since been called "treasonous" and "unpatriotic".
So is the meeting it a smoking gun or was it all just a waste of time?
This is the eighth episode of Russia, If You're Listening.
Each week, host Matt Bevan brings the story of a character involved in the investigation.</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S01 07 - Paul Manafort: The dictator's fixer | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080085/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Veteran Republican strategist Paul Manafort spent 30 years working for dictators before he struck gold in Ukraine.
But when he returned to America and became the boss of the Trump campaign, his past caught up with him.
How did this man get landed with over a dozen federal indictments, and why is he still refusing to flip?
This is the seventh episode of Russia, If You're Listening.
Each week, host Matt Bevan brings the story of a character involved in the investigation.</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S01 06 - Christopher Steele: The spy and the pee tape | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080086/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Christopher Steele is the author of the infamous Trump/Russia dossier.
You remember - the one that contains allegations about sex workers urinating on a hotel bed.
But there's so much more to the dossier than that.
It outlines a massive conspiracy between Donald Trump and the Russian government - a list of allegations which, if proven, would constitute by-far the biggest attack on American democracy in history.
But is Christopher Steele a credible Russia expert?</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S01 05 - Carter Page: The useful idiot | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080087/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Both the Russians and the Republicans have called Donald Trump's former foreign policy advisor Carter Page "an idiot".
It seems everyone has been able to manipulate him to do their bidding.
So is Carter Page an actual idiot or a Russian spy?
This is the fifth episode of Russia, If You're Listening.
Each week, host Matt Bevan brings the story of a character involved in the investigation.
You can get in touch at russia@abc.</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S01 04 - George Papadopoulos: The coffee boy | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080088/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080088/</guid><description>Podcast Description George Papadopoulos is the first known link between the Trump campaign and Russia.
Just how close was the so-called coffee boy George Papadopoulos to Russian spies offering dirt on Hillary Clinton?
This is the fourth episode of Russia, If You're Listening.
Each week, host Matt Bevan brings the story of a character involved in the investigation.
You can get in touch at russia@abc.net.au.
Subscribe in Apple Podcasts or your favourite podcast app to find out how this story ends.</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S01 03 - The Oligarchs: Money and power | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080089/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080089/</guid><description>Podcast Description The oligarchs hold the power and the money in Russia.
So who are they and why does your average Russian billionaire care about who sits in The White House?
This is the third episode of Russia, If You're Listening.
Each week, host Matt Bevan will bring the story of a character involved in the investigation.
Subscribe in Apple Podcasts or your favourite podcast app to find out how this story ends.</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S01 02 - Vladimir Putin: The man with a grudge | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080090/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080090/</guid><description>Podcast Description The spy from St Petersburg and the lawyer from Chicago. Why does Russia's president have such a deep and abiding hatred for Hillary Clinton?
This is the second episode of Russia, If You're Listening.
Each week, host Matt Bevan will bring the story of a character involved in the investigation.
You can go back to hear our earlier episode on Donald Trump plus our special Trumpdate with 7.30 presenter Leigh Sales.</description></item><item><title>RUSSIA | S01 01 - Donald Trump: A Russian love affair | If You're Listening</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5806080091/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5806080091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Donald Trump has always claimed he has "nothing to do with Russia" but is that true? What if Trump was caught in a Russian web, long before he even considered a career in politics?
This is the first episode of the ABC's new podcast, Russia, If You're Listening.
Each week, host Matt Bevan will bring the story of a character involved in the investigation.
And keep an eye out for our minisode updates - available whenever news breaks.</description></item></channel></rss>