<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Springleaf on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/springleaf/</link><description>Recent content in Springleaf on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 06:00:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/springleaf/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Episode 4 | Springleaf</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4384190001/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 06:00:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4384190001/</guid><description>Podcast Description With SW5 member (and fellow undercover cop) Clarke tied up in the backroom of SW6 HQ, Pat needs to come up with a rescue plan, stat. But when he leaks Clarke's whereabouts to SW5 gang leader Janet (Natalie Cassidy), existing tensions between the two gangs begin to escalate. Meanwhile, on the comedy circuit, there's another terrible crime to deal with - a blatant case of material theft...
A true(ish) crime podcast, which sees undercover cop Pat Springleaf (James Acaster) share police wire recordings from the biggest case of his career: working to infiltrate and bring to justice the notorious SW6 gang.</description></item><item><title>Episode 3 | Springleaf</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4384190002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 06:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4384190002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pat is booked as a guest for Tom Allen's new panel show, and Donna persuades the SW6 gang to carry out a practice heist at the studio in preparation for their big casino job - bad news for fellow panellists Jo Brand and Sarah Millican. Meanwhile, 'Sita's Creatures' animal acting agency goes from strength to strength as Serpico cements his reputation as the country's leading Merdog, before making waves elsewhere on set.</description></item><item><title>Episode 2 | Springleaf</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4384190003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 06:00:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4384190003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Studio guest Romesh Ranganathan attempts to get a grip on exactly what the podcast is, Sita bags Serpico his first acting role&amp;nbsp;and Pat's crowd-work skills are tested to their limit when Donna encourages Lawrence and Huey to try out their new heist personas in public…
A true(ish) crime podcast, which sees undercover cop Pat Springleaf (James Acaster) share police wire recordings from the biggest case of his career: working to infiltrate and bring to justice the notorious SW6 gang, led by the villainous Lawrence.</description></item><item><title>Episode 1 | Springleaf</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4384190004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 06:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4384190004/</guid><description>Podcast Description A true(ish) crime podcast, based on James Acaster's undercover cop alter-ego Pat Springleaf, which sees Pat share police wire recordings from the biggest case of his career: working undercover to infiltrate and bring to justice the notorious SW6 gang, led by the villainous Lawrence (Domhnall Gleeson).
Back in 2013, ex-conman-turned-undercover-cop Pat was in the middle of a career-defining gig - but problems beset him on all sides: the gang are getting suspicious; his wife wants a divorce; the police are demanding results; and his ex partner in crime is blackmailing him.</description></item><item><title>Episode 0 - Trailer | Springleaf</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4384190005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 19:55:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4384190005/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPRINGLEAF launches Tuesday 21st November 2023 - subscribe wherever you get your podcasts.
Pat Springleaf is in quite the bind. He’s an ex con man turned undercover cop in the middle of the biggest case of his career - the gang are getting suspicious, his wife wants a divorce, the police are demanding results and his ex partner-in-crime is blackmailing him.
Not an ideal situation for someone with a burning need to please absolutely everybody.</description></item></channel></rss>